<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:26:42" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:26:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=702006#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>CeeLo Green headlines entertainment lineup for 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series at Yankee Stadium</title><description>NEW YORK -- Five-time Grammy Award-winning singer-songwriter-producer CeeLo Green will take the stage at Yankee Stadium during the much-anticipated 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series™ in New York, the National Hockey League announced today. Grammy Award-winning singer-songwriter and actress Michelle Williams, the cast of the Tony and Grammy Award-winning Broadway hit Jersey Boys, Southside...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:27:44">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=679887#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Gretzky trade to Los Angeles shocked hockey world</title><description>said, 'Let me think about it,' and called him a week later and said, 'I could live with that.'" Gretzky had just married actress Janet Jones and was spending part of the summer living in the Hollywood home of actor Alan Thicke. Knowing that Gretzky was living in Los Angeles and certain he wouldn't re-sign with the Oilers when his contract expired, Pocklington accepted McNall's offer. There was just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:29:33">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=532377#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Stars to walk the red carpet Wed. 6:30 PM ET</title><description>-studded show. Jamie Iovine, also known as DJ EYE, who will be spinning at the 2010 NHL Awards, and Hey Rosetta!, performing at the NHL Awards party, will also walk the red carpet. Host Jay Mohr, with his wife, actress Nikki Cox, and celebrity presenters including actors Mark Wahlberg, John Slattery, Jamie Kennedy, Kevin Zegers, D.B. Sweeney, Natasha Henstridge, Michael Rosenbaum and Leven Rambin; legendary...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:33:11">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=507313#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Zamboni was inquisitive, high school dropout</title><description>was used on any ice surface other than his skating rink at Paramount's Iceland. The first sale was made for $5,000 to the Pasadena Winter Garden in 1950. The second was made for Norwegian Olympic figure skater and film actress Sonia Henie, for her Hollywood on Ice Review. Frank, in fact, drove the parts to Chicago where it was assembled for Henie. "He took all the parts on a U-Haul trailer and left...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:33:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=413481#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Carrie on! Sens win one for the ladies</title><description>A few thoughts while we prepare for 13 overtime games Thursday: Ottawa goes Hollywood \-- The stars were out in full force Wednesday night at Scotiabank Place, and Ottawa Senators forward Mike Fisher gave one of them a thrill.     With girlfriend Carrie Underwood watching from a luxury suite, Fisher scored at 2:38 of overtime to send the Sens to a 3-2 win against the struggling Tampa Bay...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:36:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=401382#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Celebrities bask in Winter Classic's glow</title><description>," said Granderson, who watched the Detroit Red Wings' 6-4 win from a luxury suite. "It's great to have the Blackhawks and the Red Wings at Wrigley Field. I'm enjoying my time here." Among the other celebrities on hand were actors Vince Vaughn ("Wedding Crashers," "The Breakup"), William Petersen ("CSI"), Jeffrey Donovan ("Burn Notice") and George Stults ("7th Heaven"); actress Joan Cusack ("Working...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:39:11">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=396172#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Chillin' with ... Scottie Upshall</title><description>." Do you eat in, order in or go out? "I eat out a lot." Favorite TV show? "Californication." Favorite movie? "That new Batman movie, The Dark Knight, was outstanding." What Hollywood starlette would you go out with? "Actress and model Megan Fox." Favorite sports team of all time (excluding your team)? "It would have to be the Toronto Blue Jays of the early 1990's. The '92 Blue Jays and '93...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:40:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=380618#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Gretzky trade sent shock waves through Canada</title><description>in the future. Gretzky got married that summer, exchanging vows with actress Janet Jones on July 16 in the closest thing Canada had to a royal wedding. Less than a month later, Jones' name would be reviled in much of Canada as the cause of Gretzky's departure from the only NHL team he had ever known. In truth, there were a lot of moving parts to the deal. After news of the trade first broke, Gretzky said he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:42:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=372055#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Smith's acting debut was a real pain</title><description>It's summertime, and the living is easy for most hockey players who are pursuing interests away from the rink. But there are some who spend time at hockey camps, and there is the rare occasion when a Hollywood producer stops by and asks for players to appear in a made-for-TV movie.   That is exactly what happened to Neil Smith in the summer of 1982, as the producers for the movie based on Sidney...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>