<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:57:20" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:57:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711773#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Outside the box: Ryan O'Reilly avoids penalties as he leads Avs in goals and toward playoffs</title><description>on the ice. Not by hand, of course, but by flipping them with his stick into a bucket. That little exercise comes in handy when he's in the corners, prying the puck away from opponents. "Young kids need to learn to play like him when they're growing up," said Mitchell, who will be back on the ice Saturday against San Jose after missing four games with a back ailment. "It's not about going...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:00:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=632661#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Talented Sea Dogs show they can defence as well as attack at Memorial Cup</title><description>SHAWINIGAN, Que. - With all their skill and speed, the powerhouse Saint John Sea Dogs are not about to start trying to slow games down. But coach Gerard Gallant said Thursday his team knows how to protect a lead. An example came in the Sea Dogs' final round robin game at the MasterCard Memorial Cup, when they took a three-goal and closed out a 4-1 victory over the host Shawinigan Cataractes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:00:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=621598#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Top prospect Nail Yakupov injured in Sting's 4-0 win</title><description>Coach Jacques Beaulieu. 'Nail took alot of stitches to the face, it's all marked up. Halmo didn't hit anything else, but his head. We've got to take these hits out of out game and protect our kids.' Yakupov, who took stitches to his mouth and suffered a possible concussion, did not return to the game and is listed as day-to-day. Brett Thompson scored twice and added an assist for the Sting (33...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:01:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=601103#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Mark Howe to join legendary father Gordie in Hockey Hall of Fame</title><description>on the ice. The nets were from Olympia Stadium and so was the equipment, such as Terry Sawchuk's goaltending gear, thanks to his famous father. "It was easy for me to get kids over to play," Mark Howe said recently. "It was first-class street hockey." Decades later, the 56-year-old son of a superstar has earned the right to join his father in the Hockey Hall of Fame. What does it mean to the man known...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:04:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=541968#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Couturier headlines talented draft class in QMJHL</title><description>." Gallant, who led the Sea Dogs to their first QMJHL President's Cup Final with a league-best 109 points and was named the 2010 Canadian Hockey League Coach of the Year, can sense a few of his top players gripping their sticks a little tighter in their draft year. "I think some of these kids are feeling some pressure and not just the top prospects … we're coming back from an outstanding year in 2009...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:06:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=499258#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Blog: The Finnish Line</title><description>underway here at Hartwall Arena. There is only one surprise among the scratches and that is Michal Repik for Florida. The youngster was supposed make his NHL debut tonight, but Florida went with seven defensemen instead. The Panthers likely dressed an extra D to protect the three players that are suffering from the flu, as well as allow the team to have a look at rookie blueliner Dmitry Kulikov...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>