<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:18:16" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:18:16">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=548222#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Exter enjoying role shaping Campbell, U.S. goalies</title><description>for a loose puck away from the crease. Exter hit his head on the ice as his mask came off, leaving him unconscious and bleeding from both ears.   He laid in a coma for 14 days with a fractured skull.   "Obviously, you don't remember anything that happened on that day or time," Exter said. "I did see it (on video) after that, for sure, and it was just two kids going at it hard. Was it done intentionally...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:20:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=408973#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Once vilified, masks now are tools of the trade</title><description>to leave their feet to make saves. That created another problem: Goalies faces were now exposed to more shots than when they stood tall in net. Nowadays, NHL goalies stand for the anthem and then drop, butterfly, lunge, flip and roll and do whatever it takes for 60 minutes to stop pucks. It was the introduction of the goalie mask that allows them to do that. So, why did earlier NHL team officials frown...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:22:11">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=396699#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Edmonton Oilers snap league-leading San Jose Sharks' nine-game winning streak</title><description>SAN JOSE, Calif. - By the time Dwayne Roloson stopped a shot with his head and kept playing even when his mask came off, the San Jose Sharks had a good idea their nine-game winning streak wouldn't make it through the night. The NHL's biggest winners this season are at a loss when they face Roloson, the 39-year-old Edmonton goalie who has turned into the Sharks' most improbable nemesis. Roloson...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:24:40">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=396700#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Edmonton Oilers snap league-leading San Jose Sharks' nine-game winning streak</title><description>SAN JOSE, Calif. - By the time Dwayne Roloson stopped a shot with his head and kept playing even when his mask came off, the San Jose Sharks had a good idea their nine-game winning streak wouldn't make it through the night. The NHL's biggest winners this season are at a loss when they face Roloson, the 39-year-old Edmonton goalie who has turned into the Sharks' most improbable nemesis. Roloson...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:27:53">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370366#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Miller lends a Steadfast hand</title><description>\-- an age-old symbol of those words,” Miller says. “I didn’t want it to just be Ryan Miller this or that. I wanted meaning and we want to help patients with the battle. We want them to be tough.” Every time Miller puts his goalie mask on, he is reminded of his cousin’s brave face and courageous battle. It’s inspiring to see the bulldog emblem on the back skull plate -- a compilation of ideas he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:28:30">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=369702#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Meet Chris Mason, goaltender and gamer</title><description>the skull plate on the back of his mask to honor Leonidas, who, along with the 300 warriors, valiantly held off an army of thousands of Persian troops until finally succumbing after several days of battling the enormous odds. "They build up the Spartan wall, and I thought that was relevant to my position as a goaltender," Mason said. "I really like that kind of era and think that movie (300) is pretty...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>