<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:32:45" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:32:46">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=600029#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Trotz a model of constancy as milestone approaches</title><description>and now an NHL Network analyst, only half jokes that Trotz was his father's favorite son, albeit an adopted one. "He didn't have the skill to advance to the NHL, but he gave everything he had in the game," said Craig Button, who added that one of his father's favorite photos was a celebration following Trotz's 1994 Calder Cup title as coach of the Portland Pirates. "He was committed to helping the team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:35:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=541291#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Off-ice commitment has Recchi strong at age 42</title><description>Mark Recchi never has been afraid of hard work. And that attitude has paved the way for Recchi's ability to last more than two decades in a sport as physically demanding as hockey at the NHL level. "If you can't come to the rink and work hard every day -- it's an hour to two hours out of your day -- who wouldn't want to do that?" said Recchi, who at 42 is the oldest player in the League "It...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:37:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=523248#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Ducks honor Selanne’s 600th goal, stellar career</title><description>. "Now, I need to borrow his car," Kurri said. "Times (have) changed." While in town for the ceremony, Kurri is staying at Selanne's family home. Selanne jokes that his legendary friend gets the "master suite" when he's in town. A big fan of auto racing and car collecting, Selanne counts a Ferrari Enzo as his favorite.  Make no mistake, though, he won't be bumming a ride from Kurri during his visit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:38:47">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=517709#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brian Burke: 'My team needs me to be strong'</title><description>the formal part of the press conference had ended and more intimate interview groups formed before broaching the subject of Brendan's death. That was when Brian Burke stopped breaking up the room by telling half-jokes about how the Canadians face pressure that is "glacial, unremitting and unrelenting; I can't imagine how they're going to function in this environment," and choked up himself. "I cry less...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:40:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=405333#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Montreal's faithful anticipate All-Stars</title><description>pubs known as brasseries. Less than two kilometers west of the Bell Centre and the old Forum is a cozy brasserie known as "hockey central." Resto-Pub St. Jacques is, like the Habs, 100 years old, making it one of the oldest pubs in the city. "One of our clients was probably born in here," jokes owner Roger Boutin. "This place has been open forever." What makes Resto-Pub a genuine bleu blanc et...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:41:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=372230#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Campbell eager to get Chicago career started</title><description>Things are going so well in Chicago these days that Blackhawks GM Dale Tallon is even cracking jokes in press conferences now. As Brian Campbell pulled his brand new Chicago Blackhawks sweater with No. 51 stitched on the back over his finely pressed shirt and tie Tuesday afternoon, Tallon grabbed the slick defenseman's sport coat and noticed a bulge in the inner pocket. "A little heavier...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:43:33">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370123#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Quinn: We're tough people in Buffalo</title><description>and went to work for the city. Nationally known people who grew up in Buffalo, like Tim Russert, will tell you there's something that drives us back here. We're proud of Buffalo. "We know we're the butt of jokes, nationally, like our most-in-the-nation snowfall. It always seems like the odds are stacked against us. But there's something about us that wants to prove the rest of the country wrong. We have...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>