<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:52:33" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:52:34">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714657#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The key matchups to watch in first round of 2014 Stanley Cup playoffs</title><description>: Bruins in 7 \--- (2) Tampa Bay Lightning (46-27-9, 101 points) vs. (3) Montreal Canadiens (46-28-8, 100 points) Lightning goaltender Anders Lindback vs. Canadiens goaltender Carey Price Goalies don't really face each other, but this is a tall task for Lindback if Vezina Trophy candidate Ben Bishop remains out with an upper-body injury. Price is without a doubt the top reason Montreal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:53:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714381#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>More mature Price at top of game for Canadiens</title><description>the team's goaltender is not tolerated. Price's play during those seven seasons has not always met those exacting standards. But as he prepares to lead the Canadiens into the Stanley Cup Playoffs against the Tampa Bay Lightning, Price appears to have won over the city, and with good reason. He is one of the world's best at his position, an Olympic gold medalist who is among the NHL leaders in save...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:56:01">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714373#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Why the Canadiens will win the Stanley Cup</title><description>barely allowed its opponents to enter the attacking zone. Price was called upon to make a number of big saves after long stretches of inaction where a goal allowed could have spelled disaster for Canada, and he didn't flinch. As a result, he and his Canadian teammates have shiny gold medals That experience will serve him well in the playoffs, and it will ultimately lead the Canadiens to their first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:58:44">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714484#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Lightning, Canadiens find little room for separation</title><description>Bruins had more than his six shutouts. Price also has the mental benefit of knowing he can respond in big games based on his experience at the Olympics, where he allowed three goals on 103 shots to help Canada win gold. Price returned from Sochi with a lower-body injury which cost him eight games, but the hidden benefit to that injury is that he enters the playoffs fresher than he's ever been...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:02:40">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713432#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Osiecki to coach 2015 U.S. World Junior team</title><description>was part of the U.S. coaching staff for WJC teams that won a gold medal in 2010 in Saskatoon and 2013 in Ufa, Russia, plus a bronze medal in 2011 in Buffalo. What did he take away from those gold medal-winning teams? "The team mentality; you always talk about it, but those teams truly had a great team mentality starting with the leadership group," Osiecki said. "I think the leaders of both those groups...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:03:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713399#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Playoff Countdown: Six goalies in glare of spotlight</title><description>be cemented or sent spiraling in the other direction. Bishop and the Lightning are too early into their evolution to think it could spin too far the wrong way in just one postseason, but with his goals-against average up more than half a goal to 2.83 since the Olympic break, there will be pressure to reverse that trend. 6\. Carey Price, Montreal Canadiens -- Price has proven what he can do and earned some...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:05:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28085#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Red Wings look to solidify playoff spot vs. Canadiens</title><description>MONTREAL -- When the Detroit Red Wings hosted the Toronto Maple Leafs on March 18, the Red Wings' streak of 22 straight appearances in the Stanley Cup Playoffs was in jeopardy. A few weeks earlier, Red Wings coach Mike Babcock returned from leading Canada to the gold medal at the 2014 Sochi Olympics and defiantly stated Detroit was not going to let the streak be snapped. "We got to find a way...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:07:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=712518#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Price, top line help send Canadiens to playoffs</title><description>" prior to the game Tuesday. While Price is not the lone explanation for why the Canadiens made the playoffs, he leads the list of five reasons why that came to pass. 1\. An elite goalie If anyone needed proof of just how important Price is to the Canadiens, it came when he was injured at the 2014 Sochi Olympics while backstopping Canada to the gold medal. Any team that loses its starting goalie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:10:46">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711255#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Max Pacioretty gets 100th, Daniel Briere scores as Canadiens top Sabres 2-0</title><description>and beat Hackett with a wrist shot from close range on a power play at 16:54. Coming off an emotional shootout win in Boston on Monday night, the Canadiens were short on energy against the last-place Sabres. Through two scoreless periods, the loudest cheers from the 21,273 Bell Centre fans were for a sharp Price save on Matt D'Agostini during a Sabres power play and when Olympic moguls gold medallist...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:11:30">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=710751#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Price is still a 'work in progress' as Habs get set to face streaking Bruins</title><description>you're out of action for just about three weeks, it's all about timing and getting a feel for the game." Price missed eight games with the injury that he said he suffered while helping Team Canada win gold at the Sochi Olympics. Since returning, he has allowed 13 goals in four games, which statistically is also a work in progress. But the results are there as the Habs have gone from a precarious...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>