<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:29:32" name="MPRA" id="FW14-e009"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:29:36">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/11287/</link><title>Soth Asian Economic Zone: Extension and Possibilities.</title><description>Mehar, Ayub (2004): Soth Asian Economic Zone: Extension and Possibilities. Forthcoming in: FPCCI Economic Review</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-02"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/6822/</link><title>SOUTH ASIAN ECONOMIC ZONE: EXTENSION AND POSSIBILITIES.</title><description>Mehar, Ayub (2005): SOUTH ASIAN ECONOMIC ZONE: EXTENSION AND POSSIBILITIES.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-03"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/6366/</link><title>CURRY CUISINE: PERCEPTIONS OF INDIAN RESTAURANTS IN MALAYSIA.</title><description>Bharath, Josiam and Sadiq, Sohail and Prema, Monteiro (2007): CURRY CUISINE: PERCEPTIONS OF INDIAN RESTAURANTS IN MALAYSIA. Published in: TOURISMOS: An International Multidisciplinary Journal of Tourism , Vol. 2, No. 2 (November 2007): pp. 25-37.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-04"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/40665/</link><title>Emerging Asian ICT global players: natural born collaborators or stuck with aliens?</title><description>Golonka, Monika (2012): Emerging Asian ICT global players: natural born collaborators or stuck with aliens? Forthcoming in: International Journal of Management And Business , Vol. XX, No. XX (2012): X-X.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-05"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/31928/</link><title>Foreign direct investment in East Asian newly industrializing economies.</title><description>dumludag, devrim (2011): Foreign direct investment in East Asian newly industrializing economies.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-06"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/25306/</link><title>State and Tourism Planning: A Case Study of Cambodia.</title><description>Chheang, Vannarith (2008): State and Tourism Planning: A Case Study of Cambodia. Published in: TOURISMOS: An International Multidisciplinary Journal of Tourism , Vol. 4, No. 1 (15. April 2009): pp. 63-82.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-07"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/40599/</link><title>Cultural Constraints In Leading Malaysian SMEs To Global Markets.</title><description>Hussain, Sayed Mushtaq (2006): Cultural Constraints In Leading Malaysian SMEs To Global Markets. Published in: Proceedings of The 2nd National Conference On Entrepreneurship And Small Business, Penang (9. December 2006)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-08"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/8739/</link><title>INSTITUTIONAL Change as Cultural Change. An Illustration by Chinese Postsocialist Transformation.</title><description>EL KAROUNI, Ilyess (2007): INSTITUTIONAL Change as Cultural Change. An Illustration by Chinese Postsocialist Transformation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-09"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/12105/</link><title>Defense spending and economic growth in Asian economies: A panel error-correction approach.</title><description>Habibullah, M.S. and Law, Siong-Hook and Dayang-Afizzah, A.M. (2008): Defense spending and economic growth in Asian economies: A panel error-correction approach.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7014-10"><link>http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/12807/</link><title>Infrastructure and Regional Development: Interlinkages in India.</title><description>Majumder, Rajarshi (2005): Infrastructure and Regional Development: Interlinkages in India. Published in: Indian Economic Review , Vol. 40, No. 2 (2005)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>