<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:20:31" name="MPRA" id="FW14-e009"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:20:32">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/42801/</link><title>Modeling Voting Behavior in the Eurovision Song Contest.</title><description>Dogru, Bülent (2013): Modeling Voting Behavior in the Eurovision Song Contest.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:25:06">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/40996/</link><title>War for profit: macroculture, corsairs and partnership companies.</title><description>Kyriazis, Nicholas and Metaxas, Theodore (2012): War for profit: macroculture, corsairs and partnership companies.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:27:52">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/5996/</link><title>International Trade Patterns over the Last Four Decades: How does Portugal Compare with other Cohesion Countries?</title><description>Amador, João and Cabral, Sónia and Ramos Maria, José (2007): International Trade Patterns over the Last Four Decades: How does Portugal Compare with other Cohesion Countries? Published in: Banco de Portugal Working Paper No. 14-2007 (September 2007)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:28:22">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/9054/</link><title>The impact of a new port on the organization of maritime shipping: an attempt to generalize the results of a case-study on the foundation of St. Petersburg and its influence on Dutch maritime shipping in the Gulf of Finland and Archangel (1703-1740).</title><description>Scheltjens, Werner (2008): The impact of a new port on the organization of maritime shipping: an attempt to generalize the results of a case-study on the foundation of St. Petersburg and its influence on Dutch maritime shipping in the Gulf of Finland and Archangel (1703-1740).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:32:59">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/475/</link><title>Soziale und regionale Ungleichgewichte, politische Instabilitaet und die Notwendigkeit von Pensionsreformen im neuen Europa.</title><description>Tausch, Arno (2004): Soziale und regionale Ungleichgewichte, politische Instabilitaet und die Notwendigkeit von Pensionsreformen im neuen Europa. Published in: Schriftenreihe des Zentrums für europaeische Studien, University of Trier, FRG , Vol. 2004, No. 56 (2004): pp. 1-227.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:35:47">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/53906/</link><title>Mergers and acquisitions transactions strategies in diffusion - type financial systems in highly volatile global capital markets with nonlinearities.</title><description>Ledenyov, Dimitri O. and Ledenyov, Viktor O. (2014): Mergers and acquisitions transactions strategies in diffusion - type financial systems in highly volatile global capital markets with nonlinearities.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:39:46">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/19025/</link><title>On the Problem of Sustainable Economic Development: A Theoretical Solution to this Prisoner's Dilemma.</title><description>Funk, Matt (2008): On the Problem of Sustainable Economic Development: A Theoretical Solution to this Prisoner's Dilemma. Published in: 2008 AICIS Conference Proceedings, ”Islands of Competence: Branding Identities in a Globalized World” (9. June 2008): pp. 1-117.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:43:53">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/44026/</link><title>Ethno-Confessional Realities in the Romanian Area: Historical Perspectives (XVIII-XX centuries).</title><description>Brie, Mircea and Şipoş, Sorin and Horga, Ioan (2011): Ethno-Confessional Realities in the Romanian Area: Historical Perspectives (XVIII-XX centuries). Published in: This present collective volume, coordinated by Mircea Brie, Sorin Şipoş and Ioan Horga, contains the papers of the international conference held in Oradea between 2nd-5th of June 2011 (2011): pp. 1-319.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:48:19">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/1625/</link><title>Rethinking the Culture - Economy Dialectic.</title><description>Brons, Lajos (2005): Rethinking the Culture - Economy Dialectic. Published in: (June 2005)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:52:50">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/44082/</link><title>Ethnicity, Confession and Intercultural Dialogue at the European Union’s East Border.</title><description>Brie, Mircea and Horga, Ioan and Şipoş, Sorin (2011): Ethnicity, Confession and Intercultural Dialogue at the European Union’s East Border. Published in: Eurolimes , Vol. Suppli, (2011): pp. 1-502.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>