<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7480">phd comics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:27:50" name="MPRA" id="FW14-e009"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:27:51">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/10771/</link><title>Nonverbal language – the weapon of the insurance agent.</title><description>Mitu, Narcis Eduard (2008): Nonverbal language – the weapon of the insurance agent. Published in: Finance - Ghallenges of the Future, ISSN 1583-3712 , Vol. No. 7, (2008): pp. 146-153.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:29:21">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/1829/</link><title>On self-financing of institutions of higher learning in India.</title><description>Mishra, SK (2003): On self-financing of institutions of higher learning in India.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:30:38">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/41932/</link><title>Research and Science Today Supplement No.1(3)/2012.</title><description>Bădilă, Andreea Iuliana and Sucilă căs. Pahoni, Cipriana and Mihuţ, Cosmin and Filip, Dan Andrei and Ciubotaru, Iulian Marcel and Luca, Cătălin-Viorel and Mănescu, Alexandra Florina and Pipoș, Cristina and Popa (Lupu), Diana Gabriela and Dinu (Dragomir), Maria Magdalena and Petric, Paulian Timotei and Bran, Răzvan and Constantin, Veronica and Postăvaru, Gianina Ioana and Ciolan, Ioana Monica and Papuc, Valentin and Moșoi, Ștefan Cristian and Gheorghe, Anamaria Elena and Clucerescu (Tănase), Emilia Elena and Marin, Ştefan Claudiu and Ciorei, Mihaela Andreea and Mărcău, Flavius Cristian and Mihaela, Ruxanda and Marin, Camelia and Enescu, Camelia and Ealangi, Ionuț and Purcaru, Mihai and Pop, Alexandra Raluca and Bojincă, Moise (2012): Research and Science Today Supplement No.1(3)/2012. Published in: Research and Science Today</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:31:45">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/36977/</link><title>Trademark owners perspective on the Madrid system: practical experiences and theoretical underpinnings.</title><description>Ghafele, Roya (2007): Trademark owners perspective on the Madrid system: practical experiences and theoretical underpinnings. Published in: Journal of Intellectual Property Law and Practice , Vol. 3, No. 2 (2007): pp. 160-169.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:32:51">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/1539/</link><title>The Psychopathology of Walrasian Marxism.</title><description>Freeman, Alan (1996): The Psychopathology of Walrasian Marxism. Published in: Freeman, A. and Guglielmo Carchedi 'Marx and non-equilibrium economics', Aldershot: Edward Elgar (1996): pp. 1-29.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:35:47">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/23180/</link><title>Edith Penrose’s ‘The Theory of the Growth of the Firm’ Fifty Years Later.</title><description>Pitelis, Christos (2009): Edith Penrose’s ‘The Theory of the Growth of the Firm’ Fifty Years Later.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7480-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7480_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:36:29">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/41931/</link><title>Research and Science Today No.3.</title><description>Gheorghe, Anamaria Elena and Manole, Andrada Ligia and Andronache, Alin and Cristescu, Cătălin and Luca, Cătălin Viorel and Constantin, Pompiliu Nicolae and Rogojanu, Dumitru Cătălin and Luca, Constantin and Duţă, Andeea Emilia and Mărcău, Flavius Cristian and Ciorei, Mihaela Andreea and Marin, Ştefan Claudiu and Mihalache, Gabriela and Liţoiu (MurăriIţa), Cristina and Cigăreanu, Elena and Purcaru, Mihai and Bușe, Dan and Papuc, Valentin (2012): Research and Science Today No.3. Published in: Research and Science Today</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>