<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:15:19" name="MPRA" id="FW14-e009"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:15:19">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/44723/</link><title>Placing Romania in the European and International Market: The Role of Image in building a Nation Identity.</title><description>Soproni, Luminita and Stoica, Alina and Drinda, Roxana (2009): Placing Romania in the European and International Market: The Role of Image in building a Nation Identity. Published in: Luminita Soproni, Ioan Horga (eds.), Media and European Diversity/ Médias et Diversité Européenne, Bruxelles: Bruylant, 2012 , Vol. 8, No. Collection Voisinages Europeens (May 2012): pp. 239-254.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:17:35">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/15628/</link><title>Creative Industries: Case Studies from Arab Countries.</title><description>Harabi, Najib (2009): Creative Industries: Case Studies from Arab Countries.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:20:44">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/44940/</link><title>Agro Lending - An Instrument for viable Agribusiness.</title><description>Kovachev, Goran (2012): Agro Lending - An Instrument for viable Agribusiness. Published in: NGO Magazine: International Magazine about the NGO Sector No. No. 5 (December 2012): p. 15.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:23:27">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/6707/</link><title>Performance of the Arabic Book Translation Industry in Selected Arab Countries: Egypt, Lebanon, Morocco, Saudi-Arabia and Syria.</title><description>Harabi, Najib (2007): Performance of the Arabic Book Translation Industry in Selected Arab Countries: Egypt, Lebanon, Morocco, Saudi-Arabia and Syria.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:24:50">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/44416/</link><title>Foundations of the economic and social history of the United States: Theoretical.</title><description>Albers, Scott (2013): Foundations of the economic and social history of the United States: Theoretical.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:26:20">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/45887/</link><title>Research and Science Today No. 1(5)/2013.</title><description>ADAM, Elena and TRIȘCAȘ, Floarea Elena and NICOARĂ, Raluca-Maria and IVAN, Ruben Ioan and DUȚĂ, Paul and PANAIT, Ion and MANOLACHE, Viorella and ANDRONACHE, Alin and TRANDAFIR, Andreea and TAROPA-IACOB, Anda and DUȚĂ, Andreea Emilia and IORDAN, Costel and ALEXA, Oana Alexandra and CIOREI, Mihaela Andreea and MARCAU, Flavius-Cristian and SIMA, Isabella Cristiana and MATEIU, Mihaela and NISIPEANU, Elena and CĂLIN, Alexandra and HARANGUS, Katalin and EDU, Filip Vladimir and MARIN, Aurelia Camelia and AŞER, Nica and BOGDAN, Laura and MOGA, Monika and VULPAȘU, Dana and COSTESCU, Elena-Alis and CIUNTUC, Cristina-Elena and NECHIFOR, Caleb Otniel Traian and CRISTESCU, Cosmina and PIPOŞ, Cristina (2013): Research and Science Today No. 1(5)/2013. Published in: Research and Science Today No. 1(5)/2013 (1. March 2013)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:28:03">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/31615/</link><title>Linking farmers to markets through valorisation of local resources:the case for intellectual property rights of indigenous resources.</title><description>Bienabe, Estelle and Bramley, Cerkia and Kirsten, Johann and Troskie, Dirk (2011): Linking farmers to markets through valorisation of local resources:the case for intellectual property rights of indigenous resources.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e009-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e009/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:29:11">http://mpra.ub.uni-muenchen.de/26975/</link><title>Proceedings“Regulation and Best Practices in Public and Nonprofit Marketing”.</title><description>Matei, Lucica and Dinu, Teodora (2010): Proceedings“Regulation and Best Practices in Public and Nonprofit Marketing”. Published in: (1. August 2010): pp. 1-661.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>