<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:22" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:23">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/112711?ln=en</link><title>Male circumcision and prevalence of genital human papillomavirus infection in men : a multinational study</title><description>Male circumcision and prevalence of genital human papillomavirus infection in men : a multinational study / Albero Abril, Ginesa (Institut Català d'Oncologia) ; Villa, Luisa L. (Ludwig Institute for Cancer Research (São Paulo, Brasil)) ; Lazcano Ponce, Eduardo (Instituto Nacional de Salud Publica (Cuernavaca, Mèxic)) ; Fulp, William (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Papenfuss, Mary R. (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Nyitray, Alan G. (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Lu, Beibei (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Castellsagué, Xavier (Institut Català d'Oncologia) ; Abrahamsen, Martha (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Smith, Danélle (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) ; Bosch Jose, Francesc Xavier (Institut Català d'Oncologia) ; Salmerón, Jorge (Instituto Mexicano del Seguro Social) ; Quiterio, Manuel (Instituto Nacional de Salud Publica (Cuernavaca, Mèxic)) ; Giuliano, Anna R. (H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center and Research Institute (Tampa, Estats Units d'Amèrica)) 
Background: Accumulated evidence from epidemiological studies and more recently from randomized controlled trials suggests that male circumcision (MC) may substantially protect against genital HPV infection in men. [...] 
2013 
BMC Infectious diseases, Vol. 13, Núm. 18 (January 2013) , p. 1-10</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7003_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2013/112711/bmcinfdis_a2013m1v13n18.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>