<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:20" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:21">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/44583?ln=en</link><title>Testing the entrepreneurial intention model on a two-country sample</title><description>Testing the entrepreneurial intention model on a two-country sample / Liñán, Francisco ; Chen, Yi-Wen ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia de l'Empresa 
This paper tests the Entrepreneurial Intention Model -which is adapted from the Theory of Planned Behavior- on a sample of 533 individuals from two quite different countries: one of them European (Spain) and the other South Asian (Taiwan). [...] 
Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia de l'Empresa 2006 (Document de treball (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia de l'Empresa) ; 06/7)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/estudis/2006/hdl_2072_2213/UABDT06-7.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:46">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/108829?ln=en</link><title>Tracing the origin of the east-west population admixture in the Altai region (Central Asia)</title><description>Tracing the origin of the east-west population admixture in the Altai region (Central Asia) / González Ruiz, Mercedes (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) ; Pereira dos Santos, Cristina Maria (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) ; Jordana Comín, Xavier (Institut Català de Paleontologia) ; Simón Martínez, Marc (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) ; Lalueza Fox, Carles, 1965- (Institut de Biologia Evolutiva (Barcelona, Catalunya)) ; Gigli, Elena (Institut de Biologia Evolutiva (Barcelona, Catalunya)) ; Aluja, Ma. Pilar (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) ; Malgosa Morera, Assumpció (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) 
A recent discovery of Iron Age burials (Pazyryk culture) in the Altai Mountains of Mongolia may shed light on the mode and tempo of the generation of the current genetic east-west population admixture in Central Asia. [...] 
2012 
PLoS one, Vol. 7, Issue 11 (November 2012) , p. e48904</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2012/108829/ploone_a2012m11v7n11pe48904.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:19">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/90897?ln=en</link><title>Gender and Asia : Why Study Media Culture?</title><description>Gender and Asia : Why Study Media Culture? / Kim, Youna (The American University of Paris (France)) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Grupo de Investigación Inter Asia 
Este artículo explora la experiencia cotidiana con los media de las mujeres en los países asiáticos, en contraposición a los enormes cambios y transiciones sociales. Los medios implican los complejos procesos del cambio y la transición social, desde el comportamiento de la vida diaria a la comprensión reflexiva del mundo global, o a la construcción de una nueva identidad y una constante tensión en su expresión dentro del día a día. [...] 
This article explores women’s everyday experience of the media in Asian countries in confrontation with huge social change and transition. The media involve the complex processes of social change and transition – from the conduct of everyday life, to the reflexive understanding of a global world, to the construction of a new identity and a constant tension in its expression within the everyday. [...] 
2011 
Inter Asia papers, Núm. 23 (2011) , p. 1-25</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/intasipap/intasipap_a2011n23/intasipap_a2011n23p1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:44">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/65261?ln=en</link><title>El teatro tradicional japonés bajo la mirada del Gaijín : de Francisco Javier a nuestros días</title><description>El teatro tradicional japonés bajo la mirada del Gaijín : de Francisco Javier a nuestros días / Cid Lucas, Fernando 
En el presente trabajo se expondrán las diversas impresiones que los occidentales han formulado sobre las formas del teatro clásico japonés. Así, pues, se presentarán los tempranos testimonios recogidos en las cartas y en las relaciones de los misioneros ibéricos destinados en Japón durante los siglos XVI y XVII, y también los de los viajeros, diplomáticos y hombres de letras occidentales que estuvieron destinados en Japón tras la apertura del país en 1854 al resto del mundo. 
This essay focuses on the influence that traditional forms of Japanese drama had on Western culture. This paper will present ideas and impressions from Spanish and Portuguese men of faith who travelled to Japan during the 16th and 17th centuries and the testimony of men of letters and diplomats who settled down in the Asian country after the Opening of Japan in 1854. 
2010 
Inter Asia papers, Núm. 18 ( 2010) , p. 1-15</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/intasipap/20131747n18p1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:48:15">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/40083?ln=en</link><title>Genealogía del Tecno-Orientalismo</title><description>Genealogía del Tecno-Orientalismo / Lozano Méndez, Artur 
Esta monografía explora las raíces del discurso tecno-orientalista y sus intercambios con otros discursos. Se estudia en detalle su composición simbólica y su evolución, desde el milagro económico japonés hasta el siglo XXI. [...] 
This monograph explores the sources of techno-orientalist discourse and its exchanges with other discourses. We study in detail both its symbolic composition and its evolution from the time of the Japanese economic miracle to the xxist century. [...] 
2009 
Inter Asia papers, N. 7 (2009) p. 1-64</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7014_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/intasipap/20131747n7p1.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>