<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:13:02" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:13:03">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/63901?ln=en</link><title>Localization and object recognition for mobile robots</title><description>Localization and object recognition for mobile robots / Ramisa Ayats, Arnau ; Toledo Morales, Ricardo (dir.) ; López de Mántaras Badia, Ramón (dir.) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona Departament d'Informatica 
Tot i que apareixen noves tècniques que equipen els robots amb capacitats cognitives avançades, encara s'ha dedicat poca feina a una qüestió essencial per aquestes tècniques: mètodes ràpids i robustos per a la percepció d'elements semànticament rellevants en entorns no estructurats. [...] 
Although new approaches to enable robots with advanced cognitive capabilities are being developed, still few work is being devoted to a difficult problem in which all this techniques rely: fast and robust perception methods to detect semantically relevant elements in unstructured environments. [...] 
[Bellaterra] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, DL 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7024_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2009/tdx-0527110-122909/ara1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:46">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/56416?ln=en</link><title>Les normes du jugement moral chez l'enfant: transmission ou creation?</title><description>Les normes du jugement moral chez l'enfant: transmission ou creation? / Da Gloria, Jorge ; Carreto Batista, José 
La adquisición por el niño de las normas de regulación moral de sus propias conductas ha sido analizada desde dos enfoques teóricos contrapuestos. Las teorías del aprendizaje social (Bandura y otros) consideran que las conductas de los niños reproducen el contenido de los mensajes simbólicos que emanan de su entorno social y que son interiorizados a través de mecanismos de refuerzo de dichas conductas de reproducción. [...] 
The child's acquisition of the moral regulation norms of their own behavior has been analysed from two opposing theoretical perspectives. Social learning theories (Bandura and others) state that child behavior duplicates the content of symbolic messages produced by his social environment. [...] 
1983 
Quaderns de psicologia, Vol. 7, Núm. 1 ( 1983) , p. 23-44</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7024_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/quapsi/quapsi_a1983v7n1/quapsi_a1983v7n1p23.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>