<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:03" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:04">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113639?ln=en</link><title>Optimización Multi-Objetivo de la Secuencia de aterrizaje de aviones</title><description>Optimización Multi-Objetivo de la Secuencia de aterrizaje de aviones / Huguet García, Patricia ; Napalkova, Liana Ramos González, Juan José , dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Escola d'Enginyeria 
Se proponen dos métodos para resolver el problema de Secuencia de Aterrizaje de Aviones. En este problema el controlador debe asignar un tiempo de aterrizaje y una pista a cada avión que entran en el radar, minimizando los costes a la vez que se respetan un número de restricciones operacionales. [...] 
Es proposen dos mètodes per resoldre el problema de seqüencia d’aterratges d’avions. En aquest problema, el controlador ha d’assignar un temps d’aterratge y una pista a cada avió que entra dins el rang del radar, minimitzant els costos i alhora respectant un nombre restriccions. [...] 
Two approaches are described for solving the Aircraft Landing Scheduling Problem. In this problem, the air traffic controller must assign a landing time for each aircraft which enters the radar range, and must attempt to minimize cost while considering a number of constrains and restrictions. [...] 
2013 
Graduat o Graduada en Gestió Aeronàutica [829]</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tfg/2013/113639/HuguetGarciaPatricia-TFGAa2012-13.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:56">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113096?ln=en</link><title>Activación electroquímica de interruptores moleculares en sistemas fotocrómicos y ácido-base</title><description>Activación electroquímica de interruptores moleculares en sistemas fotocrómicos y ácido-base / Prats Álvarez, Gemma ; Gallardo García, Iluminada ; Guirado López, Gonzalo ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Química 
En los últimos años se ha dedicado gran esfuerzo al estudio de moléculas cuyas propiedades físico-químicas pueden ser controladas reversiblemente mediante un estímulo externo. Estos sistemas reciben el nombre de interruptores moleculares, debido a su capacidad de interconvertir entre dos estados diferenciados, "On" y "Off". [...] 
Extensive research has been recently devoted to the study of molecules whose physicochemical properties can be reversibly switched as response to an external stimulus. These systems are named as molecular switches due to their ability to be interconverted between an “Off” and an “On” states. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2013/hdl_10803_117473/gpa1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:26:08">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113075?ln=en</link><title>Preparation and characterization of magnetic EuO and related compounds : EuS and Eu2O3</title><description>Preparation and characterization of magnetic EuO and related compounds : EuS and Eu2O3 / Moder, Iris ; Rodríguez Viejo, Javier, dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Física) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Física 
El monóxido de europio EuO es un material ferromagnético que muestra una gran variedad de fenómenos físicos y se utiliza a menudo como sistema ideal. Cabe destacar el efecto Kerr, el transporte de espín y, para EuO , una transición metal-aislante con magnetorresistencia colosal. [...] 
Ferromagnetic europium monoxide (EuO) displays a huge variety of physical phenomena and due to its simple structure it is often used as a model system. It shows magneto-optic Kerr effect, spin-dependent transport and, in the case of Eu doped EuO, a metal-insulator transition showing a colossal magnetoresistance. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/img/uab/embargament.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:28:48">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113000?ln=en</link><title>Effectiveness of an integrated vector management control strategy for the tiger mosquito (Aedes albopictus) : a case study in Sant Cugat del Vallès (Barcelona)</title><description>Effectiveness of an integrated vector management control strategy for the tiger mosquito (Aedes albopictus) : a case study in Sant Cugat del Vallès (Barcelona) / Abramides, Gisela Chebabi ; Giménez Gómez, Nuria, dir. ; Hove, Sybille van den, dir. ; Roiz, David, dir. ; Institut de Ciència i Tecnologia Ambientals 
El mosquito tigre, Aedes albopictus (Skuse, 1894), es una especie invasora que actualmente se encuentra en los cinco continentes, extendiéndose desde su área nativa en el sudeste de Asia a través del comercio internacional de neumáticos usados y del bambú de la suerte. [...] 
The Asian tiger mosquito, Aedes albopictus (Skuse, 1894), is an invasive species that is currently found in the five continents, spreading from its native area in Southeast Asia through the international trade of used tires and lucky bamboo. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/img/uab/embargament.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:30:16">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/111681?ln=en</link><title>Development of gluten-free bread formulations</title><description>Development of gluten-free bread formulations / Miñarro Vivas, Begoña ; Capellas Puig, Marta dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciència Animal i dels Aliments) ; Albanell Trullas, Elena dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciència Animal i dels Aliments) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciència Animal i dels Aliments 
Los celíacos no toleran el gluten, la principal proteína presente en el trigo, el centeno y la cebada, que da a la masa las propiedades viscoelásticas necesarias para desarrollar productos panificables de buena calidad. [...] 
Celiac patients cannot tolerate gluten, the protein from wheat, rye and barley that gives to dough the viscoelastic properties required to develop bakery products of good quality. Its lack results in liquid batter rather than dough, yielding breads with a crumbling texture, pale colour and poor mouth-feel. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_116216/bmv1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:32:12">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/106852?ln=en</link><title>Learning strategies to increase piglets feed intake after weaning</title><description>Learning strategies to increase piglets feed intake after weaning / Figueroa Hamed, Jaime ; Pérez Hernández, José Francisco, dir. ; Manteca Vilanova, Xavier, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciència Animal i dels Aliments 
En el presente trabajo se estudian diferentes estrategias de aprendizaje de la conducta alimentaria en cerdos lactantes y destetados. Los lechones podrían aprender a preferir aromas a través de su madre (Capitulo 1 y 5), por ensayo y error (Capitulo 2 y 3) o mediante interacciones sociales con otros lechones (Capitulo 4). [...] 
The present work studies different learning strategies to increase the preference for flavours cues during lactation and after weaning. We propose that pigs may learn flavour preferences from their mother (Chapter 1 and 5), from trial and error tasks (Chapter 2 and 3) or from social interactions with conspecifics (Chapter 4), and that this learning may improve intake of new diets. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, DL 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_06_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_107976/jfh1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:36:01">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/106844?ln=en</link><title>Nosotros somos los que hemos hecho esta ciudad : autoorganización y movilización vecinal durante el tardofranquismo y el proceso de cambio político</title><description>Nosotros somos los que hemos hecho esta ciudad : autoorganización y movilización vecinal durante el tardofranquismo y el proceso de cambio político / Bordetas Jiménez, Ivan ; Marín i Corbera, Martí, 1965-, dir. ; Ysàs, Pere, 1955-, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona Departament d'Historia Moderna i Contemporania 
La historia que se relata en esta tesis doctoral constituye un análisis del surgimiento y trayectoria del movimiento vecinal en la España del tardofranquismo y el proceso de cambio político. El marco cronológico de la investigación cubre desde la inmediata posguerra, con el reemprendimiento de las migraciones y la gestión franquista de este fenómeno y del derivado crecimiento urbano, pasando por la etapa desarrollista, hasta llegar al tiempo del cambio político. [...] 
This doctoral thesis is centred on an analysis of the growth and trajectory of the neighbourhood movement in Spain during late Francoism and the transition. The time period of the research is from the immediate post-war period, through to the resurgence of mass migration. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_07_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_96186/ivj1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:40:40">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/106842?ln=en</link><title>Estudio estilístico contrastivo de las seis traducciones al chino de Platero y yo</title><description>Estudio estilístico contrastivo de las seis traducciones al chino de Platero y yo / Lin, Chi-lien ; Rovira-Esteva, Sara, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona Departament de Traduccio i Interpretacio 
El objetivo principal de esta tesis es hacer un estudio contrastivo del estilo que caracterizan Platero y yo y sus seis traducciones al chino. Primero, hemos presentado una revisión teórica sobre los parámetros extratextuales que configuran el contexto de creación y de recepción de la obra original y sus textos meta. [...] 
The main objective of this thesis is to contrast the style of the masterpiece Platero y yo and its six Chinese translations. First of all, we have revised the theories about the extratextual parameters that form the context of creation and reception of the source text and its target text. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_08_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_96414/cl1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:43:05">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/103764?ln=en</link><title>Influence of feed characteristics and sensorial perception on solid feed consumption of young calves around weaning</title><description>Influence of feed characteristics and sensorial perception on solid feed consumption of young calves around weaning / Montoro Morcillo, Carlos ; Bach, Alex dir. (Institut de Recerca i Tecnologia Agroalimentàries) ; Ferret i Quesada, Alfred dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciència Animal i dels Aliments) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Sanitat i d'Anatomia Animals 
Durant aquesta tesis es varen realitzar sis estudis en vedells joves amb l'objectiu de conèixer estratègies per incrementar el consum de concentrat al voltant del deslletament. En primer lloc, es realitzà un estudi per desenvolupar un mètode per determinar preferències oro-sensorials en vedells deslletats, aquest mètode va consistir en registrar el consum d'un grup mínim de 20 animals individualitzats, als quals se'ls ofertà una doble opció de dos ingredients o concentrats durant un període de 6 h. [...] 
In this thesis, six studies in young calves were performed in order to find strategies to increase concentrate intake around weaning. The first study was conducted to develop a method to determine oro-sensory preferences in weaned calves. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_09_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_96701/cmm1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:44:14">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/103720?ln=en</link><title>Many-to-many high order matching : applications to tracking and object segmentation</title><description>Many-to-many high order matching : applications to tracking and object segmentation / Rubio Ballester, Jose C. ; Serrat Gual, Joan, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Ciències de la Computació 
La correspondència de característiques és un problema fonamental de la Visió per Computador, que té múltiples aplicacions com el seguiment, la classificació i recuperació d'imatges, el reconeixement de formes i la visió estereoscòpica. [...] 
Feature matching is a fundamental problem in Computer Vision, having multiple applications such as tracking, image classification and retrieval, shape recognition and stereo fusion. In numerous domains, it is useful to represent the local structure of the matching features to increase the matching accuracy or to make the correspondence invariant to certain transformations (affine, homography, etc…). [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7027_10_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_96481/jcrb1de1.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>