<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:07:12" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:07:12">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/45168?ln=en</link><title>The effect of candidate quality on electoral equilibrium : an experimental study</title><description>The effect of candidate quality on electoral equilibrium : an experimental study / Aragonès, Enriqueta ; Palfrey, Thomas R. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat de Fonaments de l'Anàlisi Econòmica ; Institut d'Anàlisi Econòmica 
When two candidates of different quality compete in a one dimensional policy space, the equilibrium outcomes are asymmetric and do not correspond to the median. There are three main effects. First, the better candidate adopts more centrist policies than the worse candidate. [...] 
2006 (Working papers ; 530.02)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/worpap/2006/hdl_2072_1919/53002.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:11:14">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/109334?ln=en</link><title>Human's cognitive ability to assess facial cues from photographs : a study of sexual selection in the Bolivian Amazon</title><description>Human's cognitive ability to assess facial cues from photographs : a study of sexual selection in the Bolivian Amazon / Undurraga, Eduardo A. (Brandeis University (Waltham, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Heller School for Social Policy and Management) ; Eisenberg, Dan T. A. (Northwestern University (Evanston, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Department of Anthropology) ; Magvanjav, Oyunbileg (Brandeis University (Waltham, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Heller School for Social Policy and Management) ; Wang, Ruoxue () ; Leonard, William R. (Northwestern University (Evanston, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Department of Anthropology) ; McDade, Thomas W. (Northwestern University (Evanston, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Department of Anthropology) ; Reyes Garcia, Victòria (Institut de Ciència i Tecnologia Ambientals) ; Nyberg, Colleen (Northwestern University (Evanston, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Department of Anthropology) ; Tanner, Susan (University of Georgia (Athens, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Department of Anthropology) ; Huanca, Tomás (Centro Boliviano de Investigación y de Desarrollo Socio Integral (San Borja, Bolívia)) ; Godoy, Ricardo A. (Brandeis University (Waltham, Estats Units d’Amèrica). Heller School for Social Policy and Management) ; Tsimane' Amazonian Panel Study (TAPS). Bolivia Study Team 
Background: Evolutionary theory suggests that natural selection favors the evolution of cognitive abilities which allow humans to use facial cues to assess traits of others. The use of facial and somatic cues by humans has been studied mainly in western industrialized countries, leaving unanswered whether results are valid across cultures. [...] 
2010 
PLoS one, Vol. 5, Issue 6 (June 2010) , p. e11027</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2010/109334/ploone_a2010m6v5n6pe11027.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:13:56">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/24579?ln=en</link><title>Optimal Geometric Matching for Patch-Based Object Detection</title><description>Optimal Geometric Matching for Patch-Based Object Detection / Keysers, Daniel ; Deselaers, Thomas ; Breuel, Thomas M. 
We present an efficient method to determine the optimal matching of two patch-based image object representations under rotation, scaling, and translation (RST). This use of patches is equivalent to a fullyconnected part-based model, for which the presented approach offers an efficient procedure to determine the best fit. [...] 
2007 
ELCVIA : Electronic Letters on Computer Vision and Image Analysis, V. 6 n. 1 (2007) p. 44-54</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7031_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/elcvia/15775097v6n1p44.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>