<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:20:15" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:20:17">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/38291?ln=en</link><title>Las Ciudades como actores políticos en las relaciones internacionales</title><description>Las Ciudades como actores políticos en las relaciones internacionales / Marx, Vanessa 
La actuación de las ciudades en el contexto internacional y el reconocimiento de su papel en este ámbito plantean la necesidad de verificar si las ciudades son actores políticos en este área, ya que hasta ahora este rol ha sido ejercido en exclusiva por los gobiernos centrales. [...] 
The action of cities in the international context and the recognition of its role in this field, states the need of further examination to verify if they are actually political actors, although this role have been exclusively fulfilled by central governments. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, DL2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2009/tdx-0401109-152638/vm1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:21:25">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/36902?ln=en</link><title>Prostitutas, jugadores, pobres y vagos en los discursos periodísticos : Porto Alegre, siglo XIX</title><description>Prostitutas, jugadores, pobres y vagos en los discursos periodísticos : Porto Alegre, siglo XIX / Marocco, Beatriz ; Gómez Mompart, Josep Lluís dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Periodisme i de Ciències de la Comunicació) 
Esta investigación, en forma de tesis doctoral, más que una historia de la prensa, pretende ser una reflexión histórica, con enfoque genealógico, dedicada al estudio de la mecánica del poder y de la normatividad occidental que subyace a un objeto propio del campo de la comunicología —el modo de objetivación periodística de los individuos «sin importancia», los también denominados «hombres infames». [...] 
This investigation, more than a history of the press can be considered an historical reflection with a genealogic approach, dedicated to the study of the mechanics of the power and the western normativity that characterizes the materiality of an object own of the field of the comunicology —the press way of objetivate the reality. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2003</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2002/tdx-0123104-162826/bm1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:22:04">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/36628?ln=en</link><title>Trabajar en el nuevo capitalismo : cultura y experiencia del trabajo en el Brasil contemporáneo</title><description>Trabajar en el nuevo capitalismo : cultura y experiencia del trabajo en el Brasil contemporáneo / Martins Goulart, Patrícia ; Blanch i Ribas, Josep Maria dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Psicologia de la Salut i Psicologia Social) 
El objetivo principal de esta investigación es el de conocer el significado del trabajo, la visualización y el afrontamiento del propio futuro laboral en la muestra investigada, integrada por personas brasileñas del sur del país. [...] 
O objetivo principal desta investigação é o de conhecer o significado do trabalho, a visualização e o afrontamento do próprio futuro laboral na amostra investigada, integrada por pessoas brasileiras do sul do país. [...] 
The main objective of this research is to know the meaning of the work, the visualization of the proper labor future and the way of coping with this future in the investigated sample, integrated for brazilian people of the south of the country. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2006/tdx-0213107-155722/pmg1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:25:05">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/112190?ln=en</link><title>Memoria anual</title><description>Memoria anual / Autoridade Portuaria de Vilagarcía 
Vilagarcía de Arousa (Pontevedra) : Autoridad Portuaria de Vilagarcía , 1998 
4 documents; 
 UAB restricted access</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/min/infanu/112190/iaPORTVILAGARCIAa2000ispa.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:03">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/116231?ln=en</link><title>Viva Mulher : constructing a cervical cancer control program in Brazil</title><description>Viva Mulher : constructing a cervical cancer control program in Brazil / Porto, Marco Antonio (Universidade Federal Fluminense (Niterói)) ; Arantes Botelho Briglia Habib, Paula (Fundação Oswaldo Cruz (Rio de Janeiro). Inovatec Program) 
Through a number of isolated initiatives that began in the 1960s, Brazil accumulated knowledge and experience that in the late 1990s culminated in the implementation of the first nationwide public health action meant to coordinate health bodies and personnel from the federal, state, and municipal administrative levels to address a chronic degenerative disease. [...] 
2014 
Dynamis : Acta Hispanica ad Medicinae Scientiarumque. Historiam Illustrandam, Vol. 34, Núm. 1 (2014) , p. 101-123</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/dynamis/dynamis_a2014v34n1/dynamis_a2014v34n1p101.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:33:17">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/115509?ln=en</link><title>Comment on "Exchange Bias Dependence on Interface Spin Alignment in a Ni80Fe20/(Ni,Fe)O Thin Film"</title><description>Comment on "Exchange Bias Dependence on Interface Spin Alignment in a Ni80Fe20/(Ni,Fe)O Thin Film" / Geshev, Julian (URFGS. Instituto de Física (Porto Alegre, Brazil)) ; Pereira, L. G. (URFGS. Instituto de Física (Porto Alegre, Brazil)) ; Skumryev, Vassil (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Física) ; American Physical Society 
2008 
Physical review letters, Vol. 100, Issue 3 (January 2008) , p. 039701-1</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_06_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2008/115509/phyrevlet_a2008m1v100n3p039701.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:34:04">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/114242?ln=en</link><title>Sobre o Desenvolvimento do Talento no Desporto : um Contributo dos Modelos Teóricos do Desenvolvimento Desportivo</title><description>Sobre o Desenvolvimento do Talento no Desporto : um Contributo dos Modelos Teóricos do Desenvolvimento Desportivo / Barreiros, André (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Laboratório de Psicologia do Desporto) ; Côté, Jean (Queens’ University. School of Kinesiology and Health Studies) ; Fonseca, António Manuel (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Laboratório de Psicologia do Desporto) 
Com este artigo, pretende-se, em termos globais, sintetizar conceptualmente alguns dos mais importantes avanços das últimas décadas no âmbito da temática do talento no desporto, mas também contribuir para que os diferentes agentes desportivos, particularmente dirigentes e treinadores, os possam reconhecer e aplicar nos seus quotidianos. [...] 
With this article, we aim to offer a conceptual synthesis of some of the most important developments in past decades on the subject of talent in sport, while also helping sports stakeholders, particularly managers and coaches, to recognize and apply these conclusions in their practices. [...] 
2013 
Revista de psicología del deporte, Vol. 22, Núm. 2 (2013) , p. 489-494</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_07_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/revpsidep/revpsidep_a2013v22n2/revpsidep_a2013v22n2p489.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:37:12">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/114241?ln=en</link><title>Um olhar sobre o desenvolvimento positivo dos jovens através do desporto</title><description>Um olhar sobre o desenvolvimento positivo dos jovens através do desporto / Esperança, Jorge Manuel (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Faculdade de Desporto) ; Regueiras, Maria Leonor (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Faculdade de Desporto) ; Brustad, Robert John (University of Northern Colorado. School of Sport and Exercise Science) ; Fonseca, António Manuel (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Faculdade de Desporto) 
This article is based on the recognition of the importance of Positive Youth Development (PYD) as a concept, while also highlighting its still relatively scarce dissemination and application in sporting contexts, particularly in Portuguese-speaking countries. [...] 
2013 
Revista de psicología del deporte, Vol. 22, Núm. 2 (2013) , p. 481-487</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_08_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/revpsidep/revpsidep_a2013v22n2/revpsidep_a2013v22n2p481.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:38:11">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/114239?ln=en</link><title>Emoções no desporto : O que sabemos e o (que sentimos) que julgamos saber</title><description>Emoções no desporto : O que sabemos e o (que sentimos) que julgamos saber / Dias, Cláudia (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Centro de Investigação, Formação, Intervenção e Inovação em Desporto) ; Corte-Real, Nuno (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Centro de Investigação, Formação, Intervenção e Inovação em Desporto) ; Cruz, José Fernando (Universidade do Minho (Portugal). Centro de Investigação em Psicologia (CIPsi)) ; Fonseca, António Manuel (Universidade do Porto (Portugal). Centro de Investigação, Formação, Intervenção e Inovação em Desporto) 
Ao longo das últimas décadas, as emoções assumiram um lugar de pleno direito na investigação em psicologia do desporto, sendo, actualmente, um dos temas mais produtivos da literatura neste domínio. [...] 
Over the last decades, emotions have assumed their rightful place in sport psychology research. Emotions are currently one of the most productive themes in the literature in this field. This paper opens by analysing some basic conceptual and methodological issues concerning the definition, classification and assessment of emotions, and it outlines the main theoretical models that link emotions with performance. [...] 
2013 
Revista de psicología del deporte, Vol. 22, Núm. 2 (2013) , p. 473-480</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_09_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/revpsidep/revpsidep_a2013v22n2/revpsidep_a2013v22n2p473.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7033-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:40:24">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/114213?ln=en</link><title>BMI and self-perceived body shape in Portuguese children</title><description>BMI and self-perceived body shape in Portuguese children / Coelho, Eduarda Maria (University of Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro (Portugal)) ; Padez, Cristina (University of Coimbra) ; Moreira, Pedro (University of Porto) ; Rosado, Victor (Instituto de Investigação Científica Tropical) ; Mourão-Carvalhal, Isabel (University of Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro (Portugal)) 
This study examined the relationship between Portuguese children’s self-perceived body shape and body mass index (BMI) by gender, and BMI values were determined for each silhouette. Method: A sample of 4,211 children aged 7-10 was used. [...] 
2013 
Revista de psicología del deporte, Vol. 22, Núm. 2 (2013) , p. 371-376</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7033_10_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/revpsidep/revpsidep_a2013v22n2/revpsidep_a2013v22n2p371.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>