<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:43" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:44">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/115315?ln=en</link><title>La Activación en la Estrategia Europea de Empleo : traslación a los discursos y las políticas de España y Reino Unido</title><description>La Activación en la Estrategia Europea de Empleo : traslación a los discursos y las políticas de España y Reino Unido / Sanz de Miguel, Pablo ; Lope Peña, Andreu, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Sociologia 
La tesis doctoral titulada “La activación en la Estrategia Europea de Empleo (EEE): traslación a los discursos y las políticas de España y Reino Unido”, trata de responder dos preguntas fundamentales: 1) ¿Cómo se define la estrategia de activación en las instituciones europeas en el periodo que va desde 1997 hasta el año 2008?; 2) ¿Cómo se entiende y concreta la activación en dos países miembros de la UE (España y Reino Unido) dotados de modelos de empleo claramente diferentes? Para responder estas preguntas, se lleva a cabo una investigación de carácter cualitativo, centrada en el análisis del discurso de la activación, y las políticas implementadas en el interior de ambos estados. [...] 
The PhD entitled "Activation in the European Employment Strategy (EES): translation to the discourses and policies of Spain and the UK", seeks to answer two fundamental questions: 1) How is defined the activation approach within the European institutions in the period 1997 to 2008?, 2) How is understood and implemented this activation approach in two EU member countries (Spain, UK) embedded in different employment models? In order to answer these questions, is conducted qualitative research focused on the discourse analysis of the activation. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2013/hdl_10803_125656/psdm1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:03:50">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/102154?ln=en</link><title>Determinants of Spanish firms' life cycle and job</title><description>Determinants of Spanish firms' life cycle and job / Gutiérrez Romero, Roxana ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada 
This paper examines the role of human capital, individual entrepreneurial traits and the business environment on firms' life cycle and on job creation in Spain. For this purpose, we have constructed a pseudo-panel, by using the Global Entrepreneurship Monitor survey over the period 2001-2008. [...] 
2012 (Document de treball (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada) ; 1209)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/estudis/2012/hdl_2072_204081/wpdea1209.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:12">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/44350?ln=en</link><title>Long-run Inflation-Unemployment Dynamics : The Spanish Phillips Curve and Economic Policy</title><description>Long-run Inflation-Unemployment Dynamics : The Spanish Phillips Curve and Economic Policy / Karanassou, Marika ; Sala Lorda, Hèctor (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada 
This paper takes a new look at the long-run dynamics of inflation and unemployment in response to permanent changes in the growth rate of the money supply. We examine the Phillips curve from the perspective of what we call "frictional growth", i. [...] 
2006 (Document de treball (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada) ; 0211)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/estudis/2006/hdl_2072_2092/wpdea0211.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:21">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/37538?ln=en</link><title>Forma urbana y mercado de trabajo : accesibilidad al empleo, segregación residencial y paro</title><description>Forma urbana y mercado de trabajo : accesibilidad al empleo, segregación residencial y paro / Santana García, Juan Antonio ; Roig Sabaté, José Luis dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia Aplicada) 
El objetivo de la tesis es el análisis de la incidencia de la estructura urbana, interpretada como la distribución residencial y del empleo, sobre la determinación de los siguientes aspectos: los patrones de segregación geográfica de los diferenciales intraurbanos de desempleo, las pautas de movilidad obligada y las probabilidades individuales de paro. [...] 
The objective of the thesis is the analysis of the incidence of the urban structure, interpreted like the residential distribution of employment and population, on the determination of the following aspects: the patterns of geographic segregation of the intraurban differentials of unemployment, the commuting patterns and the individual probabilities of unemployment. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2004 
3 documents</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2003/tdx-0701104-165519/jasg1de3.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:51">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113822?ln=en</link><title>Atur juvenil, salut i exclusió social</title><description>Atur juvenil, salut i exclusió social / Espluga, Josep, 1964- (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Sociologia) 
La intención del presente artículo es presentar los objetivos y los primeros resultados de una investigación sobre paro juvenil, exclusión social y salud, que se está llevando a cabo en seis países europeos con el apoyo del Área de Investigación Socio-Económica (TSER) de la Comisión Europea. [...] 
This article shows the goals and earliers results of a research about Youth Unemployment, Social Exclusion and Health (YUSEDER), wich is carrying out in six european countries supported by the European Commision (Targeted Socio-Economic Research). [...] 
2001 
Revista Catalana de Sociologia, Núm. 15 (Setembre 2001) , p. 41-67</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2001/113822/revcatsoc_a2001m9n15p41.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:45">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/112643?ln=en</link><title>Importancia de la participación laboral como determinante del divorcio en España</title><description>Importancia de la participación laboral como determinante del divorcio en España / Simó i Noguera, Carles (Universitat de València. Departament de Sociologia i Antropologia Social) ; Solsona, Montserrat (Centre d’Estudis Demogràfics) 
El potencial de la información retrospectiva recogida en la Encuesta sobre Fecundidad y Familia (1995) nos ha animado a realizar una nueva exploración de la participación laboral como variable explicativa de la propensión a la ruptura de una unión en España de las cohortes de unión de 1966 a 1999. [...] 
The retrospective information in the Spanish Family and Fertility Survey of 1995 has an enormous potential to investigate the labour participation as a explicative covariate of union dissolution. We have studied the propensity of such a determinant for the 1966-1995 union cohorts, while evaluating his relative predictive power within an explicative model including three dimensions: the socialization of the partners, the union characteristics and the educative and professional skills. [...] 
2003 
Papeles de geografía, Núm. 37 (2003) , p. 245-259</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_06_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2003/112643/papgeo_a2003n37p245.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:50">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/112215?ln=en</link><title>La necesaria transformación del modelo productivo en España : el papel del territorio</title><description>La necesaria transformación del modelo productivo en España : el papel del territorio / Pareja-Eastaway, Montserrat (Universitat de Barcelona. Grup de Recerca Creativitat, Innovació i Transformació Urbana) ; Turmo Garuz, Joaquin (Universitat de Barcelona. Grup de Recerca Creativitat, Innovació i Transformació Urbana) ; ; Universitat de Barcelona. Facultat d’Economia i Empresa 
El fracaso de las bases del modelo productivo español fundamentado en una baja productividad se ha traducido en una incapacidad absoluta de reacción frente a la crisis económica con crecientes tasas de paro y un grave estancamiento del PIB. [...] 
El fracàs de les bases del model productiu espanyol fonamentat en una baixa productivitat s’ha traduït en una incapacitat absoluta de reacció davant la crisi econòmica amb creixents taxes d’atur i un greu estancament del PIB. [...] 
L’échec des fondements de modèle de production espagnol, basé sur une faible productivité a entraîné une incapacité totale à réagir à la crise économique avec des taux de chômage en hausse et une stagnation du PIB grave. [...] 
The failure of the foundations of the Spanish production model based on low productivity has resulted in a complete inability to react to the economic crisis with rising unemployment rates and a serious stagnation of GDP. [...] 
2013 
Documents d'anàlisi geogràfica, Vol. 59, Núm. 3 (Setembre-Desembre 2013) , p. 455-479</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_07_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/dag/dag_a2013m9-12v59n3/dag_a2013m9-12v59n3p455.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:24">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/111844?ln=en</link><title>2012 : segunda recesión</title><description>2012 : segunda recesión / Recio Andreu, Albert (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d’Economia Aplicada) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Centre d’Estudis Sociològics sobre la Vida Quotidiana i el Treball (QUIT) ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Institut d’Estudis del Treball (IET) 
El comportament del mercat laboral en 2012 presenta una sèrie de canvis significatius respecte a anteriors episodis de crisi. En 2012 ha tingut lloc una segona recessió que ha suposat la major destrucció d'ocupació des de 2009. [...] 
El comportamiento del mercado laboral en 2012 presenta una serie de cambios significativos respecto a los anteriores años de crisis. En 2012 ha tenido lugar una segunda recesión que ha significado la mayor destrucción de empleo desde 2009. [...] 
In 2012 the Spanish labour market shows significant changes in relation to previous periods of crisis. During 2012 the Spanish economy experiences a second recession which has produced the highest employment destruction since 2009. [...] 
2013 
Anuario IET de trabajo y relaciones laborales, Vol. 1, Núm. (2013) , p. 1-20</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_08_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/anuarioiet/anuarioiet_a2013v1/anuarioiet_a2013v1p1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:39">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/108324?ln=en</link><title>El empleo de la economía española : 1976-1991</title><description>El empleo de la economía española : 1976-1991 / Polo Andrés, José Clemente (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Economia i d'Història Econòmica) 
Este artículo examina la evolución del empleo en la economía española entre 1976 y 1992, cubriendo aproximadamente un ciclo completo de contracción y expansión del empleo. Aunque el propósito del artículo es simplemente presentar los desarrollos más sobresalientes acaecidos al empleo, tanto agregado como sectorial, el texto incluye algunas propuestas de modificación de la normativa que corfigura actualmente el funcionamiento del mercado de trabajo. 
Artikulu honetan, Espainiako ekonomiak 1976 eta 1992 artean izan duen eboluzioaren azterketa egiten da, gutxi gorabehera enpleguaren uzkurtze eta hedapeneko zikio oso bat besarkatuz. Artikuiuaren azken helburua enpleguari -nahiz agregatu eta nahiz sektorial bezala- gertatu zaizkion garapenik nabarienak aurkeztea besterik ez den arren, testuak jasotzen ditu gaur egungo lan-merkatuaren funtzionamendua markatzen duen arautegia aldatzeko proposamen batzuk ere. 
This arlicle examines how employment performed in the Spanish economy between 1976 and 1992, a period which approximately covers a complete cycle of decline and increase in employment. Although the purpose of the article is simply to present the most important developments in emptoyment, in both aggregate and sectorial terms, the text includes proposais for the modification of the regulations which currently control how the labour market operates. 
1992 
Ekonomiaz : revista de economía vasca, Núm. 24 (1992) , p. 72-103</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_09_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/1992/108324/ekonomiaz_a1992n24p72.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:07">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/97785?ln=en</link><title>Sampling design variance estimation of small area estimators in the Spanish Labour Force Survey</title><description>Sampling design variance estimation of small area estimators in the Spanish Labour Force Survey / Herrador, M. ; Morales, Domingo ; Esteban, M. D. ; Sánchez, A. ; Santamaría, Laureano ; Marhuenda, Y. ; Pérez, A. 
The main goal of this paper is to investigate how to estimate sampling design variances of modelbased and model-assisted small area estimators in a complex survey sampling setup. For this purpose the Spanish Labour Force Survey is considered. [...] 
2008 
SORT : statistics and operations research transactions, Vol. 32, Núm. 2 (July-December 2008) , p. 177-198  ; 
 UAB restricted access</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7063_10_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/min/sort/sort_a2008m7-12v32n2/sort_a2008m7-12v32n2p177.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>