<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:39:54" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:39:55">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/37870?ln=en</link><title>¿"A Escola funciona bem"? : participación y descentralización en una favela de Río de Janeiro</title><description>¿"A Escola funciona bem"? : participación y descentralización en una favela de Río de Janeiro / Prado, Ana Pires do ; Carrasco, Sílvia dir. (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament d'Antropologia Social i Cultural) 
La tesis pretende tratar la introducción y el impacto de la descentralización educativa en una comunidad educativa de un entorno socialmente desfavorecido. Un proceso amplio, que envuelve la descentralización administrativa, la descentralización pedagógica y la participación de la comunidad y está influenciado por las cuestiones económicas, sociales, políticas y culturales de nuestro tiempo y que se pretende analizar en su complejidad a partir del trabajo etnográfico. [...] 
This thesis aims at looking upon introduction and impact of educational decentralization in a learning community within a socially unfavorable environment. This process is extensive as it comprises administrative decentralization, pedagogical decentralization and community participation, which is influenced by economic, social, political and cultural questions of our time. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2006/tdx-0327107-155446/app1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:40:57">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/4754?ln=en</link><title>Quand les étudiants jugent leurs études : quelques enseignements d’une recherche internationale</title><description>Quand les étudiants jugent leurs études : quelques enseignements d’une recherche internationale / Lima, Laurent ; Hadji, Charles 
Du double point de vue institutionnel et moral, l’évaluation des enseignements est considérée aujourd’hui comme une obligation. Cependant, les conditions dans lesquelles une telle évaluation peut s’effectuer font l’objet d’un vif débat : « qui ? quoi ? comment ? selon quels référents ? quels indicateurs ? quelle participation des évalués ? quelle publicité des résultats ? » (Demailly, 2001). [...] 
To evaluate teaching is currently considered as compelling, both from an institutional and a moral viewpoint. However the conditions of such an evaluation have triggered strong debates: «Who? What? How? Drawing from which references? Which clues? Should the people assessed take part in the process? To what extent should the results be publicized?» (Demailly, 2001). [...] 
2005 
Papers : revista de sociologia, N. 76 (2005) p. 67-96</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/papers/02102862n76/02102862n76p67.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:44:17">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/65682?ln=en</link><title>Experiència recent en l’adaptació de la Bioquímica general de medicina a l’Espai Europeu d’Educació Superior</title><description>Experiència recent en l’adaptació de la Bioquímica general de medicina a l’Espai Europeu d’Educació Superior / Claro Izaguirre, Enrique (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Facultat de Medicina. Departament de Bioquímica i Biologi) ; Ortiz de Pablo, Jordi (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Bioquímica i de Biologia Molecular) 
La Bioquímica és una materia anual del 1er any de Medicina, on els curs 2006-2007 hem tingut 431 alumnes matriculats. Els professors del 2n quatrimestre de la matèria, dedicat a l'estudi del metabolisme, hem endegat un pla per potenciar l'aprenentatge basat en l'estudiant, una de les accions proposades a la declaració de Glasgow de la EUA. [...] 
Biochemistry is a 1st year, 2-semester compulsory subject in the UAB Medical School syllabus, where 431 students were enrolled during the course 2006-2007. The lecturers in charge of the 2nd semester, which deals with the study of metabolism, have started a new teaching plan paying more attention to active student learning, one of the items stressed in the Glasgow declaration of the EUA. [...] 
2007 
Jornades d'Innovació Docent de la UAB, 4es : 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7106_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2007/65682/jorinndoc_a2007m9n2.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>