<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:11:31" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:11:33">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/64790?ln=en</link><title>Human biology : cibernética y biología humana en el nuevo discurso expositivo de la década de 1970</title><description>Human biology : cibernética y biología humana en el nuevo discurso expositivo de la década de 1970 / Corral Guillé, Gustavo ; Ruiz Castell, Pedro ; Roqué i Rodríguez, Xavier (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Filosofia. Àrea d'Història de la Ciència) ; Centre d'Estudis d'Història de les Ciències 
En este trabajo se explica cuáles fueron las estrategias utilizadas y los resultados obtenidos en la primera exposición del nuevo esquema museográfico del Museo de Historia Natural de Londres, concebido por Roger Miles, Jefe del Departamento de Servicios Públicos de esa prestigiada institución. [...] 
This paper explains what were the strategies used and the results obtained in the first exhibition of the new exhibition scheme of the Natural History Museum in London, conceived by Roger Miles, Head of the Department of Public Services of that prestigious institution. [...] 
2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/trerecpro/2010/hdl_2072_97220/TR_GustavoCorralGuille.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:12:01">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/37895?ln=en</link><title>L'Ensenyament de la història natural a la Barcelona de la primera meitat del segle XIX : els llibres de text i la docència d'Agustí Yàñez i Girona</title><description>L'Ensenyament de la història natural a la Barcelona de la primera meitat del segle XIX : els llibres de text i la docència d'Agustí Yàñez i Girona / Sucarrats i Riera, Raimon 
Aquesta tesi doctoral analitza les característiques i el context que van envoltar la publicació dels dos llibres de text d'història natural que elaborà un dels personatges més significatius de la ciència barcelonesa de la primera meitat del segle XIX: les Lecciones de historia natural d'Agustí Yàñez i Girona en el Col·legi de Farmàcia de Sant Victorià de Barcelona. [...] 
The Lecciones de Historia Natural (Natural History Lessons) by Agustí Yàñez were published in Barcelona in two different versions, the first one in 1820 and the second one in 1844/1845. This present work analyses the main features of these textbooks, the context that made their publication possible and the way they were used in Barcelona's Pharmacy School of San Victoriano and other academic institutions in the first half of 19th century. [...] 
Bellaterra : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2006 
5 documents</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2006/tdx-1109106-133436/rsr1de5.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:15:21">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/113369?ln=en</link><title>Travelling more over time : making an in-situ exhibit at the Montréal-du-Gers palaeontological site (France</title><description>Travelling more over time : making an in-situ exhibit at the Montréal-du-Gers palaeontological site (France / Déniz-González, Itahisa (Muséum d’Histoire Naturelle de Toulouse) ; Duranthon, Francis (Muséum d’Histoire Naturelle de Toulouse) 
There are more ancient remains in palaeontological sites than in archaeological ones, and the structures of habitat or the traces of human activity are absent. In the Miocene dig of Montréaldu- Gers, remains of mammals, gastropods and pollen have been found, and they have make it possible for scientists to decode the past of the region. [...] 
Los yacimientos paleontológicos presentan restos más antiguos que los documentados en yacimientos arqueológicos, y las estructuras de hábitat o las trazas de actividad humana están ausentes. En la excavación miocena de Montréal-du-Gers, han sido recuperados restos de mamíferos, gasterópodos y polen. [...] 
Els jaciments paleontològics presenten restes més antigues que les documentades als jaciments arqueològics, i les estructures d’hàbitat o les traces d’activitat humana hi són absents. En l’excavació miocena de Montréal-du-Gers, hi han estat descobertes restes de mamífers, gasteròpodes i pol·len. [...] 
2013 
Treballs d'arqueologia, Núm. 19 (2013) , p. 41-51</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tda/tda_a2013n19/tda_a2013n19p41.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:18:21">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/109358?ln=en</link><title>The Evolution of invasiveness in garden ants</title><description>The Evolution of invasiveness in garden ants / Cremer, Sylvia (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Ugelvig, Line V. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Drijfhout, Falko P. (Keele University (Regne Unit). School of Physical and Geographical Sciences) ; Schlick-Steiner, Birgit C. (Innsbruck University (Àustria). Institute of Ecology) ; Steiner, Florian M. (Innsbruck University (Àustria). Institute of Ecology) ; Seifert, Bernhard (Natural History Museum Görlitz (Alemanya)) ; Hughes, David P. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Schulz, Andreas (Dormagen (Alemanya)) ; Petersen, Klaus S. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Konrad, Heino (University of Natural Resources and Applied Life Sciences (Viena, Àustria). Department of Forest and Soil Sciences) ; Stauffer, Christian (University of Natural Resources and Applied Life Sciences (Viena, Àustria). Department of Forest and Soil Sciences) ; Kiran, Kadri (Trakya University (Edirne, Turquia). Department of Biology) ; Espadaler, Xavier (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Biologia Animal, de Biologia Vegetal i d'Ecologia) ; d'Ettorre, Patrizia (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Aktaç, Nihat (Trakya University (Edirne, Turquia). Department of Biology) ; Eilenberg, Jorgen (University of Copenhagen. Department of Ecology) ; Jones, Graeme R. (Keele University (Regne Unit). School of Physical and Geographical Sciences) ; Nash, David R. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Pedersen, Jes S. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) ; Boomsma, Jacobus J. (University of Copenhagen. Department of Biology) 
It is unclear why some species become successful invaders whilst others fail, and whether invasive success depends on pre-adaptations already present in the native range or on characters evolving de-novo after introduction. [...] 
2008 
PLoS one, Vol. 3, Issue 12 (December 2008) , p. e3838</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2008/109358/ploone_a2008m12v3n12pe3838.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:21:57">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/102783?ln=en</link><title>Palaeoproterozoic adakite- and TTG-like magmatism in the Svecofennian orogen, SW Finland</title><description>Palaeoproterozoic adakite- and TTG-like magmatism in the Svecofennian orogen, SW Finland / Väisänen, M. (University of Turku. Department of Geography and Geology) ; Johansson, Å. (Swedish Museum of Natural History. Laboratory for Isotope Geology) ; Andersson, U.B. (Uppsala University. Department of Earth Sciences) ; Eklund, O. (Åbo Akademi University. Department of Geology and Mineralogy) ; Hölttä, P. (Geological Survey of Finland GTK) 
The Palaeoproterozoic Svecofennian orogen in the Fennoscandian shield is an arc accretionary orogen that was formed at c. 1. 92-1. 86Ga. Arc accretion, magmatism and the subsequent continent-continent collision thickened the crust up to c. [...] 
2012 
Geologica acta, Vol. 10, Núm. 4 (desembre 2012) , p. 351-371</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2012m12v10n4/geoact_a2012m12v10n4p351.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:22:43">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/89015?ln=en</link><title>Jadeitite from Guatemala : new observations and distinctions among multiple occurrences</title><description>Jadeitite from Guatemala : new observations and distinctions among multiple occurrences / Harlow, G.E. (American Museum of Natural History. Department of Earth and Planetary Sciences) ; Sisson, V. B. (University of Houston. Department of Earth and Atmospheric Sciences) ; Sorensen, S.S. (Smithsonian Institution. Department of Mineral Sciences) 
In Guatemala, jadeitite occurs as blocks in serpentinite mélange in distinct settings on opposite sides of the Motagua fault. Jadeitites north of the Motagua fault are associated with eclogites, blueschists, and garnet amphibolites and distributed over a 200km E-W area. [...] 
2011 
Geologica acta, Vol. 9, Núm. 3-4 (setembre-desembre 2011) , p. 363-387</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_06_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2011m9-12v9n3-4/geoact_a2011m9-12v9n3-4p363.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:26:08">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/85998?ln=en</link><title>The Four Phases of Plant-Arthropod Associations in Deep Time</title><description>The Four Phases of Plant-Arthropod Associations in Deep Time / Labandeira, C. C. (Smithsonian Institution, National Museum of Natural History) ; University of Maryland. Department of Entomology 
Vascular-plant hosts, their arthropod herbivores, and associated functional feeding groups are distributed spatiotemporally into four major herbivore expansions during the past 420 m. y. They are: (1) a Late Silurian to Late Devonian (60 m. [...] 
2006 
Geologica acta, Vol. 4, Núm. 4 (2006) , p. 409-438</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_07_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2006v4n4/geoact_a2006v4n4p409.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:30:01">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/85798?ln=en</link><title>A revised Ordovician age for the Sisargas orthogneiss, Galicia (Spain). Zircon U-Pb ion-microprobe and LA-ICPMS dating</title><description>A revised Ordovician age for the Sisargas orthogneiss, Galicia (Spain). Zircon U-Pb ion-microprobe and LA-ICPMS dating / Talavera, Cristina (Universidad de Granada. Departamento de Mineralogía y Petrología) ; Bea Barredo, Fernando (Universidad de Granada. Departamento de Mineralogía y Petrología) ; González Montero, Pilar (Universidad de Granada. Departamento de Mineralogía y Petrología) ; Whitehouse, Martin (Swedish Museum of Natural History) 
The Sisargas orthogneiss is located in the Schistose Domain of the Galicia Trás-Os-Montes Zone. It has previously been dated by Allegret and Iglesias (1987) who reported an U-Pb upper intercept at 570 ± 14 Ma, considered to be the crystallization age. [...] 
2008 
Geologica acta, Vol. 6, Núm. 4 (Desembre 2008) , p. 313-317</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_08_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2008m12v6n4/geoact_a2008m12v6n4p313.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:30:36">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/85793?ln=en</link><title>The role of new Iberian finds in understanding European Eocene mammalian paleobiogeography</title><description>The role of new Iberian finds in understanding European Eocene mammalian paleobiogeography / Badiola Kortabitarte, Ainara (Universidad de Zaragoza. Área de Paleontología) ; Checa, Lluís (Institut de Paleontologia Dr. M. Crusafont de Sabadell) ; Cuesta Ruiz-Colmenares, Miguel Ángel (Universidad de Salamanca. Departamento de Geología) ; Quer, Ramón ; Hooker, Jerry J. (The Natural History Museum. Palaeontology Department) ; Astibia Ayera, Humberto (Universidad del País Vasco. Departamento de Estratigrafía y Paleontología) 
This paper summarizes the new Eocene mammalian discoveries in western and northeastern Iberia and analyses the paleobiological data they provide towards an understanding of the evolutionary and paleobiogeographic history of the Eocene mammalian faunas across Europe. [...] 
2009 
Geologica acta, Vol. 7, Núm. 1-2 (Març-Juny 2009) , p. 243-258</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_09_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2009m3-6v7n1-2/geoact_a2009m3-6v7n1-2p243.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:34:42">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/74874?ln=en</link><title>Noves aportacions a la distribució del gènere Caenocara Thomson, 1859, Dorcatominae, a Catalunya (Coleoptera: Bostrichoidea)</title><description>Noves aportacions a la distribució del gènere Caenocara Thomson, 1859, Dorcatominae, a Catalunya (Coleoptera: Bostrichoidea) / Viñolas, Amador (Museu de Ciències Naturals de Barcelona) 
S’estudien els exemplars del gènere Caenocara Thomson, 1859, recol·lectats a la península Ibèrica en diversos projectes, i els dipositats en la col·lecció del Museu de Ciències Naturals de Barcelona. [...] 
Specimens of genus Caenocara Thomson, 1859, collected in the Iberian Peninsula in several projects, and the material deposited in the collection of the Natural History Museum of Barcelona are studied. [...] 
2011 
Orsis : Organismes i Sistemes, Vol. 25 (2011) , p. 121-130</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7133_10_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/orsis/02134039n25p121.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>