<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:43:56" name="UAB Digital" id="FW14-e015"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:43:57">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/111718?ln=en</link><title>Evolución tectónica y geomorfológica reciente de las cuencas de antepaís suratlásicas : cuencas de Missour y Ouarzazate</title><description>Evolución tectónica y geomorfológica reciente de las cuencas de antepaís suratlásicas : cuencas de Missour y Ouarzazate / Pastor Castilla, Alvar ; Arboleya, María Luisa, dir. ; Teixell Cácharo, Antonio, dir. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Geologia 
Esta tesis presenta un estudio sobre la neotectónica y la dinámica de la red fluvial en dos cuencas de antepaís de las cordilleras del Atlas de Marruecos, la cuenca de Ouarzazate, situada al sur del Alto Atlas, y la cuenca de Missour, al sur del Medio Atlas. [...] 
This thesis presents a thorough study about the neotectonics and the dynamics of the Quaternary river network in two foreland basins of the Atlas Mountains of Morocco, the Ouarzazate basin and the Missour Basin. [...] 
[Barcelona] : Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona, 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_01_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/tesis/2011/hdl_10803_117197/apc1de1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:46:32">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/102180?ln=en</link><title>Análisis multidisciplinar del fenómeno sismo-volcánico de El Hierro (julio 2011)</title><description>Análisis multidisciplinar del fenómeno sismo-volcánico de El Hierro (julio 2011) / Acosta Armas, Laura ; Casillas Ruiz, Ramón ; Folch i Sancho, Albert ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Facultat de Ciències 
La erupción volcánica submarina de La Restinga (10 de octubre) ha permitido, por primera vez, poner en marcha el Plan Especial de Protección Civil y Atención de Emergencias por Riesgo Volcánico en la Comunidad Autónoma de Canarias. [...] 
L'erupció volcànica submarina de La Restinga (10 d'octubre) ha permès, per primera vegada, engegar el Pla Especial de Protecció Civil i Atenció d'Emergències per Risc Volcànic en la Comunitat Autònoma de Canàries. [...] 
The volcanic submarine eruption of “La Restinga” (October 10th) has allowed, for the first time, to start the Special Plan of Civil Protection and Emergency care for Volcanic Risk in the Canary Community. [...] 
2012 
2 documents</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_02_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/trerecpro/2012/hdl_2072_204199/PFC_LauraAcostaArmas_resum.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:50:13">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/81048?ln=en</link><title>Uranium reserve, nuclear fuel cycle delusion, CO2 emission from the sea, and electricity supply : reflections after the fuel meltdown of Fukushima nuclear power units</title><description>Uranium reserve, nuclear fuel cycle delusion, CO2 emission from the sea, and electricity supply : reflections after the fuel meltdown of Fukushima nuclear power units / Mayumi, Kozo ; Polimeni, John M. ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat d'Història Econòmica 
The Great Tohoku-Kanto earthquake and resulting tsunami has brought considerable attention to the issue of the construction of new power plants. We argue in this paper, nuclear power is not a sustainable solution to energy problems. [...] 
Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat d'Història Econòmica 2011 (Documents de treball (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat d'Història Econòmica) ; 2011/13)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_03_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/estudis/2011/hdl_2072_171394/UHE2011_13.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:52:02">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/45111?ln=en</link><title>Sequencing lifeline repairs after an earthquake : an economic approach</title><description>Sequencing lifeline repairs after an earthquake : an economic approach / Casari, Marco ; Wilkie, Simon ; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat de Fonaments de l'Anàlisi Econòmica ; Institut d'Anàlisi Econòmica 
Recoveries after recent earthquakes in the U. S. and Japan have shown that large welfare gains can be achieved by reshaping current emergency plans as incentive-compatible contracts. We apply tools from the mechanisms design literature to show ways to integrate economic incentives into the management of natural disasters and discuss issues related to the application to seismic event recovery. [...] 
2006 (Working papers ; 587.03)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_04_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/worpap/2006/hdl_2072_1862/58703.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:54:02">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/114272?ln=en</link><title>Universal earthquake-ocurrence jumps, correlations with time, and anomalous diffusion</title><description>Universal earthquake-ocurrence jumps, correlations with time, and anomalous diffusion / Corral Cano, Alvaro (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Departament de Física) ; American Physical Society 
Spatiotemporal properties of seismicity are investigated for a worldwide (WW) catalog and for southern California in the stationary case (SC), showing a nearly universal scaling behavior. Distributions of distances between consecutive earthquakes (jumps) are magnitude independent and show two power-law regimes, separated by jump values about 200 (WW) and 15 km (SC). [...] 
2006 
Physical review letters, Vol. 97, Issue 17 (October 2006) , p. 178501</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_05_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/artpub/2006/114272/phyrevlet_a2006m10v97n17p178501.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:56:18">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/99650?ln=en</link><title>Arc-parallel vs back-arc extension in the Western Gibraltar arc : is the Gibraltar forearc still active?</title><description>Arc-parallel vs back-arc extension in the Western Gibraltar arc : is the Gibraltar forearc still active? / Balanyá, J.C. (Universidad Pablo de Olavide. Departamento de Sistemas Físicos, Químicos y Naturales) ; Crespo-Blanc, A. (Instituto Andaluz de Ciencias de La Tierra) ; Díaz-Azpiroz, M. (Universidad Pablo de Olavide. Departamento de Sistemas Físicos, Químicos y Naturales) ; Expósito, I. (Universidad Pablo de Olavide. Departamento de Sistemas Físicos, Químicos y Naturales) ; Torcal, F. (Instituto Andaluz de Geofísica y Prevención de Desastres Sísmicos) ; Pérez-Peña, V. (Universidad de Granada. Departamento de Geodinámica) ; Booth-Rea, G. (Universidad de Granada. Departamento de Geodinámica) 
Extremely tight arcs, framed within the Eurasia-Africa convergence region, developed during the Neogene on both sides of the western Mediterranean. A complex interplate deformation zone has been invoked to explain their structural trend-line patterns, the shortening directions and the development of back-arc basins. [...] 
2012 
Geologica acta, Vol. 10, Núm. 3 (setembre 2012) , p. 249-263</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_06_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2012m9v10n3/geoact_a2012m9v10n3p249.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:57:41">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/97743?ln=en</link><title>Paleoseismic analysis of the San Vicente segment of the El Salvador Fault Zone, El Salvador, Central America</title><description>Paleoseismic analysis of the San Vicente segment of the El Salvador Fault Zone, El Salvador, Central America / Canora, C. (Universidad Complutense de Madrid. Departamento de Geodinámica) ; Villamor, P. (GNS Science) ; Martínez Día, J.J. (Universidad Complutense de Madrid. Departamento de Geodinámica) ; Berryman, K.R. (GNS Science) ; Álvarez Gómez, J.A. (Universidad de Cantabria. Instituto de Hidráulica Ambiental “IH Cantabria”) ; Capote, R. (Universidad Complutense de Madrid. Departamento de Geodinámica) ; Hernández, W. (Servicio Nacional de Estudios Territoriales (El Salvador)) 
The El Salvador earthquake of February 13th 2001 (Mw 6. 6) was associated with the tectonic rupture of the El Salvador Fault Zone. Paleoseismic studies of the El Salvador Fault Zone undertaken after this earthquake provide a basis for examining the longer history of surface rupturing earthquakes on the fault. [...] 
2012 
Geologica acta, Vol. 10, Núm. 2 (June 2012) , p. 103-123</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_07_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2012m6v10n2/geoact_a2012m6v10n2p103.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:59:47">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/85737?ln=en</link><title>The active fault belts in eastern Tibet margin inferred using magnetotellurics</title><description>The active fault belts in eastern Tibet margin inferred using magnetotellurics / Zhao, G. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Wang, L. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Chen, X. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Tang, J. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Wan, Z. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Zhan, Y. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Xiao, Q. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Cai, J. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) ; Zhang, J. (Earthquake Administration of Shandong Province) ; Wang, J. (Institute of Geology, China Earthquake Administration) 
A magnetotelluric (MT) sounding has been carried out in the eastern margin of the Tibetan plateau. The survey line is about 145 km long, trending in NEE direction and crossing the Daliangshan block in the eastern edge of the Tibetan plateau. [...] 
2010 
Geologica acta, Vol. 8, Núm. 1 (Març 2010) , p. 99-110</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_08_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2010m3v8n1/geoact_a2010m3v8n1p99.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:04:01">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/85736?ln=en</link><title>Deep crustal electromagnetic structure of Bhuj earthquake region (India) and its implications</title><description>Deep crustal electromagnetic structure of Bhuj earthquake region (India) and its implications / Naganjaneyulu, K. (National Geophysical Research Institute, Council of Scientific and Industrial research (CSIR)) ; Ledo, J. J. (Universitat de Barcelona. Departament de Geodinàmica i Geofísica) ; Queralt, P. (Universitat de Barcelona. Departament de Geodinàmica i Geofísica) 
The existence of fluids and partial melt in the lower crust of the seismically active Kutch rift basin (on the western continental margin of India) owing to underplating has been proposed in previous geological and geophysical studies. [...] 
2010 
Geologica acta, Vol. 8, Núm. 1 (Març 2010) , p. 83-97</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_09_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/geoact/geoact_a2010m3v8n1/geoact_a2010m3v8n1p83.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e015-7484-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:08:07">http://ddd.uab.cat/record/72370?ln=en</link><title>El terratrèmol de l’11 de març del 2011 al Japó</title><description>El terratrèmol de l’11 de març del 2011 al Japó / Aliberas, Joan (IES Josep Puig i Cadafalch, Mataró) ; Arboleya, María Luisa (Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. Unitat de Geotectònica) 
El març passat un intens terratrèmol va sacsejar la costa oriental del Japó, produint un tsunami que va originar un nombre molt gran de víctimes i enormes danys materials. Vegem què va succeir. 
2011 
Ciències: revista del professorat de ciències de primària i secundària, Núm. 19 (Juny 2011) , p. 39-46</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e015/7484_10_thumb.png">http://ddd.uab.cat/pub/ciencies/16996712n19/16996712n19p39.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>