<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:35:13" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:35:14">http://www.motorcyclenews.com/MCN/bikereviews/searchresults/Bike-Reviews/BMW/BMW-C-2000-2002/</link><title>BMW C1 (2000-2002) Motorbike Review | MCN</title><description>BMW C1 125: Base model with 125cc engine. BMW C1 200: Base model with 176 cc engine producing 18bhp. BMW C1 125 Family Friend: extra luggage attachment kit and large ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:36:01">http://www.motorcycle.com/manufacturer/bmw/bmw-c-1-cityscooter-13940.html</link><title>BMW C 1 CityScooter - Motorcycle.com</title><description>BMW C 1 CityScooter, Motorcycle.com review, photos and videos of the 1999 BMW Scooter.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:39:50">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BMW_C1</link><title>BMW C1 \- Wikipedia</title><description>BMW's intention with the C1 was to appeal to car drivers in crowded city streets. However, poor C1 sales in the United Kingdom may in part be attributable to the British government's refusal of BMW's request to change helmet regulations for C1 riders.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:42:04">http://www.bikepics.com/bmw/c1-125/01/pics.asp</link><title>BikePics - 2001 BMW C1 125 Home Page on BikePics.Com</title><description>15 Photos were returned. BikePics 2001 BMW C1 125 Home Page. Featuring Photos, movies, specifications, links and reviews of BMW C1 125 Motorcycles, ATV's, Scooters, Snowmobiles and Personal Watercraft.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:43:41">http://www.autoblog.com/photos/bmw-i3-spy-shots-2/</link><title>BMW i3 Spy Shots Photo Gallery - Autoblog</title><description>BMW i3 Spy Shots Photos. Choose an Automaker. Shop For a vehicle. If } {if } {else} {/if} {else} {/if. National Show Coverage.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:45:35">http://bikez.com/motorcycles/bmw_c1_2001.php</link><title>2001 BMW C1 specifications and pictures</title><description>Engine and transmission. Single cylinder, four-stroke. Chassis, suspension, brakes and wheels. Physical measures and capacities. Parts and accessories Check out parts and accessories from our other partners.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:46:21">http://www.bmwblog.com/tag/bmw-c1-e/</link><title>BMW C1-E</title><description>BMW C1-E: Concept for a higher level of safety in the city. Interesting October 6th, 2009 by Horatiu Boeriu. This is what a safe, environment-friendly and highly practical single track vehicle for city traffic could look like in the future BMW Motorrad developed the. BMW 4 Series Gran Coupe.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:50:20">http://bmwmcmag.com/galleries/c1-e/</link><title>BMW C1-E (2009) - BMW Motorcycle Magazine</title><description>BMW resurrects the C1 scooter with a roof (produced from 1999-2003) but removes the single-cylinder engine in favor of electric motors to create the C1-E. This concept, which is not scheduled to go into production, was created as part of the European Safer Urban Motorcycling (eSUM) project.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:53:01">http://www.gizmag.com/bmw-c1-e-concept-scooter/13385/picture/105370/</link><title>E is for electric - The BMW C1-E concept scooter - Image 1 of 13</title><description>BMW's C1-E scooter is designed for urban transport. BMW has brought back the C1 as an electric-powered concept scooter called the C1-E. The BMW C1-E concept scooter. Read Gizmag's latest product comparisons. Other Images from this Gallery.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7042-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7042_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:54:41">http://ultimatemotorcycling.com/BMW_C1-E_Concept/</link><title>BMW C1-E Scooter - Electric Concept - Ultimate MotorCycling</title><description>The safety features of the C1-E have been taken from the former BMW C1 and further enhanced BMW's avant-garde two-wheeler is regarded as a milestone in safety on two wheels. It is the only motorised single-track vehicle to be exempt from mandatory helmet wearing in almost all European countries.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>