<search_results><query id="7054">yarra valley sightseeing</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:22:24" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:22:25">http://www.visitvictoria.com/Regions/Yarra-Valley-and-Dandenong-Ranges/Activities-and-attractions/Nature-and-wildlife/Yarra-Valley-Scenic-attractions</link><title>Scenic attractions in the Yarra Valley, Yarra Valley and ...</title><description>Float high above the Yarra Valley in a hot air balloon for unprecedented views of rolling hills strung with vines, lush greenery and pastures.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:24">http://www.visitvictoria.com/</link><title>Melbourne, Victoria, Australia - visitvictoria.com The official travel and accommodation site for Melbourne, Victoria, Australia</title><description>Yarra Valley &amp; Dandenong Ranges. Disappear from city bustle in the Dandenong Ranges, and indulge away in the Yarra Valley. Bulong Estate, Yarra Valley, Victoria, Australia. Kong in the city. Welcome, skip to the content.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:28:48">http://www.visityarravalley.com.au/</link><title>Yarra Valley Tourism Association</title><description>Welcome to the Yarra Valley! Book your accommodation and tours online, or browse all the fabulous things you can see and do while in the Yarra Valley &#8211; wineries and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:32:30">http://www.australia.com/traveller-testimonials-more-in.aspx</link><title>Traveller Testimonials - Great Stories About Australia</title><description>Sydney was a super mix of Adventure, Sightseeing, night life, food and fashion, while Melbourne was beautiful fauna, wildlife and culture. The Yarra valley was a heady experience in many ways. Yarra flows through the city, embellishing it with a scenic view. I loved my trip to Yarra Valley.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:21">http://www.viator.com/Melbourne-attractions/Yarra-Valley/d384-a387</link><title>Yarra Valley \- Melbourne Attractions - Viator.com</title><description>Spend a day exploring the Yarra Valley's wineries and breweries in style -- chauffeur-driven in a unique classic Chevrolet convertible. Viator.com: Book things to do, sightseeing tours, activities and attractions in more than 70 countries worldwide. Melbourne, Australia Duration: 7 hours (approx.).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:36:45">http://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g255098-d273941-Reviews-Yarra_Valley-Victoria.html</link><title>Yarra Valley \- Victoria - Reviews of Yarra Valley \- TripAdvisor</title><description>Valleys, Nature/ Wildlife Areas. Wine tasting, Dining, Antiquing, Shopping, City walk sightseeing. A wine region about an hour-and-a-quarter's drive from Melbourne. 28 reviews from our community. 7 attraction reviews.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:39:44">http://www.infohub.com/vacation-packages-cb/20637.html</link><title>CONVERTIBLE WINERY TOUR YARRA VALLEY (Price per car) - wine Tasting - Winery - Sightseeing</title><description>After lunch we travel to Sticks Winery one of Yarra Valleys most progressive unique winery with award winning wines that are sold both nationally and in key markets around the world.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:43:18">http://www.viator.com/Melbourne-attractions/Yarra-Valley-tours-tickets/d384-a387</link><title>Yarra Valley \- Tours &amp; Tickets | Viator</title><description>Yarra Valley \- Melbourne: Check out 11 Viator tours and tickets for this attraction</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:46:29">http://www.yarravalleypoint.com.au/</link><title>Yarra Valley Accommodation - Yarra Valley Attractions, Victoria</title><description>Yarra Valley attractions are endless as there are plenty of things to see, do and explore in and around this region. Accommodation ranges from a wide array of fully ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7054-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7054_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:50:10">http://www.yarravalleypoint.com.au/wineries/</link><title>Yarra Valley Wineries &amp; Restaurants Map - Yarra Valley Accommodation, Melbourne</title><description>Escape in to the stunning Yarra Valleys and enjoy your stay within a cosy and luxurious unit at the winery. Enjoy a hot air balloon ride over the lush wineries and have an ultimate sightseeing experience while holidaying in the Yarra Valley.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>