<search_results><query id="7069">Eames chair</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:27:38" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:27:39">http://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/lounge-seating/eames-lounge-chair-and-ottoman.html</link><title>Eames Lounge and Ottoman - Lounge Chair \- Herman Miller</title><description>The comfort built into the Eames lounge chair and ottoman helps explain its enduring popularity, compared to other chairs that are also considered icons of 20th century design. The foam cushions mimic the look and feel of the original but will not flatten or clump over time.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:29:25">http://www.dwr.com/product/eames-lounge-ottoman-vicenza.do</link><title>DWR \- Eames&#174; Lounge and Ottoman - Design Within Reach</title><description>Charles and Ray Eames had ideas about making a better world, one in which things were designed to bring greater pleasure to our lives. Their iconic Eames Lounge Chair ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:30:14">http://www.roomandboard.com/rnb/product/detail.do?productGroup=6861</link><title>Eames&#174; Molded Plastic Chairs with Chrome Wire Base - Chairs ...</title><description>Eames chair is a midcentury modern chair and mixes with modern dining room furniture.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:09">http://www.smartfurniture.com/products/Eames-Lounge-Chair.html</link><title>Herman Miller Eames Lounge Chair ES670 and ES671 - SmartFurniture.com</title><description>This is the Emperor of all lounge chairs. It's truly one of the most famous and well-respected chairs ever built, and now it can be yours through Smart Furniture and Herman Miller (Herman Miller secured the rights to sell Eames furniture, and there isn't a more fine or trustworthy furniture company out there).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:34:11">http://www.littlenest.com/childrens-kids-eames-lcw-chair.php</link><title>Eames LCW Chair \- Kids Replica - Little Nest USA</title><description>What could be more beautiful than scaled down mid century classic chairs suitable for children. House and Garden Australia. The Woody chair by Little Nest is a little plywood chair based on the popular LCW chair which was originally designed by Ray and Charles Eames. 30 day returns.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:35:40">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eames_Lounge_Chair</link><title>Eames Lounge Chair \- Wikipedia</title><description>This differentiates the newer chairs from the "original" (vintage) chairs which used Brazilian rosewood veneers and were constructed of five layers of plywood. This is part of the chair's unusual design, as well as its weakest link.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:37:21">http://www.wayfair.com/Herman-Miller-%C2%AE-Eames-Chair-and-Ottoman-ES67071-HML1154.html</link><title>Herman Miller &#174; Eames Chair and Ottoman - Wayfair</title><description>Its heritage goes back to the molded plywood chairs pioneered by the Eameses in the 1940s, and It's part of the permanent collection of New York's Museum of Modern Art. Living Room Chairs. We bought two of these beautiful chairs in the parchment leather and they are beautiful, we love them.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:39:42">http://hivemodern.com/pages/product1349/vitra-eames-saarinen-organic-chair</link><title>Eames &amp; Saarinen Organic Chair \- hivemodern.com</title><description>Eames &amp; saarinen organic chair. Modern design for the home. Design Charles Eames &amp; Eero Saarinen, 1940 Laminate seat shell, beech legs, upholstery Made in Germany by Vitra.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:40:16">http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/Eames%20chair</link><title>Eames chair \- Define Eames chair at Dictionary.com</title><description>Also called LCM chair. A side chair designed by Charles Eames in 1946, having a slender tubular steel frame with a seat and back of molded plywood panels. Also called Eames lounge chair.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7069-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7069_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:44:09">http://www.eq3.com/ca/en/p25852/eames-lounge-chair-and-ottoman</link><title>Herman Miller - Herman Miller Eames Lounge Chair and Ottoman - 3350-600-13</title><description>Herman Miller Eames Lounge Chair and Ottoman. Canada CAD English. Ottoman/Repose-pieds 26"w x 21.5"d x 17.25h. Designed by Charles and Ray Eames when introduced in 1956 the Eames Lounge Chair and Ottoman was one of a kind.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>