<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:50:23" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:50:24">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/01/19/ahmed-dogan-assassination-attempt-photo-crazed-gunman_n_2511483.html</link><title>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt - Gunman Aims Gun At Bulgarian Politician's Head (PHOTO, VIDEO)</title><description>A gunman reportedly attempted to assassinate the leader of Bulgaria's Turkish ethnic party during a televised conference on Saturday.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:52:29">http://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/videos/assassination-attempt-ahmed-dogan-survives/</link><title>Assassination Attempt - Ahmed Dogan Survives - The Hollywood Gossip</title><description>Ahmed Dogan Survives. An assassination attempt on Ahmed Dogan is caught live on video in Bulgaria, January 2013.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:54:14">http://metro.co.uk/2013/01/19/ahmed-dogan-bulgarian-politician-escapes-assassination-attempt-after-gun-jams-3358244/</link><title>Ahmed Dogan assassination attempt caught on video - Metro News</title><description>More like this. Bulgarian politician escapes 'assassination attempt' after gun jams. This site uses cookies. By continuing, your consent is assumed. A gun is held to Ahmed Dogan's head (Picture: AFP).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:56:09">http://themellowjihadi.com/tag/ahmed-dogan-assassination/</link><title>Ahmed Dogan Assassination</title><description>Blogging from the brig. Ahmed Dogan, of the Movement for Rights and Freedoms (MRF), escaped an assassination attempt. A gunman jumped on stage and point-blank aimed at him.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:59:40">http://www.ksdk.com/news/article/358159/28/Ahmed-Dogan-attempted-assassination-caught-on-camera</link><title>Ahmed Dogan attempted assassination caught on camera - ksdk.com</title><description>Bulgarian police detained a man after he pointed a gas pistol at an ethnic Turkish party leader as he was delivering a speech at a party caucus in the capital Saturday. No shots were fired.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:00:50">http://www.theblackvault.com/phpBB3/ahmed-dogan-assassination-attempt-gun-jams-t8483.html</link><title>The Black Vault Message Forums &#8226; View topic - Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt - Gun Jams</title><description>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt. The Black Vault Message Forums. General Discussion Topics. If it were raining hookers, I'd get hit by a fag. Discover the Truth.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:02:27">http://globalgrind.com/2013/01/19/bulgarian-politician-dodges-assassination-ahmed-dogan-gun-point-gas-footage-video/</link><title>Bulgarian Politician, Ahmed Dogan Dodges Assassination (VIDEO) - Global Grind</title><description>Bulgarian Politician Dodges Assassination In Jaw Dropping Footage. Wednesday, April 16. Ahmed Dogan, the leader of the Movement for Rights and Freedoms has dodged a serious attack.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:06:04">http://1079ishot.com/ahmed-dogan-assassination-attempt-fail-video/</link><title>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt Fail - HOT 107.9 - VIDEO</title><description>Justin Timberlake and N'Sync To Reunite At Upcoming MTV VMAs Show. Watch These Animals Having Sneezing Fits &#8212; Daily Distraction. Lee Thompson Young Never Left A Suicide Note. Another Kid Trapped In A Prize Claw Machine. Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt Fail.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-09"><link>http://www.whatreallyhappened.com/de/content/assassination-attempt-bulgarian-opposition-leader-ahmed-dogan</link><title>What Really Happened \- Assassination Attempt on Bulgarian Opposition Leader Ahmed Dogan \- WHAT REALLY HAPPENED</title><description>Search this site.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7135-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7135_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:11:57">http://www.fordforums.com/f126/ahmed-dogan-assassination-attempt-181502/</link><title>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt. - Ford Forums - Mustang Forum, Ford Trucks, Ford Focus and Ford Cars</title><description>The Pub For General Discussion. FordForums.com is the premier Ford Forum on the internet. Registered Users do not see the above ads. The failed assasin doesn't half get the s*** kicked out of him. Watch the old guy at the end coming in to have his tuppence worth.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>