<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:41:35" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:41:37">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed?term=breast%20cancer%20review</link><title>breast cancer review \- PubMed Result - National Center for ...</title><description>1: Jagsi R. Postmastectomy Radiation Therapy: An Overview for the Practicing Surgeon. ISRN Surg. 2013 Sep 11;2013:212979. Review. PubMed PMID: 24109522.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:44:18">http://cancer.northwestern.edu/breastreview/index.cfm</link><title>Breast Cancer Review: Updates from the 2013 San Antonio ...</title><description>On Friday, February 14, 2014, the Lurie Cancer Center and Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine will host the Breast Cancer Review: Updates from the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:45:23">http://www.cancernetwork.com/breast-cancer</link><title>Breast Cancer | Cancer Network - Oncology and Hematology News ...</title><description>Authoritative updates on the treatment of breast cancer for clinicians, including news on guidelines, mammography and screening, and comprehensive reviews on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:46:50">http://www.cancercenter.com/breast-cancer/</link><title>Breast Cancer: Integrative Treatment Program | CTCA</title><description>At CTCA, we fight breast cancer with advanced medical treatments that help patients experience a better quality of life. Learn more about our breast cancer treatment ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:47:29">http://www.breastcancerfund.org/</link><title>Breast Cancer Fund - Prevention Starts Here</title><description>A comprehensive review of the scientific evidence linking fetal BPA exposure to later-life health problems. Act for Change. Get cancer-causing chemicals out of products now. Wal-Mart asks suppliers to stop using harmful chemicals (San Jose Mercury News, 2/28/14).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:48:34">http://www.cancer.gov/cancertopics/factsheet/Risk/BRCA</link><title>Comprehensive Cancer Information \- BRCA1 and BRCA2 - Cancer Risk and Genetic Testing Fact Sheet - National Cancer Institute</title><description>Together, BRCA1 and BRCA 2 mutations account for about 20 to 25 percent of hereditary breast cancers (1) and about 5 to 10 percent of all breast cancers (2). Breast cancers associated with BRCA1 and BRCA2 mutations tend to develop at younger ages than sporadic breast cancers.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:49:37">http://www.cdc.gov/cancer/breast/statistics/age.htm</link><title>CDC - Breast Cancer Risk by Age</title><description>Howlader N, Noone AM, Krapcho M, Garshell J, Neyman N, Altekruse SF, Kosary CL, Yu M, Ruhl J, Tatalovich Z, Cho H, Mariotto A, Lewis DR, Chen HS, Feuer EJ, Cronin KA (eds) SEER Cancer Statistics Review, 1975&#8211;2010, National Cancer Institute.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:50:46">http://www.cancerandcareers.org/en</link><title>Cancer and Careers - The Top Resource for People Working With Cancer</title><description>Resume Review Service. Meet Tara, a breast cancer survivor trying to re-enter the workforce. Working With Cancer Is Hard. You can help make it easier by providing a generous donation today. Weathering The Storms.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:51:14">http://www.onhealth.com/breast_cancer/article.htm</link><title>Breast Cancer Symptoms, Signs, Stages, Prevention, Detection, Facts, Treatment - OnHealth</title><description>What follows is a review of information on breast cancer intended to aid patients and their families in their navigation through the vast ocean of breast cancer information and issues. Breast cancer is diagnosed with physician and self-examination of the breasts, mammography, ultrasound testing, and biopsy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:54:03">http://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/lobular-carcinoma-invasive-and-in-situ</link><title>Breast Cancer Health Center - Lobular Carcinoma (Invasive and In Situ)</title><description>While the majority of breast cancers start in the ducts of the breasts, some breast cancers begin in the lobules. The majority of breast cancers start in the ducts of the breasts. The majority of these later cancers begin in the milk ducts, rather than the lobules and both breasts may be involved.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>