<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:10:21" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:10:23">http://www.dhs.gov/photo/vice-president-biden-departing-his-residence</link><title>Vice President Biden Departing His Residence \- Homeland Security</title><description>Official website of the Department of Homeland Security. Search using USASearch. VPOTUS departs his home at the US Naval Observatory via motorcade. VPOTUS in front of his home. Find more photos.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:12:34">http://zeenews.india.com/news/world/grant-permanent-residence-to-foreigners-in-myanmar-vice-president_826672.html</link><title>Grant permanent residence to foreigners in Myanmar - Vice president</title><description>Thursday, February 13, 2014. News from e-generator.com. Most Popular in News. Myanmar Vice President U Nyan Tun has called for granting permanent residence (PR) to foreigners who would like to help the country, reported Xinhua citing the country`s official daily Saturday.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:13:36">http://www.whitehouse.gov/about/vp-residence</link><title>The Vice President's Residence &amp; Office - The White House</title><description>Historically, Vice Presidents and their families lived in their own homes, but the cost of securing these private residences grew substantially over the years. Several Presidents have chosen to use this desk, including Presidents Taft, Wilson, Harding, Coolidge, Hoover, and Eisenhower.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:14:32">http://gawker.com/5138111/cheneys-veil-lifted-on-vice-presidents-residence</link><title>Cheney's Veil Lifted on Vice President's Residence</title><description>Cheney's Veil Lifted on Vice President's Residence. In other words, the vice president's house was revealed on Google the same week Cheney moved out and Joe Biden moved in. Include only posts that have. Today's gossip is tomorrow's news. Recommended by Owen Thomas.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:16:48">http://www.sify.com/news/Grant-permanent-residence-to-foreigners-in-Myanmar-Vice-president-news-International-ncdbPcddiab.html</link><title>Sify.com \- Grant permanent residence to foreigners in Myanmar - Vice president</title><description>Follow us on. Sify.com / News / International / Grant permanent residence to foreigners in Myanmar: Vice president.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:19:07">http://news.yahoo.com/photos/vice-president-s-residence-photo-1349908290.html?format=embed</link><title>Vice President's residence \- View photo - Yahoo News</title><description>View the photo Vice President's residence on Yahoo News. Vice President Joe Biden speaks at a reception commemorating the 15th anniversary of the passage of the Violence against Women Act, at the Naval Observatory, Tuesday, September 29, 2009. Official White House Photo by David Lienemann less.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:21:03">http://oregonstate.edu/dept/rha/executive-officers/vice-president/</link><title>Vice President \- OSU Residence Hall Association</title><description>OSU Residence Hall Association. All office hours are held between 8 am and 5 pm, thus am/pm are left off times below. I may not always be available during posted times, if I have other meetings to attend. I may leave about 10 minutes early in order to make it to class on time.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:21:44">http://www.upi.com/News_Photos/view/upi/491223d65193552eb05013b682103ac1/</link><title>US Vice President Joe Biden walks with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in his residence in ...</title><description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and US Vice President Joe Biden walk the prime minister's residence in Jerusalem, March 9, 2010 UPI/Debbie Hill. New York Fashion Week 2013. Celebrity families of 2013. Government shutdown in photos. Notable deaths of 2013.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:23:46">http://www.newstrackindia.com/newsdetails/2013/02/02/306--Grant-permanent-residence-to-foreigners-in-Myanmar-Vice-president-.html</link><title>Grant permanent residence to foreigners in Myanmar - Vice president</title><description>Last 1 Month Last 6 Months All time. Yangon, Feb 2 (IANS) Myanmar Vice President U Nyan Tun has called for granting permanent residence (PR) to foreigners who would like to help the country, reported Xinhua citing the country's official daily Saturday.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>