<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:23:03" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:23:05">http://www.webmd.com/pain-management/pain-management-spinal-cord-injury-medref</link><title>Spinal Cord Injuries Causes and Types - WebMD</title><description>Spinal cord damage results in a loss of function, such as mobility or feeling. In most people who have spinal cord injury, the spinal cord is intact.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:25:32">http://www.ninds.nih.gov/disorders/sci/sci.htm</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information Page - National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke (NINDS)</title><description>A spinal cord injury usually begins with a sudden, traumatic blow to the spine that fractures or dislocates vertebrae. Most injuries to the spinal cord don't completely sever it. Advances in research are giving doctors and patients hope that repairing injured spinal cords is a reachable goal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:27:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=84877</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information on MedicineNet.com</title><description>A spinal cord injury usually begins with a sudden, traumatic blow to the spine that fractures or dislocates vertebrae. Most injuries to the spinal cord don't completely sever it. The damage begins at the moment of injury when displaced bone fragments, disc material, or ligaments bruise or tear into spinal cord tissue.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:29:14">http://health.usnews.com/health-news/news/articles/2013/11/27/oxygen-treatment-may-help-some-with-spinal-cord-injuries-study</link><title>Oxygen Treatment May Help Some With Spinal Cord Injuries - US News and World Report - Study</title><description>They may not function as they used to, but they are not completely severed. Because some connections remain, someone with an incomplete spinal injury may still be able to walk, but not in the same way they could before the injury.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:32:03">http://www.popsci.com/science/article/2013-06/regrowing-rats-severed-spinal-cords</link><title>Scientists Regrow Severed Spinal Cords In Rats - Popular Science</title><description>"It's clear that some primitive functions may be able to come back. We've shown for the very first time that we can promote long-distance regeneration in the adult spinal cord, across a complete spinal cord lesion. It's a step in the right direction," project director Jerry Silver explained.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:34:46">http://www.healthboards.com/spinal-cord-disorders/1711.html</link><title>Failed Spinal Fusion - HealthBoards Message Boards</title><description>I can barely lift my right leg and have sever pain evrytime I cough or sneeze. Has anyone had similiar results from a fusion. Is it time I seek the advice of a second opinion. I cannot accept that this is the quality of life that I have left. I am a 41 year old female with teenagers to raise.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:36:55">http://deadspin.com/5872842/high-school-hockey-player-suffers-severed-spinal-cord-after-accidental-check?tag=horrific-injuries</link><title>High-School Hockey Player Suffers Severed Spinal Cord After Accidental Check</title><description>"The accidental check from behind left Jablonski motionless on the ice at the St Louis Park Rec Center. Doctors initially thought he suffered a bruised spinal cord and two broken vertebrae, but Monday they said his spinal cord is actually severed. They don't know if Jack will walk again".</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:37:51">http://www.bioworld.com/content/gene-therapy-spinal-cord-injury-regrows-severed-axons-transgenic-mice</link><title>Gene Therapy For Spinal Cord Injury Regrows Severed Axons In Transgenic Mice - BioWorld</title><description>Jump to Navigation. Login to Your Account. Thursday, January 30, 1997. To continue reading subscribe now to BioWorld Today. Learn More about BioWorld Today.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:40:02">http://jama.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=305050</link><title>Journal of the American Medical Association \- JAMA Network - JAMA - TREATMENT OF PARAPLEGIA RESULTING FROM TRAUMA TO THE SPINAL CORD</title><description>Rotation or flexion of the spine should be studiously avoided or the spinal cord may be severed. The deformity of the spine should be promptly reduced by traction or hyperextension or both. The patient must be turned every two hours at least. Proper care of the bladder includes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:40:38">http://www.womenshealth.gov/news/headlines/665274.cfm</link><title>Re-Routing Spinal Cord Signals Restores Movement in Paralyzed Rats (5/31/2012) - womenshealth.gov</title><description>In the new research, begun five years ago at the University of Zurich in Switzerland, rats with severed spinal cords were injected with chemicals known as monoamine agonists that replace the neurotransmitters dopamine, adrenaline and serotonin, which are released from the brains of healthy individuals to help coordinat...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>