<search_results><query id="7200">uss stennis</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:16:08" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:16:09">http://www.dvidshub.net/news/99607/uss-john-stennis</link><title>DVIDS - News - USS John Stennis \- DVIDS - Defense Video ...</title><description>USS JOHN C. STENNIS \- Supply Department&#8217;s food service division (S-2) aboard the Nimitz-class aircraft carrier USS John C. Stennis (CVN 74) gave the crew ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:17:38">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_John_C._Stennis_(CVN-74)</link><title>USS John C. Stennis (CVN-74) - Wikipedia</title><description>Stennis (CVN 74) is the seventh Nimitz -class nuclear-powered supercarrier in the United States Navy, named for Senator John C Stennis of Mississippi. She was commissioned on 9 December 1995. Her home port is Bremerton, Washington. Mission and capabilities. International radio call sign of USS John C.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:19:01">http://www.clker.com/clipart-uss-stennis-hornet-launch.html</link><title>Uss Stennis \- Hornet Launch clip art - vector clip art online, royalty free &amp; public domain - Download</title><description>Hornet Launch clip art. Navy Collectionsince Friday, 30-Apr-10 15:05:54 PDT. Related clip arts and images. Searches that led to this page. Searches to clip arts on this page.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:20:28">http://www.defense.gov/News/NewsArticle.aspx?ID=32600</link><title>Defense.gov News Article - USS John C. Stennis Now Operating in Persian Gulf</title><description>American Forces Press Service. Secretary of Defense. Deputy Secretary of Defense. USS John C Stennis Now Operating in Persian Gulf. WASHINGTON, March 27, 2007 &#8211; The aircraft carrier USS John C Stennis entered the Persian Gulf today escorted by the guided-missile cruiser USS Antietam.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:21:59">http://www.gunslot.com/pictures/uss-stennis-rich-passage-bainbridge-island</link><title>The USS Stennis in Rich Passage of Bainbridge Island - Guns Lot</title><description>More From Schuyler. The USS Stennis in Rich Passage of Bainbridge Island. Prom dresses &amp; 'ac. Prom dresses &amp; 'accessories'.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-06"><link>http://kitsapsun.com/videos/detail/uss-stennis-leaves-bremerton</link><title>Kitsap, WA - Kitsap Sun - Videos - USS Stennis Leaves Bremerton</title><description>USS Stennis Leaves Bremerton. The aircraft carrier left Naval Base Kitsap. The aircraft carrier left Naval Base Kitsap at about 7 am today for a long deployment to the Western Pacific. The state of Kitsap's public salaries. Who makes the most and how municipal workers' compensation fares.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:27:00">http://www.zazzle.com/uss+stennis+gifts</link><title>Uss Stennis T-Shirts, Uss Stennis Gifts, Art, Posters, and more</title><description>Events &amp; Occasions. Displaying 1 - 60 of 332. Select a value. Not for me. Add to wishlist.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:28:08">http://www.csmonitor.com/tags/topic/USS+John+C.+Stennis</link><title>Topic - USS John C. Stennis \- CSMonitor.com</title><description>Helicopter mid-air crash kills 7 Marines in Calif desert. The aircraft collided in a remote portion of the Yuma Training Range Complex on the California side of the Chocolate Mountains very close to the Arizona border, Dooley said. The exact location hasn't been confirmed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:29:09">http://news.yahoo.com/video/uss-stennis-strike-group-return-142800306.html</link><title>USS Stennis Strike Group to return to San Diego - Watch the video - Yahoo News</title><description>Watch the video USS Stennis Strike Group to return to San Diego on Yahoo News.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7200-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7200_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:30:32">http://www.cafepress.com/+uss-stennis+baby-bodysuits</link><title>Uss Stennis Baby Bodysuits - Uss Stennis Infant Bodysuits - CafePress</title><description>Browse By Department. Best Sellers in. Sell on CafePress. Transform your creativity into beautiful products, sell them on CafePress and make money. It's easy and fun.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>