<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:09:49" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:09:50">http://earthquake.usgs.gov/</link><title>Earthquake Hazards Program - Latest Earthquakes</title><description>Significant Earthquakes Past 30 Days. We monitor and report earthquakes, assess earthquake impacts and hazards, and research the causes and effects of earthquake. View recent events or search for past earthquakes. Our scientists study earthquakes around the world.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:11:42">http://www.shakeout.org/</link><title>Select Your ShakeOut Region - ShakeOut</title><description>Great ShakeOut Earthquake Drills are an annual opportunity for people in homes, schools, and organizations to practice what to do during earthquakes, and to improve preparedness.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:14:18">http://data.scec.org/recent/index.html</link><title>Recent Earthquakes in California and Nevada - Index Map</title><description>Maps are updated within 1-5 minutes of an earthquake or once an hour. (Smaller earthquakes in southern California are added after human processing,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:16:00">http://phys.org/tags/earthquake/</link><title>Phys.org - earthquake</title><description>News tagged with earthquake. Science and technology news stories tagged with keyword: earthquake. All science news about earthquake.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:17:03">http://www.nehrp.gov/</link><title>A research and implementation partnership - NEHRP - National Earthquake Hazards Reduction Program</title><description>Latest Earthquakes in the World. Grants &amp; Contracts. National Earthquake Hazards Reduction Program. When (Physical + Numerical = Testable System). Finding what you need.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:18:06">http://www.earthquakeauthority.com/CEAindex.aspx</link><title>California Earthquake Authority (CEA)</title><description>Earthquakes strike without warning. How to file a claim. Choose CEA insurance to get peace-of-mind from knowing you can afford to repair, rebuild, or replace your covered property that may be damaged by the next catastrophic earthquake.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:19:10">http://nees.org/</link><title>NEEShub - Network for Earthquake Engineering Simulation</title><description>NEES@Texas Stokoe on Liquefaction Dr Kenneth Stokoe discusses how earthquakes can cause certain soils to liquefy in this short Hacking the Planet video. News and Announcements. December 2013 Newsletter can be found here. November 2013 Newsletter NEES/E-Defense page. Find us on Facebook.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:19:45">http://earthquake-report.com/</link><title>Earthquake Report</title><description>Major) Earthquakes list November 1, 2012 &#8211; Earthquake below Java (Indonesia. (Complete) Earthquakes list October 31, 2012 &#8211; Moderate earthquake shakes the greater Manila area, Philippines. (Complete) Earthquakes list November 1, 2012. (Complete) Earthquakes list October 30, 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:21:30">http://www.ceri.memphis.edu/</link><title>Center for Earthquake Research and Information</title><description>Recent Earthquakes in the Central and Eastern US. Click on the map to go to our awesome new interactive map that shows recent Central US earthquakes. Recent Earthquakes in the Central and Eastern US Map. Public Forum on Lessons Learned from the 2009 Christchurch New Zealand Earthquake, October 17, 2013.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:23:45">http://peer.berkeley.edu/</link><title>Pacific Earthquake Engineering Research Center - Upcoming Events - PEER - More</title><description>November 7-15, 2013. EERI Seminars on PEER NGA-West2 Project. Long Beach, California. And San Francisco, California. December 11-13, 2013.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>