<search_results><query id="7236">lomustine</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:35:05" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:35:07">http://www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/druginfo/meds/a682207.html</link><title>Lomustine : MedlinePlus Drug Information - National Library ...</title><description>Lomustine comes as a capsule to take by mouth. It is usually taken once every 6 weeks on an empty stomach. Your full dose may contain two or more different ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:35:42">http://www.drugs.com/pro/lomustine.html</link><title>Lomustine Official FDA information, side effects and uses.</title><description>Accurate, FDA approved Lomustine information for healthcare professionals and patients - brought to you by Drugs.com.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:36:26">http://www.cancer.org/treatment/treatmentsandsideeffects/guidetocancerdrugs/lomustine</link><title>Lomustine \- American Cancer Society</title><description>Lomustine (low-mus-teen) Trade/other name(s): CCNU, CeeNU. Why would this drug be used? Lomustine is used to treat brain cancer, Hodgkin disease, and other conditions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:37:43">http://www.everydayhealth.com/drugs/lomustine</link><title>Lomustine \- Side Effects, Dosage, Interactions - Drugs ...</title><description>Lomustine \- Lomustine is a cancer medication that interferes with the growth of cancer cells and slows their spread in the body. - Lomustine can weaken your immune ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:38:42">http://www.rxlist.com/ceenu-drug.htm</link><title>CeeNU (Lomustine Capsules) Drug Information: Description ...</title><description>Learn about the prescription medication CeeNU (Lomustine Capsules), drug uses, dosage, side effects, drug interactions, warnings, reviews and patient labeling.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:39:20">http://www.cancer.gov/cancertopics/druginfo/lomustine</link><title>Lomustine \- National Cancer Institute</title><description>Cancer Drug Information. In English En espa&#241;ol. This page contains brief information about lomustine and a collection of links to more information about the use of this drug, research results, and ongoing clinical trials. Use in Cancer. Lomustine is approved to be used alone or with other drugs to treat.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:39:47">http://dailymed.nlm.nih.gov/dailymed/archives/fdaDrugInfo.cfm?archiveid=11807</link><title>CeeNU &#174; (lomustine)Capsules - Daily Med</title><description>WARNINGS. CeeNU (lomustine) should be administered under the supervision of a qualified physician experienced in the use of cancer chemotherapeutic agents.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:40:39">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmedhealth/PMHT0010977/</link><title>Lomustine (By mouth) - National Library of Medicine - PubMed Health</title><description>The World's Largest Medical Library. We are sorry, but NCBI web applications do not support your browser and may not function properly. Treats Hodgkin's disease, brain tumors, and other kinds of cancers, often in combination with other medicines. Also called CCNU. This medicine is an alkylating agent.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:41:13">http://www.cincinnatichildrens.org/health/l/lomustine/</link><title>Lomustine</title><description>Possible Side Effects of Medication. Call Your Child's Doctor If. If Your Child Misses a Dose. Find Another Condition or Treatment. Lomustine (CCNU) is a medicine used to treat certain types of cancer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7236-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7236_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:42:24">http://www.webmd.com/drugs/drug-8801-lomustine+oral.aspx</link><title>lomustine oral - Uses, Side Effects, Interactions, Pictures, Warnings &amp; Dosing - WebMD</title><description>Drugs &amp; Medications - lomustine oral. Enter Search Keywords. Use the arrow keys to navigate suggestions. Health concern on your mind. See what your medical symptoms could mean, and learn about possible conditions.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>