<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:22:50" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:22:51">http://www.tomcruise.com/</link><title>Official Tom Cruise: Edge Of Tomorrow, Movies, Bio, News ...</title><description>OFFICIAL TOM CRUISE SITE: View the latest EDGE OF TOMORROW trailer! Watch career movie trailers, videos, and retrospective. Read the Tom Cruise biography or blog for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:23:16">http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000129/</link><title>Tom Cruise \- IMDb</title><description>If you had told 14 year old Franciscan seminary student Thomas Cruise Mapother IV that one day in the not too distant future he would be considered one of the top 100 movie stars of all time, he would have probably grinned and told you that his ambition was to become a priest. Nonetheless, this sensitive See full bio.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:23:45">http://www.people.com/people/tom_cruise</link><title>Tom Cruise \- People.com</title><description>See All Tom Cruise Photos. Get everything Tom Cruise straight from America's #1 celebrity brand, PEOPLE. The latest Tom Cruise news, a full collection of photos, fun facts and his complete bio all in one place.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:24:29">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Cruise</link><title>Tom Cruise \- Wikipedia</title><description>Cruise's surname originates from his great-grandfather, born Thomas Cruise O'Mara, who was renamed "Thomas Cruise Mapother". And the company has since co-produced several of Cruise's films, the first being Mission: Impossible in 1996 which was also Cruise's first project as a producer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:25:21">http://uk.eonline.com/photos/5659/tom-cruise-post-split/204298</link><title>Back to Work from Tom Cruise Post-Split - E - Online</title><description>Tom Cruise Post-Split. Connor Cruise,Tom Cruise. Tom Cruise, Suri Cruise, Disneyland, Twitter. Tom Cruise, Suri Cruise, Disneyland. Almost two weeks after news broke of his divorce to Katie Holmes, Cruise gets to work on the set of his upcoming flick Oblivion in June Lake, Calif, on July 10.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:25:56">http://www.forbes.com/pictures/mfl45khmg/tom-cruise-4/</link><title>Tom Cruise \- In Photos - The Highest-Paid Actors - Forbes</title><description>75 million Recent news of Cruise's pending divorce is a blight on an otherwise stellar year for the star. The actor suffered a career setback five years ago when he married Katie Holmes thanks to his couch jumping antics, some embarrassing Scientology leaks and the relative failure of Mission: Impossible 3.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:26:23">http://vimeo.com/tag:Tom+Cruise</link><title>Videos about Tom Cruise on Vimeo</title><description>Videos tagged "Tom Cruise". Photo Tour Celebrity and me (OFFICIAL VIDEO).mp4. 1 day ago. Over the Fence and Far Away. Eye On Celebrity Episode 123.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:26:54">http://www.popsugar.com/Tom-Cruise</link><title>Tom Cruise Latest News, Photos, and Video - POPSUGAR Celebrity</title><description>Tom Cruise began his film career in the 1980s and has become known worldwide for his roles in blockbusters like Jerry Maguire and the Mission: Impossible series. Get Alerts about Tom Cruise. View 1478 photos of Tom Cruise. Tom Cruise is Literally Back in Action in Edge of Tomorrow. Tom Cruise Wasn't "My Great Love".</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:28:01">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/tom-cruise/</link><title>Tom Cruise \- Pictures, Videos, Breaking News</title><description>Tom Cruise's Defamation Lawsuit Ends In A Settlement. This Can't Seriously Be Tom Cruise's New Lady Love Can It. Why is Rob Reiner Yelling So Much In 'The Wolf Of Wall Street'. The First 'Edge Of Tomorrow' Trailer Is Here. Tom Cruise, John Travolta Attend Dedication Of 'Super Power' Scientology Building.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:28:35">http://variety.com/exec/tom-cruise/</link><title>Tom Cruise \- Variety</title><description>Tom Cruise's 'Yukikaze' Moving Ahead With Dan Mazeau (EXCLUSIVE). Warner Bros has released the first trailer for Tom Cruise's SciFi thriller "Edge of Tomorrow," six months before the film opens on June 6. The trailer highlights Cruise's character being stuck in a.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>