<search_results><query id="7417">dota 2 heroes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:34:50" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:34:51">http://www.ign.com/wikis/dota-2/Heroes</link><title>Heroes \- Dota 2 Wiki Guide - IGN - Video Games, Wikis, Cheats ...</title><description>There are currently 107 Heroes available in the Dota 2 lineup. Each of the 10 players in the game controls a hero in DotA 2. The selection of each player's hero ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:35:44">http://store.steampowered.com/app/570/</link><title>Dota 2 on Steam</title><description>Players pick from a pool of over a hundred heroes, forming two teams of five players. This means you could gain two or more items each time you open a treasure. Each unseals to reveal an entire hero set, which include the first sets made available for Lifestealer and Puck.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:36:27">http://www.gamespot.com/dota-2/</link><title>Dota 2 \- GameSpot</title><description>Balance updates also affect 80-odd heroes. Has your favourite cheeky strategy been nerfed. Steam in-home streaming beta invites going out now. Valve dispatches unspecified number of invitations to beta period for new streaming service. DDoS pair says they took Steam servers offline overnight.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:37:27">http://steamcommunity.com/workshop/browse?appid=570</link><title>Dota 2</title><description>Filter by Hero. Create or find the best new items. Create and submit new items (such as armor, weapons, clothing, Couriers, and more) for consideration to be incorporated into the actual game. Or help identify the best by rating up your favorites. Show items tagged with all of the selected terms.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:38:01">http://www.tumblr.com/tagged/dota-2-heroes</link><title>dota 2 heroes on Tumblr</title><description>Find and follow posts tagged #dota 2 heroes. Want to see more posts tagged #dota 2 heroes. Find and follow posts tagged dota 2 heroes on Tumblr.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:38:48">http://www.gamezone.com/games/company-of-heroes-2</link><title>Company of Heroes 2 \- Games - GameZone</title><description>Video game news, video game reviews, walkthroughs, video game mods, and game trailers. Company of Heroes 2 for PC. Gamezone News by Type. Gamezone News by Platform / Console. It is 1941 and the beginning of what will become the most brutal conflict of World War II.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:39:48">http://www.dota2.com/heroes/</link><title>Heroes \- Dota 2</title><description>Dota 2 official blog with store, heroes, items, workshop, and forums.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-08"><link>http://www.1up.com/do/gameOverview?cId=2008992</link><title>1UP.com \- City of Heroes for PC from 1UP</title><description>City of Heroes is a super-powered hero based massively multiplayer online role-playing game. Create your own hero by choosing your powers and designing your own costume. I believe it comes down to the game's core, witch is that YOU are a Super Hero.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:41:27">http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2011-08-18-newell-dota-2-wont-ship-until-2012</link><title>Newell - Dota 2 won't ship until 2012 News &#8226; News &#8226; PC &#8226; Eurogamer.net</title><description>"But then," Newell continued, "with a game like this, you just keep shipping. You add new heroes. You try out new game modes. You are constantly tweaking item and hero balance. It's very much an ongoing thing.".</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7417-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7417_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:42:30">http://www.moddb.com/mods/hon-2-dota/news</link><title>Mod DB - News - HoN 2 DotA Mod for Heroes of Newerth</title><description>HoN 2 DotA Mod for Heroes of Newerth. Hello guest register or. HoN 2 Dota is a mod for Heroes of Newerth featuring a grand total of 90+ DotA heroes, custom Multiplayer maps with TCP/IP LAN support and offline play against Ai Bots. May 11, 2012 3 comments. Version 2.7 of the HoN2DotA Mod has been released.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>