<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:16:38" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:16:40">http://www.eatingitalyfoodtours.com/2013/01/23/best-food-in-rome/</link><title>Top 5 must try foods in Rome \- Eating Italy Food Tours in Rome</title><description>5 must try foods in Rome, including pizza, fritti, pastas and local Italian food specialities&#8212;arguably some of the the best food in Rome.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:17:30">http://www.tripadvisor.com/ShowUserReviews-g60817-d1076159-r132976466-Franklin_Hotel-Rome_New_York.html</link><title>The best Italian food in Rome, NY. - Review of Franklin Hotel ...</title><description>Franklin Hotel: The best Italian food in Rome, NY. - See 44 traveler reviews, candid photos, and great deals for Rome, NY, at TripAdvisor.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:18:10">http://vimeo.com/47257051</link><title>Gluten-Free Italian Food in Rome, Italy on Vimeo</title><description>TheBlondeAbroad.com The best gluten-free food in Rome, Italy. Gluten-Free Italian Food in Rome, Italy. So good you would never know it was gluten-free. Loading more stuff. Hmm&#8230;it looks like things are taking a while to load.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:18:35">http://www.lonelyplanet.com/italy/rome-lazio/activities/food-drink/taste-italy-food-tour-chianti-umbria-rome</link><title>Lonely Planet \- Taste of Italy Food Tour to Chianti and Umbria from Rome in Rome, Italy \- Lonely Planet</title><description>Head out of Rome and off the beaten track to experience a different side of Italy in Tuscany and Umbria. Provided by Viator. 13 hours approx. You'll visit the lovely towns of Cortona and Montepulciano, and sample wine, cheeses, salami, olive oil and other local specialties.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:19:19">http://www.viator.com/Rome-tourism/Italian-Food-and-Wine-Tours/d511-t3926</link><title>Italian Food and Wine Tours - Rome Recommendations - Viator.com</title><description>Pasta, wine, cheese, salami, olive oil &#8211; these are the tastes of Italy. Florence, Italy Duration: 7 hours (approx.). Siena, Italy Duration: 8 hours (approx.). Find the best food spots in town on a 4-hour Rome Food Walking Tour. Rome, Italy Duration: 4 hours (approx.).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:19:47">http://www.istockphoto.com/stock-photo-24516077-restaurant-on-the-street-in-rome-italian-food.php</link><title>Restaurant on the Street in Rome \- Italian Food stock photo 24516077 - iStock</title><description>Typical alley in Rome, Italy: sign of a restaurant and tourists. And search more of the web's best library of royalty-free stock images from iStock. All other marks are the property of their respective owners. Restaurant on the Street in Rome: Italian Food Royalty Free Stock Photo. Download With Credits.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:20:30">http://www.nileguide.com/destination/rome/best/cuisine/italian-85</link><title>Italian Food Restaurants in Rome \- NileGuide</title><description>The Best of NileGuide. Your complete guide to Rome Italian Restaurants: Get local recommendations and reviews for Italian restaurants in Rome, Italy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:21:01">http://www.usatoday.com/experience/food-and-wine/rome/</link><title>Rome Food and Wine Guide - USA TODAY Travel</title><description>You can still dig into the world's best carbonara or cacio e pepe from ivy-clad osteria and knock back Peroni in a cobbled courtyard by night, but there is also a welcome breath of fresh air blowing through this storied culinary culture.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:22:07">http://www.foodnetwork.com/shows/everyday-italian/4-series/back-home-to-rome.html</link><title>Back Home to Rome \- Everyday Italian \- Food Network</title><description>Shop by Chef or Show. Shop by Food Network Store Department. Shop Brands, Gifts &amp; Specials. Inside Healthy Eating. Inside Holidays &amp; Parties.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:22:58">http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-2237663/Ashton-Kutcher-Mila-Kunis-treat-traditional-Italian-food-romantic-Rome.html</link><title>Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis treat themselves to traditional Italian food in romantic Rome \- Mail Online</title><description>More top stories. Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis treat themselves to traditional Italian food in romantic Rome. She is filming her latest movie in Rome but Mila Kunis has enjoyed a visit from her boyfriend Ashton Kutcher over the last few days.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>