<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:51" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:53">https://docs.python.org/2/howto/regex.html</link><title>Regular Expression HOWTO &#8212; Python v2.7.6 documentation</title><description>Abstract. This document is an introductory tutorial to using regular expressions in Python with the re module. It provides a gentler introduction than the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:08:54">http://www.tutorialspoint.com/python/python_reg_expressions.htm</link><title>Python Regular Expressions - Tutorials for QC, D Programming ...</title><description>Python Regular Expressions - Learning Python in simple and easy steps : A beginner's tutorial containing complete knowledge of Python Syntax Object Oriented Language ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:09:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2717856/any-good-and-gentle-python-regexp-tutorials-out-there</link><title>regex \- Any good and gentle Python Regexp tutorials out there ...</title><description>I read through the official Regular Expression HOWTO, but it wasn't gentle enough for this OP's tiny brain. Is there anything better/easier out there?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:10:12">https://www.python.org/</link><title>Python Programming Language \- Welcome to Python.org</title><description>The official home of the Python Programming Language. ... along with tutorials and ... Looking for work or have a Python related position that you're trying to hire ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:10:53">https://pypi.python.org/pypi/regex</link><title>regex 2014.04.10 : Python Package Index - PyPI - the Python ...</title><description>Introduction. This new regex implementation is intended eventually to replace Python's current re module implementation. For testing and comparison with the current ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:11:34">https://groups.google.com/forum/#!msg/comp.lang.python/m_tCf8-A5NQ/KrseNkNY7TIJ</link><title>Google Groups \- Re \- data attributes override method attributes - Google Groups</title><description>In the Python Tutorial, Section 9.4, it is said that &gt; &gt; "Data attributes override method attributes with the same name.". The tutorial is wrong here. That should be. "Instance attributes override class attributes with the same name.".</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:12:34">http://www.onlamp.com/pub/a/python/2002/07/11/recipes.html</link><title>Cooking with Python \- Seven Tasty Recipes for Programmers - O'Reilly Media</title><description>By Robin Parma, Alex Martelli, Scott David Daniels, Ben Wolfson, Nick Perkins, Anurag Uniya, Tim Keating, Rael Dornfest and Jeremy Hylton, authors of the Python Cookbook. Simple Tests Using Exceptions. Usually Python is straightforward, but there are a few unexpected exceptions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:13:09">http://www.reddit.com/r/Python/comments/11eqtd/from_guido_on_mailpythonorg_the_async_api_of_the/</link><title>Too Many Requests \- From Guido on mail.python.org - The async API of the future - Python</title><description>Just had another read down the thread, Greg Ewing posted a nice tutorial dealing with python's new yield from construct here. This doesn't cover the yield from construct which was introduced in 3.3, i'm still trying to find a good tutorial on that, maybe at pycon this year. 1 point 2 points 3 points 1 year ago.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-09"><link>http://pylonshq.com/</link><title>Pylons Project \- Home</title><description>The Pylons Project was founded by the people behind the Pylons web framework to develop web application framework technology in Python. The most important feature of this release is Python 3.2 compatibility.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:14:45">http://www.webwareforpython.org/</link><title>Webware for Python</title><description>Apache connector benchmark. Webware switches to Subversion. WSGI Webware renamed to WSGIKit. Website re-organization in progress. New server and domain.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>