<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:15:18" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:15:20">http://www.bestbuy.com/site/olstemplatemapper.jsp?id=pcat17080&amp;type=page&amp;qp=q70726f63657373696e6774696d653a3e313930302d30312d3031~~cabcat0200000%23%230%23%237rk~~cabcat0204000%23%230%23%23vg~~nf36%7C%7C4e6f6973652043616e63656c696e67&amp;nrp=15&amp;sc=audioSP&amp;sp=-bestsellingsort+skuid&amp;usc=abcat0200000</link><title>Noise Canceling : Headphones \- Best Buy</title><description>Noise Canceling: Headphones. Read customer reviews, compare prices and buy online at Best Buy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:16:22">http://phiaton.com/</link><title>Premium Headphones, Earbuds, Headsets with Mic - Noise Cancelling Headphones, Earphones-Bluetooth Headphones, Earphones - Phiaton The ...</title><description>Phiaton PS 20 NC Noise Cancelling Earphones Noise Cancelling Earphones. Noise cancelling was seriously good. Robert Elisberg, Huffington Post. The red and black design gives them the sexy exclusive feel of an Italian sports car. John Scott Lewinski, Craveonline.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:16:52">http://store.sony.com/noise-canceling/cat-27-catid-All-Noise-Canceling-Headphones</link><title>Noise Canceling \- Headphones &amp; Earbuds Sony Store - Sony US</title><description>Make and take phone calls with the included in-line remote. Latest Xperia phones and tablets, plus apps and services. Noise Canceling In-Ear Headphones. Tune out the outside world with these Balanced Armature noise canceling in-ear headphones.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:17:32">http://en-us.sennheiser.com/noise-canceling-headphones-travel</link><title>Noise Canceling Headphones for Travel - Sennheiser</title><description>Noise Cancelling Travel. High-quality noise cancelling headphones enchant you with wonderful sound, everywhere: in planes, trains, busses, waiting halls&#8230;Since these places tend to be noisy, your travel headphones should be able to attenuate outside noise effectively.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:18:29">http://www.beatsbydre.com/headphones/pro/beats-pro.html</link><title>Noise Cancelling Headphones \- Tune Out the Noise with Beats Pro</title><description>Because Beats Pro headphones have heavily padded, pivoting ear cups, you get the noise cancelling effect without the need for power switches or batteries. It's the real studio monitor experience in a headphone.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:19:19">http://www.panasonic.com/nz/consumer/home-entertainment/headphones/noise-cancelling-headphones.html</link><title>Noise Cancelling Headphones \- Panasonic New Zealand</title><description>Browse all Noise Cancelling Headphones. Choose the one that's right for you. 1 - 4 of 4 Results.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:20:11">https://www.radioshack.com/product/index.jsp?productId=13237066</link><title>www.radioshack.com product index.jsp - productId=13237066</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:21:09">http://www.adorama.com/PCRPHC720K.html</link><title>Panasonic RP-HC720 Ear Noise Cancelling Headphones RP-HC720-K</title><description>Panasonic RP-HC720 Over Ear Noise Cancelling Head Phones, 95% Noise Canceling. The Panasonic RP-HC720-K Over Ear Headphones Noise Canceling 95%, Feed-forward canceling system with new driver provides high-quality sound reproduction even when noise-canceling circuit is off.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:21:53">http://www.jr.com/category/audio/headphones/corded-headphones/</link><title>Corded Headphones \- JR.com</title><description>Noise Cancel Capable. Order By Phone 800-806-1115. See our Headphones Product Guide. Easy to register and checkout - nice website layout with easy to navigate category tabs. Mackie Mixer Bag for 1604-VLZ Pro &amp; VLZ3 Mixer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:22:43">http://www.pioneerelectronics.com/PUSA/Home/Headphones/Noise+Cancelling/SE-NC31C-K</link><title>Pioneer Electronics USA - SE-NC31C-K - Noise Cancelling Earbud Headphones</title><description>Noise Cancelling Earbud Headphones. These noise canceling earbud headphones feature a larger 14.3mm drivers for dynamic performance and deep bass. Active noise cancellation removes 90% of ambient noise. Ultra-long 120 hour battery life. These in-ear headphones contain 4 ear tip sizes for a customized fit.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>