<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:00:09" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:00:10">http://www.instructables.com/id/How-to-Make-a-Scull-Mask/</link><title>How to Make a Skull Mask \- Instructables.com</title><description>Intro: How to Make a Skull Mask. I got this idea when I was throwing away the backing to the wall-cling that my dad and I bought last year, and I thought: well, this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:01:43">http://www.halloweenexpress.com/skeleton-skull-masks-c-1003.html?page=2</link><title>Skeleton &amp; Skull Masks (page 2) - Skeleton and Skull ...</title><description>Skeleton &amp; Skull Masks (page 2) - Buy Skeleton and Skull Halloween Masks! We also offer Skull Pirate masks, Skeleton horror masks and more. Buy your Skeleton and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:02:33">https://www.etsy.com/search?q=skull+masks</link><title>skull masks on Etsy, a global handmade and vintage marketplace.</title><description>Violent Violette Skull Mask-Gothic Victorian Black Skull Mask-Day of the Dead Mask-Whimsical Skull Mask-Wall Art-SXS ORIGINAL</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:03:58">http://www.spirithalloween.com/product/zg-incisor-mask/</link><title>Halloween Costumes \- Incisor Mask</title><description>Take your piece of Halloween when you make your mark in this gruesome and gory Incisor mask \- it's just another reason not to floss. The Incisor mask is sized for adults. Be the first to review this product. Write a Review. Follow Me on Pinterest.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:05:02">http://www.costumekingdom.com/p-21343-creepy-skull-mask.aspx</link><title>Creepy Skull Mask \- Creepy Skull Halloween Horror Mask</title><description>I never met a skull that didn&#213;t make me want to vomit in terror. The Creepy Skull Mask is no different. This terrifying visage is the perfect avatar for Halloween-borne horror. It doesn&#213;t get any simpler or more iconic than the human skull, so why worry about getting anything else.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:06:13">http://www.frightcatalog.com/halloween-masks/horror/mask-creepy-skull-72-3205HM/</link><title>Menacing Skull Mask \- Masks-Horror costumes at FrightCatalog.com</title><description>The Menacing Skull Mask will make your skeletal costume so much scarier. The mask is ivory in color and features several hairline cracks on it. Eye, mouth, and nose holes are cut into it, too. Halloween Costumes Cart. Halloween Costumes at FrightCatalog.com.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:07:37">http://www.monstermakers.com/content/demos.html</link><title>866-521-(SPFX)7739 \- The Monster Makers Online Special Effects Tutorials and Demos</title><description>To begin you will need the following materials: One generic Halloween Skull, RD-407 Mask Latex, 1 set of acrylic eyes, One Upper and one lower set of acrylic teeth, Selection of Mask Paint, Paper Towelling and two disposable brushes. How To Make Your Own Rotting Skull in 12 easy Steps.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:08:47">http://www.halloweenmart.com/accessories/animal-masks/Duck-Mask.html</link><title>Duck Mask Mask \- Masks \- HalloweenMart</title><description>59.99 Large Resin Skull Item #: 60491113. Make sure you're not last in line when you wear our Duck Mask. Item # &#8211; 61670-1607. Thor Item #: 61243690. American Dream Costume Item #: 61250260.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:10:12">http://www.mooncostumes.com/item/9178</link><title>Costumes \- Kryolan Make-Up Manual (Makeup &amp; Tattoos)</title><description>Behind The Mask A look at the master makeup artists who, in the 20 years since The Exorcist have shown themselves to be the leading rxponents of their craft our price: $24.95 IN-STOCK. Full color makeup book showing exsamples of Child's &amp; adults makeup of clown, cats, skull, old age, pirates and many more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:11:19">http://www.costumes4less.com/Masks_Costume-Accessories_Costume_C-C321-D12_C-0-C321_Store.aspx</link><title>Halloween Costumes \- Halloween Face Masks \- Adult &amp; Child Halloween Mask \- Costumes4less.com</title><description>Browse through our huge mask collection to find horror masks, or life like Halloween masks or political masks and other theme masks. Costumes4less.com offers huge collection of horror mask including halloween masks, political masks, green gremlin monster mask and other theme masks.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>