<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:00:55" name="BigWeb" id="FW14-e200"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:00:56">http://www.goldprice.org/</link><title>Gold Price</title><description>GOLDPRICE.ORG - The No. 1 current gold price site for fast loading live gold price charts in ounces, grams and kilos in 30 major currencies plus advice on how to buy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:42">http://money.cnn.com/data/commodities/</link><title>Commodities - Oil, Silver and gold prices - CNNMoney</title><description>Lists recent, active, and future prices for commodities such as energy, metals, and livestock and meat. Energy New York Mercantile Last Change % Change 52-week price range Last Update. Metals New York Mercantile Last Change % Change 52-week price range Last Update.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:03:08">http://ycharts.com/indicators/gold_price</link><title>Gold Price in US Dollars</title><description>London PM fix daily gold prices. Need to see the raw data. Download the original data directly from our source. Access watchlists and custom data alerts. Start your free account.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:04:40">http://www.thestreet.com/topic/43441/gold-price.html</link><title>Gold Prices - Get the Price of Gold \- TheStreet</title><description>The most commonly cited gold price is the 24-hour New York spot gold price*(shown here, prices in US Dollars). Gold prices today, chart of today's spot gold price, prices of Gold ETFs, how to invest in gold and gold news coverage. Today's Spot Gold Price Chart. This account is pending registration confirmation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:06:06">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/tag/gold-price</link><title>Gold Price</title><description>Gold Prices Hit Record High On US Dollar's Decline. Gold rose to a record high for a fourth straight day and silver surged on Friday, as a weaker dollar, the prospect of a US. Eleazar David Melendez. More in Politics. You might also like.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:06:54">http://www.goldpriceoz.com/gold-price-per-ounce/</link><title>Gold Prices Per Ounce Today - Gold Price OZ</title><description>Gold price per ounce today - live gold prices per ounce charts. Gold Prices Per Ounce Today. Gold prices per ounce is a free service provided by Gold Price OZ website, where shows current gold price(including bid price and ask price) and gold price history chart(London gold fixing).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:07:57">http://www.ronpaul.com/misc/gold-price-chart/</link><title>Gold Price Chart</title><description>Ron Paul is America's leading voice for limited, constitutional government, low taxes, free markets, sound money, and a pro-American foreign policy. Home / Misc / Gold Price Chart.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:09:08">http://www.bullionvault.com/gold-price-chart.do</link><title>Gold Price Chart - Live spot gold and silver rates - BullionVault</title><description>Live gold prices in Zurich, London, New York, Singapore and Toronto. You can then purchase at those same prices using BullionVault. Why do the prices quoted on BullionVault change over the weekend, when the chart doesn't. Buy gold online today at live gold prices.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:10:00">http://seekingalpha.com/author/gold-price-today</link><title>Gold Price Today - Seeking Alpha</title><description>Latest comments on Gold Price's Articles more. LATEST ARTICLES &amp; INSTAPOSTS more. Gold Price Today picture. News stories will bring you the daily rounds, we bring you the dirt, the things that are behind what is happening. If anything the last decade has told us there are always consequences.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e200-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e200/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:11:01">http://economictimes.indiatimes.com/topic/Gold-prices</link><title>Gold prices - Latest News &amp; Videos, Photos about Gold prices - The Economic Times</title><description>Wednesday Feb 2013, 0238 hrs IST FUTURES PRICE. Gold prices Latest Breaking News, Pictures, Videos, and Special Reports from The Economic Times. Gold prices Blogs, Comments and Archive News on Economictimes.com. Gold Funds have given a return of 2.7% over the last one year: Value Research.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>