<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:58:26" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:58:27">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949808730</link><title>Senior Electronics Design Engineer</title><description>The Role As the selected Senior Electronics Design Engineer you will join the small but expert R &amp; D Team which is made up over... up over 16 Engineer from Electronics, RF... and Embedded Software Engineers and report directly to the Engineering Manager. You will... team of electronic engineers. You As the... Senior Electronics Design Engineer you'll have over... you are an engineer that is a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:59:35">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949823051</link><title>Configuration Engineer</title><description>Configuration Engineer 12 Month contract Rate - £20 per hour As a Configuration Engineer your main responsibilities will involve: To maintain the database for all... As a Configuration Engineer your main responsibilities... As a Configuration Engineer your skills and... Naval / Technical Engineering and familiar with... -Apprenticeship/ONC/HNC in an engineering subject Experience: -Working... processes. Responsibilities - Engineering Awareness of Product...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:01:43">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949857415</link><title>Supplier Quality Engineer</title><description>Job Description The Supplier Quality Engineer performs a variety of activities that drive supplier quality improvements, including, but not limited to the following: -Participate in... Identify and inform engineering about issues related... in a quality engineer role for a... including purchasing, production, engineering and quality staff... Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is acting as an employment business with regards...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:05:58">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949853407</link><title>Hosting Server Engineer - Windows / Linux - Leeds</title><description>Hosting Server Engineer \- Windows / Linux - Leeds £18,000 - £25,000 (Depending on experience) **** Opportunities to progress **** Windows / Server 2008/2012 /... Hyper-V Hosting Server Engineer with experience supporting... a Hosting Server Engineer you should have... a Hosting Server Engineer you will be... add me on LinkedIn: [URL removed] Keywords: Windows / Server 2008/2012 / Linux /...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:10:26">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949857424</link><title>Supplier Quality Engineer</title><description>Job Description The Supplier Quality Engineer performs a variety of activities that drive supplier quality improvements, including, but not limited to the following: -Participate in... Identify and inform engineering about issues related... in a quality engineer role for a... including purchasing, production, engineering and quality staff... Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is acting as an employment business with regards...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:14:28">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949816614</link><title>Quality NDT Engineer</title><description>Quality Engineer Role This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced Quality Engineer with knowledge of Non Destructive Testing particular to Fluorescent Penetrant Inspection (FPI)... an experienced Quality Engineer with knowledge of... in a Quality Engineer role is required... of the Quality Engineer will be as... An experienced Quality Engineer, you will also... role of Quality Engineer your own, please...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:17:12">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949848258</link><title>Senior Quality Engineer (NPI)</title><description>Senior Quality Engineer I'm recruiting for an Aerospace company in Hampshire who is looking to recruit a Senior Quality Engineer (NPI) to join their team.... a Senior Quality Engineer (NPI) to join... the Senior Quality Engineer will be to:... procedures -Execute Quality Engineering NPI project tasks... Analyses. -Execute Reliability Engineering NPI tasks including... successful Senior Quality Engineer has a degree...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:48">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949823187</link><title>Mechanical Development Engineer (Test &amp; Analysis)</title><description>An exciting time to join this organisation as they move in to a new purpose built facility creating their first central global R&amp;D team. This... multiple mechanical development engineers to work alongside the design engineers on concept to... of 4/5 development engineers providing a support... standards. Mechanical Development Engineer Technical Skills: -Mechanical... of mechanical development engineer offers a great... Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:26:45">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949810013</link><title>Senior Electronics Engineer</title><description>*****Role: Senior Electronics Engineer***** *****Location: Kent***** *****Salary: £40,000***** As a senior Electronics Engineer you'll be responsible championing and taking control of projects. You'll also ensure... a senior Electronics Engineer you'll be responsible... for an electronics engineer to join on... Electronics Hardware/analogue Design Engineer you must have... motors * Reverse engineering of electronic automotive... The successful Electronics Engineer will receive a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7009-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7009_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:31:04">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949838217</link><title>Support Engineer</title><description>An excellent opportunity for a Technical Customer Support Engineer to join a pioneer in real time video analytics based in Surrey. Due to continued growth... Technical Customer Support Engineer to join their... Technical Customer Support Engineer you'll join an... experienced team of Engineers reporting to the... Technical Customer Support Engineer you'll have relevant... equivalent in Computer Engineering or related discipline...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>