<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:42:18" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:42:19">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949590757</link><title>Senior Web Developer - Magento, PHP, HTML, CSS</title><description>With business and private customers across the UK and beyond, This company has strong roots in Cornwall dating back to 1925. The team pride themselves... to become part of rapidly evolving business, ... with e-commerce and web applications being at the core of its strategy. Focusing... on the development of their e-commerce portfolio... require the creation of internal systems and... take complete ownership of their e-commerce and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:45:49">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949841827</link><title>Senior JavaScript Developer - Join Google guys</title><description>JavaScript Guru - Work the Google way! Central London 50-60k depending on level Company shares, bonus and benefits Founded in 2010 by a team from... work with some of the biggest names... funding from one of the UK's biggest... now house 90 of London's most sought... were only 5 of them. Their offices... football, kitchen full of fruit and other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:50:02">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949833144</link><title>Lead Developer</title><description>ABOUT THE ROLE My client is seeking a senior developer to lead our My client's team. You will guide this agile team as it develops, ... and maintains innovative web applications in a... a great source of insight and marketing... an agile team of developers to deliver... to balancethe needs of clients and internal... and mentor members of the team to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:51:05">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949786122</link><title>Head of Research Operations</title><description>Head of Research Operations Research Expert? Creative communicator? Inquisitive? £60,000 Hanger Lane W5 1UA West London The role A challenging and exciting role for a... through all aspects of what we do. As Head of Research Operations, you... forward the development of this high profile... maintenance and optimisation of our panel, which... is made up of 6000 homes representing... At this time of great change, it...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:53:57">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949846160</link><title>Graduate C# . Net Technical Support - Croydon</title><description>Graduate C# .Net Technical Support - Croydon The role The role is primarily to provide technical support and implementation services for customers in the local... work as part of consultancies and to... have developer knowledge of the application to... on more complex web training courses. Your... technical support for web products - Web product installation and... documentation for all web products - Web...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:56:35">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949844328</link><title>Graduate / Trainee Web Developer</title><description>Successful and growing IT Services company, based in Central London, is looking for a Graduate / Trainee Web developer to join their team. As a... would be part of an experienced and... maintain the in-house web platform * Integrate... one or more of the following: oJava... new technologies, especially web technologies * First... (academically/commercially) Engineering, Computer Science, Physics, Maths. You...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:01:03">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949729198</link><title>Front End JavaScript Web Developer</title><description>Front End JavaScript Web Developer Central London Up to £55,000 THE COMPANY A rare and exciting opportunity has arisen for a Front End JavaScript Web... Front End JavaScript Web Developer to be part of an award winning... with the security of an International plc... an exciting period of global expansion due... Front End JavaScript Web Developer to turn... Front End JavaScript Web Developer will have:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:01:34">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=948929043</link><title>Level 4 Higher Software Developer IT Apprentice</title><description>Level 4 Higher Software Developer IT Apprentice Shortcode: 1866 Programme: Software &amp; Web Development L3 Town: Reading Postcode: RG2 Salary: £250.12 per week Closing date:... Programme: Software &amp; Web Development L3 Town:... on a number of very high profile... including the development of the UK's Police... manage a number of systems across the... services for 15 of the UK's police...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:05:14">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949645287</link><title>Business Development Manager - Life Sciences</title><description>Bickland Industrial Park, Falmouth, Cornwall, TR11 4TA Tel: 01326 372753 [International +44 1326 372 753] Fax: 01326 378783 [International +44 1326 378 783] Company Registration... 03419143 e-mail: bill@research-instruments.com Web Site: http:// www.... Manager - Life Sciences Research Instruments (RI)... largest global supplier of hardware into the... into the Life Sciences markets. We are... with a relevant science background capable of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:07:48">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949846197</link><title>Senior Web Developer: C#. NET, ASP. NET or MVC, WCF, WPF</title><description>Web Developer and Senior Web Dev: C#.NET, ASP.NET or MVC, WCF, WPF, JIRA, Agile - Gain some Android exposure Liverpool, Merseyside (Very Central for easy Web Dev: C#.NET, ASP.NET... and experience: Computer Science or equivalent degree... in the development of line of business web applications (3-6 years... 2005/2008 Good understanding of OO , .net... Develop a mix of desktop, web based...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>