<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:28:54" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:28:55">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949838704</link><title>Web Developer - Python, Django, JavaScript</title><description>Web Developer - Python, Django, JavaScript £30,000 - 50,000 An opportunity has arisen for a Full Stack Web Developer to join a successful Technology Consultancy... side frameworks - Django (preferred), Ruby on Rails, MVC etc. - JavaScript / JQuery - HTML / CSS - SQL Databases - both MySQL and SQLServer - JavaScript Frameworks - Angular.js This role is going...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:29:59">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949667122</link><title>Technical Lead (Django, Python)</title><description>A creative digital agency is on the hunt for a new Technical Lead. This is a great opportunity to take charge of a team in... focused with good Django / Python knowledge.... and Experience - Django 1.2 + - PHP and/or Ruby on Rails - DevOps experience - usual set up Linux / PostgreSQL but does vary - Ability to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:31:02">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949847645</link><title>Web Developer| Berlin| Django| Python | API Orchestration|</title><description>Web Developer| Berlin| Django| Python | API Orchestration| Location: Berlin, Germany Category: Opensource Development Employment Type: Permanent Salary: 40,000.00 - 50,000.00 Salary Type: Per Annum... - Python - Django \- API Orchestration... years` experience with Django, Python and API... Web Developer| Berlin| Django| Python | API Orchestration| Links: ------ [1] mailto:jhicks@marcusdonald.de</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:34:05">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949860568</link><title>Python / Django Developer - St Albans</title><description>Python / Django Developer - My client is looking for a passionate Developer with an understanding of web technologies Python / Django and ideally PHP... technologies Python / Django and ideally PHP... have -Python / Django experience -Knowledge of PHP (ideally) -Other web development experience -An entrepreneurial attitude or experience working on your own -Some business acumen -A self-motivated attitude...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:02">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949857866</link><title>Python Developer</title><description>We're searching for a talented Python Developer to work in an extremely high profile Tech Company in London, specialising in creating Streaming Video solutions across... E.g. Zend, Symfony, Django * Experience with... Developer - Python, Django, MySQL</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:45">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949811208</link><title>Senior Python Developer</title><description>Typically, your role will involve developing with the following web technologies, but certainly not limited to just these! § Python § PostgreSQL § Django § AngularJS or... and proficient with Django, and have a... experience working with Django, Python, Javascript, and... experience with Python, Django, Javascript, proficient SQL, and comfortable with HTML/CSS § Comfortable in the shell: you won't be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:38:34">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949865117</link><title>Senior Linux Systems Administrator - London's leading start up</title><description>Senior Linux Systems Administrator - DevOps -Ubuntu, MySQL Mongo, Apache, Puppet, Nginx 45-55k Austin Fraser are currently seeking a highly skilled Senior Linux Systems Administrator... combination of Python, Django and PHP. This role will suit strong problem solvers and Engineer's who like to hack around with new technology and propose better ways of doing things. Key Skills: - Linux, Ubuntu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:42:20">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949856865</link><title>Junior Application Developer</title><description>With a new London office and exciting strategic work kicking off alongside various internal changes to deal with our expansion, Nomensa are looking for a... our newly re-built Django based CMS, Defacto.... solid knowledge of Django, you must have a good understanding of versioning systems, preferably GIT. Ideally you will have at least six months experience in a similar role....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:43:01">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949857104</link><title>Web Developer</title><description>We're looking for an enthusiastic full stack (with opportunity to specialise as part of career progression) web developer to assist in taking our website to... chat. Skills Range: -Python/Django experience ideally, but if you've used PHP/Ruby/etc then no problem. -Javascript experience essential.Ideally using an MVC framework e.g. Angular/Ember/Backbone etc. -HTML/CSS experience essential. Ideally use of a CSS preprocessor such as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7077-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7077_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:45:48">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949831975</link><title>Senior Web Developer</title><description>POSITION: Senior Django/Python Developer LOCATION: Central London TYPE OF ROLE: Permanent SALARY: £35,000-55,000 p/a A leading global digital agency are looking to expand their team... the use of Django and Python. They... * Python * Django * PostgreSQL * Angular JS * HTML5 * Using Linux within a shell * Excellent understanding of Object Oriented Programming The succesful candidate will...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>