<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:39:48" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:39:50">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949796215</link><title>Asbestos Consultant - Cambridge - £23-26k + BENS</title><description>Asbestos Consultant Cambridge £23,000 - £26,000 + vehicle + benefits Our client is a successful asbestos management consultancy and has an exceptional reputation within the... region and so must have a flexible... asbestos sector, please do not hesitate to call Danielle Stallard of Penguin Recruitment on 0121 442 0644. Alternatively you can email your CV and we'll call you back....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:43:23">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949842296</link><title>Field Service &amp; Commissioning Engineer</title><description>Dedicated, enthusiastic and flexible Service Engineer urgently required to work within an experienced team working with heavy machinery and electrical power systems. You will be... Bicester, Banbury and Cambridge. You can expect... to this position must be eligible to... experienced consultant, please do not hesitate to telephone 02476 100700. Links: ------ [1] mailto:laura.edmunds@automationexperts.co.uk [2] [URL removed] [3] [URL removed]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:43:57">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949831113</link><title>Chemical Process Engineer</title><description>Chemical Process Engineer - Bedford, Royston, Hertford, Biggleswade, Cambridge Salary: £30000 - £40000 dependent upon experience plus fantastic benefits Permanent Position We are a world... client. If you do not wish your... client then you must clearly state this... companies that you do not wish your CV to be sent to (for whatever reason), then please let us know of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:45:49">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949845250</link><title>Nursery Cook - Cambridge</title><description>Bright Horizons are currently recruiting for a Cook to join our fantastic Cambridge Science Park Nursery. The Nursery is based on the Cambridge Science Park... based on the Cambridge Science Park on... bus route from Cambridge to Huntingdon with... the ideal candidates must hold a full... of all we do just one of our HEART principles * Regular 1 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:47:17">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949845062</link><title>Nursery Nurse, Cambridge</title><description>Bright Horizons are currently recruiting for Qualified Nursery Nurse's to join our fantastic Bunnybrookes Day Nursery in Cambridge. The Nursery is based on the Addenbrooke's... the ideal candidates must hold a full... of all we do just one of our HEART principles - Regular 1 2 1's, support, and supervision to help your career flourish - Family friendly flexible working...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:50:53">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949756682</link><title>Deputy Room Supervisor - Cambridge Science Park</title><description>Bright Horizons are currently recruiting for Deputy Room Supervisor to join our fantastic Cambridge Science Park Nursery. The Nursery is based on the Cambridge Science... based on the Cambridge Science Park on... bus route from Cambridge to Huntingdon with... the ideal candidates must hold a full... of all we do just one of our HEART principles - Regular 1 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:52:30">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949756075</link><title>Nursery Nurse's - Cambridge Science Park</title><description>Bright Horizons are currently recruiting for Qualified Nursery Nurse's to join our fantastic Cambridge Science Park Nursery. The Nursery is based on the Cambridge Science... based on the Cambridge Science Park on... bus route from Cambridge to Huntingdon with... the ideal candidates must hold a full... of all we do just one of our HEART principles - Regular 1 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:53:54">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949822392</link><title>Service Desk Agent</title><description>My Client is a established market leader in timetabling and resource scheduling solutions for the Higher Education, Government and Private sectors. They are currently in... peer review work done to ensure excellent... the company standards; MUST BE FLUENT IN DUTCH. Purpose - To give the customers the best support experience with each Request for information, Incident or Request for change...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:57:16">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949822535</link><title>Plant Engineering &amp; Maintenance Manager - perm</title><description>Plant Engineering &amp; Maintenance Manager Location: West Midlands, Birmingham, Leamington, Bromsgrove, Warwick, Solihull, Walsall, Stafford, Telford, Coventry, Dudley, Cannock, Gaydon, Redditch, Stourbridge, Kidderminster, Wolverhampton, West... Milton Keynes, Leicester, Cambridge, Nationwide Salary: circa... in everything they do. Here, at the... join them, you must combine proven technical... In addition, you must have a technical / engineering degree. A Six Sigma Black...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:58:05">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949796000</link><title>Senior REACH Regulatory Consultant - Cambridge - £30-34k+BENS</title><description>As Senior Consultant you will be responsible for developing projects and providing chemical regulatory consultancy. You are responsible for ensuring your clients meet their regulatory... needs and so must provide exceptional REACH... environmental sector, please do not hesitate to call Danielle Stallard of Penguin Recruitment on 0121 442 0644. Alternatively you can email your CV and we'll call you back....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>