<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:16" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:17">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949256133</link><title>Solidworks Designer/ Production Engineer (Aluminium Extrusions)</title><description>Solidworks Designer/Production Engineer - modelling and rendering - construction/architectural industry - creating visuals and design drawings for tender stage through to fabrication drawings for manufacturing... - Solidworks - aluminium extrusions \- based near... particularly working with aluminium extrusions The company has a vibrant, dynamic workforce and this position is available due to expansion in their Cheshire based regional office The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:08:03">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949654336</link><title>Supplier Development Engineer</title><description>Job Title: Supplier Development Engineer Job Location: Lancashire. Department: SUPPLY CHAIN Line Manager: Supplier Development Manager Salary: Hours of work: 37.5 hrs per week with... processes such as Aluminium Extrusion, UPVC Extrusion, Injection Moulding, Die casting etc. * Thorough understanding of Process variation and Process Control. * Knowledge of Production Part Approval Process (P.P.A.P.) Abilities * This is a varied...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:10:56">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949822630</link><title>Solidworks Designer/ Production Engineer (Aluminium Extrusions)</title><description>Solidworks Designer/Production Engineer - modelling and rendering - construction/architectural industry - creating visuals and design drawings for tender stage through to fabrication drawings for manufacturing... - Solidworks - aluminium extrusions \- based near... particularly working with aluminium extrusions The company has a vibrant, dynamic workforce and this position is available due to expansion in their Cheshire based regional office The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:37">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949862322</link><title>Senior Product Development Engineer</title><description>Senior Product Development Engineer is required by a leading worldwide Solar company and will be responsible for developing design concepts into viable product offerings for... progressive die stamping, aluminum extrusion, aluminum die casting, investment casting, and injection molding. o Knowledge of and experience with different metals and alloys o Ability to take on responsibility and thrive under tight deadlines. o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:21:02">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949829299</link><title>Sales Manager - Interior Building Products</title><description>Sales Manager - Interior Building Products Job Title: Sales Manager - Interior Building Products / Materials Job reference Number: 705750-2983-1487 Industry Sector: aluminium trims, access panels, ... manufactured range of aluminium extrusions used within a... be spent selling aluminium trims used for... building boards, ceiling, aluminium trims, access panels, ... sales positions within: aluminium trims, access panels, bespoke metalwork, dry lining, partitioning, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:23:21">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=946401815</link><title>Design Engineer</title><description>This represents an excellent opportunity for an enthusiastic, experienced Design Engineer to play a responsible role in a close knit team, where your contribution will... be useful: - aluminium extrusions \- injection mouldings... - steel and aluminium pressings and castings - joining techniques (welding and riveting)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:24:00">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=947083899</link><title>Production Engineer</title><description>£30m turnover manufacturing business seeks Production Engineer who has gained experience in high and low volume manufacturing operations. The Production Engineer will provide a full... * Experience of aluminium extrusion, injection moulding, pressings, castings and joining techniques including welding, riveting etc would be advantageous but not essential. * Organised, methodical and able to follow projects through to completion. * Good...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:03">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949814642</link><title>Mechanical Maintenance Engineer</title><description>Mechanical Maintenance Engineer Loughborough, Leicestershire £28,000 - £30,000 + Overtime + Pension + Healthcare + Life Assurance Are you a Mechanical Maintenance Engineer looking for... market leaders in aluminium extrusion and due to... electrical, heavy plant, aluminium, heavy engineering, automotive, aerospace, food, hydraulics, press, presses, press shop, foundry, manufacturing, pumps, gears, rams, Loughborough, Leicestershire</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:30">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949853650</link><title>Multi-Skilled Maintenance Technicians</title><description>LOCATION: Birtley JOB TITLE: Multi-Skilled Maintenance Technicians SALARY &amp; BENEFITS: Circa £30,600 inc shift premium HOURS: Full time THE COMPANY: Our client is the world leader in aluminium solutions. Their profiles... ROLE: At their extrusion plant located in Birtley, they currently have vacancies for highly competent, time served Technicians to join their maintenance team. Working shifts, including nights, you will...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7167-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7167_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:31:29">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949823199</link><title>Quality Engineer</title><description>Quality Engineer Redditch - £30,000 Why be a Multi-Skilled Maintenance Engineer with this company? With a focus on customer satisfaction this company have a strong... Good understanding of aluminium alloys and extrusion processes What will the role involve? · Develop the Quality management system to ensure continuous improvement. · Work with customers to overcome quality issues · Process Improvement ·...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>