<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:08" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:10">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949839133</link><title>Electrical Cable Designer</title><description>Electrical Cable Designer : World class Defence Organisation based in Stevenage, Hertfordshire is currently looking to recruit an Electrical Cable Designer. Please Note: you must... is initially for 6 months (ongoing after).... of a project team. * Support/liaise with... of military, environmentally sealed cable harnesses or be a time served prototype wire-person who has diverged into interconnects design. * The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:55">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949802243</link><title>Manufacturing Engineer - RF/ Microwave Technologies</title><description>World class Defence Organisation based in Lostock, Bolton is currently looking to recruit a Manufacturing Engineer - RF/Microwave Technologies. Please Note: you must be eligible... is initially for 6 months (ongoing after).... Chip Underfill, Hermetic Sealing / testing, Module... and cross cultural teams to enable seamless... of a project team. * Define automated... Package assembly, Hermetic sealing/Testing, Module assembly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:48:49">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949814250</link><title>Test and Validation Engineer</title><description>Test &amp; Validation Engineer - Peterborough - £40,000 / £50,000 Peterborough, United Kingdom - My client, a global leader in the Automotive Industry are recruiting... to join their team with immediate effect... within the Cooling Team as an experienced, ... Work or lead teams to undertake component... in a multi-functional team and large organizations.... Engine systems: Cooling, sealing, in cylinder, vibration...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:57">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949723422</link><title>Sales Representative Medical Devices (Endovascular)</title><description>Sales Representative Medical Devices (Endovascular) Frankfurt (Germany), fulltime The job: Promotes, sells, and services the company's stent graft directly to vascular specialists within an assigned... positive mindset, initiative, team player We offer:... with the Sales team. As a sales... in EndoVascular Aneurysm Sealing. In addition, we... build our European team. Please have a... a.i.) at +31 6 17330763\. Please note:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:51:31">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949726129</link><title>Customer Service Administrator - German</title><description>For more than a century, HayssenSandiacre/Simionato has been recognized as a form/fill/seal technology and services leader worldwide. Our team of dedicated and experienced professionals design... leader worldwide. Our team of dedicated and... culture where each team member returns home... of individual and team achievements we strengthen... Customer Service Sales Team, you will be... Parts and Upgrades Team as part of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:56:13">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949743092</link><title>Valve Design Draughtsman / Valve Design Engineer - £45k - Poole</title><description>Valve Design Draughtsman / Valve Design Engineer £30-45k Basic (Dependent on Experience) + Bonus + Relocation Assistance + Benefits The company designs and manufactures high... pressure regulators, hermetically sealed bellows globe valves... are dedicated sales teams for each of... existing valve designs 6. Provide assembly and... with other project team members, liaising with manufacturing &amp; sales departments, reviewing progress as...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>