<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:24:01" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:24:02">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949810233</link><title>Systems Engineer (Flight Simulators) - Aerospace</title><description>Systems Engineer (Flight Simulators) - Aerospace Switzerland CHF - Competitive Systems Engineer / Project Engineer required by well known Aerospace client to lead the design, Switzerland... and installation of flight simulators. In return, my... activities to achieve simulator installation and acceptance... designing &amp; delivering Flight Simulators or Simulators of another kind then please submit your CV - or send directly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:24:26">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949851478</link><title>Bid &amp; Projects Functional Analyst</title><description>Bid &amp; Project Functional Analyst Thales is recruiting a Bid &amp; Project Functional Analyst. This is a role that will support the implementation of agreed... through to full flight simulators, Thales is helping make the world a safer, more secure place. Thales UK: Transport Transport networks around the world rely on technology and systems expertise from Thales for safety, reliability...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:18">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949851459</link><title>IT Support Analyst</title><description>Primary Purpose of the Role: To provide onsite and remote users desktop, laptop and general IT service support. Working as part of a wider team... through to full flight simulators, Thales is helping make the world a safer, more secure place. What we offer you At Thales we provide CAREERS and not only jobs. We value talent and provide growth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:29:23">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949851463</link><title>IT Helpdesk Team Leader</title><description>Primary Purpose of the Role: To provide hands on leadership, direction and guidance to on/off site Helpdesk support team. Working as part of a wider... through to full flight simulators, Thales is helping make the world a safer, more secure place. Thales Research and Technology Thales Research and Technology (UK) Ltd. is part of the Thales global network of research...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:31:51">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949681816</link><title>Programme Technical Instructor</title><description>ASTOR Programme Technical Instructor - 49853BR Business Context Job Purpose The ASTOR Technical Instructors are responsible for classroom and simulator based training delivery and continued... of classroom and simulator based ASTOR Air... including Sentinel R1 flight deck, mission, Radar... systems including, aircraft flight deck avionics systems, ... systems maintenance including flight deck avionics, mission systems, airborne radar systems and aircraft electrical systems....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>