<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:45:25" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:45:26">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949859398</link><title>Digital Marketing Coordinator</title><description>The Digital Marketing Company in Milton Keynes who sell Medical and Cosmetic goods are seeking a Digital Marketing Coordinator to join their expanding team. As... such as YouTube, Facebook, Twitter. - In... copy of our privacy policy can be viewed on our website.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:47:11">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949724498</link><title>Sales Executive - Retail</title><description>We are working on behalf of Richard Hardie to fill this vacancy. There are several positions available across the company. Richard Hardie is a family... to promote our Facebook activity. In summary... copy of our privacy policy can be viewed on our website.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:48:22">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949861200</link><title>Marketing Executive</title><description>Marketing Executive Bolton Very competitive salary + Benefits My client, an established on-line retailer has an exciting job opportunity for a marketing executive to work... strategies (e.g. twitter, Facebook etc), improve search... accept the T&amp;C's, Privacy Policy and Disclaimers which can be found at hays.co.uk</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:51:00">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949832821</link><title>Global Mobility Operations Manager - Connecticut</title><description>Job Ref: NH/45724/GM Package: $Negotiable + Bonus + Benefits Location: Connecticut, USA Job Type: Global Mobility Operations Manager Languages: English (essential) Position Type: Permanent Hours:... policies and procedures, privacy, security and confidentiality... follow us on Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is acting as an employment business with regards to this position.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>