<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:54:43" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:54:45">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949742107</link><title>Pre-Sales, Professional Services Consultant</title><description>This position is based in a client facing environment specifying and designing detailed infrastructure projects for a variety of customers throughout the UK. The position... position includes involvement at various stages of... be required to work with various clients... the required hardware, software and services. The... architect or pre-sales consultant within an existing... have previous experience working within a reseller...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:56:51">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949823309</link><title>Senior MS Dynamics CRM Consultant - Cheshire - £60k</title><description>MS Dynamics, CRM, Consultant I am looking for a Senior MS Dynamics CRM Technical Consultant for an exciting opportunity with a Cheshire based Software Consultancy.... Dynamics CRM Technical Consultant for an exciting... a Cheshire based Software Consultancy. The company... you will be working from the company's... as well as home working and on client... IT leadership and working with client organisations...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:57:29">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949824941</link><title>Dynamics NAV Consultant - £45-55k - UK Wide - Gold Partner</title><description>An immediate requirement has arisen for a senior NAV consultant to work within an established Microsoft Gold Partner on varied and exciting projects. My client an established... Senior NAV Functional Consultant. They require a Senior/Lead Consultant who has experience... will have: - At least4 years Dynamics... essential - Full Software Implementation life cycle... - Project managed at least 3 NAV...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:59:39">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949809734</link><title>Delivery Architect</title><description>The current vacancy is for a forward thinking technical giant. Our client is looking for a Delivery Architect who has a proven track record as... technical authority on at least one major... by having delivered at least 4-5 significant... -Extensive experience in at least one of... service-orientated architectures and software development progresses such... disciplines of enterprise software development such as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:00:36">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949816992</link><title>Business Development Consultant - IT Training sales</title><description>Business Development Consultant \- Apprenticeships/Training Sales (IT Training) Package Totals 30000 - 32000 (23000 - 25000 basic 3000 car allowance uncapped commission) Due to internal... driven Business Development Consultant \- Apprenticeship/Training Sales Home Based Manchester -... to end Recruitment Consultant with a strong... winning Business Development Consultant our client now... successful Business Development Consultant doesnt need to... the Business Development Consultant Visit new and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:02:24">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949851456</link><title>Principal Consultant - Systems Modeller</title><description>Quintec, Thales' systems and programme management consultancy have an exciting opportunity currently available to bring into the business a Systems Modelling Consultant to provide expert... perhaps from a Software Engineering environment where... Programme Management. We work with clients to... delivery. We also work with prime contract, ... will need to work with internal and... the solution o Working with stakeholders to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:05:38">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949813507</link><title>Software Engineer - Contract - Croydon</title><description>Software Engineer - Contract - Croydon Amoria Bond are looking for a Software Engineer with experience of C++ for a position in Croydon, London. We... looking for a Software Engineer with experience... Requirements capture/gathering - Software Analysis - C++... - Experience of working with a range... essential) Key Skills: Software Engineering, Software, Programming, C++, C, ... As a contractor working through Amoria Bond...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:08:46">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949846313</link><title>Sustainability Consultant (BREEAM, CSH &amp; SAP)</title><description>Sustainability Consultant \- BREEAM/CSH Assessor London Head of Environmental Initiatives Our client is looking for a personable, reliable and articulate individual to help grow our... Code for Sustainable Homes and Ecohomes/ BREEAM... in English - At least 2 qualifications... - Responsibility for at least one submission... Familiarity with SAP software and Building Regulations, ... - Able to work under tight deadlines...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:11:18">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949752396</link><title>Service Engineer - South or Midlands</title><description>This is a home based role which requires travel within the South and Midlands One of the UK's leading independent providers of green energy services... system graphics and software as required -... projects meet the clients/consultants design spec in... visit performed, detailing work carried out and... for additional site work \- Carry out... the Programme of Works and report back...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:13:40">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949853738</link><title>Customer Implementation Consultant - Based in Dublin</title><description>Customer Manager - Based in Dublin The Customer Manager is responsible for management and successful execution of customer implementations for assigned clients. The Customer Manager, ... with future developments (working with the Product... of the relationship at the appropriate levels.... as required. * Work effectively with other... Engagement Model. * Work as needed with... 3 years of software or data industry...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>