<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:07" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:09">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949760212</link><title>Paid Search Manager - USA/ Sweden/ Denmark/ Norway</title><description>A hugely successful international online travel company based in Central London are looking to expand their Digital team by taking on a number of Paid Search (PPC) Managers.... OVERVIEW * The Paid Search Manager will... Google, Bing and Facebook. * There are... BENEFITS The successful Paid Search (PPC) Account... role and other Paid Search (PPC) positions, ... online, digital, marketing, paid search, agency, marin, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:46">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949760189</link><title>Paid Search Executive - USA/ Sweden/ Denmark/ Norway</title><description>A hugely successful international online travel company based in Central London are looking to expand their digital team by taking on a number of Paid Search (PPC) Executives.... OVERVIEW * The Paid Search Executive will... Google, Bing and Facebook. * There are... BENEFITS The successful Paid Search (PPC) Account... role and other Paid Search (PPC) positions, ... online, digital, marketing, paid search, agency, marin, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:51:17">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949652635</link><title>Content Marketeer</title><description>This is a fantastic opportunity to join an award winning integrated social media &amp; content marketing agency. Over the last decade, they've experienced the rapid... including; the blog, Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, Instagram, ... (job seekers never pay anything). This low price means there is a clear incentive for the employer to give your application priority.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:52:32">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949845349</link><title>Trainee Service Desk Analyst - Part Time</title><description>Trainee Service Desk Analyst - Part time, Customer service, MS Office Capita, FTSE 100 and leading Business Process Outsourcer, is seeking a number of Part... extending. Salary is paid pro rata on... Follow Capita on facebook @careersatcapita Capita Resourcing welcome applications from all suitably qualified people regardless of gender, race, disability, age or sexual orientation. Capita Resourcing is a trading...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:56:14">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949752166</link><title>Digital Marketing Executive</title><description>Digital Marketing Executive Central London £18-23k depending on experience An amazing opportunity has arisen for someone passionate about digital marketing to join one of the... strategy - Implementing Pay Per Click campaigns... find us on Facebook at [URL removed] Job Sectors: Digital Marketing Jobs | SEO Jobs | Affiliates Jobs</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:59:12">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949724498</link><title>Sales Executive - Retail</title><description>We are working on behalf of Richard Hardie to fill this vacancy. There are several positions available across the company. Richard Hardie is a family... 20 days annual paid holiday, a company... to promote our Facebook activity. In summary this is an opportunity for talented and enthusiastic individuals to develop a rewarding career with a dynamic and progressive company. The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:59:48">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949845212</link><title>Trainee Service Desk Analyst - Part Time</title><description>Trainee Service Desk Analyst - Part time, Customer service, MS Office Capita, FTSE 100 and leading Business Process Outsourcer, is seeking a number of Part... extending. Salary is paid pro rata on... Follow Capita on facebook @careersatcapita Capita Resourcing welcome applications from all suitably qualified people regardless of gender, race, disability, age or sexual orientation. Capita Resourcing is a trading...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:03:54">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949816614</link><title>Quality NDT Engineer</title><description>Quality Engineer Role This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced Quality Engineer with knowledge of Non Destructive Testing particular to Fluorescent Penetrant Inspection (FPI)... on Fridays and paid overtime (as and... follow us on Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is acting as an employment business with regards to this position.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:07:42">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949865807</link><title>Expatriate Tax - Senior Associate</title><description>A rewarding opportunity has become available for an Expatriate Tax Senior Associate to join a leading and developing organisation based in London. The role is... planning and net pay implementation - Ensuring... follow us on Facebook, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn JAM Recruitment is acting as an employment business with regards to this position.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:12:26">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949668138</link><title>Senior PHP Developer</title><description>This UK based web-marketing company are looking to recruit a Senior PHP Developer. They are not just looking for a PHP developer; they are looking... media skills with Facebook, twitter integration -... (job seekers never pay anything). This low price means there is a clear incentive for the employer to give your application priority.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>