<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:15:32" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:15:33">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949860783</link><title>Catastrophe Model Developer</title><description>Catastrophe Model Developer City of London Who they are A world leading reinsurance intermediary, developing Catastrophe models for various natural and man-made perils, including Wind storm, Flood, Earthquake, Terrorism and other. The role Main duties and responsibilities include: * Managing, coordinating and participating in the technical development of the damage/ vulnerability component of the assigned projects, * Planning, managing and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:16:01">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949860734</link><title>Catastrophe Model Developer</title><description>Catastrophe Model Developer City of London Who they are A world leading reinsurance intermediary, developing Catastrophe models for various natural and man-made perils, including Wind storm, Flood, Earthquake, Terrorism and other. The role Main duties and responsibilities include: * Managing, coordinating and participating in the technical development of the damage/ vulnerability component of the assigned projects, * Planning, managing and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:19:59">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949840722</link><title>Structural Engineer (NZ Experience)</title><description>A structural engineer either contract or permanent is sought to join this medium sized multi-disciplinary consultancy in central London for their buildings design division. The firm have close links with a prominent New Zealand firm and they have worked together on many projects both in the UK and NZ. Following the Christchurch earthquakes and the consequential assessment and assessment work...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:24:08">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949851805</link><title>New Zealand Ground Engineering opportunities</title><description>If you've been thinking about a move to New Zealand, now is the time to act with high demand for experienced Geotechnical Engineers and Engineering... projects to assessing earthquake damaged land and geohazards, to foundation design for building or bridge structures. It is essential that you have: * A relevant science or engineering degree ideally with a post-graduate qualification *...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:25:50">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949742116</link><title>Civil Engineering Safety Engineer</title><description>Role Overview The demand for AMEC's nuclear expertise continues to grow with the forecast in the UK nuclear industry being extremely strong and stable. Long... hazards such as earthquakes, impact and blast... including extreme weather, earthquakes, impacts and blast loads. · Finite Element Analysis Techniques used for analysis of structures against extreme static and dynamic loads. · Knowledge of applicable...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>