<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:41:37" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:41:38">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949824370</link><title>Yield Manager / Revenue &amp; Pricing Analyst (Travel) to £35K</title><description>Yield Manager / Revenue &amp; Pricing Analyst (Travel) to £35K Be part of Gold Medal Travel- a business that has been sending people on fantastic... Be part of Gold Medal Travel- a... enabling robust, insight-led pricing decisions. You will... and manual competitor price analysis across key... experts in making pricing decisions by analysing... manager in developing pricing systems. RESPONSIBILITIES: a)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:42:36">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949838723</link><title>Buyer - Top Housing Developer - Northampton</title><description>My client is one of the top, award-winning Housing Developers in the UK building quality residential properties throughout the United Kingdom. Due to internal progression... documentation -Analysing supplier pricing and nominating suppliers... was posted by Gold Group - one... Services advertised by Gold Group are those of an Agency and/or an Employment Business. Please be aware that we receive a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:45:43">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949854282</link><title>Senior Insight Analyst</title><description>Senior Insight Analyst An exciting and challenging opportunity to join us at Gocompare.com is now open. We are looking for a skilled Senior Insight Analyst... at the best price, and dedicated to... in People (IIP) 'Gold' award. IIP is an internationally recognised and respected mark of good practice, focused on leading, managing and developing people to improve business performance.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:48:29">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949828405</link><title>Web Analyst</title><description>Web Analyst An exciting and challenging opportunity to join us at Gocompare.com is now open. As the Web Analyst you will be responsible for supporting... at the best price, and dedicated to... in People (IIP) 'Gold' award. IIP is an internationally recognised and respected mark of good practice, focused on leading, managing and developing people to improve business performance.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:48:57">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949840985</link><title>EDM Practice Manager - up to £100K - London</title><description>The opportunity An Enterprise Document Management (EDM) Practice Lead is needed on a permanent basis, with strong strategic management and technology skills. You will join... within a fixed price consulting arrangement Man... also a Microsoft Gold Partner, with technical competencies in Collaboration and Content, so we know better than most where you're coming from. In fact, the system we use...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:49:26">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949864762</link><title>Estimator (Tarmac)</title><description>Estimator (Tarmac) Estimator required for Tarmac projects, 2 years minimum experience estimating asphalt and associated materials. Applicants will have previous knowledge of reading from design... accurate information on prices \- Follows up... was posted by Gold Group - one... Services advertised by Gold Group are those of an Agency and/or an Employment Business. Please be aware that we receive a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:50:34">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949865123</link><title>Junior Account Manager (BDM)</title><description>JUNIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER REQUIRED POSITION FUNCTION: To work within the Enterprise Sector of the business and targeted at increasing market opportunities and increase incremental revenue... with respect to pricing, products and procedures.... was posted by Gold Group - one... Services advertised by Gold Group are those of an Agency and/or an Employment Business. Please be aware that we receive a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:51:46">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949641007</link><title>Key Account Manager - London - Oncology/ Haematology</title><description>Key Account Manager -London Therapy Area - Oncology/Haematology Quintiles are seeking an experienced Key Account Manager, passionate about working in Oncology, to work in a... Investors in People Gold Standard Recruiter of... experience Market Access, Pricing &amp; Reimbursement exp ideal Previous formulary success Disease area expertise ideally Oncology / Haematology Can demonstrate competence &amp;quot;end to end&amp;quot; selling Strong organisational and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:54:22">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949829358</link><title>Internal Communications and Engagement Manager</title><description>Internal Communications and Engagement Manager Fixed Term Contract (9 months maternity cover) An exciting opportunity to join us at Gocompare.com is now open. We're looking... at the best price, and dedicated to... in People (IIP) 'Gold' award. IIP is an internationally recognised and respected mark of good practice, focused on leading, managing and developing people to improve business performance.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:56:58">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949877901</link><title>Office Manager/ Estimator</title><description>Office Manager/Estimator £18,000 - £23,000 basic plus benefits - to start immediately Some weekend work is expected. Based in Warrington, Cheshire Our client is an... a busy RHS Gold Medal winning landscaping... Whilst costing and pricing, the applicant must be able to find competitive quotes - via research and negotiating with suppliers. * You must be able to use your...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>