<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:00:36" name="Jobsite" id="FW14-e078"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e078-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:00:36">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949855687</link><title>Recruitment Consultant (Associate)-Hays- Ipswich</title><description>Associate Recruitment Consultant Be Part of the Magic of Recruitment Join us, the world's leading recruiting experts in qualified, professional and skilled work. We offer... of England, Hays UKI on chantelle.mcarthur-clarke@hays.com A career with Hays is more than a job. Learn more about our business by liking us on Facebook: https://[URL removed]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:02:34">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949826469</link><title>Business Development Manager</title><description>At Air Products we've been helping our customers to become more productive, energy efficient and sustainable for more than 70 years. With our atmospheric, process... parts of the UKI Central South Merchant Gases sales region. As the Business Development Manager, you will: - Produce new business signings and revenues from self generated prospects as well as following up on opportunities...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:04:51">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949816145</link><title>Health and Safety manager</title><description>Health &amp; Safety Manager Here at Amazon we are currently looking to hire an experienced Health &amp; Safety Manager to join the team and play... projects across all UKI operations sitesProviding authoritative advice and guidance on health &amp; safety matters to all stakeholders within designated area of responsibility.Reviewing and auditing arrangements for health &amp; safety management and continuously improving these...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e078-7503-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e078/7503_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:06:35">http://www.jobsite.co.uk/cgi-bin/job_basket.cgi?screen=add&amp;vac_ref=949783314</link><title>Business Analyst</title><description>Description We are the leading source of intelligent information for the world's businesses and professionals, providing customers with competitive advantage. Intelligent information is a unique... Business Unit: Legal UKI Our Legal organisation focuses on connecting our customers' businesses to the ever-changing legal and regulatory environment. We provide critical online and print information, decision support tools, software and services to lawyers...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>