<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:16:10" name="Meals.com" id="FW14-e139"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e139-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e139/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:16:11">http://www.meals.com/recipe/day-the-dead-bread-140629</link><title>Day of the Dead Bread</title><description>Dia de los Muertos, or Day of the Dead, is an ancient Aztec ritual celebrated in Mexico and certain parts of Central America and the U.S. On November 1 and 2, wooden skull masks are donned and people dance in honor of their deceased relatives. While holiday traditions vary from place to place, food always plays an important role. The sweet, rich, glazed egg bread, Pan de Muerto, is always served, though it, too, varies in shape and decoration from region to region. The most common shape is round decorated with small pieces of dough on top that represent bones and skulls. Loaves in the shapes of human beings and animals—particularly rabbits—are also popular. White, colored or powdered sugar is often sprinkled on top of the loaves for a festive touch.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e139/7489_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.meals.com/ImagesRecipes/140629lrg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e139-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e139/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:16:53">http://www.meals.com/recipe/la-lechera-day-the-dead-bread-145721</link><title>La Lechera Day of the Dead Bread</title><description>Dia de los Muertos, or Day of the Dead, is celebrated in Mexico and certain parts of Central America and the U.S. On November 1 and 2, people honor their deceased relatives with colorful masks, flowers and grave decorations. This yeasty, glazed egg bread, Pan de Muerto, is commonly round with pieces of dough on top representing bones and skulls. This recipe is simple and hearty, with only a small dusting of sugar. Enjoy alone or with a sweet dip.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e139/7489_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.meals.com/ImagesRecipes/145721lrg.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>