<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7004">z-machine</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:59:03" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:59:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16537068/strftime-z-localtime-is-not-working-as-expected-in-solaris-machines</link><title>Q: strftime '%z', (localtime) is not working as expected in solaris machines</title><description>I tried this code in linux machines, my $sysdate = strftime "%Y%m%d%T", (localtime); my $daylight_saving_time = strftime '%z', (localtime); i get below output, sysdate = 2013051402:12:02 … daylight_saving_time = -0400 I tried same in solaries machines, i got this sysdate = 2013051402:12:02 daylight_saving_time = %z Anyone know the change to be done to get the daylight saving in solaries machines. Thanks in Advance. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:01:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1218390/what-is-your-most-productive-shortcut-with-vim/1220118#1220118</link><title>A: What is your most productive shortcut with Vim?</title><description>the 'a' mark to the current location, and mz sets the 'z' mark. You can move to the line containing a mark using the ' (single quote) command. Thus 'a moves to the beginning of the line containing … the 'a' mark. You can move to the precise location of any mark using the ` (backquote) command. Thus `z will move directly to the exact location of the 'z' mark. Because these are "movements" they can …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:03:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11406372/rotate-in-z-axis-like-core-animation-slot-machine</link><title>Q: Rotate in z-axis like core-animation slot machine</title><description>finished){ NSLog(@"Done!"); }]; } But it only move the UIView up and down. How can I make it spin like a Slot machine but only contains one image … or view. Like rotate in z axis. But make it look like it contains more than one image. Thanks for the help. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:06:00">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4710829/dealing-with-writable-memory-in-haskell-implementation-of-infocoms-z-machine</link><title>Q: Dealing with Writable Memory in Haskell - Implementation of Infocom's Z-Machine VM</title><description>', 'A Mind Forever Voyaging', etc. These games were implemented on top of the "Z-Machine" virtual machine. The machine is implemented as a block of RAM, a stack and a virtual processor. The process … holistically the structure of the virtual machine) so that I can implement software to run these games? For example, should I use Data.Array to represent the RAM and the state monad? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:10:08">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21051319/is-there-a-reason-mailitem-display-methods-z-order-behaviour-varies-across-mach</link><title>Q: Is there a reason MailItem.Display method's z-order behaviour varies across machines?</title><description>We're finding that calling the myMailItem.Display(false) method works fine on our development machine, in that it opens the message window in the user's foreground. Whether or not we're running … within VS/with debugger attached or simply as an installed application. However on certain customers' machines the message opens behind our Winforms application. The version of Windows doesn't seem …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:12:08">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/750606/what-technologies-are-you-using-even-though-they-are-embarassingly-out-of-date/1334763#1334763</link><title>A: What technologies are you using even though they are embarassingly out of date?</title><description>The Z-machine. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:13:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/671683/i-want-to-port-the-frotz-z-machine-interpreter-to-the-amazon-kindle-is-this-eve</link><title>Q: I want to port the Frotz z-machine interpreter to the Amazon Kindle. Is this even possible? [closed]</title><description>I want to be able to play works of interactive fiction on an Amazon Kindle 2. In order to do this, I would need to port the Frotz interpreter to the Kindle. So far, I have not been able to find anywhe …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:18:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2660108/curious-could-llvm-be-used-for-infocom-z-machine-code-and-if-so-how-in-gener</link><title>Q: Curious: Could LLVM be used for Infocom z-machine code, and if so how? (in general)</title><description>Forgive me if this is a silly question, but I'm wondering if/how LLVM could be used to obtain a higher performance Z-Machine VM for interactive fiction. (If it could be used, I'm just looking … for some high-level ideas or suggestions, not a detailed solution.) It might seem odd to desire higher performance for a circa-1978 technology, but apparently Z-Machine games produced by the modern Inform 7 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:20:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/51054/batch-file-to-delete-files-older-than-n-days/51069#51069</link><title>A: Batch file to delete files older than N days</title><description>Enjoy: forfiles -p "C:\what\ever" -s -m *.* -d &lt;number of days&gt; -c "cmd /c del @path" See forfile documentation for more details. For more goodies refer to An A-Z Index of the Windows XP command … line If you don't have forfiles installed on your machine, copy it from any Windows 2003 Server to your Windows XP machine at %WinDir%\system32\ This is possible since the EXE is fully compatible …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7004-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7004_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:26:33">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1525933/examples-of-interpreters-embedded-in-iphone-applications/1540829#1540829</link><title>A: Examples of interpreters embedded in iPhone Applications?</title><description>iPhone Frotz is an interpreter for the Z-Machine and is open source. …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>