<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:29" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:29">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10668792/need-net-solution-to-detect-if-east-asian-languages-are-installed-in-windows</link><title>Q: Need .NET solution to detect if “East Asian languages” are installed in Windows XP</title><description>the languages...or I might decide to hide the Japanese, Korean, Chinese (Simplified) and Chinese (Traditional) culture/language choices. So...how can I detect if Windows XP has the necessary East Asian language files installed? I prefer a .NET solution, but I am willing to make API calls if necessary. JP … Environment - C#, .NET 4.0, WPF, VS2010 I have a simple Windows application that supports several cultures/languages. When users select Japanese, Korean, Chinese (Simplified), or Chinese …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:12:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9/how-do-i-calculate-someones-age-in-c/13733#13733</link><title>A: How do I calculate someone's age in C#?</title><description>I don't think any of the answers so far provide for cultures that calculate age differently. See, for example, East Asian Age Reckoning versus that in the West. Any real answer has to include localization. The Strategy Pattern would probably be in order in this example. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:13:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3529659/examples-of-icons-which-dont-travel-well/3563858#3563858</link><title>A: Examples of icons which don't travel well?</title><description>It is hard to enumerate all combination for all culture and all symbols. The more simple a symbol is, the more meaning it has. It has more than one meaning to even within one culture. For example … : +, it is a cross; it is a plus; it is a target; it is Christianity related. In East Asian, it is the symbol/character of ten. -, it is a hyphen; it is a minus; it crosses out something; it is a bar …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:16:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11424644/iphone-localizing-app-icon-still-not-supported/11440980#11440980</link><title>A: iPhone: Localizing app icon still not supported?</title><description>nasty thing in another. Even colours have different connotations in different cultures. An often cited example is the colour of mourning, which is black in the West and white in some Asian cultures. … valid to expect that icons should be localizable. After all, symbols can often be culture-specific... An extreme case would be a hand signal which could mean a friendly hello in one culture and an very …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:18:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7121020/resolve-the-font-really-used-for-rendering-in-silverlight/7129507#7129507</link><title>A: Resolve the font “really” used for rendering in Silverlight</title><description>Portable User Interface. For non-East Asian cultures, this value is an alias for the font family value (shown here as a string) of "Lucida Sans Unicode, Lucida Grande". Lucida Grande and Lucida Sans Unicode in turn are aliases for the same font and are specified as a pair for compatibility reasons. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:18:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8831006/is-there-a-unicode-font-for-windows-available-that-is-as-complete-as-arial-unico</link><title>Q: Is there a Unicode font for Windows available that is as complete as Arial Unicode MS, but f…</title><description>I have to distribute a legacy application for Windows that unfortunately does not support Font Linking, but is supposed to support many language cultures, including all east Asian languages …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:22:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1463178/can-aptitude-for-learning-programming-paradigms-be-influenced-by-culture-or-nati/1463257#1463257</link><title>A: Can aptitude for learning Programming paradigms be influenced by culture or native language'…</title><description>Disclaimer: I was a Cultural Anthropologist before I got into programming, so you know I'm going to be on a high horse, here. Obviously, a person's history will have an impact on their aptitude … for any particular task, but I think this has less to do with the structure or grammar of a person's language than it does with the particular material conditions of the culture in which that language …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:23:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7289974/best-practice-in-storing-users-real-name/7290017#7290017</link><title>A: best practice in storing user's real name</title><description>it for reference. If you don't need anything more than the full name, in the format the user provided, just store that. The structure of a full name is very culture dependent; what works Western names fails … for Asian names; generalizing western and eastern names still fails for Native American names. Some people change their legal name to one word. Some folks are very proud of the titles they have earned ("Doctor So and So", "Sir Elton John", etc.) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:27:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9014857/chinese-jianpu-notation-in-musicxml-any-example-files-or-notation-tools</link><title>Q: Chinese 'jianpu' notation in MusicXML: Any example files, or notation tools?</title><description>I'm doing background research for a project to write a software tool that converts between Western music notation, and Chinese numbered 'jianpu' notation, and South Asian 'swara' notation systems … . The use case is where a composer writes a score, in Western notation using tools like Finale or Sibelius or some such, which includes parts for Chinese or South Asian instruments. Currently …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:31:31">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9/how-do-i-calculate-someones-age-in-c/229#229</link><title>A: How do I calculate someone's age in C#?</title><description>: What about people from countries that do not use the gregorian calendar? DateTime.Now is in the server-specific culture i think. I have absolutely 0 knowledge about actually working with Asian calendars …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>