<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:19:13" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:19:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3596133/what-does-operator-do-in-matlab/3596145#3596145</link><title>A: What does '/ operator do in MATLAB?</title><description>' is the conjugate or Hermitian transpose. If you wish to do a normal transpose, use .' …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3596133/what-does-operator-do-in-matlab/3596158#3596158</link><title>A: What does '/ operator do in MATLAB?</title><description>As Brandon said, ' is the conjugate or Hermitian transpose (also known as linear algebraic transpose), and .' is the array transpose. For more information see MATLAB's Arithmetic Operators page. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8336404/the-complex-conjugate-transpose-in-mathematica/8336429#8336429</link><title>A: The complex conjugate transpose in Mathematica</title><description>[a] Output: {{3 + 2 I, 1 - I}, {2 - 5 I, 4 + 3 I}} {{3 - 2 I, 2 + 5 I}, {1 + I, 4 - 3 I}} You can also use the Hermitian conjugate symbol, which you use by entering esc hc esc or \\[HermitianConjugate]. … In your title you ask for conjugate transpose. That's just ConjugateTranspose. If you want the conjugate, it's just Conjugate. Input: a = {{3 + 2 I, 1 - I}, {2 - 5 I, 4 + 3 I}} ConjugateTranspose …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19360527/algorithm-for-fast-vector-vector-a-ah-multiplication</link><title>Q: Algorithm for fast vector-vector (a * a^H) multiplication?</title><description>The vector a containing complex numbers is of size N-by-1. The task is to find the matrix A (N-by-N) obtained by multiplication a * a^H, where H is the Hermitian operator (conjugate-transpose), so … that matrix A is Hermitian. Is there any algorithm to do this faster than O(N^2)? (except that only half the matrix can be computed). Can the divide and conquer approach be applied here somehow? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:31:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21552088/eigenvectors-in-numpy-very-bad-numerics-did-i-do-something-wrong/21552947#21552947</link><title>A: Eigenvectors in Numpy: Very bad numerics? Did I do something wrong?</title><description>the conjugate transpose of a. Obviously, in the example you have, A^H A != A A^H, so the matrix V is not unitary. Therefore, V.T.conj() is not related to the inverse of V. The most common case where this assumption is correct is for hermitian matrices. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:34:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11416152/confusions-about-multiplication-of-complex-value-in-matlab/11416502#11416502</link><title>A: Confusions about Multiplication of Complex Value in MatLab</title><description>The operator ' is the also called Complex conjugate transpose in Matlab ctranspose, which basically means that it applies conj and and transpose functions. Note that this operator is call Hermitian … operator in mathematics. What you actually want is the operator transpose that is shortcut as .' In order to get the expected output, and given that you just want to multiply without conjugating …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:38:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15587816/matlab-vectorize-the-transpose-in-one-step/15588004#15588004</link><title>A: Matlab: Vectorize the transpose in one step?</title><description>0.478595 0.772810 Beware that reshape reads the matrices accessing along columns so you may not need to transpose the matrix A. Also, remember that the operator ' is the hermitian operator … , namely, conjugated of the transposed, whereas .' is simply transposition, which you could also get by transpose(A). You may want to do everything in a single line without re-typing all every time. One …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:40:06">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/433831/help-me-understand-fft-function-matlab/434206#434206</link><title>A: Help me understand FFT function (Matlab)</title><description>to the frequency 0. The Fourier transform of real, discrete-time, periodic signals has also discrete domain, and it is periodic and Hermitian (see below). Hence, the transform for negative frequencies … is the conjugate of the corresponding samples for positive frequencies. For example, if you interpret (the periodic repetition of) y as a periodic real signal defined over Z (sampling period == 1 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:45:00">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19491936/complex-symmetric-matrices-in-python/19498549#19498549</link><title>A: Complex symmetric matrices in python</title><description>Here is some code for calculating a Takagi factorization. It uses the eigenvalue decomposition of a Hermitian matrix. It is not intended to be efficient, fault tolerant, numerically stable, nor … that it will always work. """ # Construct a Hermitian matrix. H = np.dot(A.T.conj(),A) # Calculate the eigenvalue decomposition of the Hermitian matrix. # The diagonal matrix in the Takagi …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7022-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7022_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:49:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14408873/how-to-do-in-place-cholesky-factorization-in-python/14468889#14468889</link><title>A: How to do in place Cholesky factorization in Python</title><description>the transpose to cholesky. I don't think the transpose fix will work if your matrix is complex-valued, since the transpose of a complex hermitian matrix is not generally equal to its conjugate transpose …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>