<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:28" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:29">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12969636/how-to-store-user-data-in-asp-net</link><title>Q: how to store user data in asp.net?</title><description>I'm developing an e-trade web application in ASP.NET. To buy anything,first, users have to login. Let's say user logged in and started to shop. When user taps to btnBuy, i'm adding this item … to a collection. Everything is working well so far. Suppose that user bought something,bought means here, i added item chosen to theBasket which contains all the items chosen,then closed the web browser …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:02:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/389671/user-interface-inspiration-for-iphone-apps/390041#390041</link><title>A: User Interface inspiration for iPhone Apps</title><description>Go to your local best buy, game stop, or any other store with xbox360s, wiis and playstation 3s lying around. Play every single demo on these machines and rate them solely on UI experience. Triple … A console games still lead the interface world in my opinion. Soft synths are a close second and also often have beautiful UIs (as Chris Schreiner pointed out). A quick trip through logic will give you a glimpse of apple's own work in that direction. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12132208/how-can-i-implement-user-to-user-chat-on-my-website-using-php</link><title>Q: How can I implement user to user chat on my website using php</title><description>in this table and gets deleted on logout. The problem with this is that if the user doesn't log out but just closes the browser, the username does not get deleted from the 'online' table. What is the best way … if the poster of that item is online and clicks chat to initiate a chat session. To track online users, I created a 'online' table in my database so that on login, the username is stored …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:09:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8486450/android-how-to-check-trial-period-of-application-is-expired</link><title>Q: Android, How to check trial period of application is expired?</title><description>. Based on the package that user choose, for example user has chosen 2 hours plan, server sends me Expire time and I store it in local database. The question is what is the best way to check that is trial … period expired? If user buy 2 hour plan at 12:00, therefore expire time will be at 14:00. I store 14:00 in database and each time application lunched, I check the data base. But the issue is if we …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9567743/merge-records-that-meet-a-particular-criteria-tsql</link><title>Q: Merge records that meet a particular criteria - TSQL</title><description>EUR Opening 1000 3 CCY INC EUR SEL 200 3 CCY INC EUR BUY -100 3 CCY INC EUR Closing 1100 So … Opening 1000 3 CCY INC EUR SEL 200 3 CCY INC EUR BUY -100 3 CCY INC EUR Closing 1100 However i can't think …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:11:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9445090/alarm-clock-app-in-ios/9621425#9621425</link><title>A: Alarm clock app in iOS</title><description>even when it is in the background or closed. This is not available to other apps built outside of Apple, so don't even try to compete with it. If you buy all Alarm clock apps in the App Store (aka … is in (active, background, or closed)" Your best bet to simulate a background alarm is to make use of UILocalNotification for 30 seconds. If you really want to wake up your heavy sleeper, schedule …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:15:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/385959/best-practice-for-converting-integer-value-column-to-string-representation/388006#388006</link><title>A: Best practice for converting integer value column to string representation</title><description>to keep setting "Buy" in the database.) So, if you store certain values in the database as integers, then at some point, you're going to need to show them to the user as strings, and I think … @HermanD: I think it's a lot better to store the values in an integer column rather than a string column for numerous reasons. It saves database space. Easier/faster to index on an integer than …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:17:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16461846/when-can-dependency-injection-containers-become-too-big-and-what-can-i-do-about/16627068#16627068</link><title>A: When can Dependency Injection Containers become too big, and what can I do about it?</title><description>Let's say that all of your classes are going to be called via the DI container. First a little comparative case: If you go to a store to buy a pair of trousers, then you are using DI at several … buy bread in a cloth store for instance. The questions must be related to the specific DI subject (interface). Pimple is an associative array. It is not a DI - container. As far as you know …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:18:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17086041/google-inapp-purchasing-and-trial-period/17088157#17088157</link><title>A: Google Inapp purchasing and trial period</title><description>/time against the stored value and if your trial period has elapsed, prompt them to buy the upgrade or close the app. … it free for another 7 days. The only way around this is to implement your own web registration service which I imagine would be a little too difficult. The best way, assuming you're not too bothered …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:18:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20206622/can-a-200gb-or-bigger-sql-server-database-load-into-a-pagefile-when-not-enough-m/20218706#20218706</link><title>A: Can a 200GB or bigger SQL Server database load into a pagefile when not enough memory is ava…</title><description>If you want the database to be stored in memory, you need to buy more memory. In spite of what the other answer suggests, memory is the absolute best and cheapest way to make a database perform … having the same page file on a spinny disk (or no page file at all), but I don't think that it's going to be anywhere near the impact of having real memory, or that it's going to come anywhere close …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>