<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:24:33" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:24:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15537158/r-spatstat-residual-analysis-for-thomas-cluster-processes</link><title>Q: R: spatstat: Residual analysis for Thomas cluster processes</title><description>I wish to test the fit of a homogeneous Thomas cluster process, ideally using residual plots like diagnose.ppm and qqplot.ppm. Since the most straightforward way to fit a Thomas cluster process … is using kppm, I can't use the above functions. Can anyone suggest ways to do this? e.g. transforming kppm to ppm or using ppm to fit a Thomas cluster process, Many thanks …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:26:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10774099/convert-thomas-j-bradley-signature-pad-json-to-png-using-c-sharp</link><title>Q: convert Thomas J Bradley Signature Pad JSON to PNG using C#</title><description>I am testing the Signature Pad plugin by Thomas J Bradley and have it working and am able to convert the JSON signature to PNG using PHP but would like to be able to convert the JSON signature to PNG …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:28:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10355828/does-thomas-mcdonald-bootstrap-sass-support-the-use-of-generators-getting-an</link><title>Q: Does thomas-mcdonald / bootstrap-sass support the use of generators? Getting an error saying…</title><description>A simple question. Does this version support generators? I wanted to test out using it and follow along with Ryan Bates screen cast which I uses a different version. I've been playing with tables …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:29:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1711/what-is-the-single-most-influential-book-every-programmer-should-read/1713#1713</link><title>A: What is the single most influential book every programmer should read?</title><description>(Poignant) Guide to Ruby The Inmates Are Running The Asylum: Why High Tech Products Drive Us Crazy and How to Restore the Sanity The Art of Unix Programming Test-Driven Development: By Example by Kent … Software, Guided by Tests Framework Design Guidelines by Brad Abrams Object Thinking by Dr. David West Advanced Programming in the UNIX Environment by W. Richard Stevens Hackers and Painters: Big Ideas from …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:35:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17199828/test-eventkit-calendar-access</link><title>Q: Test EventKit calendar access</title><description>I had to find out that my own app was never denied on my iPhone to get access to the calendar. But on all others I was missing the code for asking for permission. Now i included the appropriate code, but how can I be sure it works without submitting it to the App Store? Thanks, Thomas …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:39:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6536837/unix-find-opposite-of-newer-option-exists/10091187#10091187</link><title>A: UNIX find: opposite of -newer option exists?</title><description>Please note, that the negation of newer means "older or same timestamp": As you see in this example, the same file is also returned: thomas@vm1112:/home/thomas/tmp/ touch test thomas@vm1112:/home/thomas/tmp/ find ./ ! -newer test ./test …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:42:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15359342/boolean-test-returning-false-when-it-should-be-true</link><title>Q: Boolean test returning false when it should be true?</title><description>I am going through a list of questions on a past examination paper. One of the questions is of type boolean. It should return false if the name is not Thomas, and true if it is. Here is my code … : public class QuestionTwo { String name; public static void main(String [] args){ System.out.println(nameTest("Thomas")); } public static boolean nameTest(String name){ if(!name.equals …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:43:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15359342/boolean-test-returning-false-when-it-should-be-true/15359361#15359361</link><title>A: Boolean test returning false when it should be true?</title><description>remove the semicolon at the end of if statement. if(!name.equals("Thomas")) Also good practice is to do equals test this way: if(!"Thomas".equals(name)) In this case, if name is null you wouldn't get NPE. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:46:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4070338/should-i-commit-testsettings-and-vsdmi-files-to-the-repository/4070380#4070380</link><title>A: Should I commit .testsettings and .vsdmi files to the repository?</title><description>Absolutely. They contain test execution settings, test lists etc. As such, they are an integral part of your project, just like e.g. App.config. Thomas …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:05">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/322529/how-to-test-an-ajax-installation</link><title>Q: How to Test an AJAX Installation</title><description>Is there a simple and foolproof way we can test an AJAX installation? We have a problem in calling a webscript using AJAX form a JS file. The error is 'ServiceLib' is not defined. The error gets … a few hits on Google. We've added some AJAX functionality to a customer's app. This works fine here in the office on dev machines and on our IIS Server, it works fine on the customer's test web site …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>