<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:08" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/425143/are-mini-notebook-computers-usable-for-classroom-programming/425504#425504</link><title>A: Are mini Notebook computers usable for classroom programming?</title><description>I used a Sony VAIO SR-77 for about 2 years as my sole computer, and I was fine with it. That was a little one with a 10" screen, weighed less than 2lbs (IIRC) and had about a 6 hour battery life … -- over 6 years ago! I got it specifically because it was small enough for me to take to school with me everyday (first high school, then first year of college) Currently, I have a slightly larger Sony …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10656405/enable-vt-x-on-sony-vaio</link><title>Q: Enable vt-x on sony vaio</title><description>Hi I have a sony vaio VPCEB3E1E model and I want to run an virtual machine with Ubuntu server 11.10 64 bit. Oracle virtual box says that vt-x is not enabled. After a little search on internet … they suggested to enable hardware virtualization from bios. The problem is that in bios there are only a few properties I can change (sony had locked bios propably). Is there any way to enable vt-x or unlock bios on my laptop? Thanks. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22220432/activing-bluetooth-for-laptop</link><title>Q: activing bluetooth for laptop</title><description>I have a problem with bluetooth drive of my laptop ( Sony Vaio EH32 ) . It's like it doesn't have a bluetooth drive ! But it has ! How can I fix this problem ? Should I install a drive for blutooth ? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:34:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18353193/vaio-sve1513cynb-series-smart-network-driver</link><title>Q: vaio : SVE1513CYNB series Smart Network Driver</title><description>I have installed Win 7 32 bit OS on my Sony Vaio SVE1513CYNB series laptop. Due to some settings the wireless connection got turned off. Now I am not finding any way to turn it on. I tried … downloading a couple of Sony VAIO Smart Network driver but it just does not works properly on my system. The Network tool does not comes up properly. Please let me know how can I fix my issue - I am …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:36:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18275326/can-you-upgrade-the-hardware-of-a-windows-8-tablet-hybrid-yourself</link><title>Q: Can you upgrade the hardware of a Windows 8 tablet/hybrid yourself?</title><description>I have just bought a Windows 8 hybrid tablet - The sony vaio duo 11. But I got the slightly cheaper model with 4gb RAM and a 128gb SSD. I am wondering if it works like a normal laptop in that I can … take it apart and upgrade these components myself - or is it all locked down and can only be opened by the sony folks? And if I can upgrade the SSD, is it just a matter of installing the standard …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:40:36">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9220705/electronic-device-information-where-to-access-laptop-tv-camera-data</link><title>Q: Electronic Device Information - Where to access Laptop/TV/Camera data?</title><description>sources and cross-referencing the data. For example, were does Decide.com get its data? For example, for some of its products (http://www.decide.com/p/sony-vaio-vpc-z216gx-l-laptops-28056580) there are over 35 different specifications - how? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20727538/genymotion-player-exe-stoped-working/20985010#20985010</link><title>A: genymotion player.exe stoped working</title><description>I had the same problem, my laptop is a Sony Vaio VPCEB17FL runs over Win7x64, to solve it: Enable VT-x (Intel). Update your video drivers …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:45:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13852174/android-4-0-based-virtual-box-emulator-cant-detect-bluetooth-4-0-from-laptop</link><title>Q: Android 4.0 based Virtual Box emulator can't detect Bluetooth 4.0 from Laptop</title><description>was successfully detected Bluetooth 2.0 from Laptop using the same Android 4.0 VM, the problem is only for Bluetooth 4.0 . I am using Sony Vaio which contains Bluetooth 4.0. Kindly some one help me please. … android application on Virtual Box. The problem is Virtual Box can find Bluetooth 2.0 from my laptop. but when I try to use Bluetooth 4.0 , VM can't detect Bluetooth 4.0 . My Laptop have Bluetooth 4.0 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:48:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13145464/what-does-it-take-to-run-the-windows-phone-8-emulator/13263281#13263281</link><title>A: What does it take to run the Windows Phone 8 emulator?</title><description>Be sure to get a windows 8 PRo 64 bit operating system. I bought a sony VAIO laptop recently and It came preloaded with windows 8 basic OS. It costs me around 75$ for windows 8 to windows 8 pro …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7034-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7034_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:52:05">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21432594/error-code-0x80004005-for-bluetooth-microsoft-mouse-connection-windows-7-64</link><title>Q: Error code 0x80004005 for Bluetooth Microsoft Mouse connection Windows 7 64</title><description>I have a Microsoft Bluetooth Notebook Mouse 5000. It often works just fine but it also routinely loses its connection to the laptop. (Sony Vaio Windows 7 64. I try to reconnect the mouse through …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>