<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:20:35" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:20:35">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8751678/32bit-jvm-processbuilder-start-and-enomem/8751767#8751767</link><title>A: 32bit JVM, ProcessBuilder.start() and ENOMEM</title><description>I think that you are being bitten by Linux memory overcommits killing your processes. That blog post suggest a sysctl variable that you can tune. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:22:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10217719/call-a-function-many-times-in-parallel/10217783#10217783</link><title>A: call a function many times in parallel</title><description>of available CPU cores and then split the iterations among them. You can further tune the scheduling using the schedule clause. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:25:12">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11752544/redis-bgsave-failed-because-fork-cannot-allocate-memory</link><title>Q: redis bgsave failed because fork Cannot allocate memory</title><description>on write, it should not failed when there has 15G free memory,which is enough to malloc necessary kernel structures . besides, when redis-server used 42G memory, bgsave is ok and fork is ok too. Is there any vm parameter I can tune to make fork return success ? Thanks. … 31 -/+ buffers/cache: 49224 15209 Swap: 8197 184 8012 my redis-server has used 46G memory, there is almost 15G memory left free As my knowledge,fork is copy …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:28:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11662781/when-is-clone-and-fork-better-than-pthreads/11662922#11662922</link><title>A: When is clone() and fork better than pthreads?</title><description>clone(2) is a Linux specific syscall mostly used to implement threads (in particular, it is used for pthread_create). With various arguments, clone can also have a fork(2)-like behavior. Very few … -threads - and this is very tricky (in particular because locking may require using futex(2) syscall in machine-tuned assembly-coded routines). You don't want to use directly clone or futex because …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:29:08">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4862012/if-i-have-a-process-and-i-clone-it-is-the-pid-the-same/20822536#20822536</link><title>A: If I have a process, and I clone it, is the PID the same?</title><description>in UNIX was calling the system call fork(), like this: ret = fork(); if(ret &gt; 0) /* parent, continue waiting */ else /* child */ This scheme posed numerous problems. The user enters "Mike" but you … are created by fork(), each one receives a copy of the memory existing at that moment, and if that memory really changes later, the mapping that was identical for those memory segments will be chaged …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:30:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7546828/why-doesnt-child-process-continue-running-after-receiving-signal/7547134#7547134</link><title>A: Why doesn't child process continue running after receiving signal?</title><description>Here's what happens in the parent: Fork a child. Send SIGUSR1 to the child. Wait for a signal. Here's what happens in the child: Wait for a signal. Print Child. Call kill(0, SIGUSR1) (0 being … possible behaviors for your program, depending on the order in which the parent and the child system calls are executed. Depending on the exact version of your operating system, on the fine-tuning of various …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:31:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15966168/perl-module-instantiation-dbi-forks-mysql-server-has-gone-away</link><title>Q: Perl Module Instantiation + DBI + Forks “Mysql server has gone away”</title><description>is that I began to get "Mysql has gone away" errors while the parser was being run in forked mode, so after much fiddling I came up with the following mysql config: # # * Fine Tuning # key_buffer … I have written a perl program that parses records from csv into a db. The program worked fine but took a long time. So I decided to fork the main parsing process. After a bit of wrangling …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:33:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22940814/performace-tuning-php-calling-java-process</link><title>Q: Performace tuning PHP calling Java process</title><description>is not possible because the HTTP response contains the 'data' processed from the uploaded files text. I considered forking the process, but that doesn't help with the server load (will probably make …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:36:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5399030/clone-fork-process-creation-is-slow-on-some-machines</link><title>Q: clone()/fork()/process creation is slow on some machines</title><description>on the affected machines: int main() { int i; for (i=0;i&lt;10000;i++) { int p = fork(); if (!p) exit(0); waitpid(p); } return 0; } What could be causing task … for their workloads and don't go to swap. Edit3: I don't see anything suspicious in dmesg Edit4: I'm not sure why this is on stackoverflow now, I'm not asking about the example program above (just using it to demonstrate the problem), but linux administration/tuning, but if people think it belongs here, cool. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7046-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7046_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:38:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16406034/benchmarking-akka-with-the-matrix-vector-example/16418539#16418539</link><title>A: Benchmarking Akka with the Matrix Vector example</title><description>/scalability-of-fork-join-pool 2) Use executor = "fork-join-executor", and I recommend setting your parallelism-factor to between 0.6 and 1.0 you'll have to tune to see which one works best for your setup, you will also need to tune your matrix chunk size to be larger, experiment with this. … 1) You're configuring to use a thread-pool-executor but only provide configuration for a fork-join-executor. thread-pool-executor has horrible scalability, see: http://letitcrash.com/post/17607272336 …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>