<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:01:22" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:01:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23161998/web-developing-for-commission</link><title>Q: Web developing for commission? [on hold]</title><description>I am currently trying to decide between two internships. My major is computer science and my long term goal is to be a software developer/engineer. The first internship is an IT intern which is paid … . The second is a web developing intern for a company (still growing) that pays on commission. (They develop/design websites for clients) I feel like the web developing intern fits more of my goals …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:02:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3648896/what-is-map-in-web-computer-science</link><title>Q: What is MAP in web computer science?</title><description>I want to ask a question about the 'MAP' in Web technology. What is the meaning of the 'MAP', I only know this is related to the web 2.0 , but don't have any idea, can anyone help me or give me some …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:03:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3169850/computer-science-as-a-community-service</link><title>Q: computer science as a community service</title><description>I came across Ushahidi today and that got me thinking about various community service software projects. What other community service software projects are there, whether they be web-based …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:05:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1970994/exploring-mathematics-of-in-computer-science</link><title>Q: exploring mathematics of/in computer science [closed]</title><description>of steel should be used, but when a software developer deploys a web server application he just guesses on the estimated load on his server and leaves the rest on luck and god, there is nothing that he …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:08:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2988919/computer-science-taxonomy</link><title>Q: Computer Science taxonomy</title><description>Technology (or Web Programming, etc). So, that is why I need kind of taxonomy of computer science (right now, but probably I would need taxonomy of other fields also, like medicine, physics … I am developing web application where users have collection of tags. I need to create a suggestion list for users based on the similarity of their tags. For example, when a user logs …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:09:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15397225/accessing-isi-web-of-science-through-soap</link><title>Q: Accessing ISI Web of Science through SOAP</title><description>I'm trying to write a python script that retrieves information about publications from ISI Web of Science. I found domoritz's python script wos.py on GitHub. It uses Suds to connect to the ISI Web … of Science web service. I've imported it into my python script and I tried this code, following the very brief instructions in the comments: from wos import * soap = WokmwsSoapClient() results …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:11:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10741923/get-a-list-of-computer-science-edu-websites-using-google/10741996#10741996</link><title>A: Get a list of computer science.edu websites using google</title><description>You could try: site:.edu computer science Example: https://www.google.com/search?q=site:.edu%20computer%20science …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17616263/what-is-the-best-programming-language-to-build-small-web-applications</link><title>Q: What is the best programming language to build (small) web applications? [closed]</title><description>I am currently a computer science student who has no web development experience whatsoever. I would really like to gain some experience in this area of computer science to make myself more marketable … in the future; my university doesn't offer any web development courses, unfortunately. What are some of the best languages to use for developing a small personal finance web application …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:16:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2322109/eliminating-boilerplate-codes-for-web-applications-is-it-rocket-science</link><title>Q: Eliminating boilerplate codes for web applications. Is it rocket science?</title><description>that there is something wrong here? It doesnt look like a rocket science but we still have to write boilerplate codes. I have worked with a proprietary system which was quite good for doing web applications. We were just … to use. I dont really mean making fancy websites just making dammed web applications in a RAD way. Good IDE support for gui layout helps but not necessary xml will be fine. How do you feel about boilerplate web codes? Do you think making a RAD platform rocket science? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:18:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7462299/f-3-0-type-providers-for-science</link><title>Q: F# 3.0 Type Providers for science [closed]</title><description>are related to web \- is it the only real use of this feature? EDIT: There is a nice introduction of Type Providers together with information on when to use them and when not to use them here …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>