<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:03:01" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:03:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2671526/technologies-and-standards-in-a-kindle</link><title>Q: Technologies and standards in a Kindle</title><description>I'm using the Kindle as an example of an embedded system to illustrate some points I'm making in a paper. Since I'm not an expert in all the technologies used, can those aware of them point them out … . For example: the GUI is programmed in embedded Java (which is probably a bad choice) Whispernet is used for the wireless platform What are the libraries or underlying technologies …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:06:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21007829/meidarecorder-failing-on-kindle</link><title>Q: MeidaRecorder failing on kindle</title><description>I have been using the following code on all android devices for a while with no problem. I have since updated my Amazon code to match and their test have produced FAIL with the code. After testing …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:08:12">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7988699/breadcrumb-titlebar-in-kindle-book</link><title>Q: breadcrumb titlebar in Kindle book</title><description>. It is really cool and I would like to implement that in my books. I have proper TOC, cover and start page. I followed the guidelines in Kindle Publishing Guide. Actually, I am using KindleGen … Some books or periodicals from Amazon Kindle store have this cool feature that shows a breadcrumb or title bar when you read them. It shows up as the first line of the text. It is not the bar …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:08:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22135409/using-cookiemanager-in-kindle</link><title>Q: Using CookieManager in Kindle</title><description>to successfully use cookies in native code on some Android devices (Android 4.3 and 4.4) by using CookieManager. However, I got an empty cookie list on my Kindle 3rd generation (Android 4.2.2). What's the right way to share cookies between WebViews and native code when using Kindle devices? Thanks, … I'd like to use cookies set in WebView in native code. By following instructions described in here (http://blog.winfieldpeterson.com/2013/01/17/cookies-in-hybrid-android-apps/) I was able …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:11:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14953116/kindle-vs-android</link><title>Q: kindle vs android</title><description>I develop application for android and kindle. I want to use one layout for two devices, is that possible or I should provide layout for android and kindle separately? Сan I separate functional … implementation from ui, to avoid developing 2 projects at the same time?Does Kindle have some restrictions(sound, authorization, repository work) or it is of full value Android device? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:13:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13580466/webview-browser-in-kindle-fire</link><title>Q: Webview browser in Kindle Fire</title><description>Is the webview browser used in Kindle Fire the same as in ordinary Android webview? If not, what are the differences? Specifically, I'm interested in performance issues or quirks you have to be aware … of when adapting web apps for Kindle Fire. Amazon won't send any Kindle Fires to Sweden, so I can't test it myself - yet. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:16:26">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22433186/kindle-fire-emulator-not-starting</link><title>Q: Kindle Fire emulator not starting</title><description>I have installed everything that is required as per the amazon documentation for setting up the kindle fire emulator. When I try to run Kindle Fire HDX 8.9 with Android 4.2.2 and CPU ARM using …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:19:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8309624/detect-app-is-running-on-kindle-fire</link><title>Q: Detect app is running on Kindle Fire</title><description>Does anyone know how to detect if the app is running on Kindle Fire ? My app needs to turn off a few features if running on the Kindle Fire and I want to use the same build as Google Marketplace. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:23:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16787241/android-kindle-push-notification</link><title>Q: Android Kindle Push Notification</title><description>We wanted to build up own custom solution for sending push to Kindle Devices. we don't want to go with Urban airship, Parse and other solutions. Please give us some approach or idea with which we can implement it. Is there any open source code for the same? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:23:36">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12097757/developing-websites-for-kindle</link><title>Q: Developing websites for Kindle [closed]</title><description>website in your opinion? What is/are the screen resolution(s) and DPI I should design for? How do I detect Kindle (but not Kindle Fire) via JS/CSS media queries? What browser engine do they use? What … I've recently entertained the idea of designing and developing a special mobile version of my website for the experimental web browser in Amazon Kindle. Not Kindle Fire, but the e-Ink ones. However …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>