<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:57" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2233435/machine-learning-and-natural-language-processing/2233871#2233871</link><title>A: Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing</title><description>, vector spaces, and probability. Some recommended texts are: Daniel Jurafsky and James H. Martin. 2008. Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational … Linguistics and Speech Recognition. Second Edition. Prentice Hall. Christopher D. Manning and Hinrich Schütze. 1999. Foundations of Statistical Natural Language Processing. MIT Press. James Allen. 1995 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:29:26">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22943209/how-i-can-get-references-for-natural-language-processingnlp-and-named-entity-r/22960179#22960179</link><title>A: How I can get references for Natural Language processing(NLP) and Named Entity Recognition?</title><description>conference on Applied natural language processing (pp. 316-324). Association for Computational Linguistics. Tjong Kim Sang, E. F., &amp; De Meulder, F. (2003, May). Introduction to the CoNLL-2003 shared task … : Language-independent named entity recognition. In Proceedings of the seventh conference on Natural language learning at HLT-NAACL 2003-Volume 4 (pp. 142-147). Association for Computational Linguistics …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:31:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/573620/how-to-get-started-on-information-extraction/573737#573737</link><title>A: How to get started on Information Extraction?</title><description>Just to answer one of the comment. I am more interested in Text Information Extraction. Depending on the nature of your project, Natural language processing, and Computational linguistics … Programming Collective Intelligence (chapters on "searching, and ranking", Document filtering, and maybe decision trees). Suggested projects utilizing this knowledge: POS (part-of-speech) tagging, and named …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>