<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:38:38" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:38:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13854338/getting-current-directory-in-windows-ce-5-0-using-c-sharp-compact-2-0</link><title>Q: Getting current directory in Windows CE 5.0 using C# compact 2.0</title><description>" but my program is running from an SD Card. I copied the program to "Program Files" folder on device but it again gave me directory "\Windows". How do I get the current directory or more specifically how do I get SD Card/Flash Memory path? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:39:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10477392/write-once-read-many-memory</link><title>Q: Write once read many memory</title><description>i'm looking for a WORM memory with a fast and not serialized access (like CD or DVD). Do you know if exists this kind of memory such as USB memory or Compact Flash? Googeling i did not find anything … , there were some sandisk news about a SD Worm card but nothing in official web site. I need this for a cash register software log. Thank you. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:42:08">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17132967/can-you-compact-a-sqlite-database-on-the-fly-once-its-deployed-on-an-android</link><title>Q: Can you “compact” a SQLite database on-the-fly once it's deployed on an android device?</title><description>deployed on a device? And is it common practice, or wise, to do this frequently? I ask this because I don't know what sort of memory the internal memory of an Android device is - if it's flash memory … After creating my first SQLite database for use in an Android app I found that it seriously needed compacting after just a few 'drop table' operations etc. Then after reading some of the SQLite …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:44:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1840830/why-is-there-no-support-for-mdi-in-compact-framework/1841068#1841068</link><title>A: Why is there no support for MDI in Compact-Framework?</title><description>on a CF is smaller as the CF has limited resources such as memory, storage space (I will refuse to define this as disk space as the distinction on the CF is blurred - i.e. flash ram, sd cards, compact flash … cards and so on but no hard disk of any kind!) and limited no of connectivity (blue tooth and compact flash \- in my experience) and finally a much smaller screen with limited estate. Really …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:46:26">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6597020/efficient-writing-to-a-compact-flash-in-python/6598770#6598770</link><title>A: Efficient writing to a Compact Flash in python</title><description>Speed depending on buffer size is unrelated to the specific characteristics of compact flash, but inherent to all I/O with (relatively) slow devices, even to all kinds of system calls. You should … make the buffer size as large as possible without exhausting memory \- 2MiB should be enough for a Flash drive. You should use the time and strace utilities to determine why your program is slower …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:48:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3505859/customized-ui-windows-or-linux/3505955#3505955</link><title>A: Customized UI - Windows or Linux?</title><description>where all the code I created was the OS. It was not Win-Embedded and not a pink cell phone. If you have the storage (Compact Flash card, SD card, or just enough memory, etc) create and save all your UI …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:49:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/816993/handling-persistent-storage-and-cold-boots-with-ce-4-2</link><title>Q: handling persistent storage and cold boots with ce 4.2</title><description>from a compact flash card back into main memory. I do not know how to programaitcly access the CF card however so I am sort of stumped. There is also two apps from symbol that sound like they may help … morning and post whatever solution (if any) I come up with here as well. Any thoughts in the mean time? Thanks, Joe Update: I have ordered a CF card overnight for it and Motorola has opened up a case - I should have something more Tuesday. …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>