<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:21:08" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:21:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19814497/combine-or-construct-korean-letters</link><title>Q: Combine or construct korean letters</title><description>Is there anyway that I can combine this Korean consonants and vowels into a complete character. For example if I have ㄱㅏㅁㅅㅏㅎㅏㅂㄴㅣㄷㅏ It would be 감사합니다 Is there any way to do this? I can only … think of bruteforcing every case that would have to count many many cases. Below is my try. Not optimal and take too much time. if strings.Contains(input_str, "ㅏㄴㅈ") { input_str …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:23:00">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13827104/apple-script-save-korean-file-name-in-unicode</link><title>Q: Apple script - save Korean file name in unicode</title><description>I'm trying to save multiple excel files into .csv files. Also, I want to put the name of each excel file as a cell in each file. The problem is that my file name is in Korean and when I put the name … within a file, the letters are broken. A possible solution that I come up with is to convert the Korean file name as unicode but couldn't figure it how. The following is the code that I use. Thanks …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:24:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4730659/regex-to-count-english-words-as-single-char-inside-char-count-of-asian-words</link><title>Q: regex to count english words as single char inside char count of asian words</title><description>need some help from a regex jedi master: If I have a string of mb chars (specifically, Japanese, Korean or Chinese) with English words sprinkled throughout, I would like to count: asian characters … , etc. chars. I am searching for a regex pattern I can use to count these strings, that will function in php and js. Example: これは猫です、けどKittyも大丈夫。 should count as 13 chars. thanks for your help! jeff …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4730659/regex-to-count-english-words-as-single-char-inside-char-count-of-asian-words/4730800#4730800</link><title>A: regex to count english words as single char inside char count of asian words</title><description>What ever you are trying to achieve, this will help you: To count only Hiragana+Katakana+Kanji (Japanese) Chars (excluding punctuation marks): var x = "これは猫です、けどKittyも大丈夫。"; x.match(/[ぁ-ゖァ-ヺー一-龯々 … ]/g).length; //Result: 12 : これは猫ですけども大丈夫 Updated: To count only words in Alphabet: x.match(/\w+/g).length; //Result: 1 : "Kitty" All in one line (as function): function myCount(str) { return …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:29:56">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5177536/count-the-number-of-words-in-nsstring/5269733#5269733</link><title>A: Count the number of words in NSString</title><description>of characters for those languages.. Check around with Chinese/Japanese native speakers and see what they think. If I were to do it, I would tokenize the string with spaces and particles (at least for japanese, korean) and count tokens. Not sure about chinese.. … it? In that sense, there's probably 3 words in "sekai no aidia" (or 2 if you don't count particles like NO/GA/DE/WA, etc). Same as english - "world's idea" is two words, while "idea of world" is 3 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:30:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5177536/count-the-number-of-words-in-nsstring/5248451#5248451</link><title>A: Count the number of words in NSString</title><description>with -[NSString length] method. I'm a Korean speaker, (so maybe out of your case :) and in many cases we count characters instead of words. In fact, I never saw people counting words in my whole life. I … for each culture. For Japanese, you need Japanese culture specialist. However, I don't think Japanese people needs word count feature seriously, because as I heard, the concept of word itself is not so …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:34:00">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17521769/mysql-length-for-different-languages-returns-different-size</link><title>Q: mysql Length() for different languages returns different size</title><description>select length('abcdefg') english, length('가나다라마바사') korean from dual This returns below. english korean 7 21 Is there any function returning the count of character not character bytes? I mean what I need is english korean 7 7 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15976178/word-count-not-accurate-after-removing-string-with-wildcard</link><title>Q: Word Count not accurate after removing string with wildcard</title><description>I have a file written for translation in Korean that has some of the words already written in English in parentheses. I did a find (*) and then replace was left empty. Now when I check the word … , it said it removed 170 words in parenthesis but the total word count of the file shows a difference of only 20, which is impossible, I counted with my own eyes and there are really 170 words less. What am I doing wrong? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:40:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10479752/why-does-the-like-count-in-my-page-rollback</link><title>Q: Why does the 'like' count in my page rollback?</title><description>/quotations/79 (note: this page is in Korean) Click Like Notice the like count increments Refresh your browsers Notice that after step #4 the count is rolled back? The like is posted to my Facebook wall … I'm attempting to implement facebook "likes" and having a bit of trouble. The count keeps rolling back after a page refresh. Steps to reproduce Navigate to http://bookmill.co.kr/books/9 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:42:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2935544/a-php-library-class-to-count-words-in-various-languages</link><title>Q: A PHP Library / Class to Count Words in Various Languages?</title><description>aware that the latter count is much easier, but very much prefer the former, if at all possible. I'd love it if I just had to look at English, but I need to consider every language here, Chinese, Korean … Some time in the near future I will need to implement a cross-language word count, or if that is not possible, a cross-language character count. By word count I mean an accurate count of the words …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>