<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:30:29" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:30:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/487258/plain-english-explanation-of-big-o/487278#487278</link><title>A: Plain English explanation of Big O</title><description>to 1 or more other towns by a road of a certain distance. The Travelling Salesman problem is to find the shortest tour that visits every town. Sounds simple? Think again. If you have 3 towns A, B … of an algorithm The Telephone Book The next best example I can think of is the telephone book, normally called the White Pages or similar but it'll vary from country to country. But I'm talking about …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:31:12">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21711412/find-the-largest-interval-of-non-intersecting-roads</link><title>Q: Find the largest interval of non intersecting roads</title><description>This is a problem I'm stuck trying to solve. Assume you have 2 major roads A and B that run parallel to each other. Now we have a set of roads R, that all have one endpoint on A and the other … and recursively call the function again. But I'm not sure how this works. And I'm not sure if its O(n log n) For q2 i have no idea. I have a feeling this can be done by dynamic programming and I'm missing some sort of data structure with which I could solve this easily. Please help. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:34:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21720017/i-would-like-a-few-pointers-for-a-program-im-trying-to-create-in-python-3-3-3</link><title>Q: I would like a few pointers for a program I'm trying to create in Python 3.3.3</title><description>So far, I've had a few bumps in the road, but I've been able to correct them, though my programming is quite sloppy as I've just started Python. The idea is to create a dice game called "Pig … :",pot1) (pot1) =+ die (R,r,H,h) is raw_input ("(R)oll again or (H)old?") if input is(R,r) (roll_again) is 1 else input is (H,h) (roll_again) is 0 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:38:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9406317/android-sqlite-query-return-0-rows-without-reload</link><title>Q: Android: SQLite Query Return 0 Rows Without Reload?</title><description>My application has a SQLite database to contain a list of highways. It shows them all in a list. It first tries to query the database for the roads. If the query doesn't return any, it calls … another method that downloads a list from a remote server, and populates the database. After that returns, it immediately queries the database again. That's how it should work. How it actually works …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:40:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20455918/algorithm-for-connecting-set-of-points</link><title>Q: Algorithm for connecting set of points?</title><description>indirectly through another point) - and the total length of the lines is minimal. For example, suppose these are towns in a desert and we are constructing a road network. We want to use the minimum … amount of materials to construct the roads but still have every town reachable by road. For N = 2 the solution is of course simply a line segment between the two points: +------------------+ For N …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:42:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12277645/how-do-i-obtain-the-coordinates-along-gmaps-directions</link><title>Q: How do I obtain the coordinates along GMaps directions?</title><description>the coordinates that will make a track along a road look exactly as if I'm using snapping/directions even when I'm not. I've tried tools such as QLandkarte GT and Viking, and with the latter I was able … such tracks, but for starters: it would look much neater if I could edit the readings so that they are right on top any roads in Google Maps. How can I achieve this? EDIT: I want to find …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:44:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/653063/upload-progress-using-pure-php-ajax</link><title>Q: Upload progress using pure PHP/AJAX?</title><description>I'm sure this has been asked before, but as I can't seem to find a good answer, here I am, asking... again. :) Is there any way, using only a mixture of HTML, JavaScript/AJAX, and PHP, to report … the actual progress of a file upload? In reply to anyone suggesting SWFUpload or similar: I know all about it. Been down that road. I'm looking for a 100% pure solution (and yes, I know I probably won't get it). …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:46:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22385863/actionscript3-saving-objects-created-when-application-is-running/22402747#22402747</link><title>A: ActionScript3 - Saving objects created when application is running</title><description>: Save ByteArray to UTF8 external file; then read it back to ByteArray, and you're on the road again if you need to trace them out, Base64 encode them (simple but powerful class here: https://gist.github.com/burakkirkil/4051420) … The standard trace panel in flash is text based, therefore no bytes can be output properly (ByteArray). I'm not pretty sure what are the types of objects you need to store, but you can do two things …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:48:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6019185/how-to-create-a-query-to-get-all-records-from-one-table-and-fill-in-field-inform</link><title>Q: How to create a query to get all records from one table and fill in field information from a…</title><description>Road") This gets around the odd bug/error I'm getting with the query since it puts it into a table and doesn't deal with the query directly again. I would however love to know what is causing the problems I'm having. … query that will include all of the ids from prem, and all of the records from the JimsQueryByColl where JimsQueryByColl.Collector = "Frederick Road". The current query I have is as follows but only …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:52:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8277117/3d-cad-to-opengl/8277190#8277190</link><title>A: 3D CAD to OpenGL</title><description>This is gonna be a bit of a downer, but DWG file formats explore a deep dark road I'm not sure even AutoDesk has control over. The format doesn't even belong to them (they bought it a while ago … ) and even if you could manage it, the format is updated every 3 years or so (and is set to update again soon). For now, they have all the power. Sorry. All I can say, is explore the references and take a look here (no code, sorry) …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>