<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:10:07" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:10:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/739654/how-can-i-make-a-chain-of-function-decorators-in-python/1594484#1594484</link><title>A: How can I make a chain of function decorators in Python?</title><description>, it was after listening a guy saying: "before understanding recursion, you must first understand recursion". But now, don't you feel good about mastering this? Best practices: decorators Decorators … "): return word.capitalize()+"!" def whisper(word="yes") : return word.lower()+"..."; # Then we return one of them if kind == "shout": # We don't use "()", we …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:13:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19849962/jcombobox-item-listener-selected-item</link><title>Q: JComboBox Item Listener Selected Item</title><description>I am creating a combo box and it keeps giving me an error with the item listener that I don't understand. If you could also explain your answer that would be nice. Thanks in advance: Here's … it is on the .getSelectedItem()... lines. It only gives me the error when I run the program and select a word in the box. Thanks! Here's the error in the run (line 61 is the .getSelectedItem()... line …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:16:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18091717/constantly-on-speech-recognition-listening-for-just-one-keyword</link><title>Q: Constantly-on speech recognition listening for just one keyword</title><description>and recognizing every single said word and listening for the keyword. Let's say the keyword is "cheese" in this instance. Whenever you say "cheese," the application fires an intent that starts up … I have tried to code this with Android's included android.speech.SpeechRecognizer class with no success. Basically, what I am trying to do is making my app constantly listen for one keyword …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:20:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17599648/making-the-phone-constantly-listen-for-voice-input</link><title>Q: Making the Phone Constantly Listen for Voice Input</title><description>is visible on the device's screen. Very much like the already-existent feature of the samsung galaxy s3, with which you can say "unlock" if the phone is in lock state and the phone will unlock. I don't … I am creating a personal assistant application and I want it to turn on its voice recognition system (e.g. google voice keyboard) whenever a certain set of words is spoken, when the application …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:21:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11653509/i-have-text-to-speech-that-says-the-button-text-but-all-buttons-speak-the-first</link><title>Q: I have text to speech that says the button text but all buttons speak the first button's text</title><description>. Obviously this is a problem because you don't want every button saying the same thing. It registers no errors in my LogCat so it works fine, just not the way I want it to. I don't have the java … I just completed the coding to have the text to speech button read the text on the button the user pressed.For some reason every button says the text on the first button instead of their own text …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:24:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22659395/speechrecognitionservice-with-word-recognition</link><title>Q: SpeechRecognitionService with word recognition</title><description>The title it's not clear i think. In my project i want a service that runs in background and when the user says "hello phone" or some word/phrase my app starts to recognize the voice. Actually … ". Too many bips!! It's frustrating.. I only want that it starts when i say "hello phone" or "start" or a specific word!! I try to look at this https://github.com/gast-lib/gast-lib/blob/master/library …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:25:02">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13746894/newly-appended-objects-dont-respond-to-jquery-events-from-page-load</link><title>Q: Newly appended objects don't respond to jQuery events from page load</title><description>to the jQuery events I declared on pageload. (Sorry for the layman language here - often I am a newbie at proper wording) For example, let's say I declare in a js file loaded on pageload: $('.element … functions. Then, I load new elements and append them to the page using Backbone, AJAX, or whichever asynchronous call you like. This works great, except the new objects don't seem to be linked …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:25:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15282137/kinect-speech-recognition-and-skeleton-tracking-dont-work-together</link><title>Q: Kinect speech recognition and skeleton tracking don't work together</title><description>the same thing as saying the word "Travel" out loud). Because of that, I don't want any of the input managers to know about each other. Specifically, I don't want the Kinect manager (as much … of things like inverting the skeleton stream and audio stream, capturing the audio stream in different ways, etc. I finally narrowed down the problem: something about how I'm initializing my modules does …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:28:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20048603/naivebayes-using-a-word-matrix-and-3-classes-for-prediction</link><title>Q: naiveBayes using a word matrix and 3+ classes for prediction</title><description>am getting: require(RTextTools) require(useful) script &lt;\- data.frame(lines=c("Rufus, Brint, and Meekus were like brothers to me. And when I say brother, I don't mean, like, an actual brother, but I … !","Obey my dog!", "I hear words like beauty and handsomness and incredibly chiseled features and for me that's like a vanity of self absorption that I try to steer clear …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:31:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2557207/selectively-replacing-words-outside-of-tags-using-regular-expressions-in-php</link><title>Q: Selectively replacing words outside of tags using regular expressions in PHP?</title><description>sets of rhyming words so that they can say them and hear them. The students will also participate in a variety of rhyming word activities. In order to demonstrate mastery the students will listen … to [three]sets of words[/three] and tell the teacher if the words rhyme or not. If you notice there are many occurances of the word 'words'. I want to replace all the occurances that don't occur inside any …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>