<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:20" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3930098/easy-code-sample-for-formula-for-simulating-deceleration-of-a-rotating-sphere-du/3930448#3930448</link><title>A: Easy code sample for formula for simulating deceleration of a rotating sphere due to frictio…</title><description>). On this page you'll find some examples to use the mass moment of inertia to calculate deceleration of the sphere as a result of the applied negative torque. This toqrue is a result of the friction … It has been some time ago, but according to my dynamics study books the Mass Moment of Inertia for a sphere is defined as I=(2/5)m*r^2. m is the mass, r is the radius of the sphere (all in SI untis …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:51:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14448308/problems-with-inertina-when-add-force-in-2d-physic/14449284#14449284</link><title>A: Problems with Inertina when add force in 2d physic</title><description>shape is 2 spheres, one at (0,10) and one at (0,-10), both of mass 5, then the center of gravity is at C = (5*(0,10)+5*(0,-10))/(5+5) = (0,0) and the moment of inertia is I = 5*10*10 + 5*(-10)*(-10 … shape is 2 spheres, one at (0,10) with mass 5, and one at (0,-10) with mass 10, then the center of gravity is at C = (5*(0,10)+10*(0,-10))/(5+10) = (0,-10/3) and the moment of inertia is I = 5*(40/3 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:54:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14448308/problems-with-inertina-when-add-force-in-2d-physic</link><title>Q: Problems with Inertina when add force in 2d physic</title><description>box2d use a simple version of the inertia because is quicker to compute and the result are good enough ? Or does the calculation of Box2d is correct, and I miss something when I read the code ? Thanks a lot ^^, Marius. … I try to make a very simple 2d physic functions to solve rigidBody with with sphere particles as colliders, I have so a rigidBody and particle class : function _rigidBody …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:55:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1665375/3d-globe-rotation-issues</link><title>Q: 3D globe rotation issues</title><description>Im trying to get my 3D sphere to rotate when a user moves their mouse/finger over the sphere. I can get it to rotate no problems, but when I try to add inertia to the sphere using … the Affine2DInertiaProcessor in the Surface SDK, I get jumping issues when I quickly flick the sphere, and I dont know why... Here is my initialisation code: private void InitializeManipulationProcessor …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>