<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:22:03" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:22:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10630241/radio-button-setid-store-and-able-to-get-between-different-activity</link><title>Q: Radio button setId store and able to get between different Activity</title><description>it and is it able to store and get in different Activity because i want set them as the answer of the MCQ or survey! Thank a lot int id[] = new int[10]; RadioGroup AnswerRG = (RadioGroup) findViewById … i start learning android programming. I create some radio button and at in the radio group. I search in this website, other programme said i can set the id to the radio button. How can i get …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:26:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13005887/ror-wufoo-forms</link><title>Q: RoR: Wufoo forms</title><description>don't show the same survey to a user twice.. from all i could learn from the api, wufoo can't tell you this, so the only choice you have is to create your own form on your platform and using the wufoo … precise information, let's suppose we are using wufoo to make surveys, we want our users to answer to each survey only once.. we need something like the user_id or any identifying information so we …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:30:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22791821/the-program-cannot-run-properly-dialog/22792152#22792152</link><title>A: the program cannot run properly (dialog)</title><description>that this is happening because the onCreate method isn't showing the layout yet. You can learn more about the Activity life cycle here: Android Developer: Activity. Also, try posting the Logcat with your questions … Sorry, I can't comment yet. I don't have 50 reputation points yet. Anyway, try putting the "new AlertDialog.Builder..." snippet on the onResume method of the activity. I would bet …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:31:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12767394/matrix-factorization-for-collaborative-filtering-new-users-and-items/12828587#12828587</link><title>A: Matrix factorization for collaborative filtering - new users and items?</title><description>description, categories) attributes active learning: showing new items to all users interacting with the system, or certain items to new users of the system, in a way balancing individual user experience … for dealing with new users and items (no matter whether we use matrix factorization or something else): estimating user/item features from user (demographics, surveys) or item (price, genre, textual …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:34:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2352616/agile-development/2353840#2353840</link><title>A: Agile development</title><description>Some Recent Empirical Data About Practices in Use in Industry: I just came across the Agile Practices Survey Results: July 2009. It's a fairly small sample set (123), but it offers some interesting … Refactoring Retrospectives Pair Programming Active Stakeholder Participation Potentially Shippable Software Burndown Tracking There are also charts for top 10 agile practices that: are believed …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:37:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8754967/python-getting-a-certain-no-of-strings-from-a-dictionary</link><title>Q: Python: getting a certain no. of strings from a dictionary</title><description>of help would be more than welcome...thank you all. [[' I. Antonov', ' I. Antonova', ' E. R. Kandel', ' and R. D. Hawkins. Activity-dependent presynaptic facilitation and hebbian ltp are both required … ', ' Learning internal representations by error propagation', ' Parallel distributed processing: explorations in the microstructure of cognition', ' vol. 1: foundations', ' MIT Press', ' Cambridge …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:38:35">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22306386/jquery-validator-only-validates-most-recent-dom-element</link><title>Q: jQuery Validator only validates most recent DOM element [duplicate]</title><description>to validate the survey before it is submitted; however, the plugin only validates the account most recently added to the form. How do I get the plugin to validate the entire form? What I Have Learned: I am … I am trying to create a survey that employees can fill out after completing a phone call that will be used to track what products or services were sold during the interaction. The form can have …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:40:35">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16535151/fixed-sidebar-in-bootstrap-that-starts-at-a-certain-position</link><title>Q: Fixed sidebar in bootstrap that starts at a certain position</title><description>="active item"&gt;&lt;img src="img/carousel/photo1.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="item"&gt;&lt;img src="img/carousel/photo2.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="item"&gt;&lt;img src="img/carousel/photo3.jpg"&gt;&lt;/div … -large"&gt;Learn More&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;h2 align="center" id="scrollhere"&gt;Professional Web Design&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h3 align="center"&gt;Powerful. Professional. Affordable&lt;/h3 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:42:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7848384/trouble-parsing-an-xml-string-should-be-simple</link><title>Q: Trouble parsing an XML string. Should be simple</title><description>&gt;&lt;item&gt;&lt;title&gt;&lt;![CDATA[Peer Assisted Learning (PAL) pilot kicks off at the University of Bath!]]&gt;&lt;/title&gt;&lt;link&gt;&lt;![CDATA[http://www.bathstudent.com/news/article/6003/3532/]]&gt;&lt;/link&gt;&lt;pubDate&gt;Tue, 04 Oct 2011 … 09:58:00 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;&lt;description&gt;&lt;![CDATA[\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nPeer Assisted Learning (PAL) allows more advanced students to give less advanced peers extra help in adjusting to university life …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:44:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18750392/html-table-stretching-in-outlook/18751423#18751423</link><title>A: HTML Table Stretching in Outlook</title><description>African finalists to compete against international winners – PR activities tbc. o Completion of CSR marketing brochure.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;w/o September 30th 2013 &lt;br /&gt; \- &lt;/strong&gt;Press release … to breach R20bn a year for the next 10 years, according to a 2012 Joburg Centre for Software Engineering ICT skills survey. Companies surveyed said a lack of skills was having an adverse effect …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>