<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:52:57" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:52:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5391797/edit-fan-page-icon</link><title>Q: Edit Fan Page Icon</title><description>I am need to add facebook fan page icon image by myself uploading some image for that icon. Is it possible. Is is possible to add using Facebook API? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:54:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19545961/blue-facebook-icon-use</link><title>Q: Blue Facebook Icon Use [closed]</title><description>I want to put the blue Facebook icon on my webpage that when clicked will take the patron to my Facebook page. Is this no longer an option? I've seen this on other sites, but can't seem to find the code for it anywhere via Facebook. Any solutions? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:56:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21705720/how-to-change-facebook-app-icon</link><title>Q: How to change facebook app icon</title><description>I can't seem to find the right location of the settings since facebook redesigned admin panel ... screenshots appreciated , I can only change screenshots and banners but not the app icon itself thanks …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:58:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21252790/new-facebook-developers-interface-1024x1024-app-icon</link><title>Q: New Facebook Developers interface: 1024x1024 App Icon</title><description>Facebook recently changed the interface on https://developers.facebook.com/ . Previously, when you edited an App there, you were able to set a 16x16 icon, a 75x75 icon for the app (and some other … , that icon is still used. And I am guessing that the large 1024x1024 image is also used in the "App Store" of Facebook. But can anyone tell me where else exactly this 1024x1024 image is used …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:01:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14051364/edit-an-existing-app-detail-page-icon-or-image</link><title>Q: Edit an existing app detail page icon or image?</title><description>How do you change an app detail image or icon? There is no delete or upload button once you already have uploaded an image to the app detail page(unsbumitted state). There is no way to remove it or change it so you are stuck with it? help?! Tried in safari and chrome...no luck. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21630216/facebook-how-to-integrate-app-icon-in-a-page</link><title>Q: Facebook: how to integrate app icon in a page?</title><description>In the following screenshot I've borded the various apps, integrated in the facebook page, in red. How do you do something similar? I think facebook calls them "pagelet_timeline_app_nav_app" …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:03:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6138780/facebook-share-button-and-custom-text/6138879#6138879</link><title>A: Facebook share button and custom text</title><description>]=YOUR_IMAGE_TO_SHARE_OBJECT" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;img width="14" height="14" src="'icons/fb.gif" alt="Facebook" /&gt; Facebook &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; … We use something like this [use in one line]: &lt;a title="send to Facebook" href="http://www.facebook.com/sharer.php?s=100&amp;p[title]=YOUR_TITLE&amp;p[summary]=YOUR_SUMMARY&amp;p[url]=YOUR_URL&amp;p[images][0 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:04:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9727761/how-to-link-to-external-website-from-the-app-icons-below-the-timeline-on-faceboo</link><title>Q: How to link to external website from the app icons below the Timeline on Facebook?</title><description>How do you make those icon apps below your timeline so that when you click on one of them it opens a new window (or the same window) and goes to an external website? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:07:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21532044/facebook-page-tab-thumb-icon-not-showing-for-non-admins</link><title>Q: Facebook page tab thumb icon not showing for non-admins</title><description>I've made loads of page tabs, but since the changes to the developer center in December I'm having an issue where non-admins can't see the thumbnail icon for the newly created page tab. Weirdly … they can in fact see the page tab if they go to the direct URL, they just don't get any icons linking to the tab. Only admins get them. The slider in the "status &amp; review" section for making the tab live is set to "yes." I no longer see a "sandbox mode" option, I assumed this is the new sandbox mode. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:09:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5550587/how-to-change-facebook-fanpage-tab-icon-via-api</link><title>Q: How to change Facebook FanPage “Tab” Icon via Api</title><description>I know i can have iframe tabs which in fact are apps. And for apps i can set icons. But, imagine i have a app which is used by many fan pages to make it easier to integrate content. There must … be some dirty trick to set these icons based on the fan-page the app is included. For example http://blog.tabsite.com/post/376/Customize-Your-Fan-Page-Icon-with-TabSite makes exactly that. Any idea on this ? …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>