<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:18:40" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:18:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3499538/code-golf-conways-game-of-life</link><title>Q: Code Golf: Conway's Game of Life [closed]</title><description>The Challenge: Write the shortest program that implements John H. Conway's Game of Life cellular automaton. [link] EDIT: After about a week of competition, I have selected a victor: pdehaan … , for managing to beat the Matlab solution by one character with perl. For those who haven't heard of Game of Life, you take a grid (ideally infinite) of square cells. Cells can be alive (filled) or dead …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:20:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4586814/code-golf-countdown-number-game</link><title>Q: Code Golf: Countdown Number Game</title><description>Challenge Here is the task, inspired by the well-known British TV game show Countdown. The challenge should be pretty clear even without any knowledge of the game, but feel free to ask … for clarifications. And if you fancy seeing a clip of this game in action, check out this YouTube clip. It features the wonderful late Richard Whitely in 1997. You are given 6 numbers, chosen at random from …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:22:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2508441/simulate-golf-game-strategy</link><title>Q: Simulate Golf Game Strategy</title><description>I am working on what at best could be considered a "primitive" golf game, where after a certain bit of randomness is introduced I need to play out a hole of golf. The hole is static and I am …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10051169/game-state-tree-for-golf-solitaire</link><title>Q: Game State Tree for Golf Solitaire</title><description>I am working on a homework project in which we need to generate a state tree for the game of Golf Solitaire. To do this I decided to create a Move class which represents a move from one stack … unfamiliar with the game: Golf Solitaire Rules. Note - We did not need to implement the restriction on playing a Queen after a King. public void makeTree() { _root = makeNode( null, null, 0 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:27:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1582359/code-golf-reversi</link><title>Q: Code Golf: Reversi</title><description>OK, here's a rather elaborate code golf challenge: Implement a game of Reversi (Othello). The game should display the current state of the game-board and allow players at a single computer … to alternately input moves. Incorrect input and disallowed moves must be caught, but can be ignored silently. The game must end when no more moves can be made (either because the board is full or because …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:28:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15132771/how-to-build-a-a-simple-html5-golf-game</link><title>Q: How to build a a simple HTML5 golf game?</title><description>I would like to do a simple HTML5 golf game. And I found this, http://www.html5canvastutorials.com/labs/html5-canvas-interactive-ball-physics/ I've change the gravity to 0 and it works perfect …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:32:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/72383/whats-the-point-of-perl-golf</link><title>Q: What's the point of Perl golf? [closed]</title><description>Perl golf is a programmers' game which involves solving a problem with the shortest perl program possible. (ie, the winner is the person who completes the round in the lowest number of (key)strokes). What is the point of Perl golf? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18816655/what-is-wrong-with-this-simple-golf-game-java-code</link><title>Q: What is wrong with this simple Golf Game Java code?</title><description>I'm lost. In my Java 1 class I'm supposed to debug this simple code and fix it. It's a simple Golf Game. I know this question is basically asking you guys too do my homework, but I want help getting … this file. */ public class GolfGameTest { public static void main(String[] args) { System.out.println("Golf Game Calculator"); GolfGame golfGame = new GolfGame(); golfGame.getTotalScore(); } } …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:34:12">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4347718/code-golf-towers-of-hanoi</link><title>Q: Code Golf: Towers of Hanoi</title><description>is on the bottom, and the smallest on the top an empty rod an empty rod The GOAL of the game is to move the original "stack" of disks on another rod, that is - put all of the disks on another rod, so …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:35:52">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5281031/code-golf-snake-folding</link><title>Q: Code Golf: Snake Folding [closed]</title><description>consists of segments each segment can rotate 90 degrees (picture the game snake), or go straight, the challenge is not colliding with other parts of the snake. Example: Input: 10 Output: 300 The input …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>