<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7145">why do cats purr</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:20:42" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7145-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7145_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:20:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14183625/designing-dtos-and-do-service-layer</link><title>Q: Designing DTO's and DO service layer</title><description>{get; set;} void Run(){...} void Purr() {...} } Methods and some properties are only needed for server actions. That's why I designed another, data transfer object for this cat type … ); } When the mapper is translating the DTO object back to DO it will have to hit the DB in order to fill the missing properties of the Cat object (blood type, etc') Needles to say this action is absurd …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7145-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7145_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:22:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1082453/question-about-java-polymorphism-and-casting/1082486#1082486</link><title>A: Question about Java polymorphism and casting</title><description>be a Cat with properties unique to it (purring, rigorous regime of self-cleaning, etc.). If the cast is not possible then a ClassCastException is thrown at runtime. Nobody wants a dog that purrs. ((M … to be taken for a walk, and all the cats need to be played with using a bird-shaped toy. To do this we call the takeForWalk() method that only exists on Dog, or the play() method which only exists on Cat …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7145-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7145_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:24:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19073066/javascript-function-scope-and-finding-properties-of-a-parent-object/19073221#19073221</link><title>A: Javascript function scope and finding properties of a parent object</title><description>")); animals.push(new dog("bowser")); animals.push(new cat("purr")); You can then have code that operates on the contents of the animals array without regard for what kind of animal it is. So … is window and won't do what you want. The issue in your design is that a Writers object doesn't know anything about an Owner object, thus is can't have methods that report the size of the Owner …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7145-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7145_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:25:52">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20903519/return-bad-json-including-object-proto-from-javascriptcalling-api</link><title>Q: Return bad json including object(__proto__) from javascript(calling API)</title><description>&amp;mdash;the universal patterns that explain why we behave the way we do. Are you a Rebel, Artist, Visionary, Healer, Saboteur, Storyteller, Victim, Warrior? This book reveals all!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;9\. &lt;a href="http … the answers in your archetypes—the universal patterns that explain why we behave the way we do. Are you a Rebel, Artist, Visionary, Healer, Saboteur, Storyteller, Victim, Warrior? This book reveals …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>