<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:27:17" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:27:18">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19072830/vim-automatically-leave-insert-mode-after-some-time</link><title>Q: Vim: Automatically leave insert mode after some time</title><description>I am using this snippet in MacVim, and it doesn't work. When I enter Insert mode, and I don't do anything, Vim leaves insert mode after 15 seconds. However, if I press Enter or Backspace, or if I … I want to make Vim leave Insert mode automagically after some time (15 seconds). Here is what I've got in my .vimrc: " set 'updatetime' to 15 seconds when in insert mode au InsertEnter * let …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:28:37">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3288893/why-do-we-have-closures-in-javascript</link><title>Q: Why do we have closures in JavaScript?</title><description>, or a closure is a stack-frame which is not deallocated when the function returns. Am starting to understand this concept, but the more i understand the more i keep on wondering why do we have to use … them. An example like this one makes me understand the concept but leaves me asking, there is a simpler way of doing this! function sayHello(name) { var text = 'Hello ' + name; var sayAlert …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:29:56">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21670459/why-is-fi-1-i-1-undefined-behavior</link><title>Q: Why is f(i = -1, i = -1) undefined behavior?</title><description>of attention, I will summarize the main points/answers. First, allow me a small digression to point out that "why" can have closely related yet subtly different meanings, namely "for what cause … ", "for what reason", and "for what purpose". I will group the answers by which of those meanings of "why" they addressed. for what cause The main answer here comes from Paul Draper, with Martin J …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:32:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6513585/javascript-or-expression-in-a-switch-case/6514571#6514571</link><title>A: JavaScript or-expression in a switch case</title><description>Since the other answers explained how to do it without actually explaining why it works: When the switch executes, it finds the first matching case statement and then executes each line of code … the way you expected. For that reason some people like to put a comment in to say "fall through" to make it clear when break statements have been omitted on purpose. I do that in the following example …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:33:06">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3133449/why-does-git-rebase-give-me-merge-conflicts-when-all-im-doing-is-squashing-comm</link><title>Q: Why does git-rebase give me merge conflicts when all I'm doing is squashing commits?</title><description>the sed script against it to make sure it was doing what I wanted it to do (it was). Again, I don't even know why there would be a conflict, so it wouldn't seem to matter so much which strategy is used … message file else # Use our pre-canned message echo "Created two line file" &gt; $1 fi P.S.: Yes, I know some of you cringe when you see me using emacs as a fall-back editor. P.P.S.: We do know we'll …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:33:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7448468/why-cant-i-reliably-capture-a-mouseout-event</link><title>Q: Why can't I reliably capture a mouseout event?</title><description>question... Why can't the browser can't reliably capture the mouseout event? If I can reliably tell when the mouse has left the div using the above workaround, why can't the browser do it? I … I need to know when the mouse cursor leaves a div. So I hook up the mouseout event. However, if I move the mouse very quickly out of the div, the mouseout event doesn't fire. That's right: the mouse …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:36:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4674560/why-does-this-perl-produce-not-a-code-reference</link><title>Q: Why does this Perl produce “Not a CODE reference?”</title><description>I need to remove a method from the Perl symbol table at runtime. I attempted to do this using undef &amp;Square::area, which does delete the function but leaves some traces behind. Specifically, when … $square-&gt;area() is called, Perl complains that it is "Not a CODE reference" instead of "Undefined subroutine &amp;Square::area called" which is what I expect. You might ask, "Why does it matter? You …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:37:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1595611/how-to-properly-create-a-custom-object-in-javascript/1598077#1598077</link><title>A: How to “properly” create a custom object in JavaScript?</title><description>arguments to be passed in, in which case x and y become undefined and are assigned to the prototype's this.x and this.y. If the constructor function were doing anything more complicated, it would fall flat … a mishmash of metaclasses, all behaving slightly differently. What's worse, most JavaScript tutorial material is terrible and serves up some kind of in-between compromise to cover all bases, leaving …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:40:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12773749/why-wont-repaint-always-call-paintcomponent-and-why-it-doesnt-always-behave</link><title>Q: Why won't repaint() always call paintComponent and why it doesn't always behave properly whe…</title><description>the transformation, my paintComponent method seems to only clear the row, but leave everything displayed above as it was before the repaint() call. The new piece will fall through the phantom blocks and land … invisible blocks and phantom blocks. So, my second question is, why is paintComponent() behaving in this way. Obviously I need to do a good bit of reading on Repaintmanager and Java painting in general …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:42:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/109141/how-do-you-manage-a-large-product-backlog</link><title>Q: How do you manage a large product backlog? [closed]</title><description>We have a large backlog of things we should do in our software, in a lot of different categories, for example: New problem areas for our products to solve New functionality supporting existing … that falls to Product Management, but it is tricky for a lot of reasons. Firstly, we have a number of different systems that hold the different things (market requirements document in files, bugs …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>