<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:36:11" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:36:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15983956/pig-order-command-fails</link><title>Q: Pig ORDER command fails</title><description>, count and percentage. The program fails at last line when tries to order according to most used. Could someone help? logs = LOAD '$LOGS' USING ApacheCombinedLogLoader AS (remoteHost, hyphen, user, time … :15,286 [main] WARN org.apache.pig.backend.hadoop.executionengine.mapReduceLayer.MapReduceLauncher - Ooops! Some job has failed! Specify -stop_on_failure if you want Pig to stop immediately on failure …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:39:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17978144/extracting-non-matching-records-between-files-in-pig-latin</link><title>Q: extracting non-matching records between files in Pig Latin</title><description>I am beginner, learning Pig latin. Need to extract the records from the file. Have created two files T1 and T2, Some tuples are common to both the files, So need to extract the tuples present only in T1 and need to omit the common tuples between T1 &amp; T2. Can someone please help me... Thanks …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:44:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23038927/how-to-find-last-7-days-records-using-pig-latin</link><title>Q: How to find last 7 days records using pig latin?</title><description>I am a beginner to Pig latin. I have a requirement to find the last 7 days records from the csv with contains last 4 years of data. Can anyone help me to understand this. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:45:02">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10306899/pig-latin-translator-javascript</link><title>Q: Pig Latin Translator - JavaScript</title><description>So for my cit class I have to write a pig Latin converter program and I'm really confused on how to use arrays and strings together. The rules for the conversion are simple, you just move the first … letter of the word to the back and then add ay. ex: hell in English would be ellhay in pig Latin I have this so far: &lt;form name="form"&gt; &lt;p&gt;English word/sentence:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="text" id="english …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:48:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16687450/apache-pig-how-to-get-number-of-matching-elements-between-multiple-bags</link><title>Q: Apache Pig - How to get number of matching elements between multiple bags?</title><description>I'm a new user of Apache Pig and I have a problem to solve. I'm trying to make a little search engine with apache pig. The idea is simple: I have a file, which is the concatenation of multiple … : ({(word2), (word7), (word5)}) Now, here is my problem: i would like to get the number of matches betwen the query and each document. With this example, I would like to have this output: 1 2 1 I tried to make a JOIN between the bags but it didn't worked. Could you help me please ? Thank you. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:49:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15400008/python-pig-latin-converter</link><title>Q: python pig latin converter</title><description>Please help me! I am converting a text file with multiple lines to pig latin. Example: the Pig Latin translation of: This is an example. should be: Histay siay naay xampleeay. I need any … punctuation to be left where it should be (end of the sentence in most cases) I also need any word that starts with a capital letter in the original to start with a capital letter in the pig latin version …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:50:05">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22862683/converting-a-sentence-to-pig-latin</link><title>Q: Converting a sentence to pig latin?</title><description>I'm trying to convert a sentence to pig latin but I can;t get it to work. Conditions: 1\. If it starts with a vowel, add way to the word (e.g eagle become eagleway) 2\. If it starts with a consonant … part 2. I don't understand how to go through the chars and strip the whole part. Any help is appreciated. Thanks. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:50:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22778531/python-pig-latin-function</link><title>Q: Python: Pig Latin Function</title><description>I'm stuck on a really hard question for my class in which I need to create a Pig Latin converter in Python for a given string. Basically, here are the rules. For any word that begins with one … )): if i[j] in vowels: print(j) break def igpay(astring): vowelfinder(astring) for i in alist Any advice is helpful …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:52:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23095064/pig-latin-translator-consonants</link><title>Q: Pig Latin translator, consonants</title><description>Ok so I got a small code on trying to convert english into Pig Latin, I got the vowels working but the consonants are more difficult, based on what i have i can only remove the first consonant, So … the word "what" is translated into "hatway" instead of "atwhway" please help, I'm still new to VB this is what i have Public Const Vowels As String = "aeiou" Public Const Consonant As String …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:56:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23015725/percentile-calculation-in-pig-latin</link><title>Q: Percentile calculation in Pig Latin</title><description>I'm trying to calculate percentile using Pig. I need to group data using an attribute and calculate percentiles for each tuple in the group based on sales. I've seen there is no built in Pig function to do this. Wondering if anyone faced similar problem before can help me. …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>