<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:12:41" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:12:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1402675/compiling-external-c-library-octave-for-iphone-fortran-compiler-missing/1404014#1404014</link><title>A: Compiling external C++ library (Octave) for iPhone (Fortran compiler missing?)</title><description>. You could configure and build gfortran, but it's going to be a PITA. You'll likely need to merge in changes from Apple's customized GCC 4.2 fork found under iPhone here with a recipe for building it for Darwin, such as this. You might try f2c as the Octave project suggests. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7166-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7166_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:13:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14883383/testing-linq-queries-ef-and-the-repository-pattern</link><title>Q: Testing Linq Queries EF and the Repository Pattern</title><description>to change the query logic in the actual repository - that sounds like a PITA and recipe for problems. I would like to keep the query in one method and test that method. It later occurred to me, I …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7166-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7166_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:16:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2766306/core-data-json-touchjson-on-iphone/2767712#2767712</link><title>A: Core Data - JSON (TouchJSON) on iPhone</title><description>this loop in my book in the Multi-threading chapter in the section on exporting recipes. Update NSDate That sounds like a bug in the JSON parser that you are using as it should be able to handle … dates. However your workaround is viable except you need to convert it on both sides which is a PITA. I would look into your parser and see why it is not translating dates correctly as that is a pretty big omission. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7166-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7166_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:18:37">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21733148/swapping-a-child-template-within-a-modal</link><title>Q: Swapping a child template within a modal</title><description>I am building an ember app that features an analysis pane displayed as a modal. We have used the modal recipe from the cookbook. The analysis pane has a table of contents on the left, and a space … . This is inefficient and makes saving state a hugh PITA Using a template/View/Controller for the detail pane that encapsulates all of the available table of contents options. This is the only thing I've got …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7166-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7166_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:22:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16137401/adding-a-fade-transition-to-onclick-thumbnails</link><title>Q: Adding a Fade Transition to OnClick Thumbnails</title><description>/big/pita-2.jpg')"&gt; &lt;img src="img/thumbnails/pumpernickel.jpg" alt="Rollover image" height="80" onClick="switchImage(5, 'img/big/pumpernickel-2.jpg')"&gt; &lt;img src="img/thumbnails/seeded.jpg … anyway!"; break; case 2: header = "Caraway Rye"; paragraph = "Indulge in the best Ruben you’ve ever had with an all time Wildpatch favourite. Using an old family recipe …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>