<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:29:05" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:29:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8067880/whats-the-pro-and-cons-of-fabric-against-ant</link><title>Q: What's the pro and cons of fabric against ant? [closed]</title><description>I have been using ant to make a build tool for website deployment. I use Ant to glue different tools such as less-compiler, YUI-compressor, Google Closure Compiler and JSlint together. However, one … drawback for Ant is that the xml build file and task dependency is not quite human-readable and makes the update task a pain. I stumbled on Fabric today and found the way it organizes tasks clear …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:31:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4955686/shell-scripting-vs-programming-language/4955849#4955849</link><title>A: Shell scripting vs programming language</title><description>Shell script is the most intuitive way to have a "glue" on your system. However, it does not have some useful concepts, like inheritance and modularization, that languages like Python (which is very … used to "glue" systems too) have. True, the use of language depends basically on the task you are trying to do. For the most cases I've worked, shell script worked well, although I'm using a lot …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:33:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/241007/possible-to-integrate-google-appengine-and-google-code-for-continuous-integratio/242262#242262</link><title>A: Possible to integrate Google AppEngine and Google Code for continuous integration?</title><description>You'd probably have to have some glue on another computer which monitored SVN commits and deployed a new version for you. Google Code has yet to develop and release an API (which they need to do soon … , however, will vary with each project, so that's something you need to sort out yourself (you might wanna take a look at the fabric deployment system). Then, just set a cron job going which updates a local SVN checkout on the middle machine, and you're done. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:34:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14695292/scaling-out-windows-services/14696366#14696366</link><title>A: Scaling out Windows Services</title><description>platform-specific offerings such as Azure Service Bus and Amazon SQS. ~ NServiceBus MSMQ @ MSDN RabbitMQ ZeroMQ Azure Service Bus @ MSDN Amazon SQS @ Amazon AWS ~ Note that the service bus is just the glue … to distribute your work. I don't personally have any experience with it, so there's not much I can say for it other than it has good monitoring support out-of-the-box. ~ How to: Host a Workflow Service with Windows App Fabric @ MSDN …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:36:31">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18417178/languages-that-dont-have-the-single-classpath-issue-in-java/18420414#18420414</link><title>A: Languages that don't have the single classpath issue in Java</title><description>, among which your desired multiple 'class spaces'. OSGi provides the fabric for modular applications, that is applications build out of cohesive and minimally coupled components. You have chosen … . Unfortunately, the current state of the art is that we have a lot of developers in Java who have grown up believing class loading hacks are how you glue open source projects together. The good news …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>