<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:42:41" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:42:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19767269/entity-framework-code-based-migration-not-working-after-upgrade-from-ef-4-3-to-e</link><title>Q: Entity Framework Code Based Migration not working after upgrade from EF 4.3 to EF 6</title><description>by the Entity Framework team we are now planning an upgrade to EF6 and .NET 4.5 After amending a couple of using clauses (due to the namespaces changes in the latest releases) everything seems … with the code based migration. My code based migration configuration is the following: internal sealed class Configuration : DbMigrationsConfiguration&lt;Context&gt; { public Configuration …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:47:02">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4685793/symptoms-and-alternatives-to-overused-oop/4686412#4686412</link><title>A: Symptoms and alternatives to overused OOP</title><description>a case where sealed was used inappropriately. Also missing in C++, but with obscure ways to get that working. But yes, the WPF object model sucks fairly heavy. Inheriting 6 levels deep and using backdoors like a dependency property is offensive. Inheritance is hard, let's go shopping. … the visibility to a module. That concept is completely absent in C++, the build model just doesn't support it. Otherwise a great concept, "I only trust the members of my team to get it right". Of course you …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:50:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12378220/api-design-and-security-why-hide-internal-ids/12382871#12382871</link><title>A: API design and security: Why hide internal ids?</title><description>be predetermined or guessed? Everybody with opposable thumbs will be replaying sessions in web apps. And many more that I'm sure other ppl here will come up with. SEAL team 6 doesn't necessarily mean … there are 6 seal teams. Just keeps the enemy guessing. And the time spent guessing by a potential attacker is more money in your pocket any way you slice it. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14149654/my-hashtable-is-reversing-its-outputs</link><title>Q: My HashTable is reversing its outputs</title><description>11th attacks, was killed by Seal Team 6 in Pakistan.") Console.WriteLine("Please input the year of your birth.") Dim x As Integer Dim Y As Integer Try x = Console.ReadLine …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:55:12">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15310843/j2me-jar-manifest-jad-file-and-nokia-publish-qa-failure</link><title>Q: j2me JAR Manifest, JAD File and Nokia Publish QA failure</title><description>Recently I've developed some application which is simple Weider 6 excersises browser. I've created manually JAD file with elements from JAR manifest, however my application was revoked by Nokia … Publish QA team with following reason: Dear publisher, While processing your content we found the following MIDlet-attributes are not present in the JAD and JAR manifest files: Key 'MicroEdition-Profile …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:57:37">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14998286/how-to-replace-a-string-in-php</link><title>Q: How to replace a string in PHP?</title><description>://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/";a:1:{s:7:"creator";a:1:{i:0;a:5:{s:4:"data";s:11:"Mike Little";s:7:"attribs";a:0:{}s:8:"xml_base";s:0:"";s:17:"xml_base_explicit";b:0;s:8:"xml_lang";s:0:"";}}}}}i:49;a:6:{s:4 … : Cliff Seal: Content Strategy – No one cares about your content (yet.)";s:7:"attribs";a:0:{}s:8:"xml_base";s:0:"";s:17:"xml_base_explicit";b:0;s:8:"xml_lang";s:0:"";}}s:4:"guid";a:1:{i:0;a:5:{s:4:"data";s …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:59:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20268172/resign-ios-app-from-a-distribution-identity-to-a-developer-identity</link><title>Q: Resign iOS App from a distribution identity to a developer identity</title><description>signed with a developer certificate, I want/need (Q.A. team wants actually) to resign the previous created .ipa with developer certificates. I use the following commands to resign the app : unzip … works on iOS devices running on iOS 6.x but fails with the previous error on iOS 7.x only (I tried 2 iOS 6.x devices, iPhone 4S and 5, and also I tried with 4 devices running iOS 7.x). So the problem …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:03:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22987936/c-sharp-xdocument-get-all-images-from-xml-and-show-them-in-longlistselector</link><title>Q: C# XDocument get all images from XML and show them in LongListSelector</title><description>in the South China Sea. All contact with the team is lost when the North Korean Government quickly seals off the area. The United States responds by dispatching an elite team of Delta Force Operators … tactics and total customization of weapons and armor to survive in dynamic, hostile environments including Zero-G. Earth, 2019. A team of US scientists makes a frightening discovery on an island …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:04:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22958906/c-sharp-xdocument-get-a-attribute-from-a-specific-element</link><title>Q: C# XDocument get a attribute from a specific element</title><description>is lost when the North Korean Government quickly seals off the area. The United States responds by dispatching an elite team of Delta Force Operators to recon the situation. As tension rises between … and armor to survive in dynamic, hostile environments including Zero-G. Earth, 2019. A team of US scientists makes a frightening discovery on an island in the South China Sea. All contact with the team …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:08:33">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/23091394/c-sharp-binding-images-from-xml-to-longlistselector</link><title>Q: C# Binding images from XML to LongListSelector</title><description>with the team is lost when the North Korean Government quickly seals off the area. The United States responds by dispatching an elite team of Delta Force Operators to recon the situation. As tension … of weapons and armor to survive in dynamic, hostile environments including Zero-G. Earth, 2019. A team of US scientists makes a frightening discovery on an island in the South China Sea. All contact …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>