<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:12:29" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:12:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7888944/scala-punctuation-aka-symbols-and-operators</link><title>Q: Scala punctuation (AKA symbols and operators)</title><description>that outlines all the insane shortcuts that Scala seems to have in an easy way. Can you point me to, or better yet write, such a guide? Just a comment, document, HTML page or blog post with a list of punctuation and the thing it does. In particular, I'm confused about: -&gt; ||= ++= &lt;= _._ :: :+= … I'm reading some Scala code, trying to learn the language and understand the code itself, and I keep coming across some unintelligible punctuation that does stuff. The problem is that it's pretty …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:13:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6970843/compress-guids-by-hashing-in-small-data-sets/6978136#6978136</link><title>A: Compress Guids by hashing in small data sets</title><description>You can convert hex (base16) to base64, and remove all the punctuation. You should save 25% for using base64, and another 4 bytes for punctuation. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:15:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/804456/are-guids-good-passwords/804685#804685</link><title>A: Are GUIDs good passwords?</title><description>I think what you actually want is a cryptographically-random number, not a GUID. GUIDs and UUIDs are not random -- as JohnFx said, they tend to incorporate discoverable values like the MAC address … random syllables to create pronounceable nonsense words; intersperse some digits and punctuation, and you've got a good password. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:16:33">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18354477/guidattribute-progid-what-are-they-for/18355096#18355096</link><title>A: GuidAttribute &amp; ProgId, what are they for?</title><description>ProgID however, as ProgIDs are limited to 39 characters and can contain no punctuation other than a period. In such case, a ProgID can be manually assigned to the class using ProgIdAttribute. The reason not listed here is that manually assigning it makes it consistent across builds. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:18:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2734398/lucene-analyzer-to-use-with-special-characters-and-punctuation</link><title>Q: Lucene Analyzer to Use With Special Characters and Punctuation?</title><description>I have a Lucene index that has several documents in it. Each document has multiple fields such as: Id Project Name Description The Id field will be a unique identifier such as a GUID, Project …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:22:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5354342/how-do-i-sql-query-for-words-with-punctuation-in-postgresql</link><title>Q: How do I SQL query for words with punctuation in Postgresql?</title><description>If I have strings/phrases like this stored in the database: What are Q-type Operations? Programmer's Guide A.B.C's of Coding Is there a way to pass a query parameter in like "Programmers" or "abc" or "q-type" and have it find "Programmer's", "A.B.C" and "Q-type"? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:24:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16843539/marklogic-xquery-searchsearch-term-option/16844531#16844531</link><title>A: Marklogic Xquery search:search term-option</title><description>://docs.marklogic.com/guide/search-dev/count_estimate to understand index lookups. Adding punctuation automatically makes that term punctuation-sensitive: http://docs.marklogic.com/cts:word-query explains … Word indexes are not punctuation-sensitive, because words are not punctuation. I recommend reading http://developer.marklogic.com/try/ninja/page8 to understand the various query options and http …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:27:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8768667/can-you-show-me-some-example-for-the-keymap-js-the-definitive-guide</link><title>Q: can you show me some example for the Keymap.js,(The Definitive Guide)?</title><description>:"R", 83:"S", 84:"T", 85:"U", 86:"V", 87:"W", 88:"X", 89:"Y", 90:"Z", // Keypad numbers and punctuation keys. (Opera does not support these.) 96:"0",97:"1",98:"2",99:"3",100:"4",101:"5 … ", // Punctuation keys that don't require holding down Shift // Hyphen is nonportable: FF returns same code as Subtract 59:";", 61:"=", 186:";", 187:"=", // Firefox and Opera return 59,61 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:31:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1853305/comma-separated-thousand-nsstring-stringwithformat/1853313#1853313</link><title>A: comma separated thousand NSString stringWithFormat</title><description>with different punctuation &amp; formatting). In particular, check out the number formatting guide linked to at the top of the class documentation …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7211-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7211_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:33:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21357295/javascript-regex-cant-match-ellipsis</link><title>Q: Javascript Regex can't match ellipsis</title><description>the characters). Problem is, it does not work with ellipsis "..." and I guess neither it does with other unconventional forms of punctuation. How can I fix my REGEX to match this and other forms of punctuation? Is there any noob friendly example driven guide to REGEX out there? …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>