<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:33:13" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:33:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1557163/flight-simulation-physics</link><title>Q: Flight Simulation Physics</title><description>Can anyone recommend a tutorial/guide for developing a simplistic flight simulator engine? I want to create a simple flight sim engine for the fun of it. Language of choice...Actionscript 3 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:35:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3763953/flight-simulator-with-an-api</link><title>Q: Flight Simulator with an API</title><description>I would like to experiment with various control algorithms, currently I use FlightGear and connect over telnet but when it is running it is making my compter crawl. What I was wondering is are there any flight simulators that would allow me to plug my AI that are not as resource hungry? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:38:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14337661/need-flight-simulation-library</link><title>Q: need flight simulation library [closed]</title><description>I want to fly an aircraft with a joystick control. What i want is some open source flight simulation library that will do the mathematics/physics and produce a position value, i.e., given an initial …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:42:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/662851/reading-data-from-flight-simulator</link><title>Q: Reading data from Flight Simulator</title><description>I'm looking at building some hardware components to interface with Microsoft Flight Simulator which (hopefully) will display things that are currently taking up screen real estate (altimeter …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:44:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3451626/learning-how-to-create-a-flight-simulator</link><title>Q: Learning how to create a flight simulator [closed]</title><description>If I want to learn how to build a flight simulator, what are best books to start with? Thanks Dmitri …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:45:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17313261/opengl-custom-viewing-routine-flight-simulator</link><title>Q: OpenGL custom viewing routine flight simulator</title><description>One of the ways to view a scene is to either use gluLookAt or to create your own custom viewing routine. I came across this custom viewing routine in a flight simulator in a book. void pilotView …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:46:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/718935/is-a-functional-language-a-good-choice-for-a-flight-simulator-how-about-lisp</link><title>Q: Is a functional language a good choice for a Flight Simulator? How about Lisp?</title><description>I have been doing object-oriented programming for a few years now, and I have not done much functional programming. I have an interest in flight simulators, and am curious about the functional … programming aspect of Lisp. Flight simulators or any other real world simulator makes sense to me in an object-oriented paradigm. Here are my questions: Is object oriented the best way to represent …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:49:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13514556/how-do-i-calculate-the-up-vector-in-a-flight-simulator</link><title>Q: How do I calculate the up vector in a flight simulator?</title><description>I am writing 3D app for OpenGL ES 2.0 where the user sets a path and flies over some terrain. It's basically a flight simulator on rails. The path is defined by a series of points created from …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:52:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22440336/request-help-on-virtual-flight-sim-simulation-instrument-panel</link><title>Q: Request help on Virtual Flight Sim / Simulation Instrument Panel</title><description>a friend and myself are trying to create a virtual instrument panel. Screensetup: 5040x1050 Eyefinity Screen centered below a touchscreen with 1920x1080. Actual "Simulation" is Mechwarrior Online …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:53:35">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21331821/how-to-use-terrain-database-from-flight-simulator-x-to-use-in-a-view</link><title>Q: How to use terrain database from flight simulator x to use in a view</title><description>I want to create a view form fsx to make a display the synthetic vision. I don't know how to make use of the terrain database to generate the view of terrains and if the alttitde value aproaches to li …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>