<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:26:50" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:26:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20944212/python-regular-expression-that-disregards-text-with-a-certain-word/20944404#20944404</link><title>A: Python: Regular expression that disregards text with a certain word</title><description>to be mild, tender, and attractive. If growth is checked, roots may become tough, pithy, and too spicy. Then matches the last character with .+ Radishes require friable, well drained soils … , and attractive. If growth is checked, roots may become tough, pithy, and too spicy. Since there is no rows, continue with a repeat of this group. This continues until: Radishes require friable, well …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:29:05">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20944212/python-regular-expression-that-disregards-text-with-a-certain-word</link><title>Q: Python: Regular expression that disregards text with a certain word</title><description>I have the following text, stored in a dictionary entry called info['growing_info'] Radishes require friable, well drained soils with a pH range of 5.8-6.8. Sow at any time during the season … or bedding scheme that will eliminate unplanted ground to discourage weeds. Radishes are adversely affected by hot, dry weather. They remain in prime condition only a few days and should be grown …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:30:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21653376/angularjs-double-nested-ng-repeat-not-working</link><title>Q: AngularJS double nested ng-repeat not working</title><description>' , 'menu': [ {'name':'Dungeness crab fritters with scallions, chervil, and celery root julienne'}, {'name':'Grilled Llano Seco Ranch pork loin with roasted artichokes … '}, {'name':'Zuppa di frutta with clementine sherbet'}, {'name':'Dill, radishes, and curly endive'}, {'name':'Panna cotta with blood orange gelatin …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:32:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16439977/convert-rss-pubdate-string-to-time-and-date-in-jquery</link><title>Q: Convert RSS pubdate string to time and date in jQuery</title><description>cress avocado grape radish bush tomato ricebean black-eyed pea maize eggplant. Cabbage lentil cucumber chickpea sorrel gram garbanzo plantain lotus root bok choy squash cress potato summer purslane … salsify fennel horseradish dulse. Winter purslane garbanzo artichoke broccoli lentil corn okra silver beet celery quandong. Plantain salad beetroot bunya nuts black-eyed pea collard greens radish water …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:35:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17653050/too-many-arguments-error-in-bash-script/17656404#17656404</link><title>A: Too many arguments error in bash script</title><description>as: if test -f "$video_title".$ext2 #QUOTES! then Like all commands, the shell will break up the parameters you give to the command on white spaces. Thus, your title "The Life of a Radish" will get broken … up as five separate parameters "The", "Life", "of", "a", and "Radish" before being passed to this test command. This explains your error message: youtube2mp3.sh: line 31: [: too many arguments …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:38:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9689765/how-to-scroll-diagonally-with-jquery-or-javascript/9693737#9693737</link><title>A: How to scroll diagonally with jQuery or Javascript</title><description>rutabaga maize radish broccoli rabe lotus root kohlrabi napa cabbage courgette mustard squash mung bean.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;​ CSS body { height: 1000px; // 1000 keyframes } #wrapper …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:41:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20274581/css-selector-issue-different-background-to-parent-div-when-checkbox-is-checked</link><title>Q: css selector issue: different background to parent div when checkbox is checked</title><description>chard spinach amaranth scallion collard greens coriander brussels sprout caulie leek ricebean. Dandelion lotus root plantain mung bean spring onion radish soko fennel cucumber komatsuna. Shallot bell … caulie leek ricebean. Dandelion lotus root plantain mung bean spring onion radish soko fennel cucumber komatsuna. Shallot bell pepper broccoli welsh onion kohlrabi kale celery corn fava bean epazote …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:44:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22583846/find-the-nearest-word-in-spelling</link><title>Q: Find the nearest word in spelling</title><description>("localhost" , "root" , "") &amp;&amp; mysql_select_db("test") ) { echo 'connected&lt;br&gt;'; } else { echo 'Failed … { return false ; } ?&gt; and this is my array code two.php &lt;?php $input = $_POST["name"]; $words = array('apple','pineapple','banana','orange', 'radish','anything …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:47:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7227621/cant-execute-stat-on-android-2-3-4-command-not-found/21509736#21509736</link><title>A: Can't execute “stat” on android 2.3.4 command not found</title><description>-daemon monkey mount mpdecision mtpd mv nandread ndc netcfg netd netmgrd netstat newfs_msdos nl_listener notify ping pm port-bridge pppd printenv ps qcks qmuxd qseecomd racoon radish reboot renice … watchprops wipe wm wpa_supplicant No stat, as you can see. If you have root privileges, a simple solution is to install something like BusyBox which adds some such bread-and-butter scripted functions …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:48:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22311839/html-inline-javascript-function-not-working</link><title>Q: HTML inline javascript function not working</title><description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; &lt;dl&gt; &lt;dt&gt;Sashimi&lt;/dt&gt; &lt;dd&gt;Sliced raw fish that is served with condiments such as shredded daikon radish or ginger root, wasabi and soy sauce&lt;/dd&gt; &lt;dt&gt;Scale&lt;/dt&gt; &lt;dd&gt;A device used …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>