<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:52:20" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:52:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22242038/color-grid-cells-in-the-united-states-and-canada</link><title>Q: color grid cells in the United States and Canada</title><description>I would like to color grid cells in the United States and Canada. My goal is very similar to this question: R Plot Filled Longitude-Latitude Grid Cells on Map However, that question only deals … with the United States and I cannot figure out how to add Canada. I was able to draw a map of the U.S. and Canada by modifying code found here: https://groups.google.com/forum/#!topic/ggplot2/KAKhoE0GO4U …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:53:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9496613/how-to-create-a-map-of-the-united-states-and-free-to-fill-color-of-each-state</link><title>Q: How to create a map of the United States and free to fill color of each state? [closed]</title><description>If there is easy ways to create a map(static image) and set diffence color to each state? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:56:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16659034/how-to-draw-d3-map-with-united-states-canada-mexico-and-puerto-rico</link><title>Q: How to draw D3 Map with United States, Canada, Mexico and Puerto Rico</title><description>I'm looking to use D3 to draw a map with some points on it. The Albers Projection US works great. I need a map with Canada (by province), Mexico (by state) and Puerto Rico on it as well. Any recommendation for the best projection on this map would be greatly appreciated. Thanks!-Dre …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:57:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17174102/is-there-a-weather-regions-map-of-united-states</link><title>Q: Is there a weather regions map of United States?</title><description>for example i will do one weather query and not for each user in Manhattan. Is there a map that divide United Stated to weather regions or a site that return weather conditions and the polygon …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:59:18">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/224322/united-states-state-shapes-for-office</link><title>Q: United States State shapes for Office</title><description>in a color. Are there open source libraries of state shapes/polygons (or - if not open source - others) that I can import into Word, Excel, etc. that I can use to show complicated graphs based on states? I have Map Point, but haven't been able to figure out how to shade the states in a complex way. … I want to create visuals along the lines of CNN's "red-state, blue-state" shadings of the states in the U.S. for my project. I'm planning to do something fancier than just shading the state's shape …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:01:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13785466/default-center-on-united-states</link><title>Q: Default center on United States?</title><description>By default, google offers this example of how to center a map on Chicago, IL: var chicago = new google.maps.LatLng(41.850033, -87.6500523); Is it possible to have the default center focus on the entire United States? I can't find this anywhere. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:02:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14829258/how-can-i-get-a-list-of-instantiated-beans-from-spring/14835708#14835708</link><title>A: How can I get a list of instantiated beans from Spring?</title><description>. That way, you can easily reset state of your singletons / mocks without having to destroy / refresh the context. Example: You have a mock DAO: public void MockDao implements IDao { private Map … ); } @After public void reset() { database.clear(); } } The annotation will make sure reset() will be called after each unit test to clean up the internal state. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:04:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15641392/hover-over-tooltip-on-map-of-the-united-states</link><title>Q: Hover-Over Tooltip on Map of the United States</title><description>I would like to make a simple website that has a picture of the United States. When the user hovers their mouse over a particular state, I want to display a tooltip with information on that state … to every state contour. What would be the most logical way to go about this? Does the type of image I use for the United States (bitmap-based vs. vector-based)? Thank you for your help!. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:06:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14406894/javascript-map-of-united-states-with-geocoordinate-plots</link><title>Q: Javascript Map of United States with Geocoordinate Plots</title><description>I'm looking for an open source or inexpensive option for a simple map of the united states to plot geo points on OR fill in states with colors like Google Analytics does for traffic. I don't want … anything fancy, just a map with states and the ability to darken areas, states or plot dots on it for a location service I'm building. Google Maps can plot the markers, but I want this to be stupid …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:07:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/553705/naming-convention-for-state-region-province/3685069#3685069</link><title>A: Naming Convention for State / Region / Province</title><description>Google uses the term administrative_area_level_1 in their geocoder. administrative_area_level_1 indicates a first-order civil entity below the country level. Within the United States … , these administrative levels are states. Not all nations exhibit these administrative levels. administrative_area_level_2 indicates a second-order civil entity below the country level. Within the United States …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>