<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7417">dota 2 heroes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:06:03" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7417-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7417_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:06:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14660771/read-stream-xml-file/14660908#14660908</link><title>A: read stream xml file</title><description>); foreach ($xml-&gt;games-&gt;game as $game) { echo (string) $game-&gt;name; } Outputs; Dota 2 Grand Theft Auto IV Champions Online: Free For All Company of Heroes Company of Heroes: Opposing Fronts … Company of Heroes: Tales of Valor CrimeCraft GangWars Darksiders DC Universe Online Deus Ex: Human Revolution Global Agenda HOMEFRONT Demo Metro 2033 Red Faction: Armageddon Sniper: Ghost Warrior Team Fortress 2 The Lord of the Rings Online™ Tribes: Ascend …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7417-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7417_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:07:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10089789/get-img-src-from-xml-cdata</link><title>Q: Get img src from XML CDATA</title><description>/. The image is inside a CDATA tag written in HTML. Here is the XML code: &lt;content:encoded&gt; &lt;![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;We celebrate Happy Bear Pun Week a day earlier as Lone Druid joins Dota 2&amp;#8242;s cast of heroes.&lt;/p … be more than we can bear.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bear witness to &lt;a href="http://www.team-dignitas.net/articles/blogs/DotA/1092/Dota-2-Ultimate-Guide-to-Warding/" target="_blank"&gt;Team Dignitas&amp;#8217; Ultimate …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7417-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7417_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:10:31">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/986400/c-how-can-i-extract-a-valid-string-within-a-string</link><title>Q: C++ - How can I extract a valid string within a string?</title><description>", // Pooling Mode "oi", // Observer Info "mi", // Mini Heroes "fr", // Fast Respawn "so" // Switch On }; Examples: Here are some example input, with the desired output: "DotA v6.60 … The Problem: I am trying to extract a valid game mode for Defense of the Ancients (DotA) from a game name using C++. Details: Game names can be, at most, 31 characters long There are three game …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7417-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7417_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:12:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18431320/error-trying-to-import-json-to-django-database-typeerror-string-indices-must</link><title>Q: Error Trying to Import JSON to Django Database - TypeError: string indices must be integers</title><description>file and it's not working. It's a command file that is used to import data into the database. So here's what happens when I run the command: PS C:\django-1.5.1\dota\mysite&gt; python manage.py … trying to import the fields from each game item listed in this JSON file. I'm just starting with 2 fields to try to get this working. You can view the JSON file from the URL below, but it is formatted …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>