<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:20:18" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:20:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8630197/collision-detection-by-color-in-car-game</link><title>Q: Collision detection by color in car game</title><description>I'm trying to create a car game in C# with XNA. I have a picture, the track, as the background. The track is painted black, so I need to check when the car is outside the black color, then I know …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:22:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19355439/what-kind-of-feature-vector-is-better-to-detect-whether-there-is-a-car-in-a-car</link><title>Q: What kind of feature vector is better to detect whether there is a car in a car park slot ?</title><description>pictures. Each car park slot is presented with very less pixels. I select four pixel points to define ROI, and I apply the perspective transformation in the image, please see Image 1. SVM would … My aim is to detect whether a car slot is empty or occupied by a car. Finally, the number of cars will be counted in a car park. The camera is monitoring the car park as it is seen in the sample …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:23:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21318690/barbecue-barcode-background-matching-picture-background</link><title>Q: Barbecue - Barcode background matching picture background</title><description>So I'm trying to get the background on the barcode to match the color on the image I'm trying to stick the barcode on. Here is an example to show you what I'm saying. You see, most of my car … is covered in that off-white color, while the bar code has a white background. Here is the code I am using to generate it. Barcode barcode = BarcodeFactory.createCode128B(MemberId); barcode.setDrawingText …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:25:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18034232/drawing-a-selection-rectangle-on-a-picture-box-c-sharp</link><title>Q: drawing a selection rectangle on a picture box c#</title><description>I have to display a picture ( in my case a picture of some cars ) , and have to select the cars appearing in the current frame with a rectangle , I want to enable selecting a rectangle around a car … ( the picture itself , and not a solid color ) . Every small idea is well appreciated . Edit :- I asked for a headlines and not a full code ( but if there is so , I would like to get ;d ) , I am new with c …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:27:33">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15416103/chrome-extension-display-a-picture-in-a-popup-with-ajax-and-jquery</link><title>Q: Chrome-extension : Display a picture in a popup with AJAX and JQUERY</title><description>I'm currently developing a chrome extension which permits to display a picture when the user sends a word. I use AJAX and JQUERY to get the picture. I've a problem to display the picture within … the popup. In fact, it works on a normal html page but not in the popup. If you want to test : http://algec.iut-blagnac.fr/~groupe6pjt/testAjax/pageHTML.html. When I try to display the picture …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:28:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15554690/convert-complex-xml-feed-to-csv-using-php</link><title>Q: convert complex xml feed to csv using php</title><description>to the below feed how do i change the above code to add the model, pictures,images,types.... to the csv? &lt;cars&gt; &lt;car&gt; &lt;color&gt;blue&lt;/color&gt; &lt;price&gt;2000&lt;/price&gt; &lt;model /&gt; &lt;pictures&gt; &lt;image&gt;1.jpg … &lt;/image&gt; &lt;image&gt;2.jpg&lt;/image&gt; &lt;/pictures&gt; &lt;type&gt; &lt;bodykit&gt;yes&lt;/bodykit&gt; &lt;turbo&gt;no&lt;/turbo&gt; &lt;sound&gt;surround&lt;/sound&gt; &lt;/type&gt; &lt;/car&gt; &lt;car&gt; &lt;color&gt;red&lt;/color&gt; &lt;price&gt;10000&lt;/price&gt; &lt;model …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:29:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11672413/list-all-users-objects</link><title>Q: list all user's objects</title><description>as the title says I'm trying to list all cars of one specific user, also each car has two options show and update as you see in the picture, my problem is when I want to show or edit the selected … is te index.html.erb file: &lt;div class="container"&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Listing Cars&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;table class="table table-condensed"&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;th&gt;Brand&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;Color&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;Model&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:30:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13512955/pygamehow-to-make-the-rect-of-an-image-transparent-or-the-same-color-with-backg</link><title>Q: pygame:How to make the rect of an image transparent or the same color with backgroud?</title><description>I just started using pygame today, and got a little trouble. I rotated the car image, but it seemed that the rect area not suited to the image perfectly(as showed in the picture, the white area … is larger than the image I rotated). Can you make the rect area's color transparent or the same as background so that the image looks better? Thanks Hello, This is my concerning code(from 'Rapid …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:32:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4919851/image-feature-identification</link><title>Q: image feature identification</title><description>and location of the house, trees, sidewalk, and car. Also, the textures and colors of the house, cars, trees, and sidewalk. use extracted information to generate a model How can I extract that information? … I am looking for a solution to do the following: ( the focus of my question is step 2. ) a picture of a house including the front yard extract information from the picture like the dimensions …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:34:06">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7334183/changing-the-color-of-the-particular-part-of-an-image-by-using-as3/7334710#7334710</link><title>A: changing the color of the particular part of an image by using as3</title><description>In example you provided there is no color manipulation on the picture. Every time you change the color — new .swf asset with car loaded into the app(example). in my opinion that's the easiest way … (hardest, maybe in some cases impossible) part here will be to select particular part of the picture were you need to convert colors. Update the idea is that, you load your app, withh .swf asset only …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>