<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:20:50" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:20:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11710989/facebook-privacy-policy-error</link><title>Q: Facebook privacy policy error</title><description>In Facebook developer account I am creating an app Id for one of my android App's. In Settings -&gt; auth-dialog I copied the below URL in Privacy Policy. http://developers.facebook.com/policy/ I got … an error saying ... Error A valid Privacy Policy URL must be provided in order to be compliant with Facebook Platform Policy. I gave the same URL for my other app few months back and it worked. Please suggest. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:22:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7187673/like-button-and-privacy-concern</link><title>Q: Like button and privacy concern</title><description>Facebook, thus immediately sending data about the user without his consent, without him even clicking on it. I seek a way to avoid that. Idea: Show a local image with a local href which starts loading … the Facebook stuff only when user actually clicks on it. The problems as I see them: The user clicks on my DOM element and now I'd need to act like the real FB button was pressed, but how can I do …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:23:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9293223/graph-api-and-location-privacy</link><title>Q: Graph API and location privacy</title><description>I'm aware that the Post Graph API object has a privacy attribute that can be specified when an app is allowing the user to create a post. From that documentation, we can see …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:24:33">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10561472/facebook-asking-about-privacy-policy-url</link><title>Q: Facebook asking about “Privacy Policy URL”</title><description>Help! I can't seem to find the "privacy policy field" upon logging to developers facebook. When I click on the URL they sent (http://developers.facebook.com/apps/XXXXXXXXXX/auth) and logged … in with our admin account, it doesn't show "basic" setup, where I could find the "privacy policy field". How can update the "privacy policy field"? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:26:36">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22933055/posting-with-deny-privacy-not-working-and-how-to-save-privacy</link><title>Q: Posting with DENY privacy not working (And how to save privacy)</title><description>with DENY to achieve my goal without using ALLOW? (Important) How can I setting this custom privacy into user's facebook? Because I want Facebook app to keep this privacy (user does not need to change the setting again when using original facebook app). Note: My app works with Facebook SDK 3.8 … My android app posts a status with deny privacy for some friends (who cannot see), but it's not working. Here's my Graph API call: POST me/feed?message=this is message &amp;privacy='value':'CUSTOM …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:27:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20952329/facebook-users-privacy-settings</link><title>Q: facebook users privacy settings</title><description>does the privacy settings of a facebook user affect whether or not i can receive their comments, posts or likes when i make an api call that fetches posts, comments or likes from a facebook page … ? knowing that this thing does not always occur, meaning that data fetches correctly most of the times, but sometimes it doesn't. and when some post or comment do not fetch, i get the "unsupported get request" error, while the actual post/ comment exists when i go visit it directly from facebook. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:28:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9121345/facebook-feed-dialog-setting-the-privacy-dropdown</link><title>Q: Facebook Feed Dialog - setting the Privacy dropdown</title><description>://fbrell.com/f8.jpg&amp; name=Facebook%20Dialogs&amp; caption=Reference%20Documentation&amp; description=Using%20Dialogs%20to%20interact%20with%20users.&amp; message=Facebook%20Dialogs%20are%20so%20easy … !&amp; redirect_uri=http://www.example.com/response Is it possible to set the privacy dropdown (the one left of the Share button) to default to Public? And how? (Note: it is OK if the user then changes the dropdown manually) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:29:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20288625/cant-share-link-due-to-privacy-settings</link><title>Q: Can't share link due to privacy settings?</title><description>I've set up an app on facebook, and it is now live. Everything is working as expected and I can use the FB JS SDK to trigger a feed popup dialog, which also works great. The problem is when I try … to trigger a share popup dialog. In the dialog it states: Some people may not be able to see this attachment because of its privacy settings. The link itself is pretty simple, and is in the form …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:31:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8226699/check-photo-privacy-for-a-user</link><title>Q: Check Photo privacy for a user</title><description>My project is a Facebook application developed in asp.net MVC3. I want to check the privacy of a Facebook photo for a particular user. I have Facebook userid and Facebook photo path. How can I check whether this user had permission to view this photo? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:32:02">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18618541/facebook-privacy-parameter-not-working</link><title>Q: Facebook privacy parameter not working</title><description>I'm working on an fb-app which does offline-publishing on behalf of its users and I cannot get the privacy parameter working. The facts: app is authorized with publish_actions permission simple … publishing works: without any privacy-parameter the posts get the default visibility which was chosen during authorization process publishing with reduced visibility also works. This one reduces …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>