<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:23:24" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:23:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15296737/including-shoes-in-shoes-package</link><title>Q: Including Shoes in Shoes package</title><description>-less computer, downloads Shoes and then runs as expected. However, when I ask it to include Shoes, the packager seems to get stuck on something from the get-go. At least, in some other cases … I've been having a problem with including Shoes in a Shoes app for Windows. The packager tool works perfectly when I don't ask to include Shoes in the app: I get an .exe that, if launched on a Shoes …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:24:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9450819/shoes-installation</link><title>Q: Shoes installation</title><description>I run Ubuntu 11.10 and I am attempting to download shoes. I download it like it says on the site, double click the .run program , and it gives me a text file. please help …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:24:56">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/548657/shoes-and-gems</link><title>Q: Shoes and Gems</title><description>Code: Shoes.setup do gem 'mechanize' end require 'rubygems' require 'mechanize' Running Shoes on it says: no such file to load -- mechanize Thank you. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:25:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1424395/run-shoes-clone-in-ironruby</link><title>Q: Run Shoes clone in IronRuby</title><description>I found cool article on Creating cross platform GUI's with IronRuby where someone re-created the Shoes DSL by _why the lucky stiff in IronRuby. Awesome right! So, I downloaded the IronRuby … , Version=1.0.0.2000 Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=null (LoadError) from ./shoes.rb:5 from hello_world.rb:1 from :0:in `require' How do I get these sample apps to run? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:27:09">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9933170/running-shoes-ruby-1-9-3-problems</link><title>Q: Running shoes ruby 1.9.3 problems</title><description>I have installed shoes successfully but when I run the command to start shoes./dist/shoes I get this message bash: ./dist/shoes: No such file or directory I'm running Ubuntu 11.10 and using ruby … 1.9.3 rvm. I installed shoes by following the instructions on this web page https://github.com/shoes/shoes/wiki/Building-Shoes-on-Linux I get this error when I run rake gcc -I. -c -o shoes/world.o …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:29:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/672972/click-event-in-shoes</link><title>Q: Click event in Shoes</title><description>On clicking a slot , I change the contents of the slot to provide user feed back, then call some code which takes several seconds to run. However the changes to the slot do not render until after … the 'slow' process has completed. Is there any way I can force the rendering to happen before the 'slow' code runs. In the following example the user never sees 'Processing, please wait ...' class …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:29:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1093355/run-shoes-gui-app-in-ide</link><title>Q: Run Shoes gui app in IDE</title><description>Is there any way to write Shoes application using IDE (NetBeans for example)? I hadn't found this solution and I don't like running Shoes app, selecting files, run. I'm sure code for packing Shoes and IDE code will be different (I hope in require directives only), but I'm intresting in possibility. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:30:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2365362/ruby-shoes-packager-including-shoes-in-the-app</link><title>Q: Ruby Shoes packager including Shoes in the app</title><description>makes are all 70-80K files (they obviously don't include shoes or ruby). These exe's will run on my XP machine that already has Shoes on it. but when I copy them to another laptop they start a "Shoes … I can't seem to get the Ruby Shoes packager to correctly create an exe with Shoes included. I'm using the Raisins release (0.r1134), with the pack.rb replaced from github. The exe's the packager …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:32:18">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1854808/shoes-url-not-working-in-ubuntu</link><title>Q: shoes url not working in Ubuntu?</title><description>i have been using Shoes in windows from couple of months and it was working awesome, but now i am having Ubuntu set up on my machine and i am trying to run shoes in it but it seems like URL …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:33:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17165865/issue-with-shoes-setup</link><title>Q: Issue with Shoes setup</title><description>When i am running shoes.rb file, which contains code to install gem, it throws error. Undefined method setup for Shoes:Class Code: Shoes.setup do gem 'activerecord' # install AR if not found … File.exist?("shoes_app.sqlite3") ActiveRecord::Schema.define do create_table :notes do |t| t.column :message, :string end end end end class ShoesApp &lt; Shoes require …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>