<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:10:48" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:10:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6048013/location-specific-gps-based-apps-and-the-apple-review-process-should-they-wor</link><title>Q: Location-specific (GPS-based) apps and the Apple Review Process, should they work without GP…</title><description>is: In order to make the app be likely to be accepted on the app store do I.. (1) Not worry about it as there's evidence that the Apple Reviewers have some way of simulating the GPS. I can then supply … location. For example, a GPS tour of a historical battleground might have content that is triggered at particular lat/long coordinates when the user is at the actual physical location. So my question …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:12:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18598127/http-schema-org-showing-reviews-count-in-google-search</link><title>Q: http://schema.org - Showing reviews count in Google search</title><description>Looking at Google Search, I see a lot of results which show only the number of users reviews (i.e. without the rating stars). For example see: https://www.google.it/search?q=torta+yogurt Looking … current implementation: http://www.google.com/webmasters/tools/richsnippets?url=http://www.autoblog.it/post/267311/classifica-e-tempi-f1-gp-belgio-primo-vettel-alonso-secondo-foto The question …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:13:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4437669/please-review-these-requirements-im-abit-lost</link><title>Q: Please Review these Requirements im abit lost</title><description>sends message. Player Typeb views target history. This program requires a gps connection is this a functional requirement ? Non-Functional: ????? what would they be based on my functional ones ? I will seriously give everyone cookies if they can answer my Questions ! …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:14:47">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13449856/phonegap-ios-application-got-rejected-for-gps-usage</link><title>Q: Phonegap iOS application got rejected for GPS usage</title><description>Regards, App Review The problem is we removed UIBackgroundModes "location" string completely, so geo-updates with getLocation() method are perfomed only in app foreground mode. What could be the problem and how to solve it? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:15:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6461195/multi-party-real-time-gps-tracking-for-ios</link><title>Q: Multi-party Real-time GPS tracking for IOS [closed]</title><description>devices and then capture the GPS through the instamapper API. However, the updates are not quick enough - only 1 every 10 seconds. I believe I would like to sample one time per second or more. I ran … store reviews. I like Glympse for my personal use, but they do not have an API yet. Any suggestions on existing IOS products that accomplish this functionality? If not, any source code that is close so I can make required tweaks? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:16:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10273668/code-quality-review-android-app-development</link><title>Q: Code Quality Review - Android app development [closed]</title><description>. Right now, that I have gotten it to where I want it for version one, I want to essentially get a code review. Any feedback, constructive criticism, or anything I can do better would be greatly … (this); tv.setMovementMethod(new ScrollingMovementMethod()); String applicationText; applicationText = "This app was created by Joyel Puryear (Infotechnologist.biz). It is a simple app that gets your current GPS …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:17:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12351659/communicating-a-gps-gprs-gsm-tracker-with-the-server</link><title>Q: Communicating a GPS/GPRS/GSM tracker with the server</title><description>I am developing a vehicle tracking system which uses GPS/GPRS/GSM. The tracking device I am currently using is GV100, a GPS/GPRS/GSM tracker from Quectel ([www.quectel.com][1].) I am not able … then can send and receive data via this port. I can save the data sent from the client on server's file system and review it any time. (Am not storing the data in relational database because I don't want …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:19:02">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2375365/help-on-my-django-models-for-my-shoe-review-website</link><title>Q: Help on my django models for my shoe review website</title><description>What i'm trying to achieve at this point: Allow me to add new shoe objects, and shoe review objects. complete Allow "Owner Reviews" on each shoe complete (I think, but there might be somewhere … shoe. My overall goal is to have an easy way to be able to suggest shoes with similar attribute ratings to those that the user have rated in the past. Then allowing those shoe reviews to be filtered …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:20:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6864768/android-gps-laptimer-idea-do-you-think-its-accurate-enough-for-this</link><title>Q: Android GPS/LapTimer Idea - Do you think it's accurate enough for this?</title><description>So I ride Motocross when I'm not programming and was thinking about making an app that can log lap times via Android's GPS(mark a finish line via GPS and everytime you pass this point it records … the lap time). Initially I didn't think the GPS was nearly accurate enough to log times within tenths of a second, especially from what I've been reading online but then I took a look at the Android …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:20:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3140999/what-gps-dongles-work-with-windows-7-and-the-net-4-0-system-device-location-nam</link><title>Q: What GPS Dongles work with Windows 7 and the .Net 4.0 System.Device.Location Namespace?</title><description>using the GPS dongle that comes with a M$ Mapping product.. Does anyone know of any other Dongles that definately will appear as a sensor in Win7? I like the look of this one, it gets good reviews … I want to add full GPS support into my application. The .Net 4.0 System.Device.Location namespace information here is perfect for my needs. When this was first announced and the Beta release was out …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>