<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:27:51" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:27:52">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16642227/add-recipe-to-database-how-to</link><title>Q: Add recipe to database, how to?</title><description>These are our 3 tables. We want to a new recipe into the tables. The user gets a screen where they can fill in the RecipeName, the Method and they can select 3 ingredients from dropdown menu's. We … are working with asp.net in visual studio with C#. So when the user fills in every field the RecipeName and the Method will be added to the Recipes table. Then the ingredients which belong …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:29:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13427389/recipe-database-search-by-ingredient</link><title>Q: Recipe Database, search by ingredient</title><description>I have the following 3 tables in my database, and am having some trouble querying them for the results I want. I'm trying to search for recipes by ingredients. SQL Fiddle of the schema below … : fiddle Here are my tables: Ingredients +---------------+---------+ | ingredient_id | name | +---------------+---------+ | 1 | tomato | | 2 | onion | | 3 | rice …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:31:28">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18139970/parse-a-recipe-and-determine-if-gluten-free</link><title>Q: Parse a recipe and determine if gluten free [closed]</title><description>/3 cup of raw white rice 2 pounds ground beef 3/4 cup of chopped fresh mint leaves How can I programmatically determine if the recipe is gluten free. Is defining a list of gluten-containing foods, and checking if the ingredients typed in don't match, be the most efficient way? … I have been assigned an application where a user types in ingredients for a recipe and I try and figure out things like if the recipe is vegan, vegetarian, or gluten free. I'm trying to figure out …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:32:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5569065/checking-that-a-recipe-contains-an-ingredient-mysql</link><title>Q: Checking that a recipe contains an ingredient - MYSQL</title><description>have any rice, or anything else thats needed in it). In my PHP I have an array containing all the ingredients the user has. At the moment they way I'm running this is going through every recipe (loop 1 … efficient way of doing this. Any help very much appreciated. I've got a table that holds 3500 recipes ([recipe]): rid | recipe_name And another table that holds 600 different ingredients ([ingredients …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:34:06">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19437444/generating-recipes-from-collection-of-ingredients-using-prolog</link><title>Q: Generating recipes from collection of ingredients using prolog</title><description>. There will be no more than a couple of dozen ingredients, and probably no more than half a dozen properties. In C I would model this as an array of structs. I then want to be able to generate recipes that use … combinations of ingredients subject to constraints. For example, total calories &lt; 1000 and fat less than 30% and more than 25g protein. I might also want to say "exclude white rice" e.g. because I'm out …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:34:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13803955/regex-syntax-to-explode-recipe-list-elements</link><title>Q: RegEx syntax to explode recipe list elements</title><description>I am processing a list of recipe ingredients, an example of which looks like this: Peanuts, Wheat Starch, Vegetable Oil, Modified Starch, Sugar, Mumbai Spice Flavour [Onion Powder, Herbs … , Celery)], Rice Flour, Salt, Colours (Concentrated Beetroot Juice, Curcumin, Paprika Extract). I wish to explode each ingredient into an array (using PHP), seperated by commas. The problem I have …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:36:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14809548/deep-copy-of-object-array-instance-java/14810072#14810072</link><title>A: Deep Copy of Object Array Instance, Java</title><description>("Chicken"); recipe.ingredients[1] = new Ingredient("Broth"); Recipe copy = new Recipe(recipe); copy.ingredients[2] = new Ingredient("Rice"); copy.name = "Chicken Rice Soup … Add a copy constructor to the recipe class, which creates a new instance of recipe and copies all of the fields from an original recipe. Recipe.java public class Recipe implements Cloneable …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:38:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1558658/php-mysql-forms-flexible-search-ex-x-ingredients-can-make-y-recipes</link><title>Q: PHP &amp; MySQL &amp; forms — flexible search? (ex: X ingredients can make Y recipes)</title><description>a checkbox-based form that can search that table such that if I check 5 different ingredients (carrots, pork, rice, butter, potatoes) the query will return every recipe that I can make with only those 5 … I'm just getting started with PHP/MySQL, so please forgive the rather simplistic question: As a practice example, I want to create a small dbase of recipes. Each recipe has X different ingredients …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:40:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12877476/sql-searching-at-least-2-similar-rows-between-different-tables</link><title>Q: SQL: Searching at least 2 similar rows between different tables</title><description>: turkey and rice. Recipe 3 has: fish, rice and salt. Recipe 4 has: turkey, potatoes and salt. Result based on recipe 1 should be: 4 Result based on recipe 2 should be: None Result based on recipe 3 should … This is my current setup: I have 2 tables, RECIPE and INGREDIENTS. RECIPE holds the ID among other data. INGREDIENTS has X rows needed for each RECIPE. How can one match 2 recipes with at least 2 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:42:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6644322/i-would-like-to-seperate-each-recipe-into-its-own-box-and-i-am-looking-for-other</link><title>Q: I would like to seperate each recipe into its own box and I am looking for other ideas</title><description>I would like to seperate each recipe into its own box but I'm not finding too much on the web as to how to do it. Any help would be great. &lt;?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?&gt; &lt;!-- WebChef … Recipes Author: Randy White date: 7/10/2011 Filename: meals.xml Supporting Files: meals.css \--&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE recipes [ &lt;!ELEMENT recipes (heading,recipe*,name*,description*,ingredients …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>