<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:35:15" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:35:15">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/72393/python-and-re</link><title>Q: Python and “re”</title><description>A tutorial I have on Regex in python explains how to use the re module in python, I wanted to grab the URL out of an A tag so knowing Regex I wrote the correct expression and tested it in my regex … testing app of choice and ensured it worked. When placed into python it failed. After much head scratching I found out the issue, it automatically expects your pattern to be at the start of the string …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:36:32">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7465590/nameerror-name-re-is-not-defined</link><title>Q: NameError: name 're' is not defined</title><description>I am very new to python. Very new. I copied the following from a tutorial #!/usr/bin/python import re from urllib import urlopen from BeautifulSoup import BeautifulSoup webpage = urlopen('http … "\n" I get the error: Traceback (most recent call last): File "test.py", line 8, in &lt;module&gt; patFinderTitle = re.compile('&lt;title&gt;(.*)&lt;/title&gt;') NameError: name 're' is not defined What am I …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:38:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16617682/help-learn-python-tutorial-modules-and-packages</link><title>Q: *Help* Learn Python Tutorial Modules and Packages</title><description>I'm stuck in an exercise on learnpython.org referring to Modules and Packages. The Exercise is: In this exercise, you will need to print an alphabetically sorted list of all functions in the re … module, which contain the word find. The Code I put: import re for x in dir(re): if x[:4] == "find": print x Code Output: findall finditer Expected Output: ['findall', 'finditer …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:39:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22489243/re-in-python-lastindex-attribute</link><title>Q: RE in Python - lastindex attribute</title><description>I'm writing tutorial about "advanced" regular expressions for Python, and I cannot understand lastindex attribute. Why is it always 1 in the given examples: http://docs.python.org/2/library …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:40:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21088666/scrapy-python-re-statement</link><title>Q: scrapy python re statement</title><description>I am learning about scrapy. I am using scrapy 0.20 that is why I am following this tutorial. http://doc.scrapy.org/en/0.20/intro/tutorial.html I undrstood the concepts. However, I have one thing yet … . In this statement sel.xpath('//title/text()').re('(\w+):') the output is [u'Computers', u'Programming', u'Languages', u'Python'] what is re('(\w+):') using for please? to help answering …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:42:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9449840/sqlalchemy-tutorial-example-not-working</link><title>Q: sqlalchemy tutorial example not working</title><description>I'm trying to work my way through the example given in the sqlalchemy tutorial but I'm getting errors. As far as I can tell I'm following the example to the letter. Here's the code that I have from … it so far. It fails when I .first() after I query the DB. I'm on version 0.7.5 and python 2.7 from sqlalchemy import Column, Integer, String from sqlalchemy.ext.declarative import …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:43:41">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19310809/stuck-at-learnpython-org-tutorialregarding-modules</link><title>Q: Stuck at LearnPython.org Tutorial(Regarding Modules) [closed]</title><description>module, which contain the word find. I have absolutely no clue where to start. Do i loop through the module list? Is that even possible? (Sorry if i sound clueless, new to Python) Given Code: import re # Your code goes here Expected Output: ['findall', 'finditer'] … I'm stuck on an exercise at LearnPython.org regarding Modules and Packages. The questions says: In this exercise, you will need to print an alphabetically sorted list of all functions in the re …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:44:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17766725/how-to-re-install-lxml</link><title>Q: How to re-install lxml?</title><description>I am using python 2,7.5 on mac 10.7.5, beautifulsoup 4.2.1. I am going to parse a xml page using the lxml library, as taught in the beautifulsoup tutorial. However, when I run my code, it shows bs4 … : easy_install, pip, port, etc. I tried to add a line to my code to see if lxml is installed or not: import lxml Then python can just successfully go through this code and display the previous error message …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:45:01">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9201723/parsing-lines-in-python-use-re-or-not</link><title>Q: Parsing Lines in Python: Use RE or Not?</title><description>be structured in Python? I've been going through the various on line tutorials, and they've helped me with understanding the syntax, but not much in the way of handling the language itself -- especially someone … I'm a Perl programmer who's attempting to learn Python by taking some work I've done before and converting it over to Python. This is NOT a line-by-line translation. I want to learn the Python …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:46:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5555224/help-with-specific-python-re-application</link><title>Q: Help with specific Python re application</title><description>folks, I am working on using Python re to parse a configuration file that contains lines like this: [VAR: abc123] ... ... .CSIIND~~~LOCAL~~~I4~~~0~~~ [VAR: def234] ... &lt;bunch … I'm probably a bit slow on this, but I've been seeking out every tutorial and resource I can find, to no avail. Please help me, at least with directional suggestions! I don't mean to ask for finished …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>