<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:04:19" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:04:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/406760/whats-your-most-controversial-programming-opinion/406825#406825</link><title>A: What's your most controversial programming opinion?</title><description>huge amounts of ugly XML boilerplate that is difficult to validate and write quickly. You have massive APIs where half of those are just to integrate the work of the other APIs, interfaces … with their own darned descriptor syntax, the overly complex database and groupware products? The point of this is not that complexity==bad, it's that unnecessary complexity==bad. I've worked in massive …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:06:28">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22959936/wamp-server-home-page-opening-fine-in-android-but-deployed-web-pages-not-loading</link><title>Q: WAMP Server home page opening fine in android but deployed web pages not loading</title><description>:03:24:22 +0530] "GET /sampletest/ HTTP/1.1" 200 60504 Note: The sampletest application works fine on laptop and its not loading in android, but wampserver home page opens fine in android WAMP … I tried to host html 5 mobile responsive site using Wamp server. But the project (sampletest) works fine on my laptop and I tried to test the same in my android using a wifi hotspot. When accessing …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:08:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1396191/what-should-every-developer-know-about-legal-matters/1463552#1463552</link><title>A: What should every developer know about legal matters?</title><description>the period of employment, whether at home or at work. Many companies have non-compete clauses in employment agreements that restrict the software an employee can produce for distribution outside … at the option (or best efforts) of the developer, and make it clear who pays for fixes and upgrades. Even after you consult a lawyer about software development and distribution agreements, you should read …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:10:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2219198/to-crm-or-not-to-crm-ms/2246260#2246260</link><title>A: To CRM or not to CRM (MS)?</title><description>/library/j-eaed10/) that discusses COTS vs home grown software. Here's a snippet. One of the common questions that arise in big companies is the decision whether to build or buy: for the current … the client needs. They are motivated to build the most generic software they can because it will potentially fit into more ecosystems. But the more general it is, the more customization is required. That's when an army of consultants shows up, sometimes taking years to get all the custom coding done. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:10:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15754726/css-drop-down-menu-not-working-in-ie9</link><title>Q: CSS Drop-Down Menu Not Working in IE9</title><description>working in that drop-down list is the "Consultant Directory." I tried it using the "compatibility view" option in IE9, but it did not do anything. I am copying and pasting the code I am using below … UPDATE: I am using Yahoo's SiteBuilder software and, since I suspect the problem may have to do with the doctype header, I did a Google search on that for SiteBuilder. Someone in another forum …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:12:26">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3773944/how-do-i-verify-users-of-my-php-application/3774022#3774022</link><title>A: How do I verify users of my PHP application?</title><description>You could integrate phone-home behavior into your software but you should probably consult a lawyer to discuss privacy issues about that and to work out privacy guidelines and terms of use for your … it could potentially be used to compromise your client's infrastructure or for spying on your client. Regarding your phone-home function, be warned that the client could just locate and remove it, so …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:13:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13734491/codeigniter-index-php-configuration-not-working</link><title>Q: CodeIgniter index.php configuration not working</title><description>Ok I'm so confused... I have this working on my laptop, but can't get it to work on my desktop using the SAME EXACT SOURCE. So I feel like it's not CI, but I even transferred my httpd.conf … SmartWare.swstor/HALEY-HP/Source/DStable/public/register, referer: http://dstable.localhost/index.php/register Again, it works when I go to http://dstable.localhost/index.php/register, but not http …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:15:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18588157/apachemod-wsgi-stopped-working-remotely</link><title>Q: Apache+mod_wsgi stopped working remotely</title><description>I have a django application. I can connect to it using the django development server. Some time ago I configured it to be able also to work with apache+mod_wsgi, and it worked. Now I want to use tha … apache server again, but it only works from localhost, and not from another client. I wonder if I have changed something at the configuration, which seems to be OK as from localhost it works like …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:17:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15534185/adding-an-android-phon-to-a-dns-server/15544005#15544005</link><title>A: Adding an android phon to a DNS server?</title><description>configuration on the phone itself. All you need is just create a regular DNS address record. (Consult your DNS administrator (or ask on superuser.com if your need help)) Home/office network (DHCP). If you … does not need any special configuration/software \- it's a DHCP server which needs to be configured. Dynamic DNS. Your phone can submit it's address via dynamic DNS. This will work for any case - LAN …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:19:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5792295/problems-with-getting-mod-wsgi-to-work-with-apache</link><title>Q: Problems with getting mod_wsgi to work with Apache</title><description>This is probably a very basic question but I'm not used to Apache and I can't seem to find my way around this. I'm trying to get mod_wsgi to work with Apache so that I could get my Django app up … and running. However, there seems to be some problem in getting Apache to work with mod_wsgi After following the mod_wsgi documentation, this is what I've done so far: Downloaded, renamed and copied …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>