<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:32:35" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:32:35">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/365158/how-can-we-protect-the-vulnerable-online</link><title>Q: How can we protect the vulnerable online?</title><description>by a trained individual to protect these kids Code alarm / suspicious analysis into the forum How has anyone else tackled this and what Ideas do other people have on this? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:33:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22493513/how-can-one-protect-against-whiletrue-loops-in-javascript</link><title>Q: How can one protect against while(true) loops in javascript?</title><description>I have been working with teaching kids programming in Javascript using a combination of online and self made environment. At some stage most of the kids encounter a time when they create …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1224602/visual-studio-2008-reading-or-writing-protected-memory-when-debugging</link><title>Q: Visual Studio 2008 reading or writing protected memory when debugging</title><description>On a brand new Vista machine, I'm getting the following error - instantly - whenever I try to start a project in debug mode: Attempted to read or write protected memory. This is often … a brand new blank project exhibits the same behavior. And I don't get any message when I Start Without Debugging. I've read online about a few fixes: There was a service pack to .NET 2.0 in 2007 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20922582/how-to-encode-html-source-code-so-that-no-one-can-see-it-on-web-asp-net-c-sharp/20922607#20922607</link><title>A: How to encode html source code so that no one can see it on web. asp.net c#</title><description>You can simply use this online tool to encrypt your HTML contents Link but keep in mind that will slightly slow down rendering performance. i used to do that many times when i was kid and realized … that is not necessary at all if your looking for an App use this link in addition. there are other tricky way to protect your media content as well. *but please realize that smart minds can read anything from your page :) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:36:27">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8065211/javascript-class-change-to-aspbutton-control-not-available-on-server-side</link><title>Q: javascript class change to asp:button control not available on server side</title><description>So I have looked for days for a solution online to this, and I've tried different ways of doing this, but can't seem to find a complete solution. So please HELP! I have a form that a user … is filling out online. At one point in the form, they select keywords they want to associate with their input. I have created a table layout of buttons with each keyword in a button. &lt;asp:Button ID …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:38:06">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6926774/how-do-i-prevent-people-from-stealing-photos-from-my-website/12890781#12890781</link><title>A: How do I prevent people from stealing photos from my website?</title><description>. If you don't want anyone to use them, not even a kid pasting it in their homework, you shouldn't post it online at all. But in general you want to protect the pictures from being used illegally … of those pictures, while other 'hobbyists' may want to use the pictures just for their own site or something. I think you should ask yourself against who and what use you want to protect the pictures …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:39:56">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8143679/is-ntsetinformationthread-safe-to-use</link><title>Q: Is NtSetInformationThread safe to use?</title><description>I am attempting to implement some very basic debugger protection to prevent kids from using easy tricks to reverse engineer my software. While these simple measures are easy to bypass … , they will at least keep out the uninformed. The following code is from a tutorial online, and I wanted to ask for your opinions as to whether this is safe to use in production code? I am hesitant because …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:41:08">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3552744/javascript-spam-prevention-based-on-comment-content/3552835#3552835</link><title>A: Javascript spam prevention based on comment content</title><description>in a dialogue online. It really should only be used in an environment where you need to protect people from content (like maybe if you are working on some product page marketed to kids). …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:42:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12698114/how-can-i-parse-a-json-response-saved-in-a-text-file</link><title>Q: How can I parse a json response saved in a text file</title><description>:\/\/screen.yahoo.com\/","dispurl":"screen.&lt;b&gt;yahoo&lt;\/b&gt;.com","title":"Watch videos online \- &lt;b&gt;Yahoo&lt;\/b&gt;! Screen","abstract":"Watch videos online for free on &lt;b&gt;Yahoo&lt;\/b&gt;! Screen. Find sports, kids … free mailing lists, photo &amp;amp; file sharing, group calendars and more. Discuss hot topics, share interests, join online communities."}, {"date": "","clickurl":"http:\/\/homes.yahoo.com\/","url …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:44:36">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12700480/how-extract-array-elements-in-json</link><title>Q: How extract array elements in json</title><description>online for free on &lt;b&gt;Yahoo&lt;\/b&gt;! Screen. Find sports, kids and funny videos including the latest news video clips." }, { "date":"", "clickurl":"http … sharing, group calendars and more. Discuss hot topics, share interests, join online communities." }, { "date":"", "clickurl":"http:\/\/homes.yahoo.com\/", "url …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>