<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:50:03" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:50:04">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20751807/issues-with-twitter-geocode-parameter-in-twitter-search-api</link><title>Q: Issues with twitter geocode parameter in twitter search api</title><description>. MUCH LOVE. thanks Protected =&gt; Followers count =&gt; 47889293 Language =&gt; popular Created at =&gt; Mon Dec 23 21:03:03 +0000 2013 id =&gt; 4.15226068632E+17 text =&gt; Good first half that ! source =&gt; Twitter … I am trying to get twitter feeds using twitter search api with geocode params. I am setting the get param as $getfield = '?geocode=37.781157,-122.398720,1mi&amp;lan=en&amp;result_type=mixed' However, I …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:51:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21623793/c-modeling-a-timeline</link><title>Q: C* Modeling a timeLine</title><description>is that I have my doubts about the scalability of modeling the twitter timeline in this fashion. The problem: What will happen if I have a userA (rock star) or more that is extremely popular …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:52:59">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12553748/how-to-change-icon-color-in-twitter-bootstrap-to-dark</link><title>Q: How to change icon color in twitter bootstrap to dark?</title><description>="#"&gt; &lt;i class="icon-star"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Most popular&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href="#"&gt; &lt;i class="icon-heart"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Etc.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:54:29">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4079575/javascript-pop-up-window</link><title>Q: javascript pop-up window</title><description>In some web pages, when we stop mouse cursor on some words (e.g. some popular movie star names) on the web page, a pop-up box near the words will show-up, showing maybe some related pictures … for the move star, a short summary for the movie star, and related twitter link for this movie star. Then we can move mouse on the pop-up windows to click for picture or twitter link. When the mouse cursor …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:55:28">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2752967/django-comments-and-rating-systems</link><title>Q: Django Comments and Rating Systems</title><description>on this. Hope you guys can give me some suggestions. Here are the things that I would like to have: Tag Clouds Articles Archive (by months/by years) Articles Rating (e.g. with Stars or customize icons … ) Pagination of the comments if get too long OpenIDs supports (e.g. facebook, hotmail, blogger, twitter...etc) Support login before user can comments Able to retrieve Blogs' Header and customized …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:57:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4046142/google-chrome-text-shadow-rendering</link><title>Q: Google Chrome text shadow rendering</title><description>evident if hand writing fonts are used such as Monotype Corsiva http://www.newfonts.net/index.php?pa=show_font&amp;id=130 One of the places you can see this clearly is on Twitter \- http://dev.twitter.com … they only fix the "popular" bugs, a practice so lame that it looks impressive! I am very disappointed with Chrome! Web typography and CSS3 are used by more and more people every day to make the web …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:57:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19387254/why-use-jslint-and-jshint-together/19387367#19387367</link><title>A: Why use JSLint and JSHint together</title><description>possible that that the newest version of JSLint have some special checks that are missing from JSHint, but in general JSHint is more popular (github stars) and moves faster (many commits and contributors … to read the JSLint XML format, but of course JSHint can generate that as well, so again it's not a good reason. The creator of JSHint also started a thread about this on Twitter which may aid your …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:58:42">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4459810/open-source-iphone-apps/4460087#4460087</link><title>A: Open source iPhone apps</title><description>– iPhone port of the extremely popular, and beautiful 3D Tux Racer game. Tweejump – Platform jumping game inspired by Icy Tower. Utilizes Cocos2D. Tweetee – Enhanced version of the Natsulion Twitter Client … For Wesnoth – Fantasy themed turn based tactical RPG game available on several platforms and now the iPhone/iPad. Colloquy – Conversion of the most popular Mac IRC client to the iPhone. Countitout …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:59:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12645038/stristr-not-working-with-html-tags</link><title>Q: stristr not working with html tags</title><description>I am creating a RSS feed aggregator which retrieves not just the description but also the entire content of the post by visiting each links.I am filtering unwanted info like facebook,twitter … understanding and also others use getcontent function which works fine.The sample-source of a post in deccan herald is: &lt;h1&gt;Crazy star Ravichandran takes potshots at TV channels&lt;/h1 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:00:52">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/1648340/how-hard-is-developing-for-iphone/1648630#1648630</link><title>A: How hard is developing for iPhone?</title><description>you have to be a good all-rounder is that the apps that succeed have it all - design, inspiration, execution. Consider involving a designer if your taste doesn't match what seems to be popular. Don't … your app isn't complete rubbish and doesn't get 10 1-star reviews right away sheer numbers will get you some sales. To make it big is hard, and you will need to investigate marketing, review sites …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>