<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:02:39" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:02:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10756413/facebook-pay-dialog-in-iframe</link><title>Q: Facebook pay dialog in iframe?</title><description>In my canvas application i perform redirect to facebook pay dialog and it appears inside app iframe with Facebook header and footer (so they are doubled). The option "display=iframe" is not allowed for this type of dialog so i can't see any way to avoid doubled headers and footers. Any help? Thanks. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:04:19">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/16642885/facebook-local-currency-payment-pay-dialog-is-not-working</link><title>Q: Facebook Local currency payment Pay dialog is not working</title><description>Though FB local currency documentation is in initial design mode. I follow there steps to invoke the payment dialog but it just show an error (and also make no communication with call back url) here …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:05:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7832515/trouble-with-facebooks-pay-dialogue</link><title>Q: Trouble with facebook's pay dialogue</title><description>by the application. Hi guys. The error message above is an example of what I receive when trying to integrate facebook's pay dialogue with my app. I am aware that this error occurs when there is a discrepancy … between the url domain you provide to facebook and the url you place in your redirect uri variable. However, in this situation, the url's match exactly. Site Url: www.vgiver.com/ Site Domain …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:06:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21476131/error-when-trying-to-pay</link><title>Q: Error when trying to pay</title><description>I do not know what I am doing wrong. Just trying to make my first app with facebook payment, but always get Blockquote"Es ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuche es später noch einmal …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:07:25">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20674517/pay-with-a-like-on-ios-android</link><title>Q: Pay with a like on iOS &amp; Android [closed]</title><description>How can I allow my iOS &amp; Android user to use premium features if they liked a facebook page or if they twitted a message. In other word how to implement Pay With A Tweet or Pay With A Like in mobile apps? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:09:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15928037/pay-dialog-not-appearing</link><title>Q: Pay Dialog not Appearing</title><description>I'm trying to launch the Pay Dialog to enable purchasing of in game currency in our app. However, no matter what I try, the dialog does not appear, no error message or anything. I'll just run … through a list of all the things that I've tried to root the problem out. If I run the app from our webpage, a popup appears with API Error Code: 1151. If run within Facebook, this pop up does not appear …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:10:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17152615/facebook-invoke-the-pay-dialog-via-direct-url-in-local-currency-payments</link><title>Q: Facebook: invoke the pay dialog via direct URL in local currency payments</title><description>The docs of the new approach to make payments in FB using local currency payments doesn't specify how to invoke the pay dialog via direct URL: Invoking the Pay Dialog Can I still use the "old method … " (changing the parameters to: method, action, product, etc.)?: https://www.facebook.com/dialog/pay?app_id=YOUR_APP_ID&amp; (...) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:11:54">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19077408/facebook-pay-method-title-and-description</link><title>Q: Facebook 'pay' method title and description</title><description>When I user the 'FB.UI' with method pay, like this: var obj = { method: 'pay', action: 'purchaseitem', product: encodeURI(order_info.product), request_id: .... }; FB.ui(obj, function (data).... How do i change the title &amp; description user see in the payment dialog? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:12:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12486276/facebook-pay-dialog-not-returning-resposnse</link><title>Q: Facebook Pay Dialog not returning resposnse</title><description>I'm trying to open a Pay Dialog and it's not going well. When I set the action to buy_credits or ear_credits it works. But when I set action to buy_item it returns an error of" 1383046 - Sorry … ( { method: 'pay', action: 'buy_item', order_info: { 'item_id': '1a'}, dev_purchase_params: {'oscif': true} }, js_callback …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:13:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14729178/facebook-pay-dialog-not-showing-local-currency-dialog</link><title>Q: facebook pay dialog not showing local currency dialog</title><description>facebook pay dialog shows credits only, when i click on buy credits rather then it should goto next dialog where it should ask me the payment options it just says your purchase is successful … : 'pay', action: 'buy_item', order_info: {'item_id': 'tokens', 'price':p}, dev_purchase_params: {'oscif': true} }; //FB.ui(obj, js_callback); FB.ui(obj, function(paydata …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>