<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:32:45" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:32:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10287683/python-convert-wav-to-mp3</link><title>Q: Python convert wav to mp3</title><description>I've looked at pymedia (discontinued), pyglet(great but no converter in there) and audiotools(command line cd ripping), and none seem suitable. In Python 2.7 , how do you do convert … (wavFileLocation, 'mp3') If there is no python way, how would you do it in a manner which python can invoke? (e.g. Call a Cross platform command line tool... if exists return (name, pythonCodeForInvocation) ) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:33:16">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3641920/how-to-encode-a-wav-to-a-mp3-on-a-android-device</link><title>Q: Convert recorded WAV to MP3 [duplicate]</title><description>Is there a way to convert WAV to MP3 in android. My application records audio as WAV and I want to convert it to MP3 but without using NDK. Most answers I found is that I have to resort to using … Android NDK. But I still don't know much about NDK. So, is there anyway to convert it to MP3. Like just some libraries or something? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:33:50">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3049572/how-to-convert-mp3-to-wav-in-python</link><title>Q: How to convert MP3 to WAV in Python</title><description>If I have an MP3 file how can I convert it to a WAV file? (preferably, using a pure python approach) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:35:38">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5289620/convert-mp3-to-wav-on-android</link><title>Q: Convert mp3 to wav on Android</title><description>There seem to be a lot of questions regarding the inverse wav to mp3 conversion, but none to go the other way. My situation is that I can use steganography to embed data in wav files. I can convert … , retrieving the files in mp3 format is not a problem, but converting those mp3 files back to wav to perform the steg. extraction is. Does anyone know where I should start? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:37:14">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4997923/is-there-any-pure-java-way-to-convert-wav-to-mp3</link><title>Q: Is there any pure java way to convert .wav to .mp3?</title><description>I've struggled a lot with Java but could not combine a working example of Java .wav to .mp3 converter. This converter will be used in a Java applet so it should depend only on libraries written in pure Java with no underlying C code calls. Can anyone provide a fully working example? Thank you …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:38:20">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/14659267/jlayer-convert-mp3-to-wav</link><title>Q: JLayer convert mp3 to wav</title><description>I am trying to convet mp3 to wav with JLayer, while It seems that it can not set rate. public void convert(String sourceName, String destName, ProgressListener progressListener …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:38:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2994337/how-to-convert-mp3-to-pcm-using-delphi-code</link><title>Q: How to convert MP3 to PCM using delphi code?</title><description>I have Bass component from http://www.un4seen.com/bass.html. I load mp3 and triying to change the format to PCM but it wont do nothing? or any suggestion will be appreciated. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:40:48">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12921181/using-ffmpeg-sharp-convert-a-wav-to-mp3</link><title>Q: Using ffmpeg-sharp, convert a wav to mp3</title><description>Using the ffmpeg-sharp project, how do I convert a wav to mp3? I feel silly to ask, but I can't find any explanation on how to do it. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:41:24">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/17928484/converting-mp3-to-wav-on-android-and-controlling-the-quality-bitrate</link><title>Q: Converting MP3 to WAV on Android and controlling the Quality/bitrate</title><description>I am using JLayer to convert MP3 to WAV however I need to lower the quality/ bitrate as it is taking 1-2 minutes to convert on a Nexus 7. The wav does not need to be high quality as its background …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7490-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7490_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:42:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/3498215/what-is-the-algorithm-to-convert-an-mp3-file-to-a-wav-file</link><title>Q: What is the algorithm to convert an mp3 file to a wav file?</title><description>What is the algorithm to convert an mp3 file to a wav file? …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>