<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:42:44" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:42:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19550457/convert-mp3-wav-midi-to-integer-values</link><title>Q: Convert MP3/WAV/MIDI to integer values</title><description>an MP3 or WAV or MIDI file to a series of integer values within a certain bounds? Failing that, any suggestions on how I could program such a thing? (Java/C#/C++/whatever, language doesn't matter) … if I could make this thing play music, and 255 notes should be enough to do that. There is no practical reason for this aside from fun. So does anyone know of a library or service that will convert …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:43:56">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10066805/wav-to-mp3-convertion</link><title>Q: Wav to MP3 Convertion</title><description>I'm making a program in Delphi, which records the audio from vinyl records, then detects and separates the different tracks from each other. My problem is I can't convert the recorded wav files … to mp3. I have tried to use LAME, but that gives me an mp3 file that plays to slow (eg. I start with a 1 min wav and it lands up as a 5 min mp3) Please can you suggest source code or components with which I can convert wav files to mp3s. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:44:44">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/22825411/java-how-to-convert-mp3-to-a-wav-clip-without-external-programs</link><title>Q: Java: How to convert mp3 to a wav clip without external programs</title><description>I have a java program that plays .wav files by putting them into Clips. I wanted to know if there was a way (without JLayer or any external libraries) to convert an mp3 file into a wav file that I could put into a Clip? Thanks …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:46:26">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/19550457/convert-mp3-wav-midi-to-integer-values/19550617#19550617</link><title>A: Convert MP3/WAV/MIDI to integer values</title><description>This is just a high level concept, but using a program like ableton you could convert songs or sounds to midi with its sound-to-midi tool. At that point your midi notes are now values. You could … then Send the midi values out from ableton using its output ports (ex. midi to usb port). The midi values may not be the exact number you would want to work with, so at that phase, you could create a program converting the midi values to a specific integer from 0-255. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:47:49">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/7915353/algorithm-for-encoding-wav-to-mp3</link><title>Q: algorithm for encoding wav to mp3</title><description>I want to create a program to convert some music files from wav to mp3. WAV should be raw bitstream and reading it shouldn't be much of a problem, but I don't even know where to start with learning … how to encode that raw stream into mp3. I've already read how to build up header of mp3 frame, but I'd like to know how exactly are music data stored. As I;m quite new to this stuff, some thorough …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:48:51">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12216969/convert-wav-to-ogg-or-mp3-on-the-fly-in-c</link><title>Q: Convert wav to ogg or mp3 on the fly in C</title><description>or ogg is a good option. Now, how can I do this? In practice this means that the following functions have to be available: . convert a location in a mp3 (or ogg) file (offset) to a location in a wav … file and vice versa. . convert a buffer/offset from wav format to buffer/offset in mp3 (ogg) format. Can someone give me a hint? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:49:57">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20696948/how-to-do-text-to-speech-with-python-on-a-toshiba-laptop-and-windows-7</link><title>Q: How to do text to speech with python on a Toshiba laptop and Windows 7?</title><description>: no sound was played, yet no exceptions were raised. I have even used the same pygame code on a raspberry pi and successfully played an mp3 file. I have also tried converting it to a wav file, which has … unofficial text to speech program accessed through the urllib2 module. This ends up creating an mp3 file. For details on the code, much of this code is from http://glowingpython.blogspot.com/2012/11 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:51:43">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12318538/is-it-worth-to-keep-file-descriptors-open-in-case-i-need-to-read-the-file-0-5/12327917#12327917</link><title>A: Is it worth to keep file descriptors open in case i need to read the file 0…5 times per se…</title><description>don't work natively with formats like MP3 \-- they always convert to uncompressed formats first. One of the reasons for this is that the sample-accurate seek-time of MP3's is MUCH worse. In theory … , an MP3 reading library could close the file and reopen where it left off if nothing changed, but I don't think MP3 libraries support this. By contrast, uncompressed files are super fast and easy to seek …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:52:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15861601/mp3-file-length-isnt-shown-correct</link><title>Q: mp3 file length isn't shown correct</title><description>I'm trying to convert a WAV file into MP3 file using LAME (win7,vs2010,c++). I found this code: convert wav to mp3 using lame The convert works fine, but when i'm trying to open the file using … windows media player the length of the file is wrong. Is there any way to fix this using lame lib?(not with another program or another lib or command line,only with c++ code...) EDITED: after some …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7491-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7491_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:54:30">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15445037/directshow-mp3-compression</link><title>Q: DirectShow MP3 Compression</title><description>in VB.Net. They've always worked great until now. I'm attempting to convert a .wav file to .mp3. Using GraphStudio and the following filters chained together with the default connections I get … the compressed files. FileSource-Async--&gt;WaveParser--&gt;MPEG Layer3--&gt; WAV Dest --&gt; Filewriter. However, when I connect the same filters together in my VB.Net program I get no compression at all. I've even …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>