<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:02:21" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:02:22">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15146041/hdf5-compound-type-native-vs-ieee</link><title>Q: HDF5 Compound type Native vs. IEEE</title><description>, but in creating the datatype for the file, serial_no used H5T_STD_I64BE. Why does he do this? /* * Create the compound datatype for memory. */ memtype = H5Tcreate (H5T_COMPOUND, sizeof (sensor_t)); status … manually calculate the * offset of each member. */ filetype = H5Tcreate (H5T_COMPOUND, 8 + sizeof (hvl_t) + 8 + 8); status = H5Tinsert (filetype, "Serial number", 0, H5T_STD_I64BE); status = H5Tinsert …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:02:52">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/6916884/why-must-we-define-both-and-in-c</link><title>Q: Why must we define both == and != in C#?</title><description>some entities may neither be equal nor unequal, (like IEEE-754 NaN's), but those seem like the exception, not the rule. So this doesn't explain why the C# compiler designers made the exception the rule … The C# compiler requires that whenever a custom type defines operator ==, it must also define != (see here). Why? I'm curious to know why the designers thought it necessary and why can't …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:04:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2262945/exponent-in-ieee-754/2274735#2274735</link><title>A: Exponent in IEEE 754</title><description>if it was 2's complement, it would be (-128 to +127). I don't really know the reason why the standard chooses the bias form, but maybe the committee members thought it would be more useful to allow extremely large numbers, rather than extremely small numbers. … Note that there is a slight difference in the representable range for the exponent, between biased and 2's complement. The IEEE standard supports exponents in the range of (-127 to +128), while …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:04:34">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/231760/what-does-a-type-followed-by-t-underscore-t-represent/12727104#12727104</link><title>A: What does a type followed by _t (underscore-t) represent?</title><description>types defined in this section end in ‘‘_t’’ was prompted by the problem of name space pollution. It is difficult to define a type (where that type is not one defined by IEEE Std 1003.1-2001) in one … symbols ending in ‘‘_t’’, which permits the implementor to provide additional types. Because a major use of types is in the definition of structure members, which can (and in many cases must) be added …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:05:07">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/177393/what-is-the-correct-way-to-initialize-a-very-large-struct</link><title>Q: What is the correct way to initialize a very large struct?</title><description>bigstruct temp = { 0 }; controller-&gt;bigstruct = temp; After reviewing the C99 spec, I could see why; C99 basically requires that anonymous structures exist on the stack. It's a good concept … , but this structure was 4 Megabytes large, and only ever intended to exist on heap! We've resorted to making our own 'initialize' function that explicitly sets the members, but that's ugly …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:06:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21766461/net-and-beyond-best-practices-for-using-double-arithmetic/21767001#21767001</link><title>A: .NET and beyond: best practices for using double arithmetic</title><description>Two things you need to read: What Every Programmer Should Know About Floating-Point Arithmetic, or Why don’t my numbers add up? David Goldberg's most excellent 1991 paper, What Every Computer … with a discussion of the IEEE floating point standard, and concludes with examples of how computer system builders can better support floating point. And a couple of source of the paper in PDF form …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:07:53">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4763141/data-modeling-supertype-subtype/4766712#4766712</link><title>A: Data Modeling: Supertype / Subtype</title><description>Cardinality is critical. Putting it in will actually assist in resolving the model. I am not fussed re IDEF1X (circles) vs IEEE (crows feet), but I always put them in as I go, and keep changing them … as the model progresses. your model does not show that a Band is made up of one-to-many Members. Et cetera. . While programming can progress incrementally (once the definition is stable)), modelling does …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>