<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:11:05" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:11:05">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2580809/getting-london-gold-price-from-web-service</link><title>Q: getting london gold price from web service</title><description>hi all i'm trying to access the gold price info through this web service: http://www.webservicex.net/LondonGoldFix.asmx but it always return false to in the result here is my code after I adding …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:12:29">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11585039/get-silver-or-gold-rate</link><title>Q: Get Silver or Gold Rate</title><description>I'm written widget program to get price of silver or gold price from Bloomberg website these are parts of the script : function getPrice() { var url = new URL(); url.location = "http … for Gold Price (.indexOf("GOLD")) (let say right now 1,585.60) What is the subcheck.match() script to get that price? …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:13:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/9078057/how-to-read-the-gold-price-from-the-given-link</link><title>Q: How to read the gold price from the given link</title><description>I am working on a application to shows the live gold price in my android application, I am stuck at one point. I am pasting a link http://www.marketonmobile.com/gold_price_india.php This web page … have current gold price and I want to read only that gold price and want to show it only in my android application, please suggest me any proper solution. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:13:55">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8604363/grab-gold-value-using-curl</link><title>Q: grab gold value using curl</title><description>I am new to php curl, can you help me to write code for grabbing gold value from this page http://www.domain.com/gold.php from following line i just want 27742.00 Gold price today in India (Rs …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:15:10">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8265816/need-reference-for-bse-nseindian-stock-exchange-api-for-fetching-gold-and-silv</link><title>Q: Need reference for BSE/NSE[Indian] stock exchange api for fetching gold and silver prices</title><description>This needs to be specifically for indian stock exchange. If its a free one then its great but a chargeable one would also be fine</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:16:46">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21188659/how-to-get-price-of-gold-and-silver-from-xml-and-make-it-upload-each-3-second</link><title>Q: how to get price of gold and silver from XML and make it upload each 3 second</title><description>I have this XML file I try to load prices of gold and silver and update it each 4 second I try this using this line to get the child element of parent with attr = "Gold Canadian $" but no use … working update I try to to get silver price and I could not it will remove the gold price ?? goldBid = $(this).find("name[Gold Canadian $]").children('bid').text(); &lt;?xml version="1.0" encoding …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:17:40">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18812861/magento-update-prices-based-on-precious-metal-price</link><title>Q: Magento: Update prices based on precious metal price</title><description>the product price will be current gold price * product wight + markup. I have subscribed for a feed providing metals prices, but i need to embed that functionality. Is there a extension that can deal with that? Thank you! … i am making site that offers precious metals products like coins, bullion and so on and i need to have the prices of those product auto update then the price of a precious metal is changed. Basically …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:18:17">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/20988807/product-weight-based-price-option-required-in-prestashop</link><title>Q: Product weight based price option required in prestashop</title><description>I need an option to set price based on the product weight. For eg, let us consider the senario of gold/silver ornaments. 1 gm gold ornament rate is calculated based on the current market price … of gold rate. ie., product rate = weight * current metal rate. How this can be done in prestashop? Any one kindly help me. . . …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:19:11">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10082201/changing-prices-in-opencart-according-to-script</link><title>Q: Changing prices in OpenCart according to script</title><description>and selling at a loss. I've written a script that is attached that pulls the gold, silver, and platinum price, then denominates the prices in bitcoins. So, for each metallic item on the website, I'd like … ounce gold coin, of the Krugerrand type: a quarter ounce gold coin weighs 7.77 grams, so on the product page the weight would be listed with that figure. The base price would be set at 7.77 grams …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:20:23">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10244133/set-product-price-programatically-with-weight-and-tax-percentage-in-magento</link><title>Q: Set Product Price programatically with weight and tax percentage in Magento</title><description>I have a online jewellery store build with magento. The products are gonna be in gold. Since the gold price needs to be changed daily. we have planned to have a separate section to feed the gold … price daily. now i wanna set the price of the any product with the global gold price obtained in the previous section with the weight of the product. There are also some more parameters involved …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>