<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:22:12" name="StackOverflow" id="FW14-e131"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:22:13">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/10661521/idea-needed-about-vehicle-counting-by-analysing-the-white-pixels-of-the-binary-f/10661577#10661577</link><title>A: Idea needed about vehicle counting by analysing the white pixels of the binary foreground image</title><description>Isolate the traffic from the background - take two images, run high pass filter on one of them, convert the other to a binary image - use the binary image to mask the filtered one, you should be able … to use edge detection to identify the roof of each vehicle as a quadrilateral and you should then be able to compute a relative measure of it. You then have four scenarios: no quadrilaterals …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:23:03">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/15250564/good-practice-for-setting-up-multiple-wcf-services-in-virtual-directories-under</link><title>Q: Good practice for setting up multiple WCF services in virtual directories under one root url</title><description>they won't affect other live WCF services running. Normally I isolate them by website, but since these are all under one 'roof' so to speak, Ihave to do some IIS trickery to properly isolate them. I had … I am setting up our server to handle all our WCF web services. What I want to know is, what is the best practice for proper isolation of each service under one root domain? I'm using something like …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:23:45">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/2814317/performance-analysis-strategies/2814400#2814400</link><title>A: Performance analysis strategies</title><description>.. Have sysadmin/netadmin monitor network saturation. Copy production data and code to another, isolated test system and measure performance. See where CPU and Disk performance go through the roof …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:24:21">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/11875983/play-flash-video-streaming-with-external-program/12282495#12282495</link><title>A: Play flash video / streaming with external program</title><description>you'll notice your CPU usage run through the roof, which heats your older laptop up to the point where it shuts itself off to prevent damaging it's internal components. (also uses a ton of power/drain … is something like an extension or plugin for chrome or firefox. There are countless of these that will isolate the flash video on the site you're on and let you download, and possibly convert …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:25:39">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/8256723/python-whats-the-difference-between-pythonbrew-and-virtualenv/21966507#21966507</link><title>A: python: what's the difference between pythonbrew and virtualenv?</title><description>like rvm does. This allows to isolate python version and libraries installed used for each project. However, it does not install python versions itself. Thus, sounds like most people use a combination … and switch between them. PS: I am just starting to figure it out, please correct me if anything here is wrong. PPS: It seems to me that this whole business can be improved by combining pyenv and virtualenv under one roof... …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e131-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e131/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:26:58">http://stackoverflow.com/questions/13121482/grouping-data-in-pairs</link><title>Q: Grouping data in pairs</title><description>in using the already parsed results within a loop. I have a long string of HTML I'm trying to parse with PHP. So far, I have preg_match's that are isolating what I want, but I would like some help … regular expressions are isolating the headings and paragraphs, and I'm using a for loop to grab less than or equal to 13 results, because the div into which they will be output has limited dimensions …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>