<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:13:38" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:13:39">http://movies.about.com/od/reeveskeanu/</link><title>Keanu Reeves \- Hollywood Movies \- About.com</title><description>Info on actor Keanu Reeves including photos, movie news, reviews, Keanu Reeves interviews, and sites featuring Keanu Reeves' biography, movies, and music ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:18:00">http://movies.about.com/cs/somethingsgotto/a/smtgkr120703.htm</link><title>Something's Gotta Give - Keanu Reeves Interview - Hollywood Movies</title><description>Keanu Reeves interview on the romantic comedy movie Something's Gotta Give starring Jack Nicholson and Diane Keaton.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:20:55">http://movies.about.com/od/somethingsgotto/</link><title>Something's Gotta Give Movie \- Jack Nicholson, Keanu Reeves ...</title><description>Information on the romantic comedy movie Something's Gotta Give, starring Jack Nicholson, Diane Keaton and Keanu Reeves. Something's Gotta Give movie ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:21:37">http://movies.about.com/library/weekly/blsomethingsgottopicsa.htm</link><title>Something's Gotta Give Movie Photo Gallery - Jack Nicholson Diane ...</title><description>Photos from the movie Something's Gotta Give starring Jack Nicholson, Diane Keaton, Keanu Reeves, Amanda Peet and Frances McDormand.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:24:42">http://movies.about.com/od/constantine/</link><title>Keanu Reeves, Constantine Photos, Credits, Trailer, Interviews</title><description>Information on the movie Constantine, starring Keanu Reeves and Rachel Weisz. Constantine movie synopsis, photos, interviews, Constantine movie cast, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:16">http://movies.about.com/od/thedaytheearthstoodstill/a/earth-stood.htm</link><title>Day the Earth Stood Still - Keanu Reeves, Jennifer Connelly</title><description>Keanu Reeves, Jennifer Connelly, Jon Hamm, and director Scott Derrickson discuss The Day the Earth Stood Still, the 2008 remake of the classic sci-fi movie.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:06">http://movies.about.com/cs/matrix3/a/matrix3review.htm</link><title>The Matrix Revolutions Movie Review - Keanu Reeves Carrie-Anne ...</title><description>Review of the movie The Matrix Revolutions, starring Keanu Reeves, Carrie- Anne Moss, Hugo Weaving and Laurence Fishburne. The Matrix Revolutions movie ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:15">http://movies.about.com/cs/somethingsgotto/a/smtgdk120703_2.htm</link><title>'Something's Gotta Give' and Kissing Keanu Reeves \- Hollywood ...</title><description>Diane Keaton discusses Something's Gotta Give, kissing Keanu Reeves, nude ... I just trusted Nancy's expertise about a movie that was so close to her heart.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:50">http://movies.about.com/library/weekly/blconstantinepicsa.htm</link><title>Constantine Movie Photos - Constantine Photos, Keanu Reeves ...</title><description>Photos from the movie Constantine, featuring Keanu Reeves, Rachel Weisz, Djimon Hounsou, Shia LaBeouf and Gavin Rossdale.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7026-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7026_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:29">http://movies.about.com/library/weekly/aasomethingsgottotrailer.htm</link><title>Something's Gotta Give Movie Trailer - Hollywood Movies \- About.com</title><description>Movie trailer for Something's Gotta Give starring Jack Nicholson, Diane Keaton, Amanda Peet and Keanu Reeves.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>