<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:55:19" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:55:20">http://sbinfocanada.about.com/cs/startup/a/needtosucceed_3.htm</link><title>Business Start Up Money - Finding the Money to Start a Business</title><description>5 Resources You Need to Succeed to Start a Business. Start up Money. Image (c) Paul Eekhoff / Getty Images. Top Related Searches; small business advisors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:56:46">http://biztaxlaw.about.com/od/startingyourbusiness/tp/startupsummer.htm</link><title>Starting a Business - Steps to Starting a Small Business</title><description>5 First Steps to Business Startup ... Finding Business Advisors to Help with Startup. You will need an attorney and a CPA to help you with business startup.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:11">http://biztaxlaw.about.com/u/ua/businessstartupsteps/noattnyatstart.htm</link><title>Start a Business Attorney - Why You Don't Need a Start-up Attorney</title><description>Why you don't need an attorney to help you with business startup. ... For example, forming a LLC in NY rather than a corporation will result in a $1600 publication fee. ... (copyrighted trademark without attorney,y) www.eatonrealtyadvisors.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:42">http://financecareers.about.com/od/fullservicefirms/a/HighTower.htm</link><title>Jobs at HighTower Advisors \- Financial Careers - About.com</title><description>HighTower Advisors is a new financial advisory firm serving high net worth clients . ... HighTower is headquartered in Chicago, with other administrative offices in New ... Negatives: As a startup, HighTower is very much a work in progress, with  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:04:15">http://biztaxlaw.about.com/od/accounting-advisors/tp/Finding-Financial-And-Tax-Advisors-Bookkeeper-Accountant-And-Cpa.htm</link><title>Accountant - CPA - Bookkeeper - Financial and Tax Advisors</title><description>Find out questions to ask when hiring financial or tax advisors, and how to fire a ... an accountant to help you navigate the maze of legal requirements for startup.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:08:09">http://sbinformation.about.com/cs/bestpractices/a/aa021603a.htm</link><title>Peer Business Advisor Groups Ease The Pressure of Ownership</title><description>Small business owners achieve great benefits from the power of a peer advisory group. Learn how joining a group of small business peers can ease the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:08:52">http://entrepreneurs.about.com/od/salesmarketing/a/firstclient.htm</link><title>How to Land Your First Consulting Client - Entrepreneurs - About.com</title><description>No one will stop you from calling yourself a consultant and startup can cost as little ... After all, research shows that clients use their networks to select consultants ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:11:13">http://nonprofit.about.com/od/boardquestions/a/6-Questions-And-Answers-About-Your-Nonprofits-First-Board-Of-Directors.htm</link><title>Your Nonprofit's First Board of Directors - About.com</title><description>Recruiting and organizing your nonprofit's first board of directors may be the most important thing you do. The right mix of people and skills will get your startup ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:06">http://biztaxlaw.about.com/od/startingyourbusiness/</link><title>Starting a Business, Buying a Business - US Business Law / Taxes</title><description>... in the process of starting a small professional practice in the Chicago area. ... If you have questions, want to comment, give them advice, go to the Startup ... you will need for your first business tax return, including finding a tax advisor,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:58">http://careerplanning.about.com/od/occupations/a/wedding_planner.htm</link><title>Wedding Planner - Career Information - Career Planning - About.com</title><description>Find out what skills you need, what your earnings and startup costs will be, and ... People who work in this field are also known as wedding or bridal consultants.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>