<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:45:03" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:45:05">http://discipline.about.com/od/specificbehaviorproblems/a/Kids-Don-T-Listen-Change-How-You-Give-Directions.htm</link><title>Kids Don't Listen? Change How You Give Directions - Discipline</title><description>When kids don't listen, parents need to change how they give instructions. ... A simple change in the way you word something can greatly improve your chances ... For example, if you want a child to pick up his toys, don't say, “Can you please  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:46:59">http://marriage.about.com/od/listening/a/0607notlisten.htm</link><title>Reasons Why Your Spouse Won't Listen to You</title><description>A listening problem in your marriage could be related to issues that your ... Comments that use words like "always", "never", and "constantly" can cause a ... If your spouse says no, don't get pouty. ... Perhaps you do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:48:35">http://christianity.about.com/od/whatdoesthebiblesay/a/Obedience-To-God.htm</link><title>Obedience To God - What Does The Bible Say About Obedience?</title><description>But don't just listen to God's word. You must do what it says. Otherwise, you are only fooling yourselves. For if you listen to the word and don't obey, it is like ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:50:33">http://babyparenting.about.com/od/childdevelopment/a/casualremarks.htm</link><title>Casual Remarks - Toddlers and Twos - About.com</title><description>... assume that our children don't understand or even listen to the things we say ... the cherished subjects of the offensive comments are listening to every word.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:53:34">http://christianity.about.com/od/practicaltools/a/part4spendtime_3.htm</link><title>The Word of God - Spending Time With God - Part IV (Page 3)</title><description>Knowing means nothing if we don't do what it says. James wrote about this: Do not merely listen to the word, and so deceive yourselves. Do what it says. Anyone  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:56:32">http://marriage.about.com/od/conflictandanger/a/Upset-Spouse.htm</link><title>Upset Spouse? Here's What to Do and What Not to Say \- Marriage</title><description>You can upset your spouse even more if you don't acknowledge your spouse's feelings, if you try to fix things, or if you downplay the reason your ... Listening involves more than hearing what your spouse has to say. ... Actually say the words.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:39">http://christianity.about.com/od/womensresources/a/hearingfromgod.htm</link><title>How to Hear from God and Know His Voice - Christianity - About.com</title><description>God smacking people whenever they don't listen. ... His Word In order to actually "hear" from God, we have to know some things about God's character. ... One of my favorite authors, Joyce Meyer, says, "There's no such thing as a driv...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:00:25">http://shakespeare.about.com/od/teachingshakespeare/a/shakespeare_words.htm</link><title>Shakespeare Words – How to Understand Shakespeare Words</title><description>Shakespeare Words \- Shakespeare's words and phrases are easier to ... like listening to a strong accent and your ear soon adjusts to the new dialect. ... Where today we would say “don't hurt me,” Shakespeare would have said “hurt me not.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:03:28">http://tweenparenting.about.com/u/ua/familyhome/Explicit-Lyrics.htm</link><title>Explicit Lyrics \- How Do You Handle Explicit Lyrics with Your Preteen?</title><description>I don't really pay that much attention to the lyrics. .... rock, I don't care about it they can say bad language exept ni*** and other mean words they don't often say.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:06:09">http://marriage.about.com/cs/listening/a/spouselisten.htm</link><title>When Your Spouse Won't Listen \- Marriage - About.com</title><description>You cannot force your mate to hear what you are saying or to understand how you are feeling if your partner don't want to. Forcing or manipulating someone into ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>