<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:09:24" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:09:25">http://usgovinfo.about.com/od/incometaxandtheirs/a/Federal-Gas-Tax-Rates.htm</link><title>The Gas Tax - A History - US Government Info - About.com</title><description>Jun 28, 2011 ... Find out how much gas tax the federal government collects. ... Drivers now pay 18.4 cents a gallon in the federal gas tax. ... the fiscal year 1932, a time of severe depression when the government saw revenue in steep decline.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:11:42">http://useconomy.about.com/od/grossdomesticproduct/f/katrina_damage.htm</link><title>Hurricane Katrina Damage Facts and Economic Effects - US Economy</title><description>Oct 31, 2012 ... Many factors contributed, including Katrina's path through the Gulf oil fields ... oil prices to increase by $3 a barrel, and gas prices to nearly reach $5 a gallon. ... than during the Dust Bowl migration during the Great Depressi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:14:03">http://useconomy.about.com/od/inflationfaq/tp/Types-of-Inflation.htm</link><title>Different Types of Economic Inflation - US Economy - About.com</title><description>1\. Creeping Inflation. People know that next year's car model will probably cost more. ... During the Great Depression of 1929, prices dropped 10% -- a year.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:14:54">http://cars.about.com/b/2012/10/01/vote-are-cars-like-the-audi-s-series-still-relevant.htm</link><title>Vote: Are cars like the Audi S-series still relevant? - About.com</title><description>Oct 1, 2012 ... Just like paying three times as much to fix the vehicle or extra costs to insure it. ... the factors in the equation not how much a gallon of gas costs or how ... for the high end – even in the Thirties during the Depression some fo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:18:35">http://politicalhumor.about.com/library/blbushisms.htm</link><title>Bushisms - Funny George Bush Quotes Updated Frequently</title><description>Keep up to date on all the latest adventures in Bushspeak with this hilarious ... 8, 2009\. "So I analyzed that and decided I didn't want to be the president during a depression greater than the Great Depression, or the .... "And I, unfort...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:20:05">http://cars.about.com/u/ua/toppicks/ua_fuelefficient.htm</link><title>Your picks: Favorite fuel-efficient cars - About.com</title><description>The diesels in europe are much much more efficient as hybrids and do not have the ... Okay the way to go is the fuel cell car but until then the diesel would be the ... such waste after all the tribulation the depression era generation went through...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:21:53">http://useconomy.about.com/od/criticalssues/tp/future_predictions.htm</link><title>Forecast of Top Ten Economic Trends - US Economy - About.com</title><description>Nov 6, 2013 ... Business taxes are passed on through higher prices, or through layoffs ... The successful raid to eliminate Osama bin Laden showed that special ops are more cost-effective. ... Before you panic over $5 a gallon gas, find out how You...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:23:45">http://chemistry.about.com/b/2010/08/20/why-you-shouldnt-mix-bleach-and-ammonia-bleach-and-ammonia-chemical-reactions.htm</link><title>Why You Shouldn't Mix Bleach and Ammonia - Bleach ... \- Chemistry</title><description>Aug 20, 2010 ... And then the ammonia and chlorine gas react to form chloramine, ... Then I poured 1 gallon of bleach down the gofer hole and then one .... Wow, bleach and amonia is so much easier – and I don't have to wash the shovel afterwards. ....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:26:43">http://suvs.about.com/od/fueleconomy/a/jf_gasguzzler.htm</link><title>The Gas Guzzler Federal Tax- Is My SUV a Target? - SUVs &amp; Minivans</title><description>The Gas Guzzler Tax is a graduated Federal excise tax that is added on to the cost of new vehicles that don't reach certain fuel economy standards. ... When the law was first enacted in 1978, SUVs and light trucks represented less than 25% of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:28:09">http://usliberals.about.com/b/2007/11/06/american-middle-class-rage-over-bush-economic-spending-priorities.htm</link><title>American Middle-Class Rage Over Bush Economic, Spending ...</title><description>Nov 6, 2007 ... Yesterday, as I paid $3.39 per gallon for gas, I wondered why economic ... has caused many families to switch from home equity loans to credit cards to ... to the 24% decline experienced during the Great Depression of 1929.".</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>