<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:32:15" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:32:17">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/flyfishingbasic1/a/Fly-Fishing-Small-Creeks.htm</link><title>Fly Fishing Small Creeks - About.com</title><description>Many of us have to travel, one, two, even three miles to get on a quality trout river where we ... When it comes to fly fishing tiny creeks like I do, preparation is key.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:33:28">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/flyfishingbasic1/a/What-Size-Fly-Rod-Should-I-Use.htm</link><title>What Size Fly Rod Should I Use? - Fly Fishing \- About.com</title><description>You can always get away with fishing lighter gear on larger waters, but it's tough to fish oversized gear on ... For larger waters, fish and flies, you have to go big.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:36:00">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/fishspecies/tp/Steelhead-Fishing-Tips.htm</link><title>Steelhead Fishing \- Five Keys to Catching Steelhead Trout</title><description>Steelhead. Sea-run trout. Call them what you want, these silver beasts are among the best fighters you'll ever tussle with in a freshwater stream -- if you can find ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:36:51">http://sandiego.about.com/od/outdoorrecreatio1/tp/top_lakes.htm</link><title>Top Lakes For Fishing in San Diego - About.com</title><description>Although trout can be snagged during the right time, largemouth bass is king here. ... feet above sea level, thus making it the ideal spot for trout fishing in the county, due to the fish's need for cold climate. ... If you fly fish, this is where ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:39:19">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/flyfishingbasic1/a/Fly-Rod-Sizes.htm</link><title>What Fly Rod Sizes to Use - Fly Fishing \- About.com</title><description>What fly rod sizes to use while fly fishing could be a bit confusing for ... medium sized rivers, go with a hybrid rod that can fish both types of fisheries, ... If anything , you want to get a rod that's a happy medium if you fish different types o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:41:41">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/fishspecies/a/Fly-Fishing-For-Carp.htm</link><title>Fly Fishing for Carp - How to Fly Fish for Carp - About.com</title><description>Have you ever wanted to fly fish for carp, but didn't know where to start? ... a client thirty shots at carp he learns his weaknesses,language and is ready to go. ... Casting is the main focus as the double haul is needed and presenting flies with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:44:37">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/wheretofish/a/River-Fly-Fishing.htm</link><title>River Fly Fishing Tips - About.com</title><description>River fly fishing tips, including the different species that inhabit our favorite ... First of all, you need to know where river trout are hanging out when you go river fly fishing. ... Bass can also be found on many rivers, although not as often a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:47:38">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/wheretofish/a/Best-Fly-Fishing-In-The-Western-US-Montana-Idaho-Colorado-Washington.htm</link><title>Best Fly Fishing in the Western U.S. - About.com</title><description>This is by no means THE list of the best fly fishing waters out there, rather a collection of some ... But you're going to have to hike in to find the best ones. ... With the Weber and Ogden Rivers bookending the town, you can't go wrong in Odgen,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:51:18">http://gotexas.about.com/od/fishing/a/RainbowTrout.htm</link><title>Texas Rainbow Trout Fishing \- Texas Travel \- About.com</title><description>However, in addition to excellent year around rainbow trout fishing in the ... Texas residents and visitors have literally dozens of locations to fish during the winter ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:53:49">http://flyfishing.about.com/od/flyfishingbasic1/a/Fly-Fishing-For-Monster-Trout.htm</link><title>Fly Fishing for Monster Trout - About.com</title><description>Tips on fly fishing and catching monster trout from a Montana guide who knows ... Every red blooded fly fisherman needs to catch at least one monster at some time in ... behind the counter of at least one fly shop and your hog photo will go viral ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>