<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:02:15" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:02:16">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/russia/ss/photourkremlin.htm</link><title>Photo Tour of the Moscow Kremlin - Pictures and Info about the ...</title><description>Tour the Moscow Kremlin through this picture gallery. Photos and information accompany each element of the Kremlin, from the Grand Kremlin Palace to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:03:49">http://gorussia.about.com/od/moscow_attractions/tp/Soviet-Sights-In-Moscow-Moscow-Ussr-Sites.htm</link><title>Soviet Sights in Moscow – Moscow USSR Sites - Russia Travel</title><description>If you're a history buff – or just curious about the Moscow sights &amp; attractions that are relics of the Soviet Union – here is a USSR tour of Moscow: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:08:08">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/moscowtravel/a/Moscow-Greeter-Tours.htm</link><title>Moscow Greeter - Free Tours of Moscow, Russia</title><description>Free tours by local guides offer visitors the opportunity to see the real Moscow! Learn how Muscovites live and see a side of the city you can't see on a guided ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:12:00">http://cruises.about.com/od/grandcirclecruises/ss/gct_Rossia.htm</link><title>Russian Waterways Cruise Tour -Grand Circle M/S Rossia - St ...</title><description>This article focuses on a tour of the cabins, deck areas, interior common ... Grand Circle Russian Waterways M/S Rossia CruiseTour - St. Petersburg to Moscow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:14:01">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/russia/p/vodkamuseum.htm</link><title>Vodka Museum in Moscow Features Russia's National Drink</title><description>The Vodka Museum in Moscow is an opportunity to learn about Russia's favorite ... The facilities will take visitors on a tour through Russian vodka history, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:16:01">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/russia/tp/moscowfive.htm</link><title>Moscow Must-See Sights - Eastern Europe Travel - About.com</title><description>Say goodbye to Moscow with a boat tour through the city. In summer, boat tours are pleasant and relaxing, and this alternative view of the city is charming.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:18:02">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/moscowtravel/</link><title>Moscow Travel - Travel to Moscow Russia - Eastern Europe Travel</title><description>Moscow Metro Photos Take this tour of the Moscow Metro's most beautiful stations, likened to palaces or art. Their interiors were created with fine materials by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:19:28">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/moscowtravel/tp/Moscow-Travel.htm</link><title>Moscow Travel - Guide for Visitors to Moscow, Russia</title><description>It's the top tourist attraction in Moscow and shouldn't be missed under any circumstances! This tour of the Moscow Kremlin shows photos of its features and offers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:20:36">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/russia/tp/healthandsafetyrussia.htm</link><title>Important Health and Safety Tips for Russia Travel</title><description>Large cities like Moscow and St. Petersburg have large, mixed populations, so under most ... The one-night stand might seem like a fun addition to your trip.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:22:36">http://goeasteurope.about.com/od/moscowtravel/ss/stalinsisters.htm</link><title>Photos of Stalin's Seven Sisters in Moscow \- Eastern Europe Travel</title><description>Moscow State University - Main Building Exemplifies Stalinist Architecture ... Luxury Hotels in Moscow \- Moscow Luxury Hotels · Photo Tour of the Moscow ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>