<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:10:55" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:10:56">http://golosangeles.about.com/od/latravelplanning/tp/TopMyths.htm</link><title>Top 10 Myths and Misconceptions about Los Angeles</title><description>Los Angeles Beach Cities Weather by Month ... areas in Hollywood, Downtown LA, Venice Beach, Santa Monica, Pasadena, Long Beach and down the coast.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:12:54">http://gocalifornia.about.com/od/casdmenu/a/San-Diego-Camping-Campgrounds.htm</link><title>San Diego Camping - California Travel - About.com</title><description>San Diego Camping: In and Near the City. You can choose San ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:14:09">http://gocalifornia.about.com/od/calamenu/a/la_christmas.htm</link><title>Christmas in Los Angeles - California Travel - About.com</title><description>Oddly for such a big city, many of these activities have a small-town flavor, making ... Take Pacific Coast Hwy to Robert Rd (near the Redondo Beach Hollywood ... Naples Island is a canal-filled section of Long Beach where people take a lot of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:16:29">http://bipolar.about.com/b/2012/02/06/highly-sensitive-to-noise.htm</link><title>Highly Sensitive to Noise? - Bipolar Disorder - About.com</title><description>Feb 6, 2012 ... I went through trauma of noise in Long Beach, CA with the .... The noise from the traffic, boom cars, city buses, ambulances, ..... attuned to the subtleties of the surrounding environment light, noise, sound, temperature, etc.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:20:22">http://orangecounty.about.com/od/neighborhoods/p/Fullerton-An-Industrial-College-Town.htm</link><title>Neighborhood Profile: Fullerton, California</title><description>With roots as a wild west railway town, Fullerton, California grew explosively ... school -- education services in Fullerton as well as several surrounding cities.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:23:07">http://gocalifornia.about.com/od/calamaps/</link><title>Best Los Angeles Road Maps and Information - California Travel</title><description>A collection of maps of County and city. ... This Los Angeles beach map shows the locations of the best beaches from Malibu to Long Beach. Downtown Los ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:25:41">http://gocalifornia.about.com/cs/sanfrancisco/a/unionsquare.htm</link><title>Union Square San Francisco - California Travel - About.com</title><description>The city's first mayor probably didn't imagine that would happen when he set Union ... surround Union Square, and shopping extends blocks from the central plaza. ... Museum of Modern Art. Chinatown and North Beach are behind you, and the ... Post ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:26:15">http://gocalifornia.about.com/od/calamenu/tp/hotels_santa_monica_malibu.htm</link><title>Top Hotels in Santa Monica and Malibu - California Travel - About.com</title><description>Use this guide to find the best-rated hotels in Malibu and Santa ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:27:44">http://golosangeles.about.com/od/thingstodoindowntownl1/tp/Thing-to-Do-in-Downtown-Los-Angeles.htm</link><title>Top Things to Do in Downtown Los Angeles - Los Angeles Travel</title><description>Unlike other large cities, many people visit Los Angeles without ever setting foot ... is still the hub of long distance and commuter rail transportation in Los Angeles , ... Multiple live entertainment venues and restaurants surround the Nokia Plaz...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:28:22">http://crime.about.com/od/murder/a/blackdahlia.htm</link><title>The Black Dahlia Murder Case - Crime and Punishment - About.com</title><description>In July 1946, she moved to Long Beach, California to be with an old boyfriend, Gordon Fickling, who she dated in Florida before her relationship with Matt ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>