<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:51:41" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:51:42">http://dc.about.com/od/museums/p/NaturalHistory.htm</link><title>Smithsonian National Museum of Natural History \- Washington DC</title><description>The Smithsonian National Museum of Natural History is one Washington, DC's best museums, learn about the Natural History exhibits and see visiting tips.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:52:29">http://gonyc.about.com/od/museums/tp/AMNH.htm</link><title>American Museum of Natural History (AMNH) Visitors Guide - NYC</title><description>Want to visit the American Museum of Natural History? Check out our AMNH Visitors Guide with directions, admissions information, must-see exhibits and tips for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:53:50">http://dc.about.com/od/photosofmuseums/ig/NMNH/</link><title>National Museum of Natural History Pictures - Washington DC</title><description>See pictures from the National Museum of Natural History, the Smithsonian natural history museum in Washington, DC.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:55:20">http://dc.about.com/b/2014/04/14/natural-history-museum-to-build-new-dinosaur-hall.htm</link><title>Natural History Museum to Expand its Dinosaur Hall - Washington DC</title><description>6 days ago ... The National Museum of Natural History is set to exhibit one of the most complete T. rex specimens ever discovered! The Smithsonian museum ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:58:08">http://dinosaurs.about.com/od/dinosaurmuseums/p/amnh.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Exhibits at the American Museum of Natural History</title><description>Visiting the fourth floor of the American Museum of Natural History in New York is a bit like dying and going to dinosaur heaven: there are over 600 complete or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:02:03">http://gonyc.about.com/cs/atozmuseums/a/amnh.htm</link><title>American Museum of Natural History (AMNH) Basics - NYC</title><description>The American Museum of Natural History (AMNH) is home to a diverse collection of outstanding exhibits, including the Rose Planetarium. We've assembled all ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:04:31">http://godc.about.com/od/smithsonianmuseums/qt/NMNH_RO.htm</link><title>National Museum of Natural History \- A Smithsonian Museum</title><description>A favorite for kids of all ages, the National Museum of Natural History offers exhibits such as dinosaur skeletons, ant farms, the Sant Ocean Hall, gems and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:05:08">http://gonyc.about.com/od/upperwestmuseums/tp/amnh_exhibits.htm</link><title>Permanent Exhibits at the American Museum of Natural History \- NYC</title><description>Don't miss out on these great permanent exhibits when you visit the American Museum of Natural History. These exhibits are some of the best permanent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:05:55">http://dinosaurs.about.com/od/dinosaurmuseums/p/smithsonian.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Exhibits at the Smithsonian Institution National ... \- Dinosaurs</title><description>The Smithsonian Institution National Museum of Natural History is comparable in size to New York's American Museum of Natural History, but less of its floor ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:08:34">http://dc.about.com/od/touristattractions/ss/PhotosNatlMall_7.htm</link><title>Photo of the Smithsonian National Museum of ... \- Washington, D.C.</title><description>The National Museum of Natural History is part of the Smithsonian Institution and houses a national collection of more than 125 million natural science ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>