<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:53:00" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:53:01">http://chemistry.about.com/od/howthingsworkfaqs/f/fallleafcolor.htm</link><title>Why Do Leaves Change Color in the Fall? - Chemistry - About.com</title><description>Find out why leaves change color in the fall. Learn about the different pigments found in leaves and how bright autumn foliage is produced.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:55:11">http://chemistry.about.com/library/weekly/aa082602a.htm</link><title>Chemistry of Autumn Leaf Color - Fall Leaves \- About.com</title><description>Chemistry of Autumn Leaf Color - Fall Leaves: autumn leaf color ... In the absence of these pigments, other plant chemicals also can affect leaf color. An example ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:56:39">http://gonewengland.about.com/od/fallfoliage/a/whyleaveschange.htm</link><title>Why Do Leaves Change Color in the Fall? - New England Travel</title><description>Learn why leaves change color in the fall. Many factors combine to transform the landscape into a colorful fall palette. Here's the fascinating science behind the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:58:17">http://forestry.about.com/cs/fallcolor/a/fallcolor_2.htm</link><title>The Science of Leaf Change - How Tree Leaves Change Color in Fall</title><description>Fall leaf color change starts very subtly late in September and early October in ... OK, with science out of the way, on to "where can I find out about this years leaf ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:59:36">http://weather.about.com/od/climatechange/a/How-Weather-Affects-Fall-Colors.htm</link><title>How Weather Affects Fall Colors - About.com</title><description>Contrary to popular belief, weather doesn't cause leaves to change color; but it does determine color intensity and arrival.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:00:22">http://forestry.about.com/od/fallcolor/a/why_leaf_color.htm</link><title>Why Leaves in Fall Change Color - The Process Behind Leaf Color ...</title><description>... a resulting drop in chlorophyll and the lack of moisture causes leaf color change. ... This color wave starts as yellow appears but can be quickly replaced by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:03:34">http://forestry.about.com/od/fallcolor/ss/fall_leaf_xsec.htm</link><title>The Fall Leaf Color Change - Forestry - About.com</title><description>It takes a complex biological process to express fall colors in a tree species. I provide a short illustrate explanation of the process of autumn leaf color. ... 10 Best Trees You Should Plant · Tree Identification Using a Tree Leaf Key ·...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:06:22">http://usparks.about.com/od/fallfoliage/a/Fall-Colors.htm</link><title>Guide to Fall Colors in the U.S. - US National Parks - About.com</title><description>Why Do Leaves Change Colors? The answer lies in one word: chlorophyll. It's the chemical that gives leaves their green color. Chlorophyll is also responsible ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:09:35">http://detroit.about.com/od/Tours/a/Color-Change-And-Michigan-Fall-Foliage-And-Leaves.htm</link><title>Michigan Fall Foliage and Leaves \- Color Change and ... \- Detroit</title><description>Sep 26, 2013 ... Fall color driving tours include Michigan's Gold Coast by Traverse City and the Sleeping Bear ... When Do Leaves Change Color in Michigan?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:11:05">http://houseplants.about.com/od/diseases/f/FallingLeaves.htm</link><title>Why Are My Leaves Falling Off? -- Falling Leaves \- Houseplants</title><description>This is the most common cause of leaf drop, but it can be the hardest to correct. In my experience, shock is most often caused by a sudden change in conditions.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>