<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:44:16" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:44:17">http://womenshistory.about.com/od/basketball/a/timeline.htm</link><title>History of Women's Basketball</title><description>Aug 16, 2008 ... The history of women's basketball is as old as the history of basketball ... women's basketball began at Iowa State College, Carleton College, Mount ... known women's basketball game between two high schools was played in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:46:40">http://inventors.about.com/od/inventorsalphabet/a/James_Naismith.htm</link><title>James Naismith Biography and the History of Basketball \- Inventors</title><description>Biography of Canadian James Naismith who invented basketball in 1891. ... the YMCA (Young Men's Christian Association) training school, took a soccer ball and ... 1896, when the University of Iowa invited student athletes from the new University ....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:48:23">http://parentingteens.about.com/od/activitiesorteens/a/winteractivitiesteens.htm</link><title>Winter Activities for Teens 101 Fun Activities - Parenting Teens</title><description>Winter activities resource article for teens and their parents, 101 Fun Activities for Teens to Do This Winter. ... Go watch your high school basketball team.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:50:03">http://okc.about.com/od/ousooners/p/University-Of-Oklahoma-Sooners-Womens-Basketball.htm</link><title>University of Oklahoma Sooners Women's Basketball \- Oklahoma City</title><description>The Sooners women finished just 5-22 in Coale's first season and 8-19 the next, but a WNIT appearance in 1999 ... 22 Kellogg, Shaya F 6-2 182 Fr. Ames, Iowa ( Ames) ... Former Norman North High School boys' basketball head coach.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:50:35">http://homeschooling.about.com/u/sty/ncsg/ncsupportgroups/Lighthouse-Christian-Homeschool-Association.htm</link><title>Lighthouse Christian Homeschool Association - Submit an Entry ...</title><description>Lighthouse Eagles varsity girls at 2010 HSPN Tourney ... teen activities; Lighthouse Eagles basketball and volleyball; high school graduation; group Iowa testing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:52:26">http://okc.about.com/od/osucowboys/p/Oklahoma-State-University-Cowgirls-Womens-Basketball.htm</link><title>Oklahoma State University Women's Basketball \- Cowgirls Team ...</title><description>Started in 1972, the Oklahoma State University Cowgirls women's basketball program reached the NCAA tournament for the first time in ... Former Stillwater Public Schools junior high basketball coordinator ... 1/11/14 at Iowa State 6:00 p.m.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:53:53">http://sportscareers.about.com/od/careerpaths/a/ysportsofficial.htm</link><title>Youth Sports Official - Youth Sports Umpire - Youth Sports Referee</title><description>Officiating sports at the youth or high school levels provides a terrific outlet for women and men who care about scholastic sports but may not have the time to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:55:53">http://collegeapps.about.com/od/collegerankings/tp/20-best-liberal-arts-colleges.htm</link><title>Top Liberal Arts Colleges - 20 Top Ranked Colleges</title><description>The college has been true to the spirit of a liberal education since its founding in ... admissions; high percentage of students go on to graduate school; See cost, financial aid, ... A top women's college, Bryn Mawr is a member of the Tri-College ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:57:25">http://parentingteens.about.com/b/2011/01/14/moving-a-high-school-jr-to-a-new-town.htm</link><title>Moving a High School Jr to a New Town? - Parenting Teens \- About ...</title><description>Jan 14, 2011 ... He loves Iowa, where we have to move. The issue is .... My problem is my 15 yo who is a high school freshman this year. ...... He is a standout basketball and baseball player who has become a huge fish in a very small pond.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7260-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7260_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:58:56">http://chicago.about.com/od/familyhealthlifestyles/tp/ChicagoSummerCampsProSports.htm</link><title>Chicago Summer Camp - Chicago's Pro Team Sports Camps for ...</title><description>Find youth Chicago summer camps for the Bears, Bulls, Cubs, White Sox, ... elite training schools and youth summer camps in Illinois, Indiana, Michigan, Iowa, and Wisconsin. ... from beginner level to elite for children ages 3 through high school....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>