<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:32:57" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:32:59">http://marriage.about.com/od/entertainmen1/p/tomcruise.htm</link><title>The Marriage of Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes - About.com</title><description>The whirlwind romance and quick engagement of Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise ended after five years when Katie filed for divorce.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:34:03">http://movies.about.com/cs/thelastsamurai/a/smtc120103.htm</link><title>The Last Samurai Movie - Tom Cruise Interview - Hollywood Movies</title><description>Tom Cruise talks about his role in the movie The Last Samurai, training for the samurai movie, and what attracted him to the role. Tom Cruise interview from the  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:34:48">http://movies.about.com/od/cruisetom/</link><title>Tom Cruise Photos, Movies, News, and Interviews - Hollywood Movies</title><description>Tom Cruise movies, photos, Tom Cruise interviews, and news on this controversial actor.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:35:55">http://weddings.about.com/od/celebrityweddings/a/tomkat.htm</link><title>Katie and Tom Wedding Details - Weddings - About.com</title><description>On Saturday, November 18th, Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise were married in what was certainly the celebrity wedding of the year, if not the decade! This lavish  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:37:00">http://movies.about.com/b/2011/02/11/tom-cruise-rock-of-ages.htm</link><title>Tom Cruise Close to Signing on to Rock of Ages - Hollywood Movies</title><description>Feb 11, 2011 ... This deal's been rumored to be in the works for months, but now Tom Cruise has made it to the final negotiations stage to join Rock of Ages.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:37:53">http://marriage.about.com/od/entertainmen1/a/cruisequotes.htm</link><title>Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes Quotes - Marriage - About.com</title><description>The whirlwind romance and marriage of Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes continues to make the news. Here are quotes about their marriage relationship and future ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:39:04">http://divorcesupport.about.com/b/2012/06/29/tom-cruise-katie-holmes-to-divorce.htm</link><title>Tom Cruise, Katie Holmes To Divorce - Divorce Support - About.com</title><description>Jun 29, 2012 ... Given the way Tom Cruise has chosen to end his marriages in the past, the way Katie has handled this may be a case of Karma that is long ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:40:03">http://movies.about.com/od/jackreacher/ig/Photos/Rosamund-Pike-Tom-Cruise-Pic.htm</link><title>Rosamund Pike and Tom Cruise Jack Reacher Film Picture</title><description>Actors Rosamund Pike and Tom Cruise picture from the movie Jack Reacher. Page 7.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:41:05">http://movies.about.com/od/cruisetom/a/cruise042805.htm</link><title>Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes Hollywood Couple - Hollywood Movies</title><description>Every media outlet on the planet is reporting the news of Hollywood's latest hot couple. Tom Cruise of the upcoming "War of the Worlds" and Katie Holmes from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 01:41:57">http://movies.about.com/od/waroftheworlds/a/warworlds062805.htm</link><title>Wars of the Worlds Movie Review - Tom Cruise \- Hollywood Movies</title><description>If the world's not tired of Tom Cruise, then “War of the Worlds” should do spectacular business at the box office. Cruise's recent attention-grabbing engagement to ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>