<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:59:44" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:59:45">http://goitaly.about.com/od/restaurantsandcafes/tp/rome-traditional-foods.htm</link><title>What to Eat in Rome \- Traditional Foods of Rome Italy - Italy Travel</title><description>A good place in Rome to try traditional foods is Trattoria Checchino dal 1887. ... You can also visit the About.com guide to Italian Food to read up on Italian ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:00:26">http://goitaly.about.com/od/restaurantsandcafes/</link><title>Restaurants and Cafes in Rome, Italy - Italy Travel - About.com</title><description>Rome is a great city for Italian restaurants and cafes. Here you will find listings for ... Gelato - Italian Ice Cream - The Best Gelato in Rome Everyone loves gelato ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:01:17">http://goitaly.about.com/od/foodandwineofitaly/p/eatingout.htm</link><title>Eating Out in Italy - Italian Meal and Dining Customs - Italy Travel</title><description>Food is a very important part of Italian culture and dining it Italy can be a real ... rome jewish ghetto picture ... It's a good chance to experience Italian culture.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:02:02">http://goitaly.about.com/od/foodandwineofitaly/</link><title>Italian Food and Wine - Eating and Drinking in Italy - Italy Travel</title><description>Italian Food and Wine is very diverse - each region has its own special foods and ... and cafes, and books that will help you find the best places to eat in Rome.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:02:32">http://goitaly.about.com/od/restaurantsandcafes/tp/eating-in-rome.htm</link><title>Eating in Rome \- Restaurants and Food in Rome Italy - Italy Travel</title><description>This guide to eating in Rome will help you learn about Roman food and ... Food markets are a good place to get an introduction to the local cuisine and what's in ... or Lazio (the surrounding region), check this directory on our Italian Food site.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:03:18">http://goitaly.about.com/od/festivalsandevents/a/easter.htm</link><title>Easter in Italy - Italian Easter Traditions and Celebrations in Italy</title><description>Find out about Italian Easter traditions and Easter celebrations in Italy. Easter ... Good Friday and Easter with the Pope in Rome and Saint Peter's ... Easter food.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:04:18">http://goitaly.about.com/od/foodandwineofitaly/ss/shopping_italy.htm</link><title>Food Shopping in Italy - Italian Grocery Shopping Guide - Italy Travel</title><description>How to shop for groceries in Italian food stores and supermarkets. ... Well, the best way to save money in Italy is to buy picnic ingredients and walk to a park or nearby piazza to consume ... 72 Hours in Rome: What to See and Where to Eat.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:04:53">http://goitaly.about.com/od/thingstodoinitaly/u/italy-attractions.htm</link><title>Where to Go in Italy - What to See and Where to Go in Italy</title><description>Here are suggestions for what to see and do in Italy including Italy's top travel ... Italy's top travel destinations, off the beaten track suggestions, Italian food and wine, ... In Rome you'll encounter ancient monuments, medieval and Renaissanc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:06:08">http://goitaly.about.com/od/romeshopping/a/rome-food-markets.htm</link><title>Rome's Food Markets - Food Markets in Rome Italy - Italy Travel</title><description>Full of color and variety, Rome's food markets are a great place to find out what fruits, ... Following are Rome's top food markets and what to find in these markets.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:06:59">http://goitaly.about.com/od/restaurantsandcafes/tp/rome-restaurants.htm</link><title>Rome Restaurants \- Recommended Restaurants in Rome Italy</title><description>Use this guide to Rome restaurants to find recommended restaurants in Rome ... or exceptional just a very good, inexpensive Italian meal with good house wine.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>