<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:42:15" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:42:17">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/tp/Messi-Vs-Real-Madrid.htm</link><title>Lionel Messi vs Real Madrid \- The Argentine's Goals For Barcelona ...</title><description>A look at the goals Lionel Messi has scored against Real Madrid.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:42:46">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/a/Lionel-Messi-Vs-Cristiano-Ronaldo.htm</link><title>Lionel Messi vs Cristiano Ronaldo - World Soccer - About.com</title><description>When Barcelona meet Real Madrid the biggest subplot is the battle of Lionel ... Messi memorably scored the second goal against Manchester United in the 2009  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:43:32">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/tp/Five-Lionel-Messi-Videos.htm</link><title>Five Classic Lionel Messi Videos - World Soccer - About.com</title><description>There is a personal goalscoring duel between the pair each weekend in La Liga as Barca and Real Madrid dispose of the opposition almost at will.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:43:57">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/p/Cristiano-Ronaldo.htm</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldo - Profile of Real Madrid Soccer Player Cristiano ...</title><description>His US$131 million move from Manchester United to Real Madrid in 2009 made ... in the 2010-11 season, scoring the winning goal against Barcelona in the final. ... Barcelona's Lionel Messi would exceed that tally the following season, but ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:44:21">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/tp/Ten-Of-The-Best-Barcelona-Players.htm</link><title>A Look at the 10 Best Barcelona Players - World Soccer - About.com</title><description>A look at 10 of the best Barcelona players to have donned the famous blaugrana shirt. ... Messi is the club's record goalscorer and the 2009, 2010, 2011and 2012 ... A total of 274 goals in 345 appearances between 1950 and 1961 speaks for itself. ....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:45:13">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/leaguesandclubs/tp/Record-Champions-League-Scorers.htm</link><title>Record Champions League Scorers - World Soccer - About.com</title><description>Real Madrid's captain, the former Spain international was the club's talisman and ... It is now beyond doubt that Messi will become the record Champions League scorer. ... The Dutchman scored most of his Champions League goals with ... but realize...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:45:59">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/Soccer-History/a/Real-Madrid-Versus-Barcelona-The-History-Of-El-Clasico.htm</link><title>El Clásico History - Real Madrid's Rivalry With Barcelona</title><description>Real Madrid and Barcelona's rivalry is one of the most pungent ... between the two, as Rafael Morera's two goals ensured Los Merengues were 2-1 victors. ... Johan Cruyff, and of modern times Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo, have all  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:47:02">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/ig/Messigallery/Messi5.htm</link><title>Lionel Messi Photos - A Gallery of Lionel Messi Photos - World Soccer</title><description>Messi celebrates after scoring Barcelona's fifth goal against Real Madrid on May 2, 2009. Getty Images. A total of 38 goals in all competition in the 2008/09 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:47:44">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/players/a/Who-Is-Lionel-Messi.htm</link><title>Who Is Lionel Messi? - World Soccer - About.com</title><description>Messi became Barcelona's all-time leading scorer when he surpassed Cesar ... haul of 235 goals against Granada in March 2012, and is already considered ... The Real Madrid star is a magnificent physical specimen and goalscorer in his ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:48:58">http://worldsoccer.about.com/od/internationals/tp/worldcupmidfielders.htm</link><title>Best Midfielders - 10 of the Best Midfielders in the World</title><description>Strikers may score most of the goals, but many of the game's real artisans reside ... hostile reception that Barcelona players receive when they visit Real Madrid.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>