<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:22:07" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:22:08">http://running.about.com/od/shoesapparelandgear/a/foottypes.htm</link><title>How to Pick the Best Running Shoes for Your Foot Type</title><description>To figure out what type of running shoes are best for you, you first need to know that kind of feet you have. Here are the three types of feet, with tips on how to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:23:10">http://running.about.com/od/shoesapparelandgear/f/twopairsshoes.htm</link><title>Do I Need Two Pairs of Running Shoes? - Running and Jogging</title><description>Some experts recommend rotating two pairs of running shoes. Do I need to buy two pairs of running shoes?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:23:48">http://running.about.com/od/runningshoereviews/</link><title>Running Shoe Reviews and Recommendations for Runners</title><description>Choosing the right running shoes is one of the most important decisions you'll make as a runner. Get advice and recommendations for all types of feet and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:24:58">http://running.about.com/od/shoesapparelandgear/ht/runningshoe.htm</link><title>How To Buy the Right Running Shoes \- Running and Jogging</title><description>Choosing the right running shoes is one of the most important decisions you can make as a runner. Spending the time and money to get the best running shoes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:25:44">http://running.about.com/od/trailrunning/tp/besttrailrunningshoes.htm</link><title>Best Trail Running Shoes for Men - Running and Jogging - About.com</title><description>If you frequently run on trails or in inclement weather, you need a sturdy running shoe with added traction and a thicker sole. Check out these top trail running ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:26:51">http://running.about.com/od/runningshoereviews/tp/replacerunningshoes.htm</link><title>Signs Your Running Shoes Need to Be Replaced</title><description>Running in old or worn out running shoes can lead to running injuries. One of the best things you can do to prevent running injuries is to replace your shoes at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:27:55">http://walking.about.com/od/shoechoice/f/runningshoes.htm</link><title>Can You Wear Running Shoes for Walking? - About.com</title><description>Aug 31, 2013 ... Answer: Not all running shoes are good for walking, but most shoes you see designated as walking shoes at the average shoe store are worse.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:28:22">http://sportsmedicine.about.com/od/runningworkouts/tp/Stability-Shoes.htm</link><title>Best Stability Running Shoes \- Sports Medicine - About.com</title><description>Stability running shoes give athletes a mix of comfort and stability and are a good choice for athletes without major pronation and supination issues.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:28:54">http://running.about.com/od/shoesapparelandgear/f/replaceshoes.htm</link><title>When Should You Replace Running Shoes? - Running and Jogging</title><description>Running in old or worn-out shoes is one of the most common causes of running injuries. Get advice on when you should replace your running shoes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:29:36">http://sportsmedicine.about.com/cs/beforeyoubuy/a/aabyb_shoes.htm</link><title>What Is the Best Shoe for Your Foot Type - Sports Medicine - About ...</title><description>If you have trouble picking the best running shoes, it may help to learn more about your foot type before you shop for your next pair. Feet come in all shapes and ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>