<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:32:36" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:32:37">http://buddhism.about.com/od/Morality/a/Karma-And-Morality.htm</link><title>Karma in Buddhist Morality - How It Works - Buddhism - About.com</title><description>A doctrine of karma, then, is one that explains the effects of volitional action. ... that self-and-other are not two, and beings are not just autonomous units living inside their skin-pods. Our lives are interconnected with the lives of all beings. And it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:33:12">http://animation.about.com/od/flashanimationtutorials/ss/flashcs5_decovinefill.htm</link><title>Flash CS5 Deco Tool: Vine Fill Options - Computer Animation</title><description>The Deco Tool is a Flash feature that lets you auto-create multiple effects and ... pattern of interconnected vines, with leaves and flowers--or other shapes you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_03.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:33:48">http://useconomy.about.com/library/Official_Dodd_Frank.pdf</link><title>Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform and Consumer Protection Act</title><description>manipulation of the system that benefits special interests at the expense of. American families .... liquidating large, interconnected financial companies. FDIC can .... some “skin in the game” by the investment advisor--up to 3% of tier 1 capital...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:34:15">http://seniorliving.about.com/od/healthnutrition/a/skinanatomy.htm</link><title>Skin Anatomy: How Your Skin Protects You</title><description>As the largest organ in your body, your skin protects you in many amazing ways. ... depth of the subcutaneous fat layer is different from one person to another.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:34:43">http://lymphoma.about.com/od/whatislymphoma/p/lymphoma.htm</link><title>Lymphoma - What is Lymphoma? - Lymphoma Definition</title><description>The lymph system is an interconnected network of thin tubes and nodes that carries white blood ... Lymphoma may affect any of the parts of the lymph system.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:36:28">http://firstaid.about.com/od/coughing/qt/08_CoughFacts.htm</link><title>Coughing Facts - First Aid - About.com</title><description>Jan 11, 2014 ... It's all interconnected with several possible triggers and gray areas, ... like smoke or even the same type of allergies that cause itching of the skin. ... Effect of honey, dextromethorphan, and no treatment on nocturnal cough and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:39:34">http://classiclit.about.com/od/Perrault-Charles/fr/The-Fairy-Tales-Of-Charles-Perrault-Review.htm</link><title>'The Fairy Tales of Charles Perrault' Review - Classic Literature</title><description>Perrault, who was in favor with Louis XIV, provides two interconnected but ... The most strange and amazing of Perrault's tales, "Donkey Skin," is also one of his least ... fulfills her demands each time, to both shimmering and terrifying...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:40:17">http://mentalhealth.about.com/cs/familyresources/l/bladd.htm</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder Facts</title><description>Such children are showing the effects of other problems, not ADHD. .... evolves into a complex organ made of billions of specialized, interconnected nerve cells. ... These brain cell parts help to transmit incoming signals from our skin, eyes, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:41:16">http://addictions.about.com/od/LSD/a/What-Does-An-Acid-Trip-Feel-Like.htm</link><title>What Does It Feel Like to Get High on Acid - Addictions - About.com</title><description>An LSD trip is a lengthy process, typically lasting 8-12 hours, sometimes longer, and with the distortions in time perception that occur as a drug effect, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:41:54">http://vegetarian.about.com/u/ua/healthnutrition/healthyvegetariandiet.03.htm</link><title>Have you lost weight or improved your health on ... \- Vegetarian Food</title><description>I'm hoping to see even more health benefits as my time as a vegan increases, ... reasons but then began to realize that diet and health are totally interconnected. ... I have noticed my skin looks great, people want to know what I'm doing but its ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>