<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:29:34" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:29:35">http://workathomemoms.about.com/od/workathomecareers/ss/wahjobdirectory.htm</link><title>Work at Home Jobs \- Work at Home Company Directory - Page 1</title><description>Free directory of work at home jobs lists more than 200 companies that hire for ... "100 Best Companies to Work For," this management consultant company states on its ... desktop troubleshooting and software support from their home offices.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:30:07">http://homebusiness.about.com/od/consulting/tp/computer-home-based-business-ideas.htm</link><title>5 Computer Home Based Business Ideas</title><description>If you've been thinking about starting a computer home based business, ... software or the Internet, here are some home based business ideas to get you thinking. ... call centers whose employees were willing to work for a fraction of the cost. ......</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:30:42">http://homebusiness.about.com/od/money/a/homeofftax.htm</link><title>Office-in-Home Tax Deductions - Home Business Use of Your Home</title><description>If you qualify, taking deductions for business use of your home can save you money at tax time. ... I've even had tax software programs trip me on this. ... For example, if you're a consultant, you may work at client sites and do all of your ....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:31:22">http://workathomemoms.about.com/od/medicalandnursingjob1/tp/Work-At-Home-Physician-Jobs.htm</link><title>Work-at-Home Physician Jobs \- Work at Home Moms - About.com</title><description>Work-at-home physician jobs are not as common as nursing jobs from home, but not ... in pharmaceutical distribution and health care IT systems and software. ... chat, consulting with and possibly writing prescriptions for patients in the states in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:32:07">http://workathomemoms.about.com/od/workathomecareers/ss/wahjobdirectory_7.htm</link><title>Work-at-Home Jobs Company Directory - Work at Home Moms</title><description>When hunting for work at home jobs, start by finding a company in your field using ... Website providing software drivers and support info hires "database helpers" in ... Engineering consulting company based in Burlington, MA, has openin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:32:39">http://workathomemoms.about.com/od/companieshiringwahms/</link><title>Companies Hiring for Work-at-Home Jobs \- Work at Home Moms</title><description>These companies consistently hire for work-at-home jobs. ... Fields range from teaching and software development to call centers and translation. ..... experience and excellent interpersonal skills for work-at-home consultant positions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:33:39">http://entrepreneurs.about.com/od/salesmarketing/a/firstclient.htm</link><title>How to Land Your First Consulting Client - Entrepreneurs - About.com</title><description>The market for consulting services is estimated to be between $130B and $150B ... Work hard to land that first client, but also put the marketing and consulting ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:34:31">http://jobsearch.about.com/u/ua/jobsearchscams/jobscams.htm</link><title>Online Job Scams - Top Internet Job Search Job Scams - About.com</title><description>There are a variety of internet job scams, ranging from fake jobs to scams that try ... Employment Status: Full-Time, Part-Time or Contractor, Work from home ... real estate corporation designed to provide the most efficient financial consulting ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:35:30">http://workathomemoms.about.com/od/translatorsandinterpretor/p/Lionbridge.htm</link><title>Lionbridge - Translation and Internet Assessor Work at Home Jobs ...</title><description>For more about applying to its home-based positions, see this profile of VirtualBee. ... This includes developing products such as software, websites, marketing ... of a web search), social media search consultant (expressing opinions on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:35:58">http://homebusiness.about.com/od/workingathome/a/work-from-home.htm</link><title>Work from Home \- How to Find High Tech Work at Home Jobs</title><description>This article answers a readers question on how to find work at home with a high tech ... 500 companies or working for PWC and McKinsey in the consulting world. ... have advanced hardware and software needed to do your work from home.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>