<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:49:52" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:49:53">http://idtheft.about.com/od/leagalconcerns/a/Childrens-Online-Privacy-Act.htm</link><title>Children's Internet Protection Act - Identity Theft - About.com</title><description>The Children's Online Protection Act takes aim at these risks in public places. ... So, one identity theft concern is how to protect your kids from identity theft, which  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:50:47">http://familyinternet.about.com/od/computingsafetyprivacy/tp/stop_cyberbullies.htm</link><title>Cyberbullying - 10 Ways to Protect Your Children from Cyberbullying</title><description>Learn how to protect your kids from cyberbullying attacks. ... One of the best ways to understand what your kids are doing online is to do it, too. Create a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:51:26">http://familyinternet.about.com/od/computingsafetyprivacy/a/Safe_to_post_photos_of_kids_online.htm</link><title>Internet Safety - Is it Safe to Post Photos of My Kids Online?</title><description>... your kids? Learn the dangers of posting photos of kids, as well as ways to keep them safe. ... Protecting Your Kids When Sharing Photos Online. In addition to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:52:16">http://personalweb.about.com/od/parentsshouldwatchkids/Parents_Need_To_Watch_and_Protect_Their_Kids_Online.htm</link><title>Parents Need To Watch and Protect Their Kids Online \- Social Media</title><description>Kids are vulnerable because they are naive to the bad people in the world and are overly trusting or they think they are tougher, badder than the bad guys.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:52:45">http://bullying.about.com/od/Cyberbullying/a/6-Steps-To-Protecting-Your-Teens-Online-Reputation.htm</link><title>6 Steps to Protecting Your Teen's Online Reputation - Bullying</title><description>Do we really have any control over our kids' online reputations? Most Internet experts would say “yes.” But it is going to take some work. Here are six steps you  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:53:13">http://childparenting.about.com/od/technologyentertainment/a/Internet-Safety-For-Kids.htm</link><title>Internet Safety for Kids \- School-Age Children \- About.com</title><description>Today, more kids are online than ever, and at increasingly younger ages. What do parents need to know about how to protect them when they go on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:53:52">http://childparenting.about.com/od/familycomputer/a/kidsafeinternet.htm</link><title>Kid-Safe Internet Access - School-Age Children \- About.com</title><description>We have to be smart, and that means protecting our children when they are online. I advocate two different approaches to online safety - one is for a family ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:54:42">http://personalweb.about.com/cs/viewingsites/a/403siteblocking.htm</link><title>Keep Kids From Seeing Adult Sites - Social Media - About.com</title><description>There is some software out there that can help you protect your kids, and yourself , from viewing these pages. Before I show them to you I want to tell you about a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:55:32">http://parentingteens.about.com/cs/sitesforteens/a/internetusage.htm</link><title>What Parents Need To Know About Teens and Internet Usage</title><description>Note: While I will go on to the risks of Internet usage by our children, I do want to say ... Teach them to protect their privacy, that things aren't always what they seem. ... the search engines, are getting into the swing of online safety for our...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:56:14">http://divorcesupport.about.com/od/romanceafterdivorce/a/sexpredatorlinks.htm</link><title>Protect Your Children From Sexual Predators If You Date Online</title><description>Are you a single parent who is involved in online dating? If so, I caution you to not introduce your children to anyone you meat while dating online until you do a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>