<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7502">baby todler snowsuit</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:09:43" name="About.com" id="FW14-e050"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:09:44">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/carseats/a/carseatcoat.htm</link><title>Winter Coats and Car Seats - Baby Products - About.com</title><description>However, thick winter coats or snowsuits can compromise your child's car seat safety. In order for a baby car seat or toddler booster seat to function properly, the  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:10:37">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/clothing/bb/baby_snowsuit.htm</link><title>Before You Buy Winter Coats and Snowsuits for Baby \- Baby Products</title><description>Learn the pros and cons of the various winter coats and snowsuits for baby in ... If you are comfortable with a sweater and light coat, it's likely that your toddler ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:11:09">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/clothing/tp/baby_coats.htm</link><title>Winter Snowsuits and Fleece Coats for Babies and Toddlers - Top ...</title><description>Snowsuits and coats for babies and toddlers need to be warm but not too ... which is nice if your toddler will be wearing a coat for very long while in a car seat .</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:11:49">http://baby.about.com/od/healthandsafety/qt/Baby-Coats-In-Car-Seats.htm</link><title>Proper Use of Baby Coats in Car Seats - Baby's First Year - About.com</title><description>Did you know that baby coats can interfere with how well your car seat keeps your baby safe? ... Before You Buy Winter Coats and Snowsuits for Baby. See More ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:12:23">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/clothing/</link><title>Baby Clothes - Layettes - Toddler Clothes - Clothes and Shoes for ...</title><description>Buy a Winter Coat or Snowsuit for Baby Here's a quick and easy guide to choosing the perfect winter gear for baby. Baby Clothes Buying Guide Shopping for tiny ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:12:58">http://baby.about.com/u/ua/healthandsafety/Baby-Coats-And-Car-Seats.htm</link><title>Baby Coats and Car Seats - Baby's First Year - About.com</title><description>If your baby is in an infant car seat, get a COZY COVER. It is like a shower cap that fits over the whole car seat. Never put a baby in a snowsuit or heavy coat in a  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:13:37">http://baby.about.com/od/healthandsafety/tp/Winter-Baby-Warm-In-The-Car.htm</link><title>Winter Baby Products and Safe Car Seat Accessories - Travel and ...</title><description>How can you keep your baby warm and safe in cold weather? ... Yep, that's right; when not used wisely, winter coats and snowsuits can interfere with a car seat's ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:14:14">http://babyproducts.about.com/cs/tp.htm</link><title>Baby Products - TopPicks</title><description>Snowsuits and coats for babies and toddlers need to be warm but not too thick, ... videos that are sure to have your baby or toddler singing along in no time.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:14:49">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/bathsdiaperspotties/gr/boogie_wipes.htm</link><title>Boogie Wipes Review - Baby Products - About.com</title><description>Boogie Wipes are saline nose wipes for baby and toddler noses that are made to be more gentle. Do Boogie Wipes work? Learn more in this Boogie Wipes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e050-7502-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e050/7502_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:15:18">http://babyproducts.about.com/od/clothing/qt/choosing_baby_toddler_Halloween_costumes.htm</link><title>Baby &amp; Toddler Halloween Costumes - Choosing a ... \- Baby Products</title><description>Choosing a Halloween costume for your baby or toddler should be lots of fun, but ... You know the old snowsuit trick, where toddlers get all bundled up in their ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>