<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:41:02" name="Disney Family" id="FW14-e086"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:41:07">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>10 Reasons to Take Good Care of a Mother</title><description>Moms like us get stressed and depleted over time through the accumulation of a thousand little stressful things. But we can combat this problem by doing little nurturing things each day. And that self-care eventually wi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-02"><link>http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-type-1-diabetes/article-1046474-in-the-spotlight-managing-the-stress-of-a-new-diagnosis-t/</link><title>In the Spotlight: Managing the Stress of a New Diagnosis</title><description>Immediately post-diagnosis, some 60 percent of parents may experience significant stress, depression or anxiety. Here are solutions that can help.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:42:47">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>For a Few Dollars More.</title><description>Chris was paying the bills over the last couple of days and he discovered that we had a little more money in the account than usual. So what do we owe this newfound fortune? Inheritance? Windfall at the office? Extraord...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:43:33">http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-school-age/article-796133-dealing-with-the-loss-of-a-pet-t/</link><title>Dealing With the Loss of a Pet</title><description>How To Help Your Child Deal With the Loss of a Pet</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-05"><link>http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-type-1-diabetes/article-1035051-a-night-out-just-the-two-of-us-t/</link><title>Jen: A Night Out, Just the Two of Us</title><description>Parents of kids with type 1 diabetes particularly need to have some time to themselves, and this is ironically sometimes difficult to find -- though we've found a way.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:45:43">http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-preschool/article-800441-a-child--s-view-of-his-autistic-brother-t/</link><title>A Child's View Of His Autistic Brother</title><description>A Child's View On How His Family Dealt With His Brother's Autism</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:46:38">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>How to Be a Relaxed Parent</title><description>Your nightstand stacks up with all kinds of 'how-to' manuals as you seek soothing answers to these questions and others. As you read, you discover that taking care of a baby is much more complicated than you'd ever anti...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:47:55">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>To My Mother</title><description>Mom, today is your 70th Mother's Day! You first became a mother in November of 1936, during the Great Depression, when every penny counted and you wondered how in the world you and Pop could make the mortgage payment - ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:48:57">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>How Much To Pay A Babysitter</title><description>What do you want to know? Come ask the experts! A selection of answers to your questions will be regularly posted on the site.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:50:36">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>I was blown away by how much fun we had.</title><description>1 people found this helpful</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>