<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:32:32" name="Disney Family" id="FW14-e086"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:32:35">http://spoonful.com/family-fun/day-out-in-lower-manhattan-financial-district</link><title>A Day Out in New York's Lower Manhattan &amp; The Financial District</title><description>Although the southernmost tip of Manhattan is home to the New York Stock Exchange and Wall Street, the financial district is so much more than just banks and money. Three centuries ago this area was the birthplace of Ne...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-02"><link>http://family.go.com/travel/article-858483-upper-west-side-travel-t/</link><title>A Day Out in NYC's Upper West Side</title><description>To a non-New Yorker, Manhattan's Upper West Side neighborhood probably conjures up visions of the New York City created by the likes of Woody Allen and Jerry Seinfeld -- one filled with colorful and quirky characters. T...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:33:44">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>New York City in a Nutshell</title><description>The amazing Big Apple is one of my very favorite cities; I've visited as a single person, as part of a couple and as a parent, and the place just never disappoints. For a good overview of options, see Fo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:34:28">http://spoonful.com/family-fun/worlds-best-parks-playgrounds</link><title>The World's Best Parks and Playgrounds</title><description>Wee travelers need lots of outdoor time and exercise, and one of the best places to get that experience when you're traveling, just as when you're at home, is to hit the park. We wanted to let you in on some of the best...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:35:31">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Best to Let Baby Control Early Eating of Solids</title><description>Babies whose mothers give them more control over their early attempts at eating solid food appear to do a better job of regulating their own weight</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:36:25">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Let's Go to Memphis in the Meantime</title><description>1 people found this helpful</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:37:15">http://spoonful.com/family-fun/travel</link><title>New York City, New York | Kids Love a Bite From the Big Apple</title><description>Rise to the top of the Rock, ride the ferry past the Statue of Liberty, stroll Central Park, and of course, gobble the best pizza in the world.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:38:10">http://spoonful.com/family-fun/day-out-in-lower-east-side-chinatown</link><title>A Day Out in New York's Lower East Side and Chinatown</title><description>Manhattan's Lower East Side and Chinatown appear different on the outside than they do on the inside, and as you explore and peel back the layers you discover the history and soul of this unique part of the city.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:39:03">http://family.go.com/food/article-975467-three-tips-to-eat-more-fish-t/</link><title>Three Tips to Get Picky Eaters to Go Fish</title><description>Seafood is such a perfect food for kids, and yet it is something that so many children don't eat, often only because their parents think that they won't.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7109-10"><link>http://family.go.com/travel/article-913245-salem-travel-t/</link><title>A Day Out in Salem: Day Trip From Boston</title><description>Salem, Massachusetts, one of America's first cities, is a great getaway for a today's modern family — walking down the charming, cobblestone streets lined with old clapboard homes is a transporting experience.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>