<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:49:30" name="Disney Family" id="FW14-e086"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:49:34">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Kindergarten Chronicles: H is for Hundred and Y is for Year of the Rat</title><description>The Cheese has been going to kindergarten for one hundred days and oh my, what a big deal it is. Today is all about the number 100. Ever since the first day of school the kindergartners have been waiting for this day. E...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:50:44">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Mama's Kindergarten Chronicles: A is for Already Learning</title><description>After only five days into kindergarten, it is apparent that my son is already getting a good education. 'Mommy? Do you know what 'nocturnal' means?' the Cheese Eater asked me at the dinner table. 'Yes. Do you know what ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-03"><link>http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-type-1-diabetes/article-1024800-getting-on-a-good-schedule-for-the-school-year-t/</link><title>Getting on a Good Schedule for the School Year</title><description>Wish you could be one of those super-organized moms who's never forgotten a play date till the kid shows up on your doorstep? One way is to start, keep, and have everyone in the family consistently refer to a VERY detai...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:52:25">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>The Most Welcome Gift for a New Mom? Food</title><description>1 people found this helpful</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:53:16">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Starting a Book Club - Part Three</title><description>This is the third of four posts on Starting Your Own Book Club. If you missed the first two, click here for the 1st and here for the 2nd to get caught up.How to Select the Books ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:54:20">http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-back-to-school/article-747610-start-the-school-year-right-t/</link><title>Jump Start the School Year</title><description>With a bit of planning, communication and insight, parents can help their children – and themselves – get off to a great start for school this year.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:55:43">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>A big weekend for the MandaJuice family</title><description>On Friday, We got the keys to our first ever HOUSE. Dave and I have been married for almost a decade and this will be the first time we've had a home that didn't share walls with our neighbors. We've worked so hard to g...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:56:39">http://family.go.com/parenting/pkg-back-to-school/article-746201-ready-for-kindergarten-t/</link><title>Ease Kindergarten Jitters: Be Ready for the First Day of Kindergarten</title><description>A little planning can go a long way toward calming the jitters and bolstering confidence for youngsters starting kindergarten.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:57:30">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Family Movie Night is a Cure for Cabin Fever</title><description>1 people found this helpful</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:58:14">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Kindergarten Chronicles: G is for Guess-n-Go Spelling</title><description>The Cheese brought home a Thanksgiving card last week. On the front was a hand-print turkey and on the inside were the pre-printed words 'I am thankful for...' followed by blank lines. Here is what the Cheese wrote in h...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>