<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:11" name="Disney Family" id="FW14-e086"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:16">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-802378-mexican-rice-casserole-t/</link><title>Mexican Rice Casserole</title><description>This is an adaptation of an arroz con pollo recipe from the great Rick Bayless book 'Mexican Everyday.' The addition of zucchini makes it a more complete one-pot dinner, with less seasoning in the interest of kid-friend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:44">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-779157-green-greens-rice-casserole-t/</link><title>Green Greens Rice Casserole</title><description>Cheesy-green rice casserole makes a humble but delicious meal -- and a great way to showcase those enormous bunches of spinach, kale, or chard you may find at the farmer's market. Even if you usually use white rice, try...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:05">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-655926-rolled-crispy-rice-apples-t/</link><title>Rolled Crispy Rice Apples</title><description>Apples are the signature fruit of fall. Here's an easy recipe that makes the most of their fresh, crisp flavor. This fast snack can easily be made with organic ingredients for a sweet, healthful treat.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:29">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-641498-fried-rice-t/</link><title>Fried Rice</title><description>Leftovers are boring, blah and take up too much refrigerator space, right? I don't think so. I often make extras just for the sake of having leftovers for other dishes. Rice is one of those leftovers I look forward to m...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:56">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-645269--rice-pudding-t/</link><title>Rice Pudding</title><description>Rice is almost always served under something here in Dutch Pennsylvania -- whether it be gravy, chili or stewed chicken. The other way that it's enjoyed is in rice pudding. This is one of those dishes that everyone here...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:59:25">http://spoonful.com/recipes/mac-and-cheese-alfredo</link><title>Brown Rice &amp; Goat Cheese Cakes</title><description>Medium-grain brown rice has a toothsome texture and nutty flavor that complement creamy, earthy goat cheese in these elegant cakes. Serve over salad greens as a main course.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-07"><link>http://family.go.com/food/recipe-1009584-pizza-rice-balls-t/</link><title>Pizza Rice Balls</title><description>Your whole family will love this recipe! Using Uncle Ben's Rice, you can create a delicious and fun pizza rice ball meal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:00:15">http://spoonful.com/recipes/corn-and-scallion-cakes</link><title>Rice &amp; Corn Cakes with Spicy Black Beans</title><description>These crispy fried patties get a swift kick from the easy-to-make bean-and-salsa accompaniment. Instant brown rice only takes about 10 minutes, a great shortcut on a busy night.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:00:43">http://family.go.com/food/recipe-an-881517-fiesta-rice-salad-t/</link><title>Fiesta Rice Salad</title><description>This zesty rice salad is chock full of veggies and protein, and so hearty and flavorful it could easily be a main dish or a side. Try Alison Needham's delicous recipe today.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e086-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e086/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:01:00">http://spoonful.com/recipes/orzo-and-wild-rice</link><title>Wild Rice with Dried Apricots &amp; Pistachios</title><description>Colorful apricots, scallions and pistachios make this vibrant dish worthy of any holiday table. Since wild rice (really a grass) does not absorb liquid to the extent that true rice and other grains do, cook it in boilin...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>