<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:01:32" name="DeviantArt" id="FW14-e113"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e113-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:01:34">http://katanisk.deviantart.com/art/Fearful-Symmetry-53012689</link><title>Fearful Symmetry 
"The more the light shines through me 
I pretend to close my eyes 
      The more the dark consumes me, 
I pretend I'm burning bright..." 
-Shinedown, "Burning Bright" 
It was a grey day in New York City. Snow had already fallen, but wasn't doing so at the moment, and hadn't for a couple of days. The fallen snow lay in frozen, dirty piles along the roadside, not at all looking like the powdery, pristine stuff that come drifting down from the steely clouds a few days before. 
Leo Griffin didn't particularly care. Snow was snow was snow, and no matter how pretty it was, it generally did nothing more than spell bad news for him. Same with the sky. He'd even noted that, ironically, it seemed to be colder on the bright blue days when the sun blared down merrily from above. 
The boy's breath came out in little puffs of white steam as be plodded stiffly down the litter-strewn sidewalk, the soles of his shoes slapping loosely on the pavement. From top to boFearful Symmetry7 years ago in Fantasy

52 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_01_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:02:20">http://kelseyalicia.deviantart.com/art/Hate-Crime-134395278</link><title>Hate CrimeHate Crime 
It was a pleasurable April afternoon. It was so nice and sunny the students were enjoying a picnic, under the blooming cherry trees. The school thought itd be fun to have lunch outside on this lovely day. Everywhere the young kids were enjoying gazing at the pink blossom, while enjoying food from around the world. 
Under a large tree near a vivid sapphire lake was Maverick. He was feeding his girlfriend, Libra, some of his aunts homemade cheesecake. Libra seemed much happier then shed been lately. With each tasty bite her smile grew broader. 
So Libra, tell me, are you enjoying my aunts cake? as he fed her another bite. Licking her nose she smiled warmly at him. She hugged him tightly before replying to his question. 
Yes, it sure is scrumptious. So are these wonderful spinach puffs. They go so well with the mango smoothies and stuffed crab. This is one flavorsome picnic. Did you make anything yourself? she asked. tossHate Crime5 years ago in Fan Fiction

0 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_02_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:05:46">http://haphazard-witch.deviantart.com/art/Rebecca-Edit-More-Information-93221237</link><title>Rebecca Edit: More Information6 years ago in Other

18 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_03_thumb.png">http://th06.deviantart.net/fs32/200H/i/2008/211/9/9/Rebecca_by_haphazard_witch.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:07:15">http://wildewriter99.deviantart.com/art/Prologue-Speak-of-The-Devil-LOOK-IN-DESCRIPTION-405342842</link><title>Prologue Speak of The Devil (LOOK IN DESCRIPTION!)7 months ago in Scraps

1 Comment

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_04_thumb.jpg">http://th03.deviantart.net/fs70/200H/f/2013/278/1/c/prologue_speak_of_the_devil__look_in_description___by_wildewriter99-d6pbwje.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:08:40">http://kelseyalicia.deviantart.com/art/Work-134393232</link><title>WorkWork 
At the same time as the kids, began yet another year at their extraordinary school, in hopes of learning and making more progress on their own unique journeys of self-discovery, their parents began another day of working. 
It seemed still weird in addition to wonderful, after the exhilarating as well as unimaginable adventures theyd taken in their roller-coaster ride of their youths that theyve normal lives. Or as normal lives as one can have. In view of the fact that normal, along with perfect and power are only illusions. 
Yet here they were. Each and every one grown-up, married with families as well as jobs. It sorta gave a melancholy feeling to the whole gang. It wasnt hard to imagine that Atem wasnt the only one missing the thrill of saving mankind. Once youve tasted adventure, it was next to impossible, to stop thinking about, that luscious matchless sensation. 
Right now the former pharaoh was in hisWork5 years ago in Fan Fiction

0 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7128_05_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>