<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:55:12" name="DeviantArt" id="FW14-e113"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:55:14">http://misslunarose.deviantart.com/art/Punctuating-Dialogue-380557909</link><title>Punctuating Dialogue 
For non-native English speakers and young readers: If you hover over a blue word, you'll see its definition. 
Punctuating dialogue can be surprisingly difficult, even for people whose first language is English. It's one of the things that you see all the time in books, but you pay little attention to, and all your English teachers assume that you already know it. Sure, if you read a lot, you pick up the basics, but even then it can be difficult to unconsciously absorb all the rules. (Until 2012, I was making heinous mistakes with commas vs. periods. I'm still weeding out errors from my novel.) 
Anyhow, for the sake of my fellow spirits who bemoan the lack of proper dialogue education, I've researched the subject and compiled this little guide. I hope that it answers your questions, and that it isn't too dull. 
Note: I use American English. Other English-speaking countries may have slightly different rules. 
Anatomy of Dialogue 
I'm going to be using these termPunctuating Dialogue8 months ago in Writing

95 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_01_thumb.png">http://a.deviantart.net/littags/e/s/o/misslunarose.png?15</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:56:49">http://lamonaca.deviantart.com/art/Punctuating-Poetry-Part-Two-103789868</link><title>Punctuating Poetry Part TwoShifting Gears 
The great thing about punctuation is that there is rarely one single, correct, perfect way to punctuate a poem.  Given to a number of different poets, a poem could be punctuated and re-punctuated in as many different ways. 
So let's take a breather from so many rules and look at Leave the Door Open, by KrystalIce: 
Crash! 
=Thud= 
~~Twang~~ 
*Shatter* 
+BOOM+ 
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duht 
^Pink^ 
, 
^Pink^ 
, 
^Pink^ 
, 
&amp;Clatter&amp; 
rollrollroll@ 
(Ri-i-i-i-i-i---ng) 
.STOP. 
 
Damn; I should've left the door open. 
At first glance, this could make a grammarian twitch!  It's just a jumble of symbols and shapes and - hey, take a deep breath.  Come back down from Oxford and pay attention. 
This poem is an example of using punctuation, not just to punctuate ideas but to illustratePunctuating Poetry Part Two5 years ago in General Non-Fiction

8 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_02_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:58:34">http://wordcount.deviantart.com/art/Punctuating-Dialogue-A-Guide-73936110</link><title>Punctuating Dialogue: A GuideStandard Punctuation: Dialogue 
Sometimes we read dialogue so often, punctuated in so many different ways, that we either forget what we've learned (if that was anything memorable to begin with) or we rely on instinct to guide us.  A common example of this can be seen in the opening dialogue of darksouldream's piece, Bobby: 
No, replied Cindy `I think his sister Becky is staying with her, but she keeps muttering about parents out living children. The doctors been keeping her pretty sedated. 
Most Americans will cringe at this.  Why?  Well, double quotation marks are the more acceptable usage (the "traditional convention") in American Standard English.  However, in British Standard English, both the double quotation mark and single quotation mark are used.  What's the rule?  StylisPunctuating Dialogue: A Guide6 years ago in Editorial

154 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_03_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:00:10">http://magicaljoey.deviantart.com/art/GNF-Punctuation-Introduction-208778932</link><title>GNF - Punctuation Introduction 
The Grammar Nazi Files: 
Part #1: Introduction. 
Most information from: 
Truss, L. 2007 Eats, Shoots and Leaves: The Zero Tolerance Approach to Punctuation.Great Britain: Profile Books 
Rose, A. &amp; Purkis, R. 1991. English Grammar: A reference book for schools and colleges. Pietermaritzburg: Shuter &amp; Shooter 
The aim of this tutorial series is not to give you all the answers; it is more of a "self-help" guide to help you learn to love punctuation and to allow yourself permission to love it. 
If you are passionate about punctuation, take heart that you are not alone. That you are not isolated  there are others out there. 
Don't become ignorant of or indifferent to punctuation. Make an effort to educate yourself on the topic until you develop, as Lynne Truss (2007) calls it, "The Seventh Sense". When you can see incorrect punctuation all around you within your normal day-to-day activities, you have developed this sense. 
We can define punctuation in many ways. SoGNF - Punctuation Introduction3 years ago in Reviews &amp; Guides

9 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_04_thumb.jpg">http://a.deviantart.net/littags/y/e/o/magicaljoey.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:01:19">http://ml-larson.deviantart.com/art/Punchlines-and-Pay-Offs-147125960</link><title>Punchlines and Pay-Offs 
Set-Up and Punchline: Using Narrative to Tell a Joke 
"Three blokes go into a pub. Something happens, and the outcome's hilarious!" 
\-- Bill Bailey 
That's the basic recipe for any joke, isn't it? Set the scene, add a verb or two, and everyone laughs. But there's a problem with jokes, and it goes something rather like this: 
"Three blokes go into a pub, and the whole scene unfolds into a tedious inevitability." \-- Bill Bailey (again) 
The formula to telling a joke is a bit more complex than just the basic recipe. The recipe is what you need to tell the joke; milk, eggs, flour, shortening, baking powder, saffron. But if you just look at the recipe, you don't really know what's going to happen. Are we baking a cake? Biscuits? Some sort of rock-hard bread that'll keep in the pantry for two million years? We don't know! 
Telling a joke is the same thing. Just having the set up, verbs, and payoff without knowing how much of each, or if you should use the verbal equivalent to Punchlines and Pay-Offs4 years ago in Writing

7 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_05_thumb.jpg">http://a.deviantart.net/littags/n/o/s/ml-larson.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:02:10">http://stop-drop-n-roll.deviantart.com/art/Punctuation-FAQ-92797173</link><title>Punctuation FAQPunctuation FAQ: 
Use period to end strong, stand alone thoughts or as an end for a chain of lines. 
Use a comma for small separation of thought (don't use many periods unless you're going for a stronger, more standout style). 
Use semicolons for more separation than a comma, usually I use the infrequently and in the middle of lines. 
Hyphens are more penetrating than commas (bigger text effect on the page) and can be used to end stand alone thoughts (they have a more linking effect than the period). 
Separate lines with spaces for a complete chain of thought, or separate certain words (usually single words or phrases) for a strong emphasis. 
Use a colon rarely, usually for listing.  Can list thoughts, actions, things, etc. 
Some open poetry is better without punctuation, but I think that most open poetry is flimsy without some structure or form of punctuation.  It must be very compact and flow well to require no punctuation or separation at all.Punctuation FAQ6 years ago in Writing

10 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_06_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:04:04">http://inkfish7.deviantart.com/journal/The-Basics-of-Comma-Usage-276769925</link><title>The Basics of Comma UsageThis guide is meant to give you, as a writer, a thorough foundation in comma usage. I won't cover every use, but I will go over a majority of them, all of which are worth knowing. 
As far as this tutorial's subject matter is concerned, I feel comfortable explaining about ninety percent of what follows. However, I want this to be as accurate as possible, so I've gone to other sources online to back me up (primarily to fill in the gaps of my knowledge in terminology). I've included the links to these sources immediately below as well as in the author's description. I will refer to them throughout the tutorial by their source number (Source 1, Source 2, etc). If you wish to better your grammar even further, I particularly recommend grammarbook.com (Sources 2 and 3). Note that all the examples I give in this tutorial were not taken from the sources; they are my own. 
1) grammar.ccc.comnet.edu ("Conjunctions")The Basics of Comma Usage2 years ago in Personal

61 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_07_thumb.gif">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/gruzecontrol/icons/journal.gif?2</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:05:41">http://randomite93.deviantart.com/art/RP-Guide-For-Noobs-Everything-You-Need-To-Know-366728503</link><title>RP Guide For Noobs - Everything You Need To KnowHello there, it's a pleasure to meet you! My name is Randomite93, but you may call me Random or Randy. I'm assuming you've had no role play experience whatsoever, but don't feel bad about it: we were all noobs at one stage. We just got better through practice! I will tell you that the difference between you and other noobs is that you want to learn: you chose to read this guide by coming here, and that very spirit will definitely help you improve. 
I won't disturb you any further, so take a seat, relax, and dive into this guide; all written for an eager beaver like you! 
What is Role Play? 
The first thing we have to ask ourselves before we begin is: "What is this act we call 'role play'?" There are different answers, depending on our beliefs and thoughts. I believe that role play is simply telling a story: we create characters and immerse ourselves into different worlds and situations to come up with an interesting story which we enjoy being a part of. You playRP Guide For Noobs - Everything You Need To Know1 year ago in Reviews &amp; Guides

28 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_08_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:07:01">http://kitsunechann.deviantart.com/art/Writing-Lesson-Writing-Conversations-330762092</link><title>Writing Lesson: Writing ConversationsWhile I am not a professional by any means, I have been writing for many years and, more recently, beta-reading as well. In all of my experience, I've noticed that a lot of to-be authors make some really silly, simple mistakes. In an effort to help out, I'm going to be putting up a few "Quick Tips" that might help you improve your writing and get more readers. 
For this "Quick Tips" entry, I'm going to focus on conversation and the use of quotations. Here we go 
Punctuation in Quotations 
When a character is speaking, their statement is often followed by, "she said" or, "he mumbled". However, you have to keep in mind that this is still part of the sentence! 
Incorrect: "Wait, I have to tie my shoe." she said. 
Correct: "Wait, I have to tie my shoe," she said. 
Even though her statement ended, the sentence carried on to tell the reader that it was she who spoke. That's how it works with a period, but with exclamation marks and question marks, many people choose to ignore tWriting Lesson: Writing Conversations2 years ago in Writing

59 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_09_thumb.png">http://a.deviantart.net/littags/n/n/a/kitsunechann.png?3</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7211-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:10:13">http://misslunarose.deviantart.com/art/Help-I-have-a-Mary-Sue-412301021</link><title>Help! I have a Mary Sue! 
You know that you have a Mary Sue when she upsets the monochromatic color scheme of my Writer's Guides. 
Mouse over blue text to see a note. 
Internet communities often lash out at writers who create Mary Sues. Declaring the writing to be below their standards, they proceed to punish the creators. They mock the characters, verbally abuse the writers, and write hyperbolically about how much they wish the characters would die. 
Bullying writers (who may be very young) is only going to make them afraid to write—and therefore improve—or share their work. Not only that, but it discourages other writers from speaking for fear of public mockery, and it may silence the voices that could someday become great. 
If you've directly or indirectly suffered from the abuse of such individuals, let me first apologize on their behalf. I don't care if your story stinks so much that it can be smelled from fifty miles away; mocking you for it is cyberbullying. If you find people who try to hHelp! I have a Mary Sue!5 months ago in Writing

747 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7211_10_thumb.png">http://a.deviantart.net/littags/e/s/o/misslunarose.png?15</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>