<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:04:49" name="DeviantArt" id="FW14-e113"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:04:54">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-368921173</link><title>Flu Season1 year ago in Movies &amp; TV

24 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_01_thumb.png">http://th09.deviantart.net/fs70/200H/f/2013/120/2/6/flu_season_by_thefieldsofice-d63n9ed.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:05:52">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-Chapter-One-374324252</link><title>Flu Season: Chapter One 
Flu Season 
Chapter One: Patient Zero 
“This is the way the world ends. Not with a bang but a whimper.” –T. S. Eliot, "The Hollow Men" 
Day One 
Infected: 21 
Dead: 0 
The tale of the next great pandemic begins in Saddle Arabia, where Fancy Pants sits at a café, enjoying a daisy sandwich. This poor colt was completely unaware of the fact that he would soon come face to face with the greatest killer this world had ever seen, that he would spread it to hundreds of others, and that it would soon bring about his own demise. 
Fancy Pants had just finished taking the last few bites of his sandwich, when he looked down to his watch. “2:03” it read. Fearing that he may be late to his meeting, he quickly paid for his meal and left a generous tip, before rushing out the door. 
After racing up and down the streets, and asking for directions twice, Fancy Pants had finally made it to his destination. It was an old silk processing plant for him and his wife Rarity’s businFlu Season: Chapter One11 months ago in Horror

42 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_02_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:06:30">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-Chapter-Two-374955814</link><title>Flu Season: Chapter Two 
Flu Season 
Chapter Two: Transmission 
Day Seven 
Infected: 18,364 
Dead: 9,170 
As the morning’s light began to creep over Spike’s bed, he slowly began to stir. The young dragon yawned slightly before stretching out his legs. As he did this, he accidentally brushed against the mare lying next to him. Almost immediately, she was catapulted into consciousness, causing her to, groggily, turn to face him. 
Spike smiled slightly before laying a hand upon her snow white cheek. “You are such a light sleeper.” 
Sweetie Belle smiled somewhat. “Yeah, but I’m not technically awake until I’ve had a few cups of coffee.” 
The young dragon returned the smile before pressing his lips to hers. After a moment, Sweetie Belle broke the kiss with a slight giggle. 
“Wow, looks like someone’s in a good mood today,” she said, a slight blush beginning to form. 
Spike began to blush as well. “Well, I woke up next to you. Why wouldn’t I be happFlu Season: Chapter Two11 months ago in Horror

10 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_03_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:07:27">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-Chapter-Three-376388092</link><title>Flu Season: Chapter Three 
Flu Season 
Chapter Three: Epidemic 
Day Nine 
Infected: 353,175 
Dead: 159,582 
Sweetie Belle awoke this morning, from a rather pleasant dream. It was about a day, not too long ago, that her and Spike had decided to put off their plans and just go out for the day. It brought a smile to her face, thinking about the memory. However, she quickly adjusted to the present upon realizing that she had not awoken in her bed, but Applebloom’s. 
Sweetie Belle yawned and stretched before making her way out of bed and downstairs. Once she had entered the living room, she saw Spike and Applejack discussing something. As she drew closer, she could begin to hear what was being said. 
“Applejack,” began Spike, “I don’t want to freak you out, but if things get too bad in Manehatten, we may have to come out here. I just need to know that you’re okay with that.” 
The orange cowpony nodded. “Of course, Spike. You and Sweetie Belle are always welcome here. And donFlu Season: Chapter Three11 months ago in Horror

29 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_04_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:07:55">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-Chapter-Four-376580226</link><title>Flu Season: Chapter Four 
Flu Season 
Chapter Four: Pandemic 
Day Seventeen 
Infected: 13,328,426 
Dead: 5,912,437 
Sweetie Belle sat beside the window of her apartment, her gaze fixed upon a passing ambulance cart. It’s sirens wailing louder and louder before fading off into the distance. Once it was out of sight, she looked down to the sidewalks, now covered in trash bags and even a few bright red bags labeled with a black biohazard symbol. 
Not wanting to look at the disgusting sight any longer, Sweetie Belle looked to the sky hoping for some source of comfort. Unfortunately, the only thing to meet her sight was a dreary, ugly, sky. This caused her to laugh emotionlessly. ‘How fitting,’ she thought. 
With a sigh, the unicorn rose to her hooves and found the remote. As soon as she flicked on the television, she was bombarded with more bad news. 
A yellow news pony sat, wearing a brown suit, with a map of the world behind him. Much of it was covered in red, with only the least populated areas being sFlu Season: Chapter Four11 months ago in Horror

20 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_05_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:09:03">http://icyhugs.deviantart.com/art/Sars-Bird-Flu-now-Influenza-29206666</link><title>Sars, Bird Flu, now Influenza?8 years ago in Drawings

5 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_06_thumb.jpg">http://th06.deviantart.net/fs9/200H/i/2006/048/f/6/2003__SARS__2006__Bird_Flu__by_icyhugs.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:09:50">http://thefieldsofice.deviantart.com/art/Flu-Season-Chapter-Ten-422424827</link><title>Flu Season: Chapter Ten 
Flu Season 
Chapter Ten: Shock 
Day Eighty Five 
Infected: 2.242 Billion 
Dead: 1.437 Billion 
Sweetie Belle sat beside the window, gazing out upon her husband’s grave. An ever-present drizzle had turned the fresh soil to mud. She had wished to sit with him in the weather, but given her condition, Fluttershy wouldn’t allow it. Sweetie Belle had done this each day since Spike’s passing, though Twilight had found a much different way of coping. 
The Alicorn raced from notebook to notebook, scribbling various spells with her quill. She was not going to accept that Spike was gone, not without first attempting everything to bring him back. 
Her ideas were on the very fringe of what magic had considered being possible. Her notes spanned from Starswirl the Bearded’s time travel spells, to using the Crystal Mirror to cross over into another reality where another version of Spike still existed.  At the moment however, she was focusing her attention on the potion Zecora hadFlu Season: Chapter Ten4 months ago in Horror

9 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_07_thumb.png">http://st.deviantart.net/minish/main/defaulttag2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:10:47">http://aidanirving.deviantart.com/art/Hong-Kong-bans-live-chicken-sales-after-bird-f-430314184</link><title>Hong Kong bans live chicken sales after bird f3 months ago in Corporate

0 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_08_thumb.jpg">http://th06.deviantart.net/fs71/200H/f/2014/028/f/5/hong_kong_bans_live_chicken_sales_after_bird_f_by_aidanirving-d7474js.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:11:27">http://rvbomally.deviantart.com/art/The-Day-After-Yesterday-400197000</link><title>The Day After Yesterday7 months ago in Non-Isometric

56 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_09_thumb.png">http://th04.deviantart.net/fs70/200H/f/2014/007/e/9/the_day_after_yesterday_by_rvbomally-d6m9lzc.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e113-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 02:12:52">http://amyyang.deviantart.com/art/Chickens-I-370905400</link><title>Chickens I1 year ago in Domesticated Animals

0 Comments

More Like This</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e113/7477_10_thumb.jpg">http://th05.deviantart.net/fs71/200H/i/2013/130/2/6/chickens_i_by_amyyang-d64tsfs.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>