<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:31:31" name="USAJobs" id="FW14-e081"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:31:32">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/366189100</link><title>Supervisory Clinical Psychologist/Team Leader</title><description>...for one (1) full-time Supervisory Clinical Psychologist/Team Leader for the Readjustment...veteran. The Vet Center Supervisory Clinical Psychologist will work in cooperative collaboration...level. English Language Proficiency Clinical Psychologist must be proficient in spoken and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:33:42">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/366867400</link><title>Psychologist</title><description>...Rehabilitation Service Line is recruiting for a Psychologist position at the Minneapolis, MN VA...this position.;The Full Time Permanent Psychologist is located in the Extended Care &amp; Rehabilitation...rehabilitation continuum of care. The psychologist will provide diagnostic interviews...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:36:27">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/358337500</link><title>Clinical Psychologist</title><description>...advertised under this recruitment. Psychologist (Local Recovery Coordinator), Psychologist (Mental Health Intensive Case Management...authorized for this position.;As the Clinical Psychologist for Texas Valley Coastal Bend Health...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:38:00">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/360325900</link><title>Clinical Psychologist (GOPC)</title><description>...WJBD VAMC is seeking an outstanding psychologist to join our Outpatient Clinic within...disorders. Among the evidenced based therapy modalities provided are individual...requirement of licensure for an individual psychologist for a period not to exceed 2 years from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:39:38">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/365555900</link><title>Fee Basis Psychologist</title><description>Vacancy Identification Number (VIN) 979574 Psychologist (Compensation and Pension Examiner), Fee Basis-0180, Fort...position does not confer competitive status. NOTE: The Psychologist would receive $200 per exam under this Fee Basis Appointment...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:40:21">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/343136500</link><title>Psychologist</title><description>...additional year of experience as a psychologist equivalent to the next lower...comfortably to do the work. Light lifting (under 15 pounds), Light carrying (15 pounds),Reaching...the Home Based Primary Care Psychologist.;Working for the Department...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:43:49">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/363117100</link><title>Psychologist</title><description>...1 year of experience as a psychologist equivalent to the next lower...proficiency working in addiction therapy in a clinical setting, i.e...sedentary. Typically, the Psychologist sits comfortably to do the...standing, bending, carrying of light items such as papers, books...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:47:06">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/366938400</link><title>PSYCHOLOGIST (Neuropsychologist) Austin</title><description>...rehabilitation services as needed. The psychologist applies advanced professional psychological...indicated. Assists the supervisory psychologist, as needed, to manage the work of the...year postdoctoral work experience as a psychologist in the VHA or a comparable professional...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:49:30">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/367486900</link><title>PSYCHOLOGIST (Polytrauma/TBI)</title><description>...year postdoctoral work experience as a psychologist in the VHA or a comparable professional...year of experience as a professional psychologist equivalent to the next lower grade...additional year of experience as a psychologist equivalent to the next lower grade...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e081-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e081/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:53:23">https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/366861200</link><title>Psychologist (Outpatient Mental Health)</title><description>...Paducah, KY and surrounding VA locations. The psychologist will provide an array of direct patient care...individual insight oriented psychotherapy, behavior therapy, supportive psychotherapy, group therapy, couples therapy. Selectee will provide emergency...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>