<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7096">touchpad scroll dell latitude</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:47:57" name="Washington post" id="FW14-e109"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:47:57">http://www.washingtonpost.com/business/technology/windows-8-stuns-amazes-and-sometimes-lets-us-down-review/2012/10/26/7b1d9984-1f91-11e2-8817-41b9a7aaabc7_story.html</link><title>Windows 8 stuns, amazes, and sometimes lets us down (review)</title><description>Review: Just like Windows 8 has evolved, so has my opinion of the operating system.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/2010-2019/WashingtonPost/2012/10/24/National-Economy/Images/AP9508240976.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-02"><link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/business/technology/dear-hp-please-keep-making-those-crunchpads-ertouchpads/2011/08/23/gIQAhAOEYJ_story.html</link><title>Dear HP: Please Keep Making Those CrunchPads! Er...TouchPads</title><description></description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/WashingtonPost/Content/Production/Blogs/innovations/Images/893852.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:52:11">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2010/07/27/AR2010072705996.html</link><title>Acer's Aspire TimelineX 1830T-3721 Is Sleek and Attractive, but Has Iffy Ergonomics</title><description>There's a lot to love about the Acer Aspire TimelineX 1830T. At about $700, it's extremely affordable for an ultraportable, offers great workaday performance, has excellent high-def video playback, and runs for over 6 hours on its battery. However, the 1830T also suffers some ergonomic quirks that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:53:32">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2010/02/03/AR2010020303890.html</link><title>Dell Latitude E4300: A Solid but Unexciting Business Laptop</title><description>At first glance, you might mistake the Dell Latitude E4300 for an earlier-vintage laptop: Its sharp lines and subtle finish stick out in today's world of glossy gadgets with rounded corners. That's not to say the E4300 isn't a handsome portable, however--it did grow on me. Even better, the matte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:55:47">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/11/24/AR2009112403090.html</link><title>Toshiba U505-S2980 Gets in Touch With Multitouch</title><description>The Toshiba U505-S2980's main gimmick is a multitouch touchscreen. Outside of that, it is, for the most part, a decent laptop, even above average in many ways. But that one gimmick is the root of my issues with this 13-inch notebook--and helps raise its cost to a somewhat pricey $1050 (as of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:57:16">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/10/20/AR2009102003725.html</link><title>HP ProBook 5310m Ultraportable Laptop</title><description>HP has a thing of business-savvy beauty on its hands with the ProBook 5310m. Why do I say that? Even the guys in the PC World Labs--who see everything under the sun--were impressed by its industrial design. The sleek black aluminum case, the supple texture on the undercarriage...the list goes on....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:59:25">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/07/23/AR2009072303984.html</link><title>Dell Latitude XT2 Tablet PC</title><description>Go on, grab the Dell Latitude XT2--it just feels good. The rugged metal-alloy casing gives it a solid, substantial frame. Pick it up, and the 13.3-inch machine is deceptively light (3.8 pounds). Put all of that together, and you seem to have a premium choice for mobility-minded businessfolk in need...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:03:00">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/07/30/AR2009073003811.html</link><title>Samsung Go Netbook</title><description>As much as I like what Samsung is doing with its new Go netbook (known as the N310 overseas), the company is about this close to surpassing Asus as the king of the shotgun-delivery method, releasing netbooks every 2 minutes. Never mind my cattiness, though. The Go is a stylish and far-from-subdued...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:06:13">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/07/21/AR2009072102908.html</link><title>All-in-One PCs With a Touch of Style</title><description>We'll say it up front: The iMac is no longer the final word in all-in-one PCs. Though Apple's latest aluminum iMacs were the performance champs in our tests, it's the new wave of competing all-in-ones that are changing the game.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7096-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:08:51">http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/10/22/AR2008102203178.html</link><title>From Apple, a Luxury Laptop in Lean Times</title><description>Apple's new MacBook may be the finest-engineered consumer laptop ever built. But that doesn't make it an automatic purchase.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7096_10_thumb.jpg">http://media3.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/photo/2008/10/22/PH2008102203503_STMB.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>