<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:42:08" name="Washington post" id="FW14-e109"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:42:10">http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/express/post/three-alternatives-for-floral-centerpieces-this-spring/2014/04/18/ffa1507c-c71c-11e3-b708-471bae3cb10c_blog.html</link><title>Three alternatives for floral centerpieces this spring</title><description>Rather than plopping a dozen carnations into a Mason jar (just because you saw it on Pinterest does not make it cool), consider one of these off-center centerpieces.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/WashingtonPost/Content/Blogs/express/201404/Images/centerpiecethumb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:42:47">http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/food/lupo-verde-adds-to-the-italian-on-14th-street/2014/04/05/f42f3668-bb56-11e3-9a05-c739f29ccb08_story.html</link><title>Lupo Verde adds to the Italian on 14th Street</title><description>Med Lahlou's fourth local restaurant requires you to make a few visits to find its charms.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/2010-2019/WashingtonPost/2014/03/31/Others/Images/2014-03-31/FD-FIRSTBITE9_0171396284431.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:43:43">http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/food/dolcezza-opens-a-new-gelato-factory-where-you-can-taste-its-version-of-soft-serve/2014/03/24/da65ef90-6414-11e3-a373-0f9f2d1c2b61_story.html</link><title>Dolcezza opens a new gelato factory where you can taste its version of soft-serve</title><description>The local chain opens a new factory where you can sample soft-serve gelato straight out of the machines.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/2010-2019/WashingtonPost/2013/12/06/Food/Images/gelato0251386361215.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:45:09">http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/food/smoked-chicken-stock-water-plus-bird-equals-a-transformative-ingredient/2014/03/03/b1674fe4-9f1f-11e3-b8d8-94577ff66b28_story.html</link><title>Smoked chicken stock: Water plus bird equals a transformative ingredient</title><description>A barbecue expert learns something from a youngster, and tortellini en brodo will never be the same.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/2010-2019/WashingtonPost/2014/02/27/Food/Images/food191393506090.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:46:22">http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/food/roses-for-valentines-day/2014/02/09/10fc245c-8d28-11e3-98ab-fe5228217bd1_story.html</link><title>Rosés for Valentine's Day</title><description>The four rosés recommended this week represent France, Greece and California.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:48:00">http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/magazine/tom-sietsemas-valentines-to-people-and-places-he-loves/2014/02/05/544eeda4-8218-11e3-9dd4-e7278db80d86_story.html</link><title>Tom Sietsema's Valentines to people and places he loves</title><description>The food critic sends a Valentine to some of his favorite people for the 'small stuff' that adds up.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_145x100/2010-2019/WashingtonPost/2014/01/20/Others/Images/2014-01-20/333E11001390241733.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:49:18">http://www.washingtonpost.com/pb/recipes/lentil-quinoa-bolognese-sauce/13835/</link><title>Lentil Quinoa Bolognese Sauce</title><description>Use this the way you would a meaty Bolognese: over tagliatelle or the pasta of your choice, or in lasagna. This recipe feeds a crowd, or you can freeze part of it to have on hand anytime you want something that tastes decadent. You can use a blender instead of a food processor, but that might create more of a homogenous, greenish sauce rather than one with dark-green flecks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:50:15">http://www.washingtonpost.com/pb/recipes/pallotte-cacio-e-uova-cheese-and-egg-meatballs-tomato-sauce/13828/</link><title>Pallotte Cacio e Uova (Cheese and Egg 'Meatballs' in Tomato Sauce)</title><description>This is a typical example of Abruzzo's "cucina povera": poor man's cuisine. Eggs, cheese and bread crumbs, minus any meat, are mixed together, shaped into pallotte (balls or patties) and fried, then simmered in sugo finto, or a rich, meatless tomato sauce. Parsley is optional, depending on the Abruzzese town in which this dish is made. You'll need an instant-read thermometer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:50:53">http://www.washingtonpost.com/pb/recipes/tricolor-christmas-bread/13786/</link><title>Tricolor Christmas Bread</title><description>This holiday bread is a festive mix flavored with sun-dried tomatoes, black olives and pesto, with each slice showing off a cross-section of colors. The original recipe calls for this to make a single loaf, and if you have a big enough pan - and need a seven-pound loaf of bread - go for it. We've divided it into two loaves here, but dividing it into four loaves results in more manageable finished products that are suitable for sharing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e109-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e109/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:52:32">http://www.washingtonpost.com/pb/recipes/scarpetta-spaghetti-tomato-sauce/13787/</link><title>Scarpetta Spaghetti With Tomato Sauce</title><description>One of the secrets to this popular version of a ubiquitous dish is the infused oil that flavors the tomato sauce. Scott Conant, chef-owner of Scarpetta in New York, says the last thing that goes into a dish is the first thing you'll taste, so he makes an oil infused with garlic, basil and crushed red pepper flakes and adds that to his cooked tomato sauce. (The other secret would be butter.) Conant acknowledges that "spaghetti" is a misnomer for this pasta. It's linguine, or actually tonnarelli, which is easier to produce at home than spaghetti because it doesn't require a pasta extruder. Canned San Marzano tomatoes may be used to replace some or all of the fresh tomatoes in the sauce. In Internet videos of this recipe, Conant suggests that a high-quality dried pasta could replace the homemade version. You'll need a pasta-rolling machine. Type 00 flour is a fine-milled flour available at specialty stores and some supermarkets. We found it at A. Litteri, Seasonal Pantry and Whole Foods Market Foggy Bottom in the District. All-purpose flour may be substituted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>