<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:01:14" name="arXiv.org" id="FW14-e001"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:01:16">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.2505</link><title>Title: Aggregated journal-journal citation relations in Scopus and Web-of-Science matched and compared in terms of networks, maps, and interactive overlays</title><description>Title: Aggregated journal-journal citation relations in Scopus and Web-of-Science matched and compared in terms of networks, maps, and interactive overlays

Authors: Loet Leydesdorff, Félix de Moya-Anegón, Wouter de Nooy

Subjects: Digital Libraries (cs.DL)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:01:40">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.2347</link><title>Title: Automation Security</title><description>Title: Automation Security

Authors: Dr. Timur Mirzoev

Journal-ref: Proceedings of the Second International Seminar, Saint Petersburg State University of Aerospace Instrumentation. January 2007

Subjects: Other Computer Science (cs.OH)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:02:03">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.1953</link><title>Title: IPAC Image Processing and Data Archiving for the Palomar Transient Factory</title><description>Title: IPAC Image Processing and Data Archiving for the Palomar Transient Factory

Authors: Russ R. Laher, Jason Surace, Carl J. Grillmair, Eran O. Ofek, David Levitan, Branimir Sesar, Julian C. van Eyken, Nicholas M. Law, George Helou, Nouhad Hamam, Frank J. Masci, Sean Mattingly, Ed Jackson, Eugean Hacopeans, Wei Mi, Steve Groom, Harry Teplitz, Vandana Desai, David Hale, Roger Smith, Richard Walters, Robert Quimby, Mansi Kasliwal, Assaf Horesh, Eric Bellm, Tom Barlow, Adam Waszczak, Thomas A. Prince, Shrinivas R. Kulkarni

Comments: 54 pages, 9 figures, 26 tables; submitted to PASP

Subjects: Instrumentation and Methods for Astrophysics (astro-ph.IM)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:02:28">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.1301</link><title>Title: How well developed are altmetrics? A cross-disciplinary analysis of the presence of 'alternative metrics' in scientific publications</title><description>Title: How well developed are altmetrics? A cross-disciplinary analysis of the presence of 'alternative metrics' in scientific publications

Authors: Zohreh Zahedi, Rodrigo Costas, Paul Wouters

Subjects: Digital Libraries (cs.DL)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:02:49">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.0854</link><title>Title: Enabling Automatic Certification of Online Auctions</title><description>Title: Enabling Automatic Certification of Online Auctions

Authors: Wei Bai, Emmanuel M. Tadjouddine, Yu Guo

Comments: In Proceedings FESCA 2014, arXiv:1404.0436

Journal-ref: EPTCS 147, 2014, pp. 123-132

Subjects: Logic in Computer Science (cs.LO); Artificial Intelligence (cs.AI)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:03:12">http://arxiv.org/abs/1404.0462</link><title>Title: The European Union, China, and the United States in the Top-1% and Top-10% Layers of Most-Frequently-Cited Publications: Competition and Collaborations</title><description>Title: The European Union, China, and the United States in the Top-1% and Top-10% Layers of Most-Frequently-Cited Publications: Competition and Collaborations

Authors: Loet Leydesdorff, Caroline S. Wagner, Lutz Bornmann

Subjects: Digital Libraries (cs.DL)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:03:37">http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.7258</link><title>Title: Verifying Web Applications: From Business Level Specifications to Automated Model-Based Testing</title><description>Title: Verifying Web Applications: From Business Level Specifications to Automated Model-Based Testing

Authors: Christian Colombo (PEST Research Lab, Department of Computer Science, University of Malta), Mark Micallef (PEST Research Lab, Department of Computer Science, University of Malta), Mark Scerri (PEST Research Lab, Department of Computer Science, University of Malta)

Comments: In Proceedings MBT 2014, arXiv:1403.7044

Journal-ref: EPTCS 141, 2014, pp. 14-28

Subjects: Software Engineering (cs.SE)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:04:03">http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.6955</link><title>Title: Vulnerability Scanners-A Proactive Approach To Assess Web Application Security</title><description>Title: Vulnerability Scanners-A Proactive Approach To Assess Web Application Security

Authors: Sheetal Bairwa, Bhawna Mewara, Jyoti Gajrani

Comments: 12 pages, 6 figures, 3 tables, SCNDS 2013 Conference. International Journal on Computational Sciences &amp; Applications (IJCSA)2014

Subjects: Cryptography and Security (cs.CR)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:04:27">http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.6025</link><title>Title: Web-Based Visualization of Very Large Scientific Astronomy Imagery</title><description>Title: Web-Based Visualization of Very Large Scientific Astronomy Imagery

Authors: Emmanuel Bertin, Ruven Pillay, Chiara Marmo

Comments: Submitted to Astronomy &amp; Computing. 12 pages, 2 tables, 8 figures. Server available at this http URL and source code repository: this https URL Client code and demos at this http URL

Subjects: Instrumentation and Methods for Astrophysics (astro-ph.IM); Computational Engineering, Finance, and Science (cs.CE); Multimedia (cs.MM)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:04:55">http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.5401</link><title>Title: Exploring Indonesian Web Based Career Center Discrepancy of Web Popularity and Type of Services</title><description>Title: Exploring Indonesian Web Based Career Center Discrepancy of Web Popularity and Type of Services

Authors: Renny Renny, Reza Chandra, Syamsi Ruhama, Mochammad Wisuda Sarjono

Comments: Journal of Advances in Computer Science and its Applications

Journal-ref: UACEE International Journal of Advances in Computer Science and its Applications IJCSIA Volume 3 Issue 2 Publication Date 5 June 2013

Subjects: Computers and Society (cs.CY)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>