<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:25:45" name="arXiv.org" id="FW14-e001"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:25:46">http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.6923</link><title>Title: Fifty years of the CERN Proton Synchrotron : Volume 2</title><description>Title: Fifty years of the CERN Proton Synchrotron : Volume 2

Authors: Simone Gilardoni (ed.) (CERN), Django Manglunki (ed.) (CERN), Jean-Paul Burnet, Christian Carli, Michel Chanel, Roland Garoby, Massimo Giovannozzi, Steven Hancock, Helmut Haseroth, Kurt Hübner, Detlef Küchler, Julian Lewis, Alessandra Lombardi, Michel Martini, Stephan Maury, Elias Métral, Dieter Möhl, Günther Plass, Louis Rinolfi, Richard Scrivens, Rende Steerenberg, Charles Steinbach, Maurizio Vretenar, Thomas Zickler

Comments: 58 pages, published as CERN Yellow Report this https URL

Subjects: Accelerator Physics (physics.acc-ph)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:26:08">http://arxiv.org/abs/1306.6047</link><title>Title: How fast can we make interpreted Python?</title><description>Title: How fast can we make interpreted Python?

Authors: Russell Power, Alex Rubinsteyn

Comments: Tech Report

Subjects: Programming Languages (cs.PL)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:26:26">http://arxiv.org/abs/1101.4116</link><title>Title: GridCertLib: a Single Sign-on Solution for Grid Web Applications and Portals</title><description>Title: GridCertLib: a Single Sign-on Solution for Grid Web Applications and Portals

Authors: Riccardo Murri, Peter Z. Kunszt, Sergio Maffioletti, Valery Tschopp

Comments: 18 pages, 1 figure; final manuscript accepted for publication by the "Journal of Grid Computing"

Subjects: Distributed, Parallel, and Cluster Computing (cs.DC)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:26:47">http://arxiv.org/abs/1011.6332</link><title>Title: AMP: A Science-driven Web-based Application for the TeraGrid</title><description>Title: AMP: A Science-driven Web-based Application for the TeraGrid

Authors: Matthew Woitaszek, Travis Metcalfe, Ian Shorrock (National Center for Atmospheric Research)

Comments: 7 pages, 2 figures, in Proceedings of the 5th Grid Computing Environments Workshop

Subjects: Instrumentation and Methods for Astrophysics (astro-ph.IM); Solar and Stellar Astrophysics (astro-ph.SR); Distributed, Parallel, and Cluster Computing (cs.DC)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:27:12">http://arxiv.org/abs/1006.1074</link><title>Title: Youpi, a Web-based Astronomical Image Processing Pipeline</title><description>Title: Youpi, a Web-based Astronomical Image Processing Pipeline

Authors: M. Monnerville, G. Sémah

Comments: 4 pages, 2 figures, to appear in the proceedings of ADASS XIX, Oct 4-8 2009, Sapporo, Japan (ASP Conf. Series)

Subjects: Distributed, Parallel, and Cluster Computing (cs.DC)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7077-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7077_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:27:34">http://arxiv.org/abs/hep-ex/9905055</link><title>Title: Measurement of the Proton Structure Function F2 and of the Total Photon-Proton Cross Section sigma(tot) at Very Low Q2 and Very Low x</title><description>Title: Measurement of the Proton Structure Function F2 and of the Total Photon-Proton Cross Section sigma(tot) at Very Low Q2 and Very Low x

Authors: Christoph Amelung (Physikalisches Institut der Universitaet Bonn) for the ZEUS Collaboration

Comments: Contributed to the proceedings of the DIS99 Workshop, Zeuthen, Germany, April 19-23, 1999. 3 pages including 3 figures

Journal-ref: Nucl.Phys.Proc.Suppl. 79 (1999) 176-178

Subjects: High Energy Physics - Experiment (hep-ex)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>