<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:27:48" name="arXiv.org" id="FW14-e001"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:27:50">http://arxiv.org/abs/1402.6583</link><title>Title: Finding informed traders in futures and their inderlying assets in intraday trading</title><description>Title: Finding informed traders in futures and their inderlying assets in intraday trading

Authors: Lyudmila A. Glik, Oleg L. Kritski

Comments: 15 pages

Subjects: Trading and Market Microstructure (q-fin.TR)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:28:09">http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.0924</link><title>Title: On the Efficiency of the Walrasian Mechanism</title><description>Title: On the Efficiency of the Walrasian Mechanism

Authors: Moshe Babaioff, Brendan Lucier, Noam Nisan, Renato Paes Leme

Subjects: Computer Science and Game Theory (cs.GT)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:28:30">http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.7627</link><title>Title: Combination of CDF and D0 W-Boson Mass Measurements</title><description>Title: Combination of CDF and D0 W-Boson Mass Measurements

Authors: CDF Collaboration: T. Aaltonen, S. Amerio, D. Amidei, A. Anastassov, A. Annovi, J. Antos, G. Apollinari, J.A. Appel, T. Arisawa, A. Artikov, J. Asaadi, W. Ashmanskas, B. Auerbach, A. Aurisano, F. Azfar, W. Badgett, T. Bae, A. Barbaro-Galtieri, V.E. Barnes, B.A. Barnett, P. Barria, P. Bartos, M. Bauce, F. Bedeschi, D. Beecher, S. Behari, G. Bellettini, J. Bellinger, D. Benjamin, A. Beretvas, A. Bhatti, I. Bizjak, K.R. Bland, B. Blumenfeld, A. Bocci, A. Bodek, D. Bortoletto, J. Boudreau, A. Boveia, L. Brigliadori, C. Bromberg, E. Brucken, J. Budagov, H.S. Budd, K. Burkett, G. Busetto, P. Bussey, P. Butti, A. Buzatu, A. Calamba, S. Camarda, M. Campanelli, F. Canelli, B. Carls, D. Carlsmith, R. Carosi, S. Carrillo, B. Casal, M. Casarsa, A. Castro, P. Catastini, D. Cauz, V. Cavaliere, M. Cavalli-Sforza, et al. (711 additional authors not shown)

Comments: Submitted to Phys. Rev. D

Journal-ref: Phys. Rev. D 88, 052018 (2013)

Subjects: High Energy Physics - Experiment (hep-ex)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:28:49">http://arxiv.org/abs/1212.2473</link><title>Title: A Linear Belief Function Approach to Portfolio Evaluation</title><description>Title: A Linear Belief Function Approach to Portfolio Evaluation

Authors: Liping Liu, Catherine Shenoy, Prakash P. Shenoy

Comments: Appears in Proceedings of the Nineteenth Conference on Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence (UAI2003)

Subjects: Artificial Intelligence (cs.AI); Statistical Finance (q-fin.ST)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:29:08">http://arxiv.org/abs/1212.1037</link><title>Title: Modeling Movements in Oil, Gold, Forex and Market Indices using Search Volume Index and Twitter Sentiments</title><description>Title: Modeling Movements in Oil, Gold, Forex and Market Indices using Search Volume Index and Twitter Sentiments

Authors: Tushar Rao (NSIT-Delhi), Saket Srivastava (IIIT-Delhi)

Comments: 10 pages, 4 figures, 9 Tables

Subjects: Computational Engineering, Finance, and Science (cs.CE); Social and Information Networks (cs.SI); General Finance (q-fin.GN)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:29:24">http://arxiv.org/abs/1207.1069</link><title>Title: Combination of the top-quark mass measurements from the Tevatron collider</title><description>Title: Combination of the top-quark mass measurements from the Tevatron collider

Authors: The CDF, D0 collaborations, T. Aaltonen, V.M. Abazov, B. Abbott, B.S. Acharya, M. Adams, T. Adams, G.D. Alexeev, G. Alkhazov, A. Alton, B. Alvarez Gonzalez, G. Alverson, S. Amerio, D. Amidei, A. Anastassov, A. Annovi, J. Antos, G. Apollinari, J.A. Appel, T. Arisawa, A. Artikov, J. Asaadi, W. Ashmanskas, A. Askew, S. Atkins, B. Auerbach, K. Augsten, A. Aurisano, C. Avila, F. Azfar, F. Badaud, W. Badgett, T. Bae, L. Bagby, B. Baldin, D.V. Bandurin, S. Banerjee, A. Barbaro-Galtieri, E. Barberis, P. Baringer, V.E. Barnes, B.A. Barnett, P. Barria, J.F. Bartlett, P. Bartos, U. Bassler, M. Bauce, V. Bazterra, A. Bean, F. Bedeschi, M. Begalli, S. Behari, L. Bellantoni, G. Bellettini, J. Bellinger, D. Benjamin, A. Beretvas, S.B. Beri, G. Bernardi, R. Bernhard, I. Bertram, M. Besancon, R. Beuselinck, et al. (801 additional authors not shown)

Comments: 30 pages and 6 figures, published in Phys. Rev. D

Journal-ref: Phys. Rev. D 86, 092003 (2012) [31 pages]

Subjects: High Energy Physics - Experiment (hep-ex)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:29:48">http://arxiv.org/abs/1202.5272</link><title>Title: Combination of CDF and D0 measurements of the W boson helicity in top quark decays</title><description>Title: Combination of CDF and D0 measurements of the W boson helicity in top quark decays

Authors: The CDF, D0 Collaborations: T. Aaltonen, V.M. Abazov, B. Abbott, B.S. Acharya, M. Adams, T. Adams, G.D. Alexeev, G. Alkhazov, A. Alton, B. Álvarez González, G. Alverson, S. Amerio, D. Amidei, A. Anastassov, A. Annovi, J. Antos, M. Aoki, G. Apollinari, J.A. Appel, T. Arisawa, A. Artikov, J. Asaadi, W. Ashmanskas, A. Askew, B. Åsman, S. Atkins, O. Atramentov, B. Auerbach, K. Augsten, A. Aurisano, C. Avila, F. Azfar, F. Badaud, W. Badgett, T. Bae, L. Bagby, B. Baldin, D.V. Bandurin, S. Banerjee, A. Barbaro-Galtieri, E. Barberis, P. Baringer, V.E. Barnes, B.A. Barnett, J. Barreto, P. Barria, J.F. Bartlett, P. Bartos, U. Bassler, M. Bauce, V. Bazterra, A. Bean, F. Bedeschi, M. Begalli, S. Behari, C. Belanger-Champagne, L. Bellantoni, G. Bellettini, J. Bellinger, D. Benjamin, A. Beretvas, et al. (807 additional authors not shown)

Comments: 11 pages, 1 figure, to be submitted to Phys. Rev D Rap. Comm

Subjects: High Energy Physics - Experiment (hep-ex)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:30:10">http://arxiv.org/abs/1112.1051</link><title>Title: Predicting Financial Markets: Comparing Survey, News, Twitter and Search Engine Data</title><description>Title: Predicting Financial Markets: Comparing Survey, News, Twitter and Search Engine Data

Authors: Huina Mao, Scott Counts, Johan Bollen

Comments: This paper includes 10 pages, 6 figures and 10 tables

Subjects: Statistical Finance (q-fin.ST); Computational Engineering, Finance, and Science (cs.CE); Physics and Society (physics.soc-ph)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:30:25">http://arxiv.org/abs/1107.0480</link><title>Title: The Second Wave of the Global Crisis? A Log-Periodic Oscillation Analysis of Commodity Price Series</title><description>Title: The Second Wave of the Global Crisis? A Log-Periodic Oscillation Analysis of Commodity Price Series

Authors: Askar Akaev, Alexei Fomin, Andrey Korotayev

Comments: 12 pages, 9 figures. This research has been supported by the Presidium of the Russian Academy of Sciences (Project "Complex System Analysis and Mathematical Modeling of the World Dynamics")

Subjects: Statistical Finance (q-fin.ST)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e001-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e001/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 13:30:41">http://arxiv.org/abs/1012.4118</link><title>Title: Log-Periodic Oscillation Analysis and Possible Burst of the "Gold Bubble" in April - June 2011</title><description>Title: Log-Periodic Oscillation Analysis and Possible Burst of the "Gold Bubble" in April - June 2011

Authors: Sergey V. Tsirel, Askar Akaev, Alexey Fomin, Andrey V. Korotayev

Comments: 15 pages, 11 figures

Subjects: Statistical Finance (q-fin.ST); General Finance (q-fin.GN)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>