<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7008">jesse van ruller solo transcriptions</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:07:00" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:07:25">http://www.svpproductions.com/guitar3.html</link><title>Joel Zemel's Jazz Guitar Information and Resources</title><description>* Joel Zemel's Jazz Guitar Information and Resources (clueweb12-1811wb-25-08086) http://www.svpproductions.com/guitar3.html ...Scofield Pat Martino Pat Metheny Charlie Hunter Liberty Ellman Jesse van Ruller Ted Quinlan Jonathan Kreisberg Martin Taylor Joel Zemel - Helpful...CDs. Top of Page Ted Greene recorded a fascinating solo guitar album in 1977 appropriately called, "Solo Guitar". He...creative streams of his generation." more Top of Page Jesse van Ruller "Jesse van Ruller was the first European musician to win the prestigious Thelonious Monk Competition in Washington in 1995. The jury, consisting of Pat Metheny, John Scofield, Jim Hall, Pat Martino and Mark Whitfield, was of the opinion that van Ruller is one of the most promising talents of his... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:11:58">http://www.jazzguitar.be/forum/players/58-favourite-player-poll-2.html</link><title>Favourite Player Poll - Page 2 - The Jazz Guitar Forum</title><description>* Favourite Player Poll - Page 2 - The Jazz Guitar Forum (clueweb12-1314wb-03-11232) http://www.jazzguitar.be/forum/players/58-favourite-player-poll-2.html ...the guitar more than anybody, that would be Eddie Van Halen. Sorry guys, I know this is jazz forum...26 AM jesse van rullerjesse van ruller. he is a monk-award winner. Check "you tube... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:14:44">http://www.jazzguitar.be/forum/jazzguitar-lessons/17957-practical-standard-group-new-song-selection.html</link><title>Practical Standard Group new song selection - The Jazz Guitar Forum</title><description>* Practical Standard Group new song selection - The Jazz Guitar Forum (clueweb12-0512wb-31-22273) http://www.jazzguitar.be/forum/jazzguitar-lessons/17957-practical-standard-group-new-song-selection.html ...alto sax- i would like to get some transcriptions of that line of play. they would be...alto sax- i would like to get some transcriptions of that line of play. they would be...Paul Desmonds' music style and their may be transcriptions available but I don't have a source for... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:27">http://www.ejazzlines.com/c933/c1253/ejazzlines-jazz-newsletter-November-2006-c1330.html</link><title>November 2006 jazz newsletter</title><description>* November 2006 jazz newsletter (clueweb12-0200wb-11-29021) http://www.ejazzlines.com/c933/c1253/ejazzlines-jazz-newsletter-November-2006-c1330.html ...Print Music Books by Instrument Songbook Collections Transcription Books Latin Jazz Books Holiday Songbooks Jazz...Jazz Play-Alongs Play-Alongs Play-Along Transcriptions Vocal Sing-Alongs Holiday Play-Alongs Non...Williams, and Michael Buble as well as transcriptions of charts used by Frank Sinatra, Dakota...Changes shows improvisers how to prepare for soloing and comping in free settings by exploring... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:18:08">http://www.playjazzguitar.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=2575</link><title>PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions</title><description>* PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions (clueweb12-1209wb-60-02879) http://www.playjazzguitar.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=2575 PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions ...Apr 13, 2007 2:50 pm    Post subject: Jesse van Ruller posted two of his composition: 'The Secret Champ' and 'Hi Higher' (original title: High, higher, her) He also posted his transcription of 'Simple Things' by Jim Hall. Check: http... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:06">http://www.playjazzguitar.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=51050</link><title>PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions</title><description>* PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions (clueweb12-1209wb-60-02874) http://www.playjazzguitar.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=51050 PlayJazzGuitar.com Forum :: View topic - contemporary scores and transcriptions ...Apr 13, 2007 2:50 pm    Post subject: Jesse van Ruller posted two of his composition: 'The Secret Champ' and 'Hi Higher' (original title: High, higher, her) He also posted his transcription of 'Simple Things' by Jim Hall. Check: http... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:53">http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/album/1273.html</link><title>Views</title><description>* Views (clueweb12-0105wb-24-23708) http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/album/1273.html ...Index Song Index Illustrated Index How To Buy Next Previous Criss Cross Jazz 1273 CD Jesse van Ruller Views Available: February 22, 2006 It's been ten years now since Jesse Van Ruller won the Thelonious Monk Jazz Competition (the first European artist to do so) and yet audiences have yet to fully appreciate his immense talents. On his third Criss Cross date, Van Ruller really comes into his own as a unique composer and guitarist on a session composed... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:40">http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/album/1235.html</link><title>Circles</title><description>* Circles (clueweb12-0105wb-32-27987) http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/album/1235.html ...Index Song Index Illustrated Index How To Buy Next Previous Criss Cross Jazz 1235 CD Jesse van Ruller Circles Available: May 8, 2003 Award-winning Dutch guitarist Jesse Van Ruller changes gears on his second Criss Cross outing, fronting a stellar quartet with Seamus Blake...contrast, Circles showcases the leader's compositional talents first and foremost. In addition to six varied Van Ruller originals and one by tenorman Seamus Blake, the group offers a ballad reading of "Gone... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:13">http://www.hornplace.com/FAB052.html</link><title>The European Fake Book</title><description>* The European Fake Book (clueweb12-0203wb-42-04035) http://www.hornplace.com/FAB052.html ...528 9224 What's New Fake Books Artist Transcriptions Ensembles Flute Improvisation Trombone Theory Trumpet Saxophone...Beginner Trombone Beginner Sax Beginner Flute Trumpet transcriptions Sax Transcriptions Flute Transcriptions Trombone Transcriptions On Sale Clearance Corner The European Fake...Taylor Philip Catherine Richard Galliano David Linx Jesse van Ruller Lars Jansson Kenny Wheeler Hendrik Meurkens Enrico... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7008-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7008_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:32:31">http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/artist/RullervanJesse.html</link><title>Jesse van Ruller</title><description>* Jesse van Ruller (clueweb12-0105wb-81-18352) http://www.crisscrossjazz.com/artist/RullervanJesse.html Jesse van Ruller Jesse van Ruller (G) Detailed information on Jesse van Ruller can be found on www.jessevanruller.com Jesse van Ruller's contact address is var d = "jessevanruller.com"; var u = "jesse"; var m = u + "@" + d;var c = m; document.write(''+c+''); Jesse van Ruller appears on the following 6 Criss... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>