<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:43:49" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:44:06">http://www.orthopaedicweblinks.com/OCOSH_Classification/Joint_Diseases/Synovial_Chondromatosis/index.html</link><title>Synovial Chondromatosis - Orthopaedic Web Links</title><description>* Synovial Chondromatosis - Orthopaedic Web Links (clueweb12-0609wb-92-12708) http://www.orthopaedicweblinks.com/OCOSH_Classification/Joint_Diseases/Synovial_Chondromatosis/index.html Synovial Chondromatosis - Orthopaedic Web Links Joint Diseases &gt; Synovial Chondromatosis Synovial Chondromatosis (Subscribe)   Synovial Chondromatosis [OCOSH Code: D015838 240207006 M67.9 JD_SC] Search only this category the entire directory Advanced Search Synovial Chondromatosis Location: http://gait.aidi.udel.edu/res695/homepage/pd_ortho/educate/clincase/syncon.htm... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:48:28">http://cal.vet.upenn.edu/projects/saortho/chapter_86/86mast.htm</link><title>http://cal.vet.upenn.edu/projects/saortho/chapter_86/86mast.htm</title><description>* http://cal.vet.upenn.edu/projects/saortho/chapter_86/86mast.htm (clueweb12-0306wb-82-05005) http://cal.vet.upenn.edu/projects/saortho/chapter_86/86mast.htm Synovial Fluid Chapter 86 Alan J. Lipowitz   Cellular Constituents Lubrication of Joints Arthrocentesis Pathologic Changes Of Articular Tissues References Normal synovial fluid is clear, pale yellow, viscid, and does not clot. Studies of mammalian synovial fluid have found considerable similarities among species, although notable differences do exist. The majority of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:50:13">http://www.anatomy.tv/loading.aspx</link><title>Joints</title><description>* Joints (clueweb12-1009wb-69-17868) http://www.anatomy.tv/StudyGuides/StudyGuide.aspx?guideid=19&amp;nextID=5&amp;maxID=0&amp;customer=primal ...System   Respiratory System   Urinary System   Digestive System   Male Reproductive System   Female Reproductive System   Endocrine System    Joints JOINTS CHAPTER OBJECTIVES When you have completed this chapter you should be able to: Identify the main types of joints. Identify and classify the different types of joints. Understand the anatomy of a synovial joint. Describe the types of synovial joints. Understand the function of a joint. Understand the action of joints. A joint (arthroses) is the joining between two or more... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:51:33">http://www.ivy-rose.co.uk/HumanBody/Skeletal/Joints/Synovial-Joints.php</link><title>Structure of Synovial Joints</title><description>* Structure of Synovial Joints (clueweb12-0411wb-27-29086) http://www.ivy-rose.co.uk/HumanBody/Skeletal/Joints/Synovial-Joints.php Structure of Synovial Joints Jointsjoints Fibrous joints Cartilaginous joints Structure of Synovial joints Movements at Synovial Joints ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:53:27">http://www.mananatomy.com/basic-anatomy/synovial-joints</link><title>Synovial Joints</title><description>* Synovial Joints (clueweb12-1912wb-40-09209) http://www.mananatomy.com/basic-anatomy/synovial-joints Synovial Joints Synovial Joints Human Anatomy » Basic Anatomy » Synovial Joints Synovial Joint (Image source: Madhero88/Wikipedia) Synovial joints are most evolved and therefore most mobile type of joints. They possess the following characteristic features; There articular surfaces are covered with hyaline cartilage. This... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:55:32">http://anatomy.uams.edu/anatomyhtml/joints_alpha.html</link><title>UAMS Department of Neurobiology and Developmental Sciences - Joints and Ligaments Tables</title><description>* UAMS Department of Neurobiology and Developmental Sciences - Joints and Ligaments Tables (clueweb12-0308wb-10-22561) http://anatomy.uams.edu/anatomyhtml/joints_alpha.html ...ends at the mid-sacral segmental level; it serves as a muscle attachment site zygapophyseal joint a small joint between the articular processes of adjacent vertebrae a synovial plane joint Joints and Ligaments of the Upper Limb - Listed Alphabetically Joint or ligament Description Notes acromioclavicular joint the joint between the distal end of the clavicle and the acromion of the scapula a plane synovial joint; the shape of the articulation encourages the acromion to slide inferior to the clavicle during... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:57:47">http://www.surgical-pathology.com/synovial_chondromatosis.htm</link><title>Ear Pathology Online: Synovial Chondromatosis of Temporomandibular Joint</title><description>* Ear Pathology Online: Synovial Chondromatosis of Temporomandibular Joint (clueweb12-0703wb-31-07339) http://www.surgical-pathology.com/synovial_chondromatosis.htm Ear Pathology Online: Synovial Chondromatosis of Temporomandibular Joint Synovial Chondromatosis of  Temporomandibular Joint Enter your search terms Submit search form   Web www.histopathology-india.net www.surgical-pathology.com www.pathology-india.com     Synovial chondromatosis is a benign monoarticular condition that rarely occurs in the temporomandibular joint. The etiology of this disease is unknown. This benign synovial process is characterized by the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:58:57">http://www.sciencethinking.org/anatphyI/skeletal_articulations.htm</link><title>Skeletal System: Articulations (Joints)</title><description>* Skeletal System: Articulations (Joints) (clueweb12-0209wb-30-31291) http://www.sciencethinking.org/anatphyI/skeletal_articulations.htm Skeletal System: Articulations (Joints) Notes on the Web Skeletal System: Articulations (Joints) Bruce G. Stewart Related Textbook Readings Marieb...Structural classification - based on the presence or absence of a space between the articulation bones (joint cavity) and the type of connective tissue that binds the joint together. a. Fibrous: there is no joint cavity and the bones are held together by fibrous connective tissue. b. Cartilaginous: there is no joint cavity and the bones are held together by cartilage. c. Synovial: there is a joint cavity and the bones forming the joint are united by a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:01:07">http://www.moreheadstate.edu/people_server/</link><title>BIOL 231 Lecture Outline 9</title><description>* BIOL 231 Lecture Outline 9 (clueweb12-0815wb-02-15933) http://people.morehead-st.edu/fs/m.mcmurr/231-L9.html ...The pubic symphysis contains a fibrocartilage disc to absorb compression.  Another example of a cartilaginous joint is between a true (vertebrosternal) ribs and the sternum, because costal cartilage separates the bones.  A third type of joint is the SYNOVIAL JOINT (Fig. 9.3).  These joints are freely moveable, and include such joints as the shoulder, elbow, hip, and knee joints. SYNOVIAL JOINTS are defined as freely movable articulations with a joint space (synovial cavity) between the articulating... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:02:52">http://www.cram.com/tag/joints</link><title>joints Flashcards</title><description>* joints Flashcards (clueweb12-0112wb-63-02490) http://www.flashcardexchange.com/tag/joints ...congenital developmental diseases joints metabolic of the Author: SuperJoeOD Created: 2011-10-08 Types of Joints \- Flashcards: 13 Description: The 3 main types of Joints Popularity 0 Tags joints Author: donald.saylor889 Created: 2011-09-28 Muscles - Flashcards: 35 Description: Gross Anatomy Exam 2 Popularity 0 Tags forearm hindlimb joints muscles nerves thoracic Author: lindseyl13 Created: 2011-09-24 Synovial Joints \- Flashcards: 1 Description: Classification, description, functions and structures Popularity 0 Tags joints synovial Author: Jrb8109... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>