<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:50:11" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:50:30">http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles15.htm</link><title>WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive</title><description>* WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive (clueweb12-0303wb-49-02369) http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles15.htm ...2000 2001 2002 2003 (1) 2003 (2) 2004 - 2005 2006 - 2007 2008 2009 2010 - 2011 KEANU REEVES ARTICLES AND INTERVIEWS ARCHIVE 2010 - 2011 New decade, new films, new possibilities. 2010 January 7Paternity suit seeking millions from Keanu Reeves should be thrown out: lawyerAllison JonesThe Canadian Press (Ca)January 7Keanu Counters Crazy Claims: Hypnosis, Disguises and Pseudonyms, Oh My (comments: 2)Gina SerpeE! Online... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:53:35">http://en.celebrity-people.com/news-celebrity-Keanu-Reeves-info-star-000734.html</link><title>Keanu Reeves News by Celebrity-People, Stars News and Celebrities Fans Club</title><description>* Keanu Reeves News by Celebrity-People, Stars News and Celebrities Fans Club (clueweb12-0311wb-18-23940) http://en.celebrity-people.com/news-celebrity-Keanu-Reeves-info-star-000734.html Keanu Reeves News by Celebrity-People, Stars News and Celebrities Fans Club Keanu Reeves   Acteur      News Keanu Reeves HispanicBusiness.comTracked Down: Keanu Reeves, Lisa D'Amato, Alan Cumming, and more...Boston HeraldBy Inside Track Former Boston bartender-turned-film director Chris Kenneally making the red carpet scene at the Berlin International Film Festival with... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-03"><link>http://engraving85abduct.seesaa.net/article/258756288.html</link><title>47 ronin keanu reeves. colin: beyonce lace wigs</title><description>* 47 ronin keanu reeves. colin: beyonce lace wigs (clueweb12-1000tw-87-05926) http://engraving85abduct.seesaa.net/article/258756288.html ...fan club. keanu reeves 1991. keanu reeves jewish. keanu reeves and wife. trinny woodall keanu reeves. keanu reeves book. keanu reeves in london 2011. life under water keanu reeves. rupert grint death. keanu reeves syme. keanu reeves blog. chris nothcontact keanu reeveskeanu reeves movies dvd. rupert grint birthday. keanu reeves samurai. happy keanu reeves. keanu reeves private life. keanu reeves dramatica. company films keanu reeves. keanu reeves height weight. keanu reeves wolfboy. keanu reeves cameron diaz.keanu reeves... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:58:47">http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles14.htm</link><title>WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive</title><description>* WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive (clueweb12-0302wb-93-25918) http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles14.htm WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive Login | Register HOME SITE DEFENDING KEANU LIBRARY FORUMS MISC Articles by...comments: 8)Garth PearceReveal (UK)January 7SpacedGill PringleFILMINK (Aus)January 7Keanu Reeves Does Vogue Hommes International Spring Summer 2009 (comments: 1)--StyleFrizz (US)January 9Sandra Bullock reportedly to star in third film in 'Speed' franchise--BANG (UK)January 14Oakville-raised actor keen on Keanu ReevesTina DepkoOakville Beaver (Ca)January 15Keanu Reeves set for 'Bebop'Tatiana SiegelVariety (US)January 15Fox hunts down 'Cowboy Bebop' (comments... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-05"><link>http://www.kipaddotta.com/movie-stars/keanu-reeves.html</link><title>Keanu Reeves!</title><description>* Keanu Reeves! (clueweb12-0112wb-51-26641) http://www.kipaddotta.com/movie-stars/keanu-reeves.html Keanu Reeves! ...Contact Us Guestbook Keanu Reeves! Charles Reeves (born September 2, 1964) is a Canadian film actor. Keanu Reeves is perhaps best known for his role as Neo in the action film trilogy The Matrix and also for roles in Speed and comedies such as Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure. Keanu Reeves was also a member of a grunge band, Dogstar, during the 1990s, as a bassist... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-06"><link>http://www.club-keanu.com/articles/art98.html</link><title>whoa is (not) me</title><description>* whoa is (not) me (clueweb12-1314wb-79-11439) http://www.club-keanu.com/articles/art98.html ...committal Vancouver Sun (Ca) June 5 Keanu's Eccentric Adventure Los Angeles Times (US) June 5 Keanu Reeves Ready for Action Long Beach Press-Telegram (US) June 7 Reeves is 'Speed'-ing to greater glory - by bus Final Edition (US) June 9 Reeves Enjoys the Role - Any Role Gannett News Service (US) June 9 Pre-'Speed' Reeves lacked a knack for capitalizing on plum film roles Atlanta Journal-Constitution (US) June 10 The Next Action Hero? Entertainment Weekly (US) June... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:12:13">http://www.fanwink.com/ai/keanureeves.htm</link><title>keanu reeves articles and posters</title><description>* keanu reeves articles and posters (clueweb12-0409wb-36-12977) http://www.fanwink.com/ai/keanureeves.htm ...1994 (on the backside: filmposter true romance)  2.00 &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp keanu reeves cover + article (3 pages) in dutch pop magazine hitkrant of 25 june 1994  2.00 &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp  2.50 &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp keanu reeves film review (0.7 pages) in dutch tv-guide veronica of 30 july 1994: speed  3.00 &amp;nbsp &amp;nbsp  4.00  3.00 keanu reeves poster (ą45x60cm) in dutch pop magazine hitkrant of 6 august 1994 (on the backside: filmposter... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:15:04">http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles13.htm</link><title>WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive</title><description>* WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive (clueweb12-0303wb-02-17816) http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles13.htm WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive Login | Register HOME SITE DEFENDING KEANU LIBRARY FORUMS MISC Articles by...2000 2001 2002 2003 (1) 2003 (2) 2004 - 2005 2006 - 2007 2008 2009 2010 - 2011 KEANU REEVES ARTICLES AND INTERVIEWS ARCHIVE 2008 I am particularly proud of this section, mostly because it marked my first active coverage of a film. I started adding to this archive in early November 2008, which pretty much included most... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:15:44">http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/2001_0214_aol.htm</link><title>WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive :: AOL Moviefone Live</title><description>* WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive :: AOL Moviefone Live (clueweb12-0303wb-49-02354) http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/2001_0214_aol.htm WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive :: AOL Moviefone Live Login | Register HOME SITE DEFENDING KEANU LIBRARY FORUMS MISC...Moviefone: Let's take another question. Who is that? ImernBarbie or something? Do you enjoy action films or romances more? Keanu Reeves: Oh, gosh. I don't really -- I don't have one where I'd say I like romances more or action films, no. Mr. Moviefone: You know, everybody... Keanu Reeves: Remember the children. Mr. Moviefone: Exactly. Me, I like the action movies. Everybody thinks about... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7026-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7026_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:19:53">http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles5.htm</link><title>WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive</title><description>* WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive (clueweb12-0303wb-20-02006) http://www.whoaisnotme.net/articles/articles5.htm WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive Login | Register HOME SITE DEFENDING KEANU LIBRARY FORUMS MISC Articles by Subject...WINM :: Keanu Reeves Articles &amp; Interviews Archive Login | Register HOME SITE DEFENDING KEANU LIBRARY FORUMS MISC Articles by Subject Articles by Author Articles by Source Articles by Country...To Just One WomanSteven RobinsonCambio16 (Spain)JanuaryHot Dogstar! - On The Road With Keanu's Band!Lesley O'TooleTV Hits (Aus)January 1Why it doesn't matter if Keanu Reeves and Brad Pitt aren't sleeping together (comments: 1)Michael FergusonUnknown Source (US)FebruaryCareless Whispers--Details Magazine (US)February 23Interview with Keanu Reeves on Sports, Film and other Things--WSCR, Sports Radio (US)MarchLunch with KeanuJoan GoodmanUnknown Magazine... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>