<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:46:18" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-01"><link>http://business.newsplurk.com/2012_04_08_archive.html</link><title>npusb: 08 April 2012</title><description>* npusb: 08 April 2012 (clueweb12-1806wb-99-06284) http://business.newsplurk.com/2012_04_08_archive.html ...States News &amp; Search Aggregator Best Buy to shut Biddeford store By Justin Fenton, The Baltimore Sun Best Buy will close its Inner Harbor and Hunt Valley stores in May, part of a move to shutter...temporarily closed to moreBaltimore Sun ( 4/14/2012 6:02:05 AM -08:00 )Best Buy to shut Biddeford storeEmployees are told today the store will close for good May 12 as the company restructures. By Edward D. Murphy emurphy@mainetoday.com BIDDEFORD — Best Buy is shutting down its store here as part of a companywide restructuring. morePress Herald... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-02"><link>http://www.akoss.net/collectible-store/sitemap.html</link><title>Site Map</title><description>* Site Map (clueweb12-0009wb-43-26544) http://www.akoss.net/collectible-store/sitemap.html Site Map Site Map: Buy Collectible Items At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Collectible Store Today!! Buy Accessories At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Collectible Store Today!! Buy Baseballs At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Collectible Store Today!! Buy Baskets At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Collectible Store Today!! Buy Bells At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Collectible Store Today!! Buy Birdhouses At The... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-03"><link>http://www.akoss.net/cooking/sitemap.html</link><title>Site Map</title><description>* Site Map (clueweb12-0009wb-31-04086) http://www.akoss.net/cooking/sitemap.html Site Map Site Map Buy The Best Cooking Products At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Cooking Store Today!! Buy Bakeware Products At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Cooking Store Today!!Buy Bakeware Sets At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Cooking Store Today!!Buy Bakeware Sets At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Cooking Store Today!!Buy Baking and Pastry Tools At The BEST... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-04"><link>http://www.akoss.net/gift-store/sitemap.html</link><title>Site Map</title><description>* Site Map (clueweb12-0009wb-31-04089) http://www.akoss.net/gift-store/sitemap.html Site Map Site Map Buy Angels At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Gift Store Today!! Buy African American Gifts At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Gift Store Today!!Buy African American Angels At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Gift Store Today!!Buy African Art At The BEST PRICES - Shop the Akoss Gift Store Today!!Buy Angels At The BEST PRICES - Shop the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-05"><link>http://business.newsplurk.com/2012/04/best-buy-to-shut-biddeford-store.html</link><title>npusb: Best Buy to shut Biddeford store</title><description>* npusb: Best Buy to shut Biddeford store (clueweb12-1807wb-91-17291) http://business.newsplurk.com/2012/04/best-buy-to-shut-biddeford-store.html Best Buy to shut Biddeford store \- NewsPlurk Best Buy to shut Biddeford store Best Buy to shut Biddeford store By Justin Fenton, The Baltimore Sun Best Buy will close its Inner Harbor and Hunt Valley stores in May, part of a move to shutter... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:59:13">http://vieoo.com/best-buy-closings/</link><title>Best Buy closings - Word</title><description>* Best Buy closings - Word (clueweb12-1200tw-92-12019) http://vieoo.com/best-buy-closings/ Best Buy closings \- Word Best Buy closings 15 views 1 You may want to go to:Search Best Buy closings in GoogleclosingsSears closingsKmart closingsHow to post image ads on Craigslist Part One A real estate agent exampleAre... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-07"><link>http://www.lasnark.com/2009/01/26/home-depot-to-close-all-expo-design-center-locations/2660</link><title>Home Depot to Close all Expo Design Center Locations</title><description>* Home Depot to Close all Expo Design Center Locations (clueweb12-0917wb-31-26218) http://www.lasnark.com/2009/01/26/home-depot-to-close-all-expo-design-center-locations/2660 Home Depot to Close all Expo Design Center Locations ...Low Prices. Cheap Online Pharmacy. Buy Cheapest buy levitra viagra online Now Special Prices For buy levitra viagra online! Low Prices. Buy Cheapest how to get cialis without prescriotion Online Special Prices For how to get cialis without prescriotion! Best Online. Buy Cheapest cialis online purchase Now Best Online. Discount Pharmacy Online. Buy Cheapest cialis from uk supplier Online Pharmacy Store. Guaranteed Shipping. Buy Cheap viagra oral jelly Online Top Online Pharmacy Supplier. Best Online. Buying Cheap cialis rx... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-08"><link>http://www.lasnark.com/2009/01/16/circuit-city-to-close-all-stores-and-liquidate-inventory/2539</link><title>Circuit City to Close all Stores and Liquidate Inventory!</title><description>* Circuit City to Close all Stores and Liquidate Inventory! (clueweb12-0919wb-16-04135) http://www.lasnark.com/2009/01/16/circuit-city-to-close-all-stores-and-liquidate-inventory/2539 Circuit City to Close all Stores and Liquidate Inventory! ...Low Prices. Cheap Online Pharmacy. Buy Cheapest buy levitra viagra online Now Special Prices For buy levitra viagra online! Low Prices. Buy Cheapest how to get cialis without prescriotion Online Special Prices For how to get cialis without prescriotion! Best Online. Buy Cheapest cialis online purchase Now Best Online. Discount Pharmacy Online. Buy Cheapest cialis from uk supplier Online Pharmacy Store. Guaranteed Shipping. Buy Cheap viagra oral jelly Online Top Online Pharmacy Supplier. Best Online. Buying Cheap cialis rx... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:03:18">http://apusa.us/best-buy-store-closing-24887/</link><title>Best Buy Store Closing | Associated Post - United States America</title><description>* Best Buy Store Closing | Associated Post - United States America (clueweb12-1201tw-09-11232) http://apusa.us/best-buy-store-closing-24887/ Best Buy Store Closing | Associated Post - United States America Best Buy Store Closing Best Buy Store Closing March 30, 2012 by Staff   Filed under Business News Advertisements ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7029-10"><link>http://www.lasnark.com/2011/03/10/is-your-favorite-la-marijuana-dispensary-closing-soon/9432</link><title>Is your favorite LA marijuana dispensary closing soon?</title><description>* Is your favorite LA marijuana dispensary closing soon? (clueweb12-1003wb-98-02118) http://www.lasnark.com/2011/03/10/is-your-favorite-la-marijuana-dispensary-closing-soon/9432 Is your favorite LA marijuana dispensary closing soon? ...Low Prices. Cheap Online Pharmacy. Buy Cheapest buy levitra viagra online Now Special Prices For buy levitra viagra online! Low Prices. Buy Cheapest how to get cialis without prescriotion Online Special Prices For how to get cialis without prescriotion! Best Online. Buy Cheapest cialis online purchase Now Best Online. Discount Pharmacy Online. Buy Cheapest cialis from uk supplier Online Pharmacy Store. Guaranteed Shipping. Buy Cheap viagra oral jelly Online Top Online Pharmacy Supplier. Best Online. Buying Cheap cialis rx... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>