<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7030">Lyrics Bangarang</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:09:02" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7030_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:09:23">http://www.songlyrics.com/skrillex/bangarang-lyrics/</link><title>BANGARANG LYRICS - SKRILLEX</title><description>* BANGARANG LYRICS - SKRILLEX (clueweb12-0100tw-14-12822) http://www.songlyrics.com/skrillex/bangarang-lyrics/ BANGARANG LYRICS \- SKRILLEX Lyrics Popular Lyrics Billboard Hot 100 Upcoming Lyrics Top Lyrics of 2011 Top Lyrics of 2010 Top Lyrics of 2009 More » Artists Popular Artists Artists A-Z Popular Albums Upcoming Albums Adele Rihanna...Music News News Roundup Spotlight Album Reviews All Articles » Follow Us Facebook Twitter Advertise Lyrics Artists - SSkrillex LyricsBangarang (EP) AlbumBangarang Lyrics Bangarang Lyrics Artist: Skrillex Album: Bangarang (EP) Bangarang" Ringtone to your Cell Please enable javascript to see this content. Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shouts to all my lost boys we rowdy Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shouts to all my lost boys we rowdy Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shouts to all my lost boys we rowdy Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shouts to all my lost boys BANGARANG! Bass! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa-BANG-BANG o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa, BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? BASS! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? BASS! BAYYYH! Lose boys, sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha- shout to my lost boys we rowdy Shout to all my lost boys, sho-sho-sho-sho-sho-sho-shout to all my lost boys BANGARANG! Shout to all my lost boys, sho-sho-sho-sho-sho-sho-shout to all my lost boys we rowdy Shout to all my boss boys sho-sho-sho-sho-sho-sho, BAYYH, BAYYYH, BANGARANG! BASS! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-berm-WOOOOOOO! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, you feel the? Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-berm-WOOOOOOO! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, you feel the? Wah-woooo-wah, berm, berm berm, berberber,berm, berm, Wah-woooo-wah-wah-wah-wah-WOOOOOO! Wah-woooo-wah, berm, berm berm, berberber,berm, berm, Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, you feel the? Wah-woooo-wah, berm, berm berm, berberber,berm, berm, Wah-woooo-wah-wah-wah-wah-WOOOOOO! Wah-woooo-wah, berm, berm berm, berberber,berm, berm, Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, do-do-do-do-do, BANGARANG! BASS! Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shouts to all my lost boys we rowdy Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shout to all my lost boys we rowdy Shouts to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shout to all my lost boys BANGARANG! BANG (Guitar Break) we rowdy Shout to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shout to all my lost boys we rowdy Shout to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shout to all my lost boys we rowdy Shout to all my lost boys Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-shout to all my lost boys BANGARANG! BASS! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-berm-WOOOOOOO! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, you feel the? Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-berm-WOOOOOOO! Wah-wah-ooo-wah, berm-berm-berm-mmmm-berm-berm-berm! Wah-ooo-ooo-woo-yuuuuh, you feel the? BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa-BANG-BANG o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa, BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa BANGARANG! BAYYYH! Wah-wa-wa-Wah-wa-wa, BANG BANG, o-ooo-ooo-ooo-o-ooo-ooo-wa you feel the? Hey someone got my marbles! But I got these beats banging out the back of my toy car! And yo i'm eatin' sun dip right now, not giving a fuuuuck MWAH~ Send "Bangarang" Ringtone to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-02"><link>http://lyrics.mediafireku.com/b/skrillex-bangarang-ft-sirah.html</link><title>SKRILLEX – BANGARANG (FT. SIRAH) » Free Lyrics</title><description>* SKRILLEX – BANGARANG (FT. SIRAH) » Free Lyrics (clueweb12-1107wb-06-09424) http://lyrics.mediafireku.com/b/skrillex-bangarang-ft-sirah.html SKRILLEX – BANGARANG (FT. SIRAH) » Free Lyrics Lyrics Free Download Lyrics Music And Video BANGARANG (FT. SIRAH)  B, SKRILLEX  Add comments ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-03"><link>http://www.azsongs.com</link><title>AZsongs: lyrics, music videos &amp; ringtones</title><description>* AZsongs: lyrics, music videos &amp; ringtones (clueweb12-0714wb-82-00661) http://www.azsongs.com ...40 Party Rock Anthem lyrics LMFAO lyrics | video | lyrics | 41 Princess of China lyrics Coldplay lyrics | video | lyrics | 42 Tonight Is the Night lyrics Outasight lyrics | video | lyrics | 43 Safe &amp; Sound lyrics Taylor Swift lyrics | video | lyrics | 44 I Don't Want This Night to End lyrics Luke Bryan lyrics | video | lyrics | 45 I Will Always Love You lyrics Whitney Houston lyrics | video | lyrics | 46 Bangarang lyrics Skrillex lyrics | video | lyrics | 47 Springsteen lyrics Eric Church lyrics | video | lyrics | 48 Alone... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-04"><link>http://www.gettherhythm.com/skrillex/bangarang.html</link><title>gettherhythm - page not found</title><description>* gettherhythm - page not found (clueweb12-0112wb-19-02030) http://www.gettherhythm.com/skrillex/bangarang.html ...U V W X Y Z   lyrics Frank Sinatra lyrics Elvis Presley lyrics Disney lyrics Elton John lyrics Hillsong United lyrics Eminem lyrics Lil' Wayne...for Party Rocking lyrics performed by LMFAO Home lyrics performed by Dierks Bentley Turning Tables lyrics performed by ADELE My Love Is Your Love lyrics performed by Whitney Houston L-O-V-E lyrics performed by Glee Cast Headlines lyrics performed by Drake No Church in the Wild lyrics performed by Kanye West Exhale lyrics performed by Whitney Houston Bangarang lyrics performed by Skrillex You lyrics performed by Chris Young Drink On It lyrics performed by... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-05"><link>http://www.bluelyrics.net</link><title>bluelyrics.net - the lyrics site</title><description>* bluelyrics.net - the lyrics site (clueweb12-0012wb-51-24436) http://www.bluelyrics.net ...by AWOLNATION Lyrics Somethin' 'Bout a Truck lyrics by Kip Moore Lyrics Shake It Out lyrics by Florence + The Machine Lyrics Dynamite lyrics by Taio Cruz Lyrics La Isla Bonita lyrics by Glee Cast Lyrics Lights lyrics by Ellie Goulding Lyrics Not Afraid lyrics by Eminem Lyrics You Make Me Feel... lyrics by Cobra Starship Lyrics Hell On Heels lyrics by Pistol Annies Lyrics Bangarang lyrics by Skrillex Lyrics Tonight Tonight lyrics by Hot Chelle Rae Lyrics Country Girl lyrics... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7030_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:19:51">http://www.mcwba.co.uk/</link><title>Cher lyrics - Uppercut Music - lyrics &amp; videos</title><description>* Cher lyrics - Uppercut Music - lyrics &amp; videos (clueweb12-0611wb-72-08131) http://www.uppercutmusic.com/artist_c/cher_lyrics.html ...Fire to the Rain lyrics   Somebody That I Used to Know lyrics   Part of Me lyrics   Starships lyrics   Wild Ones lyrics   Call Me Maybe lyrics   Good Girl lyrics   Sexy and I Know It lyrics   Young, Wild &amp; Free lyrics   Drive By lyrics   Turn Me On lyrics   What Makes You Beautiful lyrics   AZsongs.com Recent Videos Heartbeat lyrics Lost In You lyrics Hey, Soul Sister lyrics Bangarang lyrics Here's to Us lyrics I'm a Gummy Bear lyrics Lie Baby Lie lyrics Look... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-07"><link>http://lyrics.quedeletras.com/cd-skrillex-album-bangarang/download-12288-lyrics-skrillex-bangarang.html</link><title>SKRILLEX - BANGARANG. SONG LYRICS ALBUM SKRILLEX - BANGARANG.DOWNLOAD SKRILLEX - BANGARANG VIDEO SKRILLEX</title><description>* SKRILLEX - BANGARANG. SONG LYRICS ALBUM SKRILLEX - BANGARANG.DOWNLOAD SKRILLEX - BANGARANG VIDEO SKRILLEX (clueweb12-0009wb-05-08678) http://lyrics.quedeletras.com/cd-skrillex-album-bangarang/download-12288-lyrics-skrillex-bangarang.html SKRILLEX - BANGARANG. SONG LYRICS ALBUM SKRILLEX - BANGARANG.DOWNLOAD SKRILLEX - BANGARANG VIDEO SKRILLEX SKRILLEX - BANGARANG Lyrics   Search: Artist Album Lyric song LYRICS SKRILLEX BANGARANG SKRILLEX MY NAME IS SKRILLEX SKRILLEX SCARY MONSTERS AND NICE SPRITES SKRILLEX - BANGARANG 01- Bangarang Lyrics02- Breakin' A Sweat Lyrics03- The Devil's Den Lyrics04- Kyoto Lyrics05- Summit Lyrics06- Breathe Lyrics07- Cinema Lyrics08... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7030_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:25:59">http://www.lyricsmansion.com/search_index/skrillex-lyrics.html</link><title>Skrillex lyrics</title><description>* Skrillex lyrics (clueweb12-0502wb-10-31856) http://www.lyricsmansion.com/search_index/skrillex-lyrics.html ...WORKING IN AUSSIE lyrics provided for educational purposes only. Lyrics /* cf_lead; 728x90 */monetized_ad_client_song = "";monetized_ad_client_artist = "Skrillex";monetized_ad_id = "39380461";/* cf_sky 160x600 */monetized_ad_client_song = "Insert song variable here";monetized_ad_client_artist = "Skrillex";monetized_ad_id = "39380845"; Send "Skrillex" Ringtones to your Cell Album: BANGARANG [EP] (2011)Bangarang LyricsBreakin' A Sweat LyricsKyoto LyricsSummit LyricsThe Devil's Den... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-09"><link>http://www.musicoop.com/skrillex/bangarang.html</link><title>Bangarang LYRICS by Skrillex</title><description>* Bangarang LYRICS by Skrillex (clueweb12-0204wb-75-23559) http://www.musicoop.com/skrillex/bangarang.html Bangarang LYRICS by Skrillex Bangarang Lyrics Lyrics First of the Year lyrics Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites lyrics Weekends!!! lyrics Bangarang lyrics Kyoto lyrics Kill Everybody lyrics Right In lyrics Breakn' a Sweat lyrics Top MusiCoop Songs Part of Me Lyrics I Will Always Love You Lyrics Rolling In the Deep Lyrics Set Fire to the Rain Lyrics Starships Lyrics We Are... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7030-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7030_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:19">http://www.mcwba.co.uk/</link><title>Cave In lyrics - Uppercut Music - lyrics &amp; videos</title><description>* Cave In lyrics - Uppercut Music - lyrics &amp; videos (clueweb12-0700wb-61-21255) http://www.uppercutmusic.com/artist_c/cave_in_lyrics.html ...That I Used to Know lyrics   Set Fire to the Rain lyrics   Part of Me lyrics   Starships lyrics   Wild Ones lyrics   Call Me Maybe lyrics   Good Girl lyrics   Sexy and I Know It lyrics   Young, Wild &amp; Free lyrics   Drive By lyrics   Turn Me On lyrics   Take Care lyrics   AZsongs.com Recent Videos No Church in the Wild lyrics Sorry for Party Rocking lyrics Bangarang lyrics Ours lyrics Girl Gone Wild lyrics Red Solo Cup lyrics Moves Like Jagger lyrics Somethin'... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>