<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7036">holiday houses ardennes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:25:28" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:25:54">http://www.casaspain.uk.com/wing/rs_holiday_apartments_vacation_rentals_1.asp?region=champagne-ardenne</link><title>CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE accommodation: bed and breakfast CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE vacation rentals summer</title><description>* CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE accommodation: bed and breakfast CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE vacation rentals summer (clueweb12-0100wb-02-20224) http://www.2000villas.com/wing/ren-accommodation-lodgings.aspx?reg=champagne-ardenne CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE accommodation: bed and breakfast CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE vacation rentals summer &gt; accommodation lodgings &gt; champagne-ardenne Rent accommodation...CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE accommodation: bed and breakfast CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE vacation rentals summer &gt; accommodation lodgings &gt; champagne-ardenne Rent accommodation CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE. Bed and breakfast CHAMPAGNE...LES-BAINS VIX Operation type Rental For Sale Kind Property Any Appartment Villa Semidetached Country House Hotel/Hostal Situation Any Beach City/Town Inland Mountain Nr Persons Any 2 to 4 3 to 6 5 to 8 Over 8 .capa_a { height: 58px; width: 200px; background-color: #ffffcc; } .capa_b { height: 13px; padding:2px; background-color: #5799DB; } .capa_c { height: 45px; overflow: auto; overflow-x: hidden; background-color: #ffffcc; padding-top:6px; padding-bottom:6px; padding-left:6px; } CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE apartments vacation rentals champagne-ardenne country houses champagne-ardenne accommodation lodgings champagne-ardenne vacation villas holiday rentals champagne-ardenne vacation houses holiday homes champagne-ardenne ... for City CANNES (22) VELLUIRE (22) AIX-EN-PROVENCE (21) ARGELES-SUR... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:28:12">http://www1.iha.com/Vacation-rental/J6/France/Champagne-ardenne-Rental_1.htm</link><title>CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE Rental: Holiday rental, Guest House - Bed &amp; Breakfast, GĂŽte - Self Catering Champagne-Ardenne</title><description>* CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE Rental: Holiday rental, Guest House - Bed &amp; Breakfast, GĂŽte - Self Catering Champagne-Ardenne (clueweb12-1214wb-19-13499) http://www.iha.ie/Holiday-rental/J6/France/Champagne-ardenne-Rental_1.htm CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE Rental: Holiday rental, Guest House \- Bed &amp; Breakfast, GĂŽte - Self Catering Champagne-Ardenne Ardenne Rental | Champagne-Ardenne Holiday rental | Champagne-Ardenne Guest House \- Bed &amp; Breakfast | Champagne-Ardenne GĂŽte - Self Catering Rental 62743 available offers HOLIDAY RENTALS BOOK DIRECT WITH THE OWNERS   Access member's area  "; document.getElementById("div_shadow_world_map... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:29:52">http://www.bookcottages.com/the-ardennes.htm</link><title>The Ardennes cottages. Find and book 2 bedroom holiday apartments in The Ardennes. Your guide to cottages and holiday self catering in The Ardennes, BE</title><description>* The Ardennes cottages. Find and book 2 bedroom holiday apartments in The Ardennes. Your guide to cottages and holiday self catering in The Ardennes, BE (clueweb12-0100wb-93-17623) http://www.bookcottages.com/the-ardennes.htm ...2 bedroom The Ardennes cottages or click on the links below for cottages in The Ardennes with a smaller or larger number of bedrooms. 1 Bedroom | 2 Bedrooms | 3 Bedrooms | 4 Bedrooms | 5 Bedrooms | 6 Bedrooms | 7 Bedrooms | 8 Bedrooms | 9 Bedrooms | 11 Bedrooms     Search by availability     show on map Appartment A , Luxemburg, Daverdisse, Walloon Region, The Ardennes Holiday cottage, Common plot with a house of 75 sqm. in a plot of 1700 sqm. 2 bedroom property with 2 double... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:31:44">http://www.holiday-rental.location-et-vacances.com/holiday-rental-Champagne-Ardenne,8.html</link><title>Holiday rental Champagne Ardenne</title><description>* Holiday rental Champagne Ardenne (clueweb12-1202wb-92-17800) http://www.holiday-rental.location-et-vacances.com/holiday-rental-Champagne-Ardenne,8.html Holiday rental Champagne Ardenne rental Champagne Ardenne230 adverts : Apartment , House, House with character, Cottage, Chalet, Hotellastaction = 0;function rollLayer(type) {lastaction++;if(type==0) {setTimeout("if(lastaction == "+lastaction+"){document.getElementById('rollLayer').className = 'rollLayerNoAff';}", 100);}if(type==1) {document.getElementById('rollLayer').className = 'rollLayer';}} &gt; Champagne Ardenne &gt; Francefunction click_visibilite_plus(id_bien) { executeAjax('/scripts/ajax_ajout_click_visi_plus.php','id_bien='+id_bien); }Visibility + holiday rental Holiday rental Champagne ArdenneAube - FranceRef : 16200001www:holiday-rental:location-et-vacances:com" height="78" width="96" border="0" /&gt;Mesnil Saint PĂ¨reHouse 4 personsfrom 170âŹ weekDetails  Aube - FranceRef : 16589001www:holiday-rental:location... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-05"><link>http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-provence_alpes_cote_azur-r21.html</link><title>Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Provence-Alpes-Cote d'Azur HOLIDAY RENTALS PROVENCE-ALPS-RIVIERA France</title><description>* Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Provence-Alpes-Cote d'Azur HOLIDAY RENTALS PROVENCE-ALPS-RIVIERA France (clueweb12-0412wb-00-01147) http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-provence_alpes_cote_azur-r21.html Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Provence-Alpes-Cote d'Azur HOLIDAY RENTALS PROVENCE-ALPS-RIVIERA France...Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Provence-Alpes-Cote d'Azur HOLIDAY RENTALS PROVENCE-ALPS-RIVIERA France ...Bed and Breakfast by tourism area   Holiday rentals by city   Bed and Breakfast by city Holiday rentals and bed &amp; breakfast ads in France   Home Services Customers area Holiday rentals Category   Holiday rentals Bed and Breakfast Directory     Themes   Seaside Mountain Countryside City     Regions   Alsace Aquitaine Auvergne Normandy - Lower Burgundy Brittany Centre Loire Valley Champagne Ardenne Corsica Franche Comté Normandy - Upper Paris - Ile de France Languedoc-Roussillon Limousin Lorraine Midi Pyrenees... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:35:59">http://www.bookcottages.com/the-ardennes-3.htm</link><title>The Ardennes holiday properties. Find and book 3 bedroom villas in The Ardennes. Your guide to cottages and self catering holiday apartments in The Ardennes, BE</title><description>* The Ardennes holiday properties. Find and book 3 bedroom villas in The Ardennes. Your guide to cottages and self catering holiday apartments in The Ardennes, BE (clueweb12-0102wb-80-25637) http://www.bookcottages.com/the-ardennes-3.htm ...11 Bedrooms     Search by availability     show on map Azur , Liege, Büllingen, Walloon Region, The Ardennes Holiday cottage, Closed natural plot with a house of 300 sqm. in a plot of 3000 sqm. 3 bedroom property with 6 single...more information add to shortlist Domaine Du Bonsoy Pin , Namur, Hastičre, Walloon Region, The Ardennes Holiday cottage, Natural plot with a house of 61 sqm. in a plot of 100 sqm. 3 bedroom property with 6 double... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7036_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:39:05">http://www.mediahols.com/champagne-ardenne-holiday-rentals/00038000/</link><title>CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE HOLIDAY RENTALS: apartments, villas, cottages, bed and breakfasts, houses, studio apartments</title><description>* CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE HOLIDAY RENTALS: apartments, villas, cottages, bed and breakfasts, houses, studio apartments (clueweb12-0510wb-55-01264) http://www.mediahols.com/EN/champagne-ardenne_holiday-rentals_idr2-8/rentals.php CHAMPAGNE-ARDENNE HOLIDAY RENTALS: apartments, villas, cottages, bed and breakfasts, houses, studio apartments Holiday Rentals  Owner section - Free advert  Renter Section Holiday-rental quality Multi-risk insurance  Your advert shopping basket Find a holiday home Quick property search Destination  Country, region, county, area of special interest, city, resort,... Tip... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-08"><link>http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-normandie-r4.html</link><title>Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Normandy - Lower HOLIDAY RENTALS LOWER NORMANDY France</title><description>* Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Normandy - Lower HOLIDAY RENTALS LOWER NORMANDY France (clueweb12-0411wb-72-32860) http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-normandie-r4.html ...Bed and Breakfast by tourism area   Holiday rentals by city   Bed and Breakfast by city Holiday rentals and bed &amp; breakfast ads in France   Home Services Customers area Holiday rentals Category   Holiday rentals Bed and Breakfast Directory     Themes   Seaside Mountain Countryside City     Regions   Alsace Aquitaine Auvergne Normandy - Lower Burgundy Brittany Centre Loire Valley Champagne Ardenne Corsica Franche Comté Normandy - Upper Paris - Ile de France Languedoc-Roussillon Limousin Lorraine Midi Pyrenees... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-09"><link>http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-brittany-r6.html</link><title>Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Brittany HOLIDAY RENTALS BRITTANY France</title><description>* Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Brittany HOLIDAY RENTALS BRITTANY France (clueweb12-0411wb-81-05369) http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-brittany-r6.html Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Brittany HOLIDAY RENTALS BRITTANY France ...Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Brittany HOLIDAY RENTALS BRITTANY France ...Mountain Countryside City     Regions   Alsace Aquitaine Auvergne Normandy - Lower Burgundy Brittany Centre Loire Valley Champagne Ardenne Corsica Franche Comté Normandy - Upper Paris - Ile de France Languedoc-Roussillon Limousin Lorraine Midi Pyrenees Nord-Pas-de-Calais Pays de Loire Picardy Poitou-Charentes Provence-Alpes-Cote d'Azur Rhône-Alpes Outre-Mer     Partners   BB-in-France.com Partners 1         Our selection of holidays rentals     House \- Villa6 person(s)SAINT-ARMEL     Residence - Manor9 person(s)LE CLOITRE ST THEGONNEC... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7036-10"><link>http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-languedoc_roussillon-r13.html</link><title>Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Languedoc-Roussillon HOLIDAY RENTALS LANGUEDOC ROUSSILLON France</title><description>* Holidays Rentals, vacation Rental accomodation lodging Languedoc-Roussillon HOLIDAY RENTALS LANGUEDOC ROUSSILLON France (clueweb12-0411wb-90-30347) http://www.cap-location.com/gb/holidaysrentals/holiday-rental-languedoc_roussillon-r13.html ...Bed and Breakfast by tourism area   Holiday rentals by city   Bed and Breakfast by city Holiday rentals and bed &amp; breakfast ads in France   Home Services Customers area Holiday rentals Category   Holiday rentals Bed and Breakfast Directory     Themes   Seaside Mountain Countryside City     Regions   Alsace Aquitaine Auvergne Normandy - Lower Burgundy Brittany Centre Loire Valley Champagne Ardenne Corsica Franche Comté Normandy - Upper Paris - Ile de France Languedoc-Roussillon Limousin Lorraine Midi Pyrenees... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>