<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:50:46" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-01"><link>http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4235/the-rum-diary</link><title>The Rum Diary Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed</title><description>* The Rum Diary Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed (clueweb12-0209wb-23-21080) http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4235/the-rum-diary The Rum Diary Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed ...Sign In / Create An Account      About MovieDawg.com      Advertising      Disclaimer      Support REVIEWS Overall Rating Classic Dud Story Acting Visuals Direction Read Reviews | Add A Review Tiring of the noise and madness of New York and the crushing conventions of late Eisenhower-era America, journalist Paul Kemp travels to the pristine island of Puerto Rico to write for a local newspaper, The San Juan Star, run by downtrodden editor Lotterman. Adopting the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-02"><link>http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/2472/death-of-a-dynasty</link><title>Death of a Dynasty Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed</title><description>* Death of a Dynasty Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed (clueweb12-0209wb-17-00270) http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/2472/death-of-a-dynasty Death of a Dynasty Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed REVIEWS Overall Rating Classic Dud Story Acting Visuals Direction Read Reviews | Add A Review A story which centers around Dave Katz, a journalist at a hip-hop magazine who is sent on assignment to uncover the often comedic... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:55:18">http://www.allsitecafe.com/search/write_travel_reviews.html</link><title>Write Travel Reviews</title><description>* Write Travel Reviews (clueweb12-1906wb-20-17628) http://www.allsitecafe.com/search/write_travel_reviews.html ...LordBalfors' Rules for How to Write an Effective Travel Review ... Summary: Unhappy with your travel review ratings? Perhaps these ideas may help. Things to Do When Writing a Review: LordBalfors' Rules for How to Write an Effective ...http://www.epinions.com/content_3627262084 Traveling Jobs - Learn How to Write Travel Articles and Holiday ... A dream of many writers is to get traveling jobs as journalists and travel for free. In this article you can learn how to write great travel... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-04"><link>http://www.journalism.co.uk/directory/General_sites_for_journalists/more8.shtml</link><title>http://www.journalism.co.uk/directory/General_sites_for_journalists/more8.shtml</title><description>* http://www.journalism.co.uk/directory/General_sites_for_journalists/more8.shtml (clueweb12-0603wb-10-07557) http://www.journalism.co.uk/directory/General_sites_for_journalists/more8.shtml ...Login/Register Search the entire directory only this category Advanced Search journalists &gt; Page 8 General sites for journalists Links 1 of 82 of 83 of...It Rate It Bookmark It The Poynter Institute The Poynter Institute is a school for journalists, future journalists, and teachers of journalists. http://www.poynter.org/ Review It Rate It Bookmark It The World Association of Newspapers (WAN) The World Association of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:02:08">http://www.gamecareerguide.com/forums/archive/index.php/f-10.html</link><title>Writing [Archive] - Game Career Guide Forums</title><description>* Writing [Archive] - Game Career Guide Forums (clueweb12-0107wb-61-27109) http://www.gamecareerguide.com/forums/archive/index.php/f-10.html ...survey - video games and growth Getting Into Video Game Journalism An outlet for aspiring gaming journalists Review of website and volunteer writers? Career in video game journalism? Localization Affair College Classes Games...reviewer website.. Degree or diploma in journalism? Editorials on Controversial Games Wanted Seeking interesting Game Journalists / bloggers What writing, specifically? Writers needed for new gaming site Amateur Reviewers Needed $$$$ Writers wanted for reviews and overall industry speculation "...only solution to game writing is branching." Write about games - the ground up. Writers Needed- Basic Start My Game reviews Helpful article to guide your review writing Where to begin? 'Other' Game Writing Jobs Experience freelance game Journalists [Paid] More gaming... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:03:02">http://www.recorders.com/Categories/366-Journalist-and-Broadcasting-Transcription.aspx/1/80000000%5e475</link><title>Journalist &amp; Broadcasting</title><description>* Journalist &amp; Broadcasting (clueweb12-0604wb-27-32200) http://www.recorders.com/Categories/366-Journalist-and-Broadcasting-Transcription.aspx/1/80000000%5e475 ...see upgrade SEE ACCESSORIES our price $828.00 retail price N/A you save 0 Write Review Read 0 Reviews Qty. Add to Cart see upgrade Olympus AS5000-DS5000 PRO Bundle Olympus AS5000-DS5000 PRO...see upgrade SEE ACCESSORIES our price $799.98 retail price N/A you save 0 Write Review Read 0 Reviews Qty. Add to Cart see upgrade Olympus AS5000-DS3400 PRO Bundle Olympus AS5000-DS3400 PRO... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-07"><link>http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4164/5-days-of-war</link><title>5 Days of War Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed</title><description>* 5 Days of War Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed (clueweb12-0602wb-10-20991) http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4164/5-days-of-war 5 Days of War Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed REVIEWS Overall Rating Classic Dud Story Acting Visuals Direction Read Reviews | Add A Review A veteran war journalist documents atrocities in the crossfire between Georgian and Russian forces, and finds that releasing the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-08"><link>http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4310/haywire</link><title>Haywire Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed</title><description>* Haywire Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed (clueweb12-0206wb-30-12074) http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4310/haywire Haywire Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed ...Sign In / Create An Account      About MovieDawg.com      Advertising      Disclaimer      Support REVIEWS Overall Rating Classic Dud Story Acting Visuals Direction Read Reviews | Add A Review Mallory Kane is a highly trained operative who works for a government security contractor in the dirtiest, most dangerous corners of the world. After successfully freeing a Chinese journalist held hostage, she is double crossed and left for dead by someone close to her... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:14:03">http://www.recorders.com/Categories/366-Journalist-and-Broadcasting-Philips.aspx/1/80000010%5ePhilips</link><title>Journalist &amp; Broadcasting</title><description>* Journalist &amp; Broadcasting (clueweb12-0604wb-27-32195) http://www.recorders.com/Categories/366-Journalist-and-Broadcasting-Philips.aspx/1/80000010%5ePhilips ...upgrade SEE ACCESSORIES our price $998.00 retail price $1,679.00 you save 40% Write Review Read 4 Reviews Qty. Add to Cart see upgrade LFH7277 Pro Transcription &amp; DPM9600 Recorder Philips Pro 7277 Transcription...see upgrade SEE ACCESSORIES our price $828.00 retail price N/A you save 0 Write Review Read 0 Reviews Qty. Add to Cart see upgrade Philips SpeechMike Air 3000 (LFH3000) The highly successful SpeechMike... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7037-10"><link>http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4302/addiction-incorporated</link><title>Addiction Incorporated Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed</title><description>* Addiction Incorporated Movie Profile // MovieDawg.com - Box Office Flicks - Movie Flicks Reviewed (clueweb12-0512wb-32-33487) http://www.moviedawg.com/movie/4302/addiction-incorporated ...Sign In / Create An Account      About MovieDawg.com      Advertising      Disclaimer      Support REVIEWS Overall Rating Classic Dud Story Acting Visuals Direction Read Reviews | Add A Review The true story of how Victor DeNoble's unexpected discovery of an addiction ingredient in tobacco leads to both more addictive Marlboro cigarettes and Congressional testimony. The public revelation of long held tobacco industry secrets leads journalists, politicians, attorneys and whistle blowers into an unexpected alliance, that achieves the first ever federal... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>