<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7040">vom fass gent</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:05:42" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:05:57">http://www.cityplug.be/en/Ghent/places/?what=Specialized-Stores</link><title>Shopping Specialized Stores in Ghent</title><description>* Shopping Specialized Stores in Ghent (clueweb12-0508wb-02-24083) http://www.cityplug.be/en/Ghent/Shopping/A7T11YOW_BYMN5JIB_Specialized-Stores.html ...Kouter South - University Veldstraat - korenmarkt Vrijdagmarkt 9000 Gent 9030 Mariakerke 9031 Drongen 9032 Wondelgem 9040...1 Avis 10/ 10 Shopping | Leisure AVA - Gent 1 Avis 10/ 10 Shopping | Specialized Store...Shopping | Specialized Store Bongo Shopping | Gifts - Souvenirs Gent Zuid Shopping | Specialized Store Vom Fass Gent Shopping | Specialized Store Music Man Dance Store... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:08:25">http://thisisspain.info/costa-del-sol/business-1st/vom-fass/summer-recipes/</link><title>This is Spain: Summer Recipes</title><description>* This is Spain: Summer Recipes (clueweb12-0009wb-04-14081) http://thisisspain.info/costa-del-sol/business-1st/vom-fass/summer-recipes ...Cities Costa Blanca Costa del Sol Catalonia Travel Gallery Links Mallorca Property Canaries General Contact Vom FassMixed Green Salad Summer Recipes Tequila Gold Lemon and Ginger Waldburg Balsam Summer Recipes Summer Time and Vom Fass, Fuengirola FRESH STRAWBERRY-LIMES LIQUEUR…..SIMPLY DELICIOUS!!!   Only healthy and freshly ripened strawberries are processed... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:09:47">http://www.franchiseadvantage.com/2239-vom-fass-franchise.aspx</link><title>VOM FASS - Franchise Opportunities And Business Opportunity Guide</title><description>* VOM FASS - Franchise Opportunities And Business Opportunity Guide (clueweb12-0111wb-83-02771) http://www.franchiseadvantage.com/Franchises/2239-VOM_FASS_Franchise.aspx VOM FASS \- Franchise Opportunities And Business Opportunity Guide VOM FASS Home  &gt;  Food: Service, Retail  &gt;  VOM FASS Liquid Capital Required: $80,000Total Investment: $203,000 - $393,000Training AvailableFinancing Available... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:11:38">http://www.businessbroker.net/franchise/vom-fass-franchise-for-sale-2239.aspx</link><title>VOM FASS Franchise Businesses For Sale at Business Broker</title><description>* VOM FASS Franchise Businesses For Sale at Business Broker (clueweb12-0502wb-78-12178) http://www.businessbroker.net/franchise/vom-fass.ihtml VOM FASS Franchise Businesses For Sale at Business Broker ...Tennessee Texas Utah Vermont Virgin Islands, U.S. Virginia Washington Washington, D.C. West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming VOM FASS VOM FASS Franchise Information: VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:13:33">http://www.franchisebusinesssolutions.net/Food-Related-Businesses</link><title>VOM FASS, http://www.franchisebusinesssolutions.net/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS</title><description>* VOM FASS, http://www.franchisebusinesssolutions.net/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS (clueweb12-1902wb-09-11380) http://www.franchisebusinesssolutions.net/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS VOM FASS, http://www.franchisebusinesssolutions.net/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS ...Why Buy a Franchise?Franchise Consultant ServicesFuture of FranchisingPrivacy PolicyFranchise Business Solutions VOM FASS VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually, by the German Franchise Association, for excellence) is now available in the United States! VOM FASS was the unanimous choice of the prominent panel of franchise experts, and the Federal Ministry... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:17:33">http://www.franchiseregister.com/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS</link><title>VOM FASS, http://www.franchiseregister.com/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS</title><description>* VOM FASS, http://www.franchiseregister.com/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS (clueweb12-0106wb-91-26868) http://www.franchiseregister.com/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS VOM FASS, http://www.franchiseregister.com/Food-Related-Businesses/VOM-FASS ...Repair &amp; RestorationRetail HomeRetail SalesSenior CareSignsSportsTanningUniqueDisclosureFranchise Alliance VOM FASS VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually, by the German Franchise Association, for excellence) is now available in the United States! VOM FASS was the unanimous choice of the prominent panel of franchise experts, and the Federal Ministry... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:18:01">http://www.smallbusinesssale.com/VOM-FASS-franchise/</link><title>VOM FASS Business for Sale - VOM FASS Franchise Business Information</title><description>* VOM FASS Business for Sale - VOM FASS Franchise Business Information (clueweb12-1020wb-26-26353) http://www.smallbusinesssale.com/VOM-FASS-franchise/ VOM FASS Business for Sale - VOM FASS Franchise Business Information ...have 0 items in your request list You may also be interested in these franchises: VOM FASS VOM FASS Franchise Information: VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:21:08">http://www.smallbusinessopportunity.com/</link><title>Small Business Opportunity Financing</title><description>* Small Business Opportunity Financing (clueweb12-1401wb-78-06178) http://www.smallbusinessopportunity.com/business_676259/vomfass.asp ...Consulting Financing Franchises Businesses Specific Concepts Bookmark this Page Contact Us    Home › Small Business Opportunity › Vom Fass VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually, by the German Franchise Association, for excellence) is now available in the United States! VOM FASS was the unanimous choice of the prominent panel of franchise experts, and the Federal Ministry... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:22:46">http://www.bestfranchiseopportunities.com/</link><title>Vom Fass franchise info from Best Franchise Opportunities</title><description>* Vom Fass franchise info from Best Franchise Opportunities (clueweb12-0405wb-13-23553) http://www.bestfranchiseopportunities.com/showcase/598780_VomFass_franchise.asp Vom Fass franchise info from Best Franchise Opportunities...VideoReal Estate ServicesRetailSecuritySenior Care ServicesSportsStaffingTravelVendingWholesale/Distribution  VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually, by the German Franchise Association, for excellence) is now available in the United States! VOM FASS was the unanimous choice of the prominent panel of franchise experts, and the Federal Ministry... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7040-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7040_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:23:48">http://www.restaurantfranchise.com/</link><title>Restaurant Franchise--The Online Resource for Restaurant Franchises and Entrepreneurs</title><description>* Restaurant Franchise--The Online Resource for Restaurant Franchises and Entrepreneurs (clueweb12-0611wb-59-25306) http://www.restaurantfranchise.com/franchise/61292/VomFass.php ...South Carolina    - South Dakota    - Tennessee    - Texas    - Utah    - Vermont    - Virginia    - Washington    - West Virginia    - Wisconsin    - Wyoming    VOM FASS, recent winner of the coveted and prestigious German Franchise of the Year award (presented annually, by the German Franchise Association, for excellence) is now available in the United States! VOM FASS was the unanimous choice of the prominent panel of franchise experts, and the Federal Ministry... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>