<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:58:57" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:59:28">http://www.misspronouncer.com/parks_all.html</link><title>Miss Pronouncer: How do you pronounce parks? Listen to audio pronunciations of Wisconsin parks</title><description>* Miss Pronouncer: How do you pronounce parks? Listen to audio pronunciations of Wisconsin parks (clueweb12-1405wb-69-32667) http://www.misspronouncer.com/parks_all.html ...Park  Great Divide Wayside Park  Hodgkins Park  Lake Park  Maslowski Park  Ojibwa Memorial Park  Prentice Park  West Second Street Historic District Barron County:  Bandli County Park  Barron County Fairgrounds  Barron County Park  Barron County Park  Bear Lake Sedge Meadow State Natural Area  Becker Park  Cedar Lake County Park  Eagle Point Park  Engle Creek Springs State Public Fishing Area  Four H Park  Future Farmers of America Park  Grant County Park  Grassy Lake State Public Fishery Area  Hiawatha Park  Hickey Creek State... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:01:13">http://www.edupic.net/soc_pics.htm</link><title>EduPic Social Studies Images Main</title><description>* EduPic Social Studies Images Main (clueweb12-1214wb-15-23768) http://www.edupic.net/soc_pics.htm ...cherry tree, tidal basin, washington d.c rio grande, river, international border, texas, mexico, recreation, natural resources, santa elana canyon, big bend national park rio grande, river, international border, texas, mexico...garden, gardening, food, plants, herbs, natural resources henricus settlement, colonial garden, gardening, food, plants, herbs, natural resources henricus settlement, wheelbarrow, gardening, food, tools, natural resources   henricus settlement, grinding wheel, tool sharpening, natural resources henricus settlement, woodworking vise, wood construction, carpentry, natural resources   Click on image for larger picture Mississippian Indian Mounds Top of page mississippian indian platform mounds, native american culture, moundville archaeological park, alabama mississippian indian platform mounds, native american culture, moundville archaeological park, alabama mississippian indian platform... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:02:00">http://www.npca.org/news/reports/</link><title>NPCA Reports | National Parks Conservation Association</title><description>* NPCA Reports | National Parks Conservation Association (clueweb12-0204wb-49-30598) http://www.npca.org/news/reports/ NPCA Reports | National Parks Conservation Association ...People and Americaâs Treasured Places January 2012 Cleaning up the Haze: Protecting People and Americaâs Treasured Places asks EPA to drop its proposed BART rule exemption so that our countryâs most iconic natural places are fully protected from unsightly and unhealthy air. Opportunity Knocks January 2012 In December 2011, the National Parks Conservation Association, Houston Wilderness and Rice Universityâs SSPEED Center commissioned Harbinger Consulting Group to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:04:47">http://www.texasoutside.com/public/reviews/state_park_full_list</link><title>Texas State Park Reviews &amp; Reservations</title><description>* Texas State Park Reviews &amp; Reservations (clueweb12-0702wb-03-14601) http://www.texasoutside.com/txorails/public/reviews/state_park_full_list Texas State Park Reviews &amp; Reservations ...-5718 Reserve America Map Eustace Purtis Creek State Park 8.5 903 425-2332 Reserve America Map Fairfield Fairfield Lake State Park 6.0 903 389-4514 Reserve America Map Fort Davis Davis Mountains State Park 8.7 432 426-3337 Reserve America Map Fort Meyers Beach, FL Indian Creek RV Resort 239 466-6060 Sun RV Resorts Map Fredericksburg Enchanted Rock State Natural Area 325 247-3903 Reserve America Map Galveston Galveston Island State Park 7.2 409... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:05:21">http://volunteerwithyouth.com/?cat=3&amp;eventDate=2012-07&amp;eventDisplay=month</link><title>Volunteer With Kids » Events</title><description>* Volunteer With Kids » Events (clueweb12-1507wb-00-23040) http://volunteerwithyouth.com/?cat=3&amp;eventDate=2012-07&amp;eventDisplay=month ...Event Authority â San Francisco, CAResource Conservation Coordinator (full time) – Multnomah County Office of SustainabilityNatural Areas Technician 3 (Temp, Full time) – WA Dept of Natural Resources â Tumwater, WAResearch &amp; development summer internships â Dow AgroSciences â multiple locationsUdall Foundationâs Native American Congressional Internship Program â Washington DCCorvallis Parks and Recreation Summer StaffSummer Job Ideas Boys &amp; Girls Club of Corvallis: KinderClub Assistant Boys... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:08:35">http://www.kavasoft.com/Shoebox/categories/examples/Things/National_Parks.html</link><title>Categories</title><description>* Categories (clueweb12-1300wb-28-23046) http://www.kavasoft.com/Shoebox/categories/examples/Things/National_Parks.html Categories Categories Dates People Places Asia Pacific Pacific American Samoa Pago Pago National Park of American Samoa Guam Asan War In The Pacific Northern Mariana Islands Saipan American Memorial Park North America Caribbean Puerto Rico San Juan San Juan Site U.S. Virgin Islands...of American Samoa Guam Asan War In The Pacific Northern Mariana Islands Saipan American Memorial Park North America Caribbean Puerto Rico San Juan San Juan Site U.S. Virgin Islands Christiansted Buck... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-07"><link>http://https://anpr.org/naturally.htm</link><title>ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking</title><description>* ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking (clueweb12-1910wb-39-03762) http://https://anpr.org/naturally.htm ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking Naturally Speaking By Mike Whatley Information Services Branch Manager Natural...natural resources. For example, Penn State is developing a course on "geology in the National Parks." In summary, various natural resource information messengers exist, including a good number not mentioned above, each with a particular... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-08"><link>http://anpr.org/naturally.htm</link><title>ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking</title><description>* ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking (clueweb12-1909wb-98-13860) http://anpr.org/naturally.htm ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking Naturally Speaking By Mike Whatley Information Services Branch Manager Natural...natural resources. For example, Penn State is developing a course on "geology in the National Parks." In summary, various natural resource information messengers exist, including a good number not mentioned above, each with a particular... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-09"><link>http://https://www.anpr.org/naturally.htm</link><title>ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking</title><description>* ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking (clueweb12-0409wb-90-26570) http://https://www.anpr.org/naturally.htm ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking Naturally Speaking By Mike Whatley Information Services Branch Manager Natural...natural resources. For example, Penn State is developing a course on "geology in the National Parks." In summary, various natural resource information messengers exist, including a good number not mentioned above, each with a particular... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7045-10"><link>http://www.anpr.org/naturally.htm</link><title>ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking</title><description>* ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking (clueweb12-0102wb-15-03865) http://www.anpr.org/naturally.htm ANPR - Association of National Park Rangers - Workshop Session, Naturally Speaking Naturally Speaking By Mike Whatley Information Services Branch Manager Natural...natural resources. For example, Penn State is developing a course on "geology in the National Parks." In summary, various natural resource information messengers exist, including a good number not mentioned above, each with a particular... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>