<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:46:16" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:46:38">https://angel.co/sam-yagan/followers</link><title>Sam Yagan - AngelList</title><description>* Sam Yagan - AngelList (clueweb12-1314wb-59-07945) http://angel.co/sam-yagan/followers ...Yagan - AngelList Chicago · Notable Founder · Angel · Advisor  Website Follow Please sign up or login first Overview Startups Recruiting Activity Followers Harper Reed CTO at Obama for America, former CTO of Threadless and Advisor at Sandbox Industries. Chicago · Scout 1499 followers · 237 following Gokul Rajaram Product Director, Ads at Facebook Silicon Valley · Angel... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-02"><link>http://www.builtinchicago.org/profiles/blogs/does-silicon-valley-s-startup-density-really-give-them-a-leg-up</link><title>Does Silicon Valley's Startup Density Really Give Them A Leg Up on Chicago-Based Startups? - Built in Chicago</title><description>* Does Silicon Valley's Startup Density Really Give Them A Leg Up on Chicago-Based Startups? - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-0000tw-14-18175) http://www.builtinchicago.org/profiles/blogs/does-silicon-valley-s-startup-density-really-give-them-a-leg-up Does Silicon Valley's Startup Density Really Give Them A Leg Up on Chicago-Based Startups? - Built in Chicago Startup LaunchesTechnology ExitsThe Startup EcosystemTop Digital EmployersVenture CapitalBLOGSAll Blog PostsTop Posts This WeekWeekly... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:54:06">http://www.builtinchicago.org/member/johnstanfield</link><title>John Stanfield's Page - Built in Chicago</title><description>* John Stanfield's Page - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-1006wb-16-20182) http://www.builtinchicago.org/profile/JohnStanfield John Stanfield's Page - Built in Chicago Startup LaunchesTechnology ExitsThe Startup EcosystemTop Digital EmployersVenture CapitalBLOGSAll Blog PostsFeatured PostsTop Posts This... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:56:39">http://www.builtinchicago.org/member/georgedeeb</link><title>George Deeb's Page - Built in Chicago</title><description>* George Deeb's Page - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-1006wb-76-22209) http://www.builtinchicago.org/profile/GeorgeDeeb George Deeb's Page - Built in Chicago ...PostsTop Posts This MonthWeekly UpdatesCOMMUNITYGroupsAsk A QuestionVideosPhotosForumsChicago Startup PrideEVENTSSUBSCRIBEJOBSInternshipsJobsABOUT USFoundersSponsorsCommunity PartnersPress ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:00:02">http://www.builtinchicago.org/community/questions</link><title>Networking and Information Resources - Built in Chicago</title><description>* Networking and Information Resources - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-1006wb-54-16652) http://www.builtinchicago.org/forum/topics/networking-and-information ...http://techcocktail.com TiE Midwest â Networking group for entrepreneurs, http://midwest.tie.org Chicago Lean Startup Circle: http://www.chicagoleanstartup.com/ Midwest Entrepreneurs' Forum-Â http://www.midwestentrepreneursforum.org/ MIT Enterprise forum of Chicago -Â http://www.mitefchicago.org/ PDMA chicago -Â http://www.pdma.org/chapter_home.cfm?pk_chapter=9 TechAmerica -Â http://www.itaa.org/ Â  Government Mayor's Council of Technology Advisors: http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/doit/supp_info/mayor_s_c... World Business... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:00:43">http://fi.co/contents/fast</link><title>The Founder Institute: Helping Founders to Build Great Companies</title><description>* The Founder Institute: Helping Founders to Build Great Companies (clueweb12-1415wb-20-05729) http://fi.co/contents/fast ...Bootcamp (April 17, 5:30 - 9PM) FI Chile Launch Party (April 17, 7PM - 10PM) DC Startup Ideation Bootcamp (April 18, 6 - 9 PM) 10th Founder Showcase in SF (April 24, 1 - 8 PM) Chicago Startup Ideation Bootcamp 2 (May 1, 6 - 9 PM) See all of our upcoming events here.  Advisor Standard Template   The Founder Institute encourages collaboration between entrepreneurs and other domain experts to build... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:03:26">http://www.builtinchicago.org/community/questions?page=1&amp;commentId=6280720%253AComment%253A182533&amp;x=1</link><title>Networking and Information Resources - Built in Chicago</title><description>* Networking and Information Resources - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-1006wb-19-31351) http://www.builtinchicago.org/forum/topics/networking-and-information?page=1&amp;commentId=6280720%3AComment%3A182533&amp;x=1 ...http://techcocktail.com TiE Midwest â Networking group for entrepreneurs, http://midwest.tie.org Chicago Lean Startup Circle: http://www.chicagoleanstartup.com/ Midwest Entrepreneurs' Forum-Â http://www.midwestentrepreneursforum.org/ MIT Enterprise forum of Chicago -Â http://www.mitefchicago.org/ PDMA chicago -Â http://www.pdma.org/chapter_home.cfm?pk_chapter=9 TechAmerica -Â http://www.itaa.org/ Â  Government Mayor's Council of Technology Advisors: http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/doit/supp_info/mayor_s_c... World Business... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:07:29">http://www.builtinchicago.org/member/jasongonzales</link><title>Jason Gonzales's Page - Built in Chicago</title><description>* Jason Gonzales's Page - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-1003wb-44-08672) http://www.builtinchicago.org/profile/JasonGonzales Jason Gonzales's Page - Built in Chicago ...to connect social entrepreneurs and everybody else interested in learning about social ventures here in Chicago.See More Jason Gonzales joined Daniel Goldstein's group Dec 1, 2011 3 Comments Jason Gonzales promoted Daniel Goldstein's discussion 'Social Businesses in Chicago' Dec 1, 2011 Jason Gonzales is now friends with Elliott Garms, Maria Katris and Daniel Goldstein Dec 1, 2011 Advisors \- Small Business, Startups, &amp; EntrepreneursFor people who are passionate about entrepreneurship, and want to aid and advise startups... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:11:20">http://ivca.mighty-site.com/pages/article/94.php?article_id=3271</link><title>Illinois Venture Capital Association</title><description>* Illinois Venture Capital Association (clueweb12-1210wb-81-07220) http://ivca.mighty-site.com/pages/article/94.php?article_id=3271 ...O'Keefe &amp; CompanyBlueCross BlueShield Venture PartnersCapX PartnersCeres Venture Fund, L.P.Certare Ventures, LLPChicago Growth PartnersChicago Public School Teachers' Pension &amp; RetirementChrysalis VenturesCHS Capital LLCConversus Asset...was the catalyst for building this new venue? Steve Collens: Even before companies like Groupon, Chicago's digital startup ecosystem had taken shape and had begun to accelerate in the last three years. However, despite the level of activity  and relative to other cities with even a lot less activity  Chicago had very little cooperative working space. A number of people deeply involved in Chicagos tech community saw this need and came together to address it  including Matt Moog... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:14:09">http://www.builtinchicago.org/blog/6-insider-reasons-to-apply-to-excelerate-labs-today</link><title>6 Insider Reasons to Apply to Excelerate Labs Today - Built in Chicago</title><description>* 6 Insider Reasons to Apply to Excelerate Labs Today - Built in Chicago (clueweb12-0000tw-14-18170) http://www.builtinchicago.org/profiles/blogs/6-insider-reasons-to-apply-to-excelerate-labs-today 6 Insider Reasons to Apply to Excelerate Labs Today - Built in Chicago Startup LaunchesTechnology ExitsThe Startup EcosystemTop Digital EmployersVenture CapitalBLOGSAll Blog PostsTop Posts This WeekWeekly... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>