<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7072">price gibson howard roberts custom</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:48:57" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:49:31">http://www.weboshawa.com/electric_gibson_guitars.htm</link><title>Electric Gibson Guitars</title><description>* Electric Gibson Guitars (clueweb12-0605wb-65-05919) http://www.weboshawa.com/electric_gibson_guitars.htm ...Red Gibson Custom ES-335 Dot Lefty with Gloss Finish Electric Guitar Cherry Nickel Hardware Gibson Custom ES-359 Semi Hollow Electric Guitar Vintage Sunburst Gibson Custom Mahogany Explorer Electric Guitar White Gibson Custom ES-359 AAA Flame Maple Semi-Hollow Electric Guitar Vintage Sunburst Gibson Custom Custom Shop CS-336 Plain Top Electric Guitar Faded Cherry Gibson Custom Howard Roberts Fusion III Electric Guitar Vintage Sunburst Gibson ES-335 Dot Plain-top Electric Guitar with... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:51:57">http://fisher.utstat.toronto.edu/mikevans/hroberts/guitars/guitars.html</link><title>http://fisher.utstat.toronto.edu/mikevans/hroberts/guitars/guitars.html</title><description>* http://fisher.utstat.toronto.edu/mikevans/hroberts/guitars/guitars.html (clueweb12-1509wb-39-28142) http://fisher.utstat.toronto.edu/mikevans/hroberts/guitars/guitars.html ...wound up on that movie, felt good to be getting it out there again. Think Howard was upstairs watching the whole thing go down and chuckling away. Thanx, Howard!! If you have heard the music then you will probably agree that this is quite an amazing description. Gibson Howard Roberts Custom \- The Real Howard Roberts Guitar This (front, back) is the guitar that Howard Roberts is pictured with on the album cover for the Real Howard Roberts recording. It is... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:55:54">http://www.onlinerock.com/mf_store/brands/g/Gibson_Custom/index.htm</link><title>Gibson Custom at OnlineRock.com</title><description>* Gibson Custom at OnlineRock.com (clueweb12-0605wb-72-28210) http://www.onlinerock.com/mf_store/brands/g/Gibson_Custom/index.htm ...Overall User Rating:Availability: Click to check availability.Our Price: Click "Buy It Now" for price. at Musiciansfriend.com on December 01, 2010 Gibson Custom Refin Hot-Mod 1955 Les Paul Wraptail Electric GuitarList Price: $5821.00Overall User Rating:Availability: In-Stock and Ready To Ship!Our Price: $3999.00Discount: 31% at Musiciansfriend.com on December 01, 2010 Gibson Custom Howard Roberts Fusion III Electric Guitar - UsedList Price: $3890.00Overall User Rating:Availability: Click to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:57:02">http://www.alltheinstruments.com/gibson_electric_guitars.htm</link><title>Gibson Electric Guitars</title><description>* Gibson Electric Guitars (clueweb12-0100wb-08-07186) http://www.alltheinstruments.com/gibson_electric_guitars.htm ...Top Electric Guitar Ebony Gibson Custom Shop CS-336 Plain Top Electric Guitar Faded Cherry Gibson Custom Shop SG Standard VOS Electric Guitar Faded Cherry Gibson Custom Shop SG Special VOS Electric Guitar Classic White Gibson Custom Shop CS-336 Plain Top Electric Guitar Tangerine Burst Gibson Custom Shop SG Special VOS Electric Guitar Faded Cherry Gibson Custom Shop Howard Roberts Fusion III Electric Guitar Cherry Gibson SG Supreme Electric Guitar with '57 Humbuckers Emerald Burst... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:20">http://www.retrevo.com/samples/Gibson-Guitar.html</link><title>Gibson Guitar Reviews, Ratings, Deals and Comparisons: Retrevo</title><description>* Gibson Guitar Reviews, Ratings, Deals and Comparisons: Retrevo (clueweb12-0301wb-46-16644) http://www.retrevo.com/samples/Gibson-Guitar.html ...sure as heck couldn't find any faults..." see less » Read Full Review » See All Prices pids.push('R877607'); J45 Standard...Gibson 50th Anniversary SG Standard 24Gibson CS-336 Figured TopGibson EDS-1275 Double NeckGibson ES-175Gibson ES-335 Dot Figured GlossGibson ExplorerGibson Flying V FadedGibson Howard Roberts Fusion IIIGibson Joan Jett BlackheartGibson Keb Mo BluesmasterGibson L-200 Emmylou HarrisGibson Les Paul Custom Les Paul Deluxe... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-06"><link>http://customguitarpicks.ackso.com</link><title>Custom Guitar Picks</title><description>* Custom Guitar Picks (clueweb12-1201tw-24-15167) http://customguitarpicks.ackso.com ...business days and FREE with Super Saver Shipping (For Order More 25usd). Hurry Up !! This price promotion is time limited. Order the best price from this page. read more Read the rest of this entry » Custom Guitar Picks Best Wish, EGG5AIGH1, Epiphone G-400, Epiphone Reviews, Musical Instruments Guide Gibson 1957 Les Paul Custom 3 Pickup Electric Guitar with Case (Black) Reviews March 31st, 2012 ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:07:04">http://www.guitar-4u.com/gibson-guitars7.php</link><title>Gibson guitars - Full list of Gibson guitars for sale</title><description>* Gibson guitars - Full list of Gibson guitars for sale (clueweb12-0109wb-16-04141) http://www.guitar-4u.com/gibson-guitars7.php ...Us gibson guitars. Here you can shop for gibson guitars, accessories and all kinds of musical instruments. This is their full catalog of gibson guitars: Gibson Custom ES-335 Satin Finish Electric Guitar Faded CherryMaple top, back, and rims are joined... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:10:38">http://guitarvillage.uk.com/productlist.aspx?c=136&amp;category=Archtop%2fSemi+Gibson</link><title>Guitar Village UK | Gibson Archtop/Semi Guitars</title><description>* Guitar Village UK | Gibson Archtop/Semi Guitars (clueweb12-1206wb-41-15206) http://www.guitarvillage.co.uk/productlist.aspx?c=136&amp;category=Archtop%2fSemi+Gibson Guitar Village UK | Gibson Archtop/Semi Guitars ...Fingerboard, 57 Classic Humbucker PickupsView details and buyPrice: ÂŁ2449In Stock  Gibson Howard Roberts Fusion III (ARFUCHGH1), New, Cherry, Inc. CaseThe Gibson Howard Roberts Fusion III has a Plain Laminated Maple Top, Back &amp; Rims, Ebony Fingerboard, Gold Hardware, 490R &amp; 490T Humbuckers, Rounded Neck ProfileView details and buyPrice: ÂŁ2099In Stock  Gibson ES-137CU Custom (ES3UHSGH1), New, Heritage Sunburst, Inc. CaseThe Gibson ES-137CU Custom has Laminated Curly... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7072_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:11:40">http://www.archtop.com/ac_sold.html</link><title>archtop.com: Previously Sold Instruments</title><description>* archtop.com: Previously Sold Instruments (clueweb12-1806wb-16-09700) http://www.archtop.com/ac_sold.html ...built Strat style solid body, rock maple neck, rare bird from top builder SOLD 1965 Gibson ES-175 Custom "Charlie Christian" extremely rare example with factory Charlie Christian pickup, phenomenal shape SOLD 1956 Gibson ES-350T, highly flamed, very rare twin P-90 version, Byrdland specs, very clean small town guitar, one of 62 SOLD 1974-5 Gibson Howard Roberts Custom , full size floating humbucker, unique bass and treble tone controls, a modern classic SOLD 1956... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7072-10"><link>http://www.guitarelectrics.net/category.4.electric_guitars.2.php</link><title>Guitars, Amps, Effect: Electric Guitars</title><description>* Guitars, Amps, Effect: Electric Guitars (clueweb12-0201wb-24-26910) http://www.guitarelectrics.net/category.4.electric_guitars.2.php ...Historic 1960 Special Single Cutaway Vintage Original Spec Electric Guitar (with Case) View Item | Check Price   Gibson Custom Historic 1960 Special Double Cutaway Vintage Original Spec Electric Guitar (with Case) View Item | Check Price   Gibson Custom Historic 1957 Junior Single Cutaway Vintage Original Spec Electric Guitar (with Case) View Item | Check Price   Gibson Howard Roberts Fusion III Electric Guitar (with Case) View Item | Check Price   ESP Kamikaze George Lynch Electric Guitar (with Case) View Item | Check Price   Ibanez JEM7V Steve... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>