<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:37:36" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:38:06">http://www.loveleaf.net/book/Tolkien.html</link><title>The Silmarillion, The Hobbit, The Lord of the Rings by J.R.R. Tolkien</title><description>* The Silmarillion, The Hobbit, The Lord of the Rings by J.R.R. Tolkien (clueweb12-1802wb-57-21213) http://www.loveleaf.net/book/Tolkien.html The Silmarillion, The Hobbit, The Lord of the Rings by J.R.R. Tolkien Rings. The Silmarillion, The Hobbit, The Lord of the Rings. without frames. baggins bilbo baggins bilbo the hobbit book tolkein book tolkien books tolkein books tolkien ebook tolkien fellowship of the ring fellowship... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:39:45">http://wholesale57.eu.interiowo.pl/colorado6c/lord-of-the-rings-saruman-theme.html</link><title>Lord Of The Rings Saruman Theme. It Has A Matching Theme.</title><description>* Lord Of The Rings Saruman Theme. It Has A Matching Theme. (clueweb12-0008wb-73-32865) http://wholesale57.eu.interia.pl/colorado6c/lord-of-the-rings-saruman-theme.html ...Nonsolotemplate rings saruman theme Lord of the rings saruman mini bust he s the master of isengard! saruman was the...way to see wizard saruman good as the first and that it lacked a unifying theme. Lord of the rings a three-volume fantasy masterpiece, written by j the conflict was not over, antique engatement rings however, memphis wet style pulled pork recipes for saruman had from being a sequel to the hobbit, to being, in theme. Lord of the rings (tarot deck) introduction not merely is this a the theme of each card is instantaneously... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:40:57">http://style86.eu.interiowo.pl/simply-i65/enya-lord-of-the-rings-theme.html</link><title>Enya Lord Of The Rings Theme. Enya -.</title><description>* Enya Lord Of The Rings Theme. Enya -. (clueweb12-0008wb-61-22915) http://style86.eu.interia.pl/simply-i65/enya-lord-of-the-rings-theme.html Enya Lord Of The Rings Theme. Enya -. ...Enya Lord Of The Rings Theme. Enya -. Rings78 Partial Hair Perm Styles 113What Is Gold PanningProdigal Son RingCustomized Family...to do a christmas album didn t feel it was right to impose a christmas theme on and an oscar nomination for "may it be" from lord of the rings\- the. Cover design for the three volumes of the lord of the rings by from being a sequel to the hobbit, to being, td gold travel visa in theme also contain references to tolkien s creations enya. Lord of the rings the two towers... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:44:16">http://www.cliffsnotes.com/</link><title>Tools &amp; Resources: J.R.R. Tolkien Glossary</title><description>* Tools &amp; Resources: J.R.R. Tolkien Glossary (clueweb12-0107wb-60-11659) http://www.cliffsnotes.com/Section/J-R-R-Tolkien-Glossary.id-305499,articleId-129463.html ...or famous Vote  View Results Lord of the Rings) bane a curse, the cause of destruction. (The Lord of the Rings) Lord of the Rings) baying barking. (The Hobbit) the Black Land Mordor. (The Lord of the Rings) the Blessed Realm the land to which all the elves may sail, leaving Middle-earth... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:48:17">http://www.hyper-ad.com/store/lordoftherings.html</link><title>Lord of the Rings DVDs, Videos, Audio CD, Audio Cassettes and Books</title><description>* Lord of the Rings DVDs, Videos, Audio CD, Audio Cassettes and Books (clueweb12-0202wb-16-29899) http://www.hyper-ad.com/store/lordoftherings.html Lord of the Rings DVDs, Videos, Audio CD, Audio Cassettes and Books ˇ J. R. R. Tolkien...Lord of the Rings DVDs, Videos, Audio CD, Audio Cassettes and Books ˇ J. R. R. Tolkien ˇ  Hyper-Ad Popular Books and Film Recommendations ˇ Lord of the Rings ˇ DVDs ˇ Videos ˇ Books ˇ Audio CDs ˇ Audio Cassettes      Excellent classic fantasy novel series, appropriate for all ages.  Some parents are a bit dismayed at the themes of magic and sorcery; however, since similar objections can be raised about The Wizard of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:25">http://www.fizzybrain.co.uk/the-lord-of-the-rings/c-506.html</link><title>The Lord of the Rings, links and informations about The Lord of the Rings</title><description>* The Lord of the Rings, links and informations about The Lord of the Rings (clueweb12-0200wb-11-09653) http://www.fizzybrain.co.uk/the-lord-of-the-rings/c-506.html The Lord of the Rings, links and informations about The Lord of the Rings ...The Lord of the Rings, links and informations about The Lord of the Rings ...Bay Close terms People having consulted this article carried out following search on Internet : The Hobbit trailers, LOTR Goods, The Lord of the Rings Boxset, The Lord of the Rings torrent links, The Lord of the Rings theatre, The Lord of the Rings Movies, The Lord of the Rings Games, The Lord of the Rings Books. Other set of themes InternetBooks &amp; ComicsEvents Copyright 2008 - FizzyBrain - Free The Lord of the Rings directory and... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:52:07">http://www.artistsuk.co.uk/tolkienposters.html</link><title>Tolkien Posters</title><description>* Tolkien Posters (clueweb12-0103wb-37-31253) http://www.artistsuk.co.uk/tolkienposters.html Tolkien Posters Tolkien posters Artists UK - The World's Greatest Fantasy Poster and Print Store. Lord of the Rings Posters and much more! The Hobbit \- Smaug Buy The Hobbit \- Smaug The Hobbit \- The Hobbit Buy The Hobbit \- The Hobbit The Hobbit = Treebeard Buy The Hobbit Treebeard The Hobbit \- The Carrock Buy The Hobbit \- The Carrock The Hobbit \- The Wargs Buy The Hobbit \- The Wargs The Hobbit - The Trolls Buy The Hobbit - The Trolls The Hobbit - Bilbo Buy... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-08"><link>http://www.ventechaud.fr/tags/rings/i.html</link><title>Rings</title><description>* Rings (clueweb12-0400tw-07-24560) http://www.ventechaud.fr/tags/rings/i.html ...Ring, The Two Towers, and The Return of the King), and its charming precursor, The Hobbit. The Lord of the Rings A Christian can almost be forgiven for not reading the Bible, but there's no...t read the gospel of the genre, J.R.R. Tolkien's definitive three-book epic, the Lord of the Rings (encompassing The Fellowship of the Ring, The Two Towers, and The Return of the King), and its charming precursor, The Hobbit. Movie &amp; TV Chill Out Theme From Twilight (Bella's Lullaby), Theme From The X-Files, Theme From Sex And The City, Last Tango In Paris, Lord Of The Rings:The Fellowship... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-09"><link>http://www.tolkiencollector.com/indexes/tolkiennew.htm</link><title>Tolkien Collector - The Collectible Hobbit</title><description>* Tolkien Collector - The Collectible Hobbit (clueweb12-0302wb-78-28531) http://www.tolkiencollector.com/indexes/tolkiennew.htm Tolkien Collector - The Collectible Hobbit Lord of the Rings Barbara Remington Panoramic Wilderness Poster Portfolio by Frank Cirocco John Howe Barad-dur Giclee Print...Print and Sketches by Steven Hickman A Listing of Music Inspired by Tolkiens Works The Lord of the Rings \- Composed by Johan de Meji - Conducted by Rene Joly, Ensemble Vents et Percussion Quebec The BBC Dramatization of The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings Hobbit Music Song of the Rings CD Journey of the Ring Symphony... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7080-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7080_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:59:18">http://zhena.awardspace.com/usc-trojf1/lord-of-the-rings-songs-hobbits.html</link><title>Lord Of The Rings Songs Hobbits - Wholesale Sterling Jewelry India, Kama Sutra Lovers Ring</title><description>* Lord Of The Rings Songs Hobbits - Wholesale Sterling Jewelry India, Kama Sutra Lovers Ring (clueweb12-1117wb-17-18874) http://zhena.awardspace.com/usc-trojf1/lord-of-the-rings-songs-hobbits.html Lord Of The Rings Songs Hobbits \- Wholesale Sterling Jewelry India, Kama Sutra Lovers Ring Lord Of The Rings Songs Hobbits usc trojan ring :: summer fashion looks for teens :: palladium and wedding ring :: lord of the rings songs hobbits :: Welcome, Guest! Create an account Login Shopping cart: 0 ($ 0.00) Home / usc trojan ring... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>