<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:14:49" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:15:09">http://www.evanclosson.com/projects/collisiondetectionandresponse</link><title>Efficient and Accurate Collision Detection Hierarchies with Collision Response</title><description>* Efficient and Accurate Collision Detection Hierarchies with Collision Response (clueweb12-1904wb-38-25006) http://www.evanclosson.com/projects/collisiondetectionandresponse ...bounding volume hierarchies and collision response. Many efficient bounding volume hierarchies have been created with spheres [HUBBARD96], AABBs [VAN DEN BERGEN97], k-dops also known as discrete orientation polytopes [KLOSOWSKI98], and...tight fitting bounding volumes which require less intersection tests, or looser fitting bounding volumes like spheres that require more bounding volumes to approximate a surface but require very inexpensive intersection tests... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:17:43">http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph12p.html</link><title>http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph12p.html</title><description>* http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph12p.html (clueweb12-1203wb-09-24070) http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph12p.html ...turntable initially rotating at 33 1/3 rev/min makes 25 revolutions before it stops. Calculate the angular deceleration of this turntable; assume it is constant. *12. The rotation of the...E is the mass and RE the equatorial radius. Why is this moment of inertia smaller than that of a sphere of uniform density? What would the radius of a sphere of uniform density have to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:19:08">http://www.physics247.com/physics-homework-help/rotational-motion.php</link><title>Physics Homework Help: Rotational Motion</title><description>* Physics Homework Help: Rotational Motion (clueweb12-0300wb-39-23948) http://www.physics247.com/physics-homework-help/rotational-motion.php ...2200 N. The distance between the rear legs and the front legs is 1.52m. Calculate the weight of the cow.   Answer to example 2:   The first condition of equilibrium is...kg are placed near p and q respectively, one on each end of the beam. Calculate the reaction forces at p and q.   6. A 500 N rock rests on an... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:21:35">http://www.engrasp.com/doc/etb/mod/util1/solidprop/solidprop_help.html</link><title>ETBX Solid Properties Module</title><description>* ETBX Solid Properties Module (clueweb12-0110wb-13-06828) http://www.engrasp.com/doc/etb/mod/util1/solidprop/solidprop_help.html ...Propertiescalculates the mass properties of common homogeneous solids.  Calculated mass properties...Properties module calculates the mass properties of common homogeneous solids.  Calculated mass properties include centroid, volume, surface area, and moments of inertia.   Background The Solid Properties Module uses closed-form equations to calculate the mass properties of common solid types.  Choose a solid from the menu below to view the appropriate equations. Thin Rectangular Plate Rectangular Prism Sphere Cylinder Cone Thin Circular Disk Tetrahedron Hemisphere Half Cylinder Half... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:24:59">http://www.batesville.k12.in.us/physics/PhyNet/Mechanics/RotMechanics/fall_slide_roll.htm</link><title>Falling, Sliding &amp; Rolling</title><description>* Falling, Sliding &amp; Rolling (clueweb12-0101wb-49-05938) http://www.batesville.k12.in.us/physics/PhyNet/Mechanics/RotMechanics/fall_slide_roll.htm ...object is more difficult to accelerate. However, objects resist rotational accelerations due to their rotational inertia (also called moment of inertia) - more rotational inertia means the object is more difficult to accelerate. Rotational inertia depends on: the object's mass...This would be difficult in practice.) The objects below are listed with the greatest rotational inertia first: a hoop - has the greatest rotational inertia, since all of its mass is as far as possible from its axis (center). an empty can with no lid. a hollow sphere \- like a basketball, soccer ball, or volleyball. a can of "sloshy" soup (chicken noodle) will... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:27:46">http://madsci.org/posts/archives/2000-11/975163371.Ph.r.html</link><title>Re: Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere</title><description>* Re: Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere (clueweb12-0310wb-54-15810) http://madsci.org/posts/archives/2000-11/975163371.Ph.r.html Re: Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere MadSci Network: Physics Query: Re: Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere Date: Fri Nov 24 16:48:03...R^2 is indeed the formula for inertia for a hollow sphere, but it is for a sphere with an extremely thin shell. This seems... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:30:56">http://madsci.org/posts/archives/2000-11/975163371.Ph.q.html</link><title>Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere</title><description>* Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere (clueweb12-0310wb-46-30400) http://madsci.org/posts/archives/2000-11/975163371.Ph.q.html Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere MadSci Network: Physics Query: Subject: Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere Date: Fri Nov 10 12:17:04...R1 to R2: the center of the sphere is hollow. Using thin sphere Inertia formula I=2/3MR^2: My dilema...2) any help would be appreciated. Calculate Inertia of a partially hollow sphere Current Queue | Current Queue for Physics | Physics... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:31:54">http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph13p.html</link><title>http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph13p.html</title><description>* http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph13p.html (clueweb12-1202wb-89-29697) http://curricula2.mit.edu/pivot/book/ph13p.html ...is at the midpoint of the rectangle formed by the wheels, and the moment of inertia about a vertical axis through the center of mass is 2200 kg • m2. Suppose...road is µs = 0.90 and the coefficient of kinetic friction is µk = 0.50. Calculate the instantaneous angular acceleration of the automobile about the vertical axis. *16. A large flywheel designed for energy storage at a power plant has a moment of inertia of 5 X 105 kg • m2 and spins at 3000 rev/min. Suppose... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:34:30">http://newtondynamics.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=48312</link><title>Newton Game Dynamics • View topic - My objects don't collide each other?</title><description>* Newton Game Dynamics • View topic - My objects don't collide each other? (clueweb12-1903wb-69-11108) http://newtondynamics.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=48312 ...Also, you give the static floor a mass of 100 and calculates inertia for it which is not necessary if it's supposed to be static. Just set the mass to 0 and skip the inertia stuff in that case.If it has a non-zero mass...Also, you give the static floor a mass of 100 and calculates inertia for it which is not necessary if it's supposed to be static. Just set the mass to 0 and skip the inertia stuff in that case.If it has a non-zero mass... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7094-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7094_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:36:42">http://newtondynamics.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=48326</link><title>Newton Game Dynamics • View topic - My objects don't collide each other?</title><description>* Newton Game Dynamics • View topic - My objects don't collide each other? (clueweb12-1903wb-72-03776) http://newtondynamics.com/forum/viewtopic.php?p=48326 ...Also, you give the static floor a mass of 100 and calculates inertia for it which is not necessary if it's supposed to be static. Just set the mass to 0 and skip the inertia stuff in that case.If it has a non-zero mass...Also, you give the static floor a mass of 100 and calculates inertia for it which is not necessary if it's supposed to be static. Just set the mass to 0 and skip the inertia stuff in that case.If it has a non-zero mass... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>