<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7096">touchpad scroll dell latitude</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:00:43" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:01:06">http://drivers-download-driver.com/driver-dell-latitude-e6320-notebook-touchpad-driver-a09/</link><title>Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download</title><description>* Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download (clueweb12-0308wb-86-08836) http://drivers-download-driver.com/driver-dell-latitude-e6320-notebook-touchpad-driver-a09/ Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download drivers Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 download Drivers Download...Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 drivers download drivers Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad Driver A09 download Drivers Download Download Dell Latitude E6320 Notebook Touchpad... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:01:38">http://dell.driversdown.com/dell-drivers-list/s_540_1.shtml</link><title>Dell notebook Latitude 131L driver free download - DELL Drivers Downloads</title><description>* Dell notebook Latitude 131L driver free download - DELL Drivers Downloads (clueweb12-0005wb-88-03313) http://dell.driversdown.com/dell-drivers-list/s_540_1.shtml ...CDRW/DVD, Firmware, Mu.. vTSST TS-L632D slim 8x DVD+/-RW, Firmware, Win.. vDell _Wireless (US) WLAN Card, Wireless 1350 .. vAMD Processor Driver, Driver, Windows XP, Win.. vPhilips SDVD-8820 Slim 8X DVD+/-RW, Firmware,.. vDell Latitude 131L System BIOS, English, Lati.. vSynaptics Touchpad, Driver, Windows 2000, Win.. vDell QuickSet, Application, Windows 2000, Win.. vDell Wireless 5510 Vodafone Mobile Broadband .. vDell Wireless 5700 Mobile Broadband (CDMA EV-.. vDell... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:03:48">http://dell.driversdown.com/dell-drivers-list/s_479_1.shtml</link><title>Dell notebook Inspiron 1501 driver free download - DELL Drivers Downloads</title><description>* Dell notebook Inspiron 1501 driver free download - DELL Drivers Downloads (clueweb12-0001wb-37-19503) http://dell.driversdown.com/dell-drivers-list/s_479_1.shtml ...Touchpad, Driver, Windows 2000, Windows XP, Multi Language, Multi System, v.8.2.4.6, A17 Synaptics Touchpad Driver 2007-08-27 139 5 MB Dell Premium Optical Mouse, Logitech Dell Premium Optical Mouse(Nala), Patch/Upgrade, Multi OS, Multi Language, Multi System, A00 Optical Premium Software Patch for Solving MS Office 2007 Scrolling Issue 2007-08-27 18 1024 KB Dell Premium Optical Mouse, Logitech Dell Premium Optical Mouse(Nala), Application, Windows XP, Windows XP x64, Multi Language, Inspiron 1501, Latitude... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:07:04">http://www.itcsales.co.uk/acatalog/UK_Keyboards_and_Mice.html</link><title>Dell Logitech UK EU Keyboards Mice and Touchpads</title><description>* Dell Logitech UK EU Keyboards Mice and Touchpads (clueweb12-0511wb-66-05321) http://www.itcsales.co.uk/acatalog/UK_Keyboards_and_Mice.html Dell Logitech UK EU Keyboards Mice and Touchpads ...European &amp; US EU KeyboardsPC &amp; Workstation European US EU KeyboardsLaptop European US EU KeyboardsLatitude &amp; Precision Laptop European US EU KeyboardsVostro &amp; Studio Laptop European US EU KeyboardsInspiron &amp; XPS Laptop European US EU KeyboardsDell Laptop PartsDell Laptop CD DVD CDRW DVDRW &amp; Floppy DrivesDell Laptop Palmrest &amp; TouchpadsDell Laptop Bases - PlasticsDell Laptop IO PCB PartsDell Laptop LidsDell Laptop Webcam PartsDell Laptop Speaker Audio PartsIntel Laptop Mobile CPU's OEM Parts... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-05"><link>http://www.octofinder.com/@/d73326c89ec34750ecf77b73901af02c</link><title>** VoodooPS2Controller two finger scrolling support for ALPS touchpad [ InsanelyMac News ]</title><description>* ** VoodooPS2Controller two finger scrolling support for ALPS touchpad [ InsanelyMac News ] (clueweb12-1602wb-12-17740) http://www.octofinder.com/@/d73326c89ec34750ecf77b73901af02c ...ps2 keyboard and touchpad drivers for lionelan multitouch kextappleps2trackpad synaptics touchpad v26vmware touchpad scrollingelantech maclion dell d630asus elantech kext lionelantech kext lionappleps2alps clicking lion...vertical oppositedell d620 mac touchpad kextdell xps m1530 alps multitouch driverpatched appleps2trackpaddell xps 1530 voodoops2controller osx lionelan ps2 smart pad for lionps2 keyboard 64 bits kextelantech on macchange mouse driver osx from voodoo to apple ps2insanelymac elanvoodops2 appleps2synaptic touchpad not foundalps touchpad dell latitude e5420 two finger scrolliatkos touchpad elaniatkos l1 mouse keyboardappleps2trackpad elanappleps2trackpad voodoops2 elaninsanelymac kext apple ps2 alps... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:13:51">http://www.itcsales.co.uk/acatalog/Dell_Laptop_palmrest_touchpad_parts.html</link><title>Dell Laptop palmrest and touchpad parts.</title><description>* Dell Laptop palmrest and touchpad parts. (clueweb12-0507wb-99-16705) http://www.itcsales.co.uk/acatalog/Dell_Laptop_palmrest_touchpad_parts.html Dell Laptop palmrest and touchpad parts. ...Printers &amp; Scanners Servers &amp; Racks Software Operating System Any Windows 7 Windows Vista Windows XP freedos Dell Laptop Palmrest &amp; Touchpads toggle view   ITC Group IT Store | Dell Parts | Dell Laptop Parts |  Dell Laptop Palmrest &amp; TouchpadsProduct Ref: Stock  Price (ex)       Main  Specifications  Reviews    Images For Illustration Purposes Only Dell Latitude E4300 Palm Rest and Mouse Touch Pad Assembly N471D K457C K456C 9XK2WItem Ref:6454... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:17:10">http://www.ezsystems.com/skupages/Dell_034.htm</link><title>Dell &gt; Hot Deal. New or Refurbished &gt; EZSystems.com 6J420 to 743NE</title><description>* Dell &gt; Hot Deal. New or Refurbished &gt; EZSystems.com 6J420 to 743NE (clueweb12-1313wb-71-12096) http://www.ezsystems.com/skupages/dell_034.htm ...Card GeForce2 Go NV11 6J811Dell Refurbished CD-RW 24X 10X 40X BK 680M 6J852Dell Refurbished E 6J852 120x38mm Fan for PE1500SC 6J907Dell Refurbished VERSA RAILKIT POWERVAULT 220S 6J973Dell Refurbished 3DLABS WCildcat II 5110 128MB Graphics Card 6J973 6J987Dell Refurbished 20GB Hard Drive 2.5-Inch IDE 6K042Dell Refurbished SI119810MODR5SPLITBPP2550 6K060Dell Refurbished 6K060 Latitude X200 Palmrest Touchpad Plastic Assembly 6K098Dell Refurbished Hard Drive 20GB I F3 1-inch WD-XL30 6K117... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:19:22">http://drivers-download-driver.com/lastest-drivers-software-127.html</link><title>Lastest Drivers Download</title><description>* Lastest Drivers Download (clueweb12-0308wb-38-21500) http://drivers-download-driver.com/lastest-drivers-software-127.html ...A00 Asrock G31M GS Gigabit lan driver 6208 Asrock G31M GS Gigabit lan driver 5702 Dell Latitude X1 Broadcom 57XX Gigabit Integrated Controller Driver A01 Dell Latitude X1 Broadcom 57XX Gigabit Integrated Controller Diagnostics Utility A01 Dell Latitude X1 Broadcom 57XX Gigabit Integrated Controller Application A03 Dell Latitude X1 Synaptics Touchpad Driver A17 Dell Latitude X1 Synaptics Touchpad Driver A16 Dell Latitude X1 Synaptics Touchpad Driver A14 Dell Latitude X1 Bluetooth Wireless Keyboard and Mouse Bundle Application A02 Dell Latitude... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:22:27">http://www.pinnaclemicro.com/skupages/Dell_046.htm</link><title>[ Dell ] Big Savings. Refurbished and New @ Pinnaclemicro.com EBS18012015 to FC554</title><description>* [ Dell ] Big Savings. Refurbished and New @ Pinnaclemicro.com EBS18012015 to FC554 (clueweb12-0610wb-18-02745) http://www.pinnaclemicro.com/skupages/dell_046.htm Dell ] Big Savings. Refurbished and New @ Pinnaclemicro.com EBS18012015 to FC554 ...EC30T03N016-LEC30T03N016LDell Refurbished EC30T03N016L 3052D Laptop Hinge EC30T03N016-L 9.25-Inch ECDQ003UDell Refurbished Touchpad EEDWOO8C000Dell Refurbished MEMORY COVER INSPIRON 5160 EFB0912HHEDell New PowerEdge DELTA FAN EFB0912HHE 12V...Intrusion Switch NEW F4404 F4421Dell Refurbished P4 3.4Ghz cpu 512k/800 fsb F4452Dell New F4452Dell Refurbished POWER CONNECT CABLE F4456Dell New F4456ENC F4491Dell Refurbished System Board ( Motherboard ) DIMENSION 4600/4600I F4582Dell Refurbished ADAPTEC F4582 2-Port FIREWIRE CARD IEEE 1394 F4632Dell Refurbished Latitude D810 Precision M70 Palmrest Touchpad F4632 F4633Dell Refurbished LATITUDE 810 BOTTOM COVER F4634Dell Refurbished F4634 AMZKS00040L D810 M70 MEMORY DOOR COVER F4649Dell... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7096-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7096_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:24:32">http://marketerpro.net/?f</link><title>Buy Online Computers Laptop Parts Accessories Mice Mouse Motherboards PCMCIA Cards Network Ethernet LAN Cards Screens LCD Panel Security Video Sound Speakers Firewire Modems</title><description>* Buy Online Computers Laptop Parts Accessories Mice Mouse Motherboards PCMCIA Cards Network Ethernet LAN Cards Screens LCD Panel Security Video Sound Speakers Firewire Modems (clueweb12-0005wb-04-37897) http://marketerpro.net/job-opportunity/index164.html ...Laptop Parts &amp; Accessories Computers &amp; Networking has deals on laptops, desktops &amp; accessories from brands like Apple, Dell, IBM, HP, Sony &amp; Toshiba.     Get the Buy Online course Guide here. Learn how to effectively...PII 400 MHz Notebook CPU Processor - SL3BW    WOW Dell Deluxe Leather Notebook Case Laptop Bag    Dell Dimension 4600 2400 Power button   KEYBOARD &amp; BEZEL for the Compaq Armada 7800   Compaq Armada 1700 1750 Keyboard   USB 2.0 Portable Laptop Notebook Hard Drive Case Kit!!!    Intel PII 400 MHz Notebook CPU Processor - SL3BW    Dell Inspiron 5100 Touchpad    Item Title Dell Latitude D505/C800 Touchpad    Dell Latitude C400 Touchpad    Dell Latitude C600 &amp; C610 Rubber Feet    5.25" 39-Pin SCSI Hard Drive... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>