<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:09:50" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:10:18">http://www.communityschools.org/resources/data_collection_instrument_guide.aspx</link><title>Data Collection Tools Guide</title><description>* Data Collection Tools Guide (clueweb12-0108wb-69-28218) http://www.communityschools.org/resources/data_collection_instrument_guide.aspx ...group, questions, citation for each data collection instrument referenced in the Community Schools Evaluation Toolkit. Survey # Result Indicator Respondent Questions Grade Full citation  1 Students succeed academically Teachers support students Student 1-6 3-8 Harter, S. (1985), Social Suppport Scale for Children. University of Denver, University Park, Denver, CO 80208  2 Students are actively involved in learning and their community Students feel competent Student 1-6 3-8 Harter, S. (1985). Self... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-02"><link>http://ericcolburn.com/2012/04/18/autocad-civil-3d-working-with-images-and-surfaces-professional-land-surveyor-learning-center-course/</link><title>AutoCAD Civil 3D Working With Images And Surfaces Professional Land Surveyor Learning Center Course | Eric Colburn, PLS</title><description>* AutoCAD Civil 3D Working With Images And Surfaces Professional Land Surveyor Learning Center Course | Eric Colburn, PLS (clueweb12-1800tw-05-10599) http://ericcolburn.com/2012/04/18/autocad-civil-3d-working-with-images-and-surfaces-professional-land-surveyor-learning-center-course/ AutoCAD Civil 3D Working With Images And Surfaces Professional Land Surveyor Learning Center Course | Eric Colburn, PLS ...Membership Premium Signup Welcome To Our Members Area Membership Specials Download Limit Exceeded BlueBook Foster Survey Company Newsletter Podcast Store Store Transaction Results Verify your Order Your Account Work With Me Advertising Appointments AutoCAD Civil 3D Branding Business Consulting Land Surveying 911 Marketing Product Development Premium Signup Learning Center Course April 18, 2012 in AutoCAD Civil 3D, Business, Continuing Education, Geomatics, Land Surveying... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:13:30">http://www.visionbib.com/bibliography/keyword/s.html</link><title>Keith Price Bibliography keyword Listing for s</title><description>* Keith Price Bibliography keyword Listing for s (clueweb12-0304wb-86-07631) http://www.visionbib.com/bibliography/keyword/s.html ...Recognition Using Volumes, High Level Vision Techniques, Invariants (H) * Knowledge-Based Image Understanding Systems: A Survey Survey, Landmark Recognition * Active Vision, Camera Calibration, Mobile Robots, Navigation, Road Following (H) * Comparative Study of Mobile-Based Landmark Recognition Techniques, A Survey, LBP * Matching and Recognition Using Volumes, High Level Vision Techniques, Invariants (H) * Local Binary Patterns and Its Application to Facial Image Analysis: A Survey Survey, Learning * Learning, General Surveys, Overviews (H2) * Pattern Recognition, Clustering, Statistics, Grammars, Learning, Neural Nets, Genetic Algorithms... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:17:20">http://evaluation.francophonie.org/spip.php?page=rss</link><title>Portail francophone de l’ĂŠvaluation</title><description>* Portail francophone de l’ĂŠvaluation (clueweb12-1415wb-60-29608) http://evaluation.francophonie.org/spip.php?page=rss ...Private funding in humanitarian aid: is this trend here to stay?13-04-2012 - The Active Learning Network for Accountability and Performance in Humanitarian ActionIncorporaciĂłn del enfoque de gĂŠnero en la...Humanitarian ActionIncorporaciĂłn del enfoque de gĂŠnero en la acciĂłn humanitaria13-04-2012 - The Active Learning Network for Accountability and Performance in Humanitarian ActionSupport Services Manager12-04-2012 - The... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:18:31">http://www.scoop.it/t/learning-3-point-zero/p/1183694030/2012/02/12/leadership-involvement-is-vital-to-social-intranet-success-social-media-today</link><title>Leadership Involvement is Vital to Social Intranet Success | Social Media Today | Learning 3 Point Zero | Scoop.it</title><description>* Leadership Involvement is Vital to Social Intranet Success | Social Media Today | Learning 3 Point Zero | Scoop.it (clueweb12-0100tw-09-02041) http://www.scoop.it/t/learning-3-point-zero/p/1183694030/leadership-involvement-is-vital-to-social-intranet-success-social-media-today Leadership Involvement is Vital to Social Intranet Success | Social Media Today | Learning 3 Point Zero | Scoop.it ...27 AM Active Learning shared this post on Facebook page. January 24, 6:27 AM Active Learning shared this post on LinkedIn. January 24, 6:27 AM Active Learning shared this post on Facebook. January 24, 6:27 AM Active Learning shared this post on Twitter. January 24, 6:27 AM communicationsurvey.net (via @josephracina) - January 16, 4:46 PM Straight Talk Communication Survey Discover your Straight Talk communication style with this quick and free communication survey. Active Learning... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:20:41">http://www4.ncsu.edu/unity/lockers/users/f/felder/public/Papers/Education_Papers.html</link><title>Richard Felder's Education-Related Publications</title><description>* Richard Felder's Education-Related Publications (clueweb12-0400wb-42-06834) http://www4.ncsu.edu/unity/lockers/users/f/felder/public/Papers/Education_Papers.html ...of other listed articles, e-mail Dr. Felder at rmfelder@mindspring.com. ABET - Engineering accreditation Active learning Assessment of learning (including testing and grading) Critical and creative thinking Cooperative learning Distance education...e-mail Dr. Felder at rmfelder@mindspring.com. ABET - Engineering accreditation Active learning Assessment of learning (including testing and grading) Critical and creative thinking Cooperative learning Distance education Engineering education Evaluation... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:24:30">http://hunch.net/~active_learning/</link><title>http://hunch.net/~active_learning/</title><description>* http://hunch.net/~active_learning/ (clueweb12-0919wb-83-10440) http://hunch.net/~active_learning/ ...Case, ALT 2006. Manfred K. Warmuth, Gunnar Ratsch, Michael Mathieson, Jun Liao, and Christian Lemmon, Active Learning in the Drug Discovery Process, NIPS 2001. Xiaojin Zhu, John Lafferty and Zoubin Ghahramani, Combining active learning and semi-supervised learning using Gaussian fields and harmonic functions, ICML 2003 workshop Some Surveys These are a couple surveys on the general topic of applied active learning. They don't cover the theory which is the primary topic of this tutorial, but they... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-08"><link>http://ericcolburn.com/2012/01/27/create-survey-point-groups-in-autocad-civil-3d-survey-databases-video/</link><title>Create Survey Point Groups in AutoCAD Civil 3D Survey Databases Video | Eric Colburn, PLS</title><description>* Create Survey Point Groups in AutoCAD Civil 3D Survey Databases Video | Eric Colburn, PLS (clueweb12-0100tw-51-18428) http://ericcolburn.com/2012/01/27/create-survey-point-groups-in-autocad-civil-3d-survey-databases-video/ Create Survey Point Groups in AutoCAD Civil 3D Survey Databases Video | Eric Colburn, PLS ...1 Review of LS Recommendations posted in GPS2011 Marketing Kit posted in FAQs PLS Learning Center Subscribe to Blog via Email Enter your email address to subscribe to this blog and receive notifications of new posts by email. To start connecting please log in first or Register to get started. Username Password Remember Me Active | Popular Marketing Land Surveying Services active 1 week, 1 day ago Professional Land Surveyor Practice active 1 month, 2... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:30:15">http://jolt.merlot.org/vol4no3/glass_0908.htm</link><title>JOLT - Journal of Online Learning and Teaching</title><description>* JOLT - Journal of Online Learning and Teaching (clueweb12-0002wb-82-32158) http://jolt.merlot.org/vol4no3/glass_0908.htm ...94542 USA Valerie.Sue@csueastbay.edu   Abstract This study analyzes student preference, satisfaction and perceived learning in an online college mathematics course for business majors.  Using a combination of active and passive learning objects, the online course was developed to investigate the instructional strategies students use the most, prefer and believe impact their learning.  Students answered weekly surveys about the course.  They were asked to report their usage of the learning objects and... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:33:33">http://www.nc-net.info/db_active-learning.php</link><title>NC-NET Active Learning Resources</title><description>* NC-NET Active Learning Resources (clueweb12-0208wb-29-15250) http://www.nc-net.info/db_active-learning.php ...Paulson and Jennifer L. Faust of California State University, L.A., that offers techniques for cooperative learning for individuals and for groups. Related concepts: cooperative, active, experiential, science, discussion, feedback, wait time, Socratic method, demonstration, journal, active review, concept mapping http://www.calstatela.edu/dept/chem/chem2/Active/index.htm Active Learning for the College Classroom Provides a survey of a wide variety of active learning techniques which can be used to supplement rather than replace lectures. The authors, Donald Paulson... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>