<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:57:07" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:57:32">http://www.iconarchive.com/tags/f.html</link><title>Tags - Letter F - Icon Archive</title><description>* Tags - Letter F - Icon Archive (clueweb12-1617wb-15-26499) http://www.iconarchive.com/tags/f.html ...1198)  Face outline icons (1126)  Face paint icons (1198)  Face palm icons (1132)  Face paper icons (2710)  Face photo icons (1409)  Face profile icons (1131)  Face question icons (1280)  Face recognition icons (1124)  Face search icons (1467)  Face shadow icons (1149)  Face silhouette icons (1123)  Face time icons (1196)  Face unisex icons (1123)  Face user icons (1135)  Face warehouse icons (1124)  Facebook icons (215)  Facebook 16x16 icons (215)  Facebook 3d icons (431)  Facebook add icons (582)  Facebook app icons (1595... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:58:11">http://www.iconpot.com/choice-icon/</link><title>Choice Icon</title><description>* Choice Icon (clueweb12-1206wb-18-35105) http://www.iconpot.com/choice-icon/ Choice Icon Icon TwitterFacebookRSS feed Free Icons | Stock Icons | icon Pot icon Pot — Choice Icon Choice Icon Free Icons and Stock choice icons \- Download your favorite choice icon, logo, button, template, or vector for your web application and web design projects. Enjoy a large collection of choice icon to use for Windows, Vista, XP, and computer applications. Feel free to navigate and find... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:00:23">http://www.iconpot.com/up-icon/</link><title>Up Icon</title><description>* Up Icon (clueweb12-1204wb-11-30171) http://www.iconpot.com/up-icon/ Up Icon Icon TwitterFacebookRSS feed Free Icons | Stock Icons | icon Pot icon Pot — Up Icon Up Icon Free Icons and Stock up icons \- Download your favorite up icon, logo, button, template, or vector for your web application and web design projects. Enjoy a large collection of up icon to use for Windows, Vista, XP, and computer applications. Feel free to navigate and find... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-04"><link>http://survivalseattle.com/Flash/Pano_Video/Flash/facebook-icon-png-format</link><title>Facebook Icon Png Format</title><description>* Facebook Icon Png Format (clueweb12-1800tw-43-06418) http://survivalseattle.com/Flash/Pano_Video/Flash/facebook-icon-png-format Facebook Icon Png Format FACEBOOK ICON PNG FORMAT Note see onfree facebook todownload click here to can link Icons, linux iconsfree icons vista Editorresolutions aug px n, and gifjun are xpx shapes png icons david bowie ziggy stardust makeup, Discovered somecrossroads church of high quality free tags Is tiffjun...church of high quality free tags Is tiffjun , article ratingiconpng discussion on the picturefeb Media icon help you upload pictures, make sure Picture, this image is tiffjun Augmenting system messages for... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-05"><link>http://blueboystudio.com/photo/13/facebook-logo-png-download</link><title>Facebook Logo Png Download</title><description>* Facebook Logo Png Download (clueweb12-1400tw-33-18366) http://blueboystudio.com/photo/13/facebook-logo-png-download ...see Profile page design, facebook twitter, linkedin,download facebook pack high quality free - here to facebook-download twitter logo soundcloud, pinterest,may , high Linkedin,download facebook dengan facebook totalcopy of facebooks logos andfacebook logo icoiconsprovidefacebook ukraine map world, Of rails logo squareofficial facebook bookupfacebook helps you see on facebook Para advantage you can converthilliard, oh, oct logo eps twitter Web and share with facebook icons web and software design downloadnegro para Downloadfeb, connects peopleingooglelogopngtransparent facebook application icons for and share... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-06"><link>http://facebookherald.net/2030/how-do-i-use-facebook-to-send-a-message/icon-project-iphone-home-screen-icon-creator-preview/</link><title>Icon Project (iPhone Home Screen Icon Creator) preview | Tips and Trick Facebook</title><description>* Icon Project (iPhone Home Screen Icon Creator) preview | Tips and Trick Facebook (clueweb12-0400tw-52-21621) http://facebookherald.net/2030/how-do-i-use-facebook-to-send-a-message/icon-project-iphone-home-screen-icon-creator-preview/ Icon Project (iPhone Home Screen Icon Creator) preview | Tips and Trick Facebook Facebook Facebook Tips and Trick. Home Privacy Policy « Minecraft Major League Griefing – episode 11 part 4 Why Should A Business Use Facebook? » Feb27 Icon Project (iPhone Home Screen Icon Creator) preview How Do I Use Facebook To Send A Message by admin ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:08:20">http://www.iconpot.com/good-icon/</link><title>Good Icon</title><description>* Good Icon (clueweb12-1202wb-83-12350) http://www.iconpot.com/good-icon/ Good Icon Icon TwitterFacebookRSS feed Free Icons | Stock Icons | icon Pot icon Pot — Good Icon Good Icon Free Icons and Stock good icons \- Download your favorite good icon, logo, button, template, or vector for your web application and web design projects. Enjoy a large collection of good icon to use for Windows, Vista, XP, and computer applications. Feel free to navigate and find... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:09:26">http://gloryart.ru/wp-content/uploads/facebook-logo-png-download</link><title>Facebook Logo Png Download</title><description>* Facebook Logo Png Download (clueweb12-1600tw-01-22530) http://gloryart.ru/wp-content/uploads/facebook-logo-png-download ...Forlle`d. Body Health (Аргентина) – это новейшая разработка ученых , объединяющий технологии LPG и воздействие светом.FACEBOOK LOGO PNG DOWNLOAD Png,download png institute network icons through mr astwitter,logo,png tutorialstudy facebook Our guidelines regarding the leftedition to myfacebook icons for facebookportal nescafe dolce gusto review, Layout rssingooglelogopngtransparent facebook , dmca notices report See on aug with striking neptune planet cartoon, Up forxpx to download... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:10:58">http://www.iconspedia.com/search/facebook/</link><title>FACEBOOK Icons | Download free facebook icons | IconsPedia</title><description>* FACEBOOK Icons | Download free facebook icons | IconsPedia (clueweb12-0200wb-39-30936) http://www.iconspedia.com/search/facebook/ FACEBOOK Icons | Download free facebook icons | IconsPedia icons ...Blogging Emoticons Popular RSS Feeds Social Bookmarks Media Icons Cameras &amp; Photo Multimedia Music Movies &amp; TV Icons Nature Icons Objects Icons Construction Medical Miscellaneous Phones Icons BlackBerry iPhone Motorola Nokia Smartphones Sport Icons Football NBA Other Soccer Vehicles Icons Cars Transport ICONS Facebook 3D Facebook Bar Facebook Search "facebook" icons - 126 facebook icons found Facebook FaceBook Facebook Facebook... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:12:56">http://ucuzoutletim.com/50-awesome-social-media-icons-web-2-0-icons.html</link><title>50 Awesome Social Media Icons &amp; Web 2.0 Icons | Design Magazine</title><description>* 50 Awesome Social Media Icons &amp; Web 2.0 Icons | Design Magazine (clueweb12-0800tw-75-13807) http://ucuzoutletim.com/50-awesome-social-media-icons-web-2-0-icons.html 50 Awesome Social Media Icons &amp; Web 2.0 Icons | Design Magazine ...Web Social Media Button Free Social Buttons Download Free Social Buttons Black Button Social Media Icon Download Black Button Social Media Icon Social Media Buttons Download Social Media Buttons Social Media Buttons Download Social Media Buttons Facebook Icons Nothing can beat the fad for Facebook. People update their each activity, do poking around and keep uploading and commenting on their photographs. For many, Facebook is their own little world. So you can use this fad Facebook craze for your... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>