<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7120">tortellini pasta salad</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:51:18" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-01"><link>http://brandlg.fm.interia.pl/recipe-v1a/258.html</link><title>Shrimp Tortellini Pasta Salad. With Vegetables Is A Salad Recipe Shrimp Salad.</title><description>* Shrimp Tortellini Pasta Salad. With Vegetables Is A Salad Recipe Shrimp Salad. (clueweb12-0000wb-99-09532) http://brandlg.fm.interia.pl/recipe-v1a/258.html Shrimp Tortellini Pasta Salad. With Vegetables Is A Salad Recipe Shrimp Salad. Tortellini Pasta Salad Tortellini Pasta Salad. With Vegetables Is A Salad Recipe Shrimp Salad. Ipse dixit Links Ultimi commenti Archivio Categorie Chicken Poboy SandwichesRecipe On Seasoning For Hamburger...Soup 0 Weight Watcher Points Feeds-counter Site Map Credits Best regards Find more Tortellini Pasta Salad. With Vegetables Is A Salad Recipe Shrimp Salad. Shrimp Tortellini Pasta Salad Tortellini salad tossed or caesar salad pasta salad potato salad romaine belux shrimp marinated bo buffet: deli... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:53:11">http://www.recipes-to-go.co.uk/pasta/recipe-index0003.shtml</link><title>Pasta Recipes Index</title><description>* Pasta Recipes Index (clueweb12-0612wb-33-18331) http://www.recipes-to-go.co.uk/pasta/recipe-index0003.shtml Pasta Recipes Index ...Pumpkin Seed Sauce   Purim Manicotti   Purim Ravioli   Quick &amp; Easy Couscous   Quick &amp; Easy Lasagna   Quick &amp; Easy Pasta Sauce   Quick &amp; Simple Pasta Salad   Quick &amp; Simple Pasta Salad 1   Quick And Simple Pasta Salad   Quick Chili Pasta   Quick Crispy Noodles   Quick Double Tomato And Tortellini Soup   Quick Fix Pasta Sauces   Quick Franks &amp; Macaroni   Quick Italian Spaghetti   Quick Lasagna   Quick Meal--Pasta Susanna   Quick Orzo Casserole   Quick Pasta Bolognese   Quick Pasta Salad   Quick Pierogi Minestrone   Quick Ravioli Soup   Quick Spaghetti Sauce   Quick Tomato... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:53:56">http://mapjh.fm.interia.pl/gerber-l2b/199.html</link><title>Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing. With Rice, Vegan Spinach Orange Salad.</title><description>* Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing. With Rice, Vegan Spinach Orange Salad. (clueweb12-0004wb-11-32439) http://mapjh.fm.interia.pl/gerber-l2b/199.html Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing. With Rice, Vegan Spinach Orange Salad. In Cream Dressing Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing. With Rice, Vegan Spinach Orange Salad. commenti links bloggers archivio Scalloped Corn Sugar RecipeCrystal Cake Plate HummingbirdMcgrath's Irish Tea...Food RecipesGerman-style ChickenSoup Du Jour Definition Categorie Feeds Site Map my media Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing. With Rice, Vegan Spinach Orange Salad. Tortellini Pasta Salad In Cream Dressing To pizza, try their tortellini, lazzarotto wines pasta shells stuffed with meat... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-04"><link>http://cookeatshare.com/popular/cheese-tortellini-salads</link><title>Cheese tortellini salads - CookEatShare</title><description>* Cheese tortellini salads - CookEatShare (clueweb12-0917wb-89-20856) http://cookeatshare.com/popular/cheese-tortellini-salads ...views Three Cheese Tortellini Salad, ingredients: 1 (7 ounce.) pkg. cheese tortellini, 1 c Cheese Tortellini Salad 50 views Cheese Tortellini Salad, ingredients: 1 pkg. fresh cheese tortellini, 1 pkg. Good Seasons Join CookEatShare â it's free! Get new recipes from top Professionals! Share recipes and reviews with friends! Save and organize all you recipes! over 2 million users! Sign Up Now Cheese Tortellini Pasta Salad 270 views Cheese Tortellini Pasta Salad, ingredients: 1/4 c. balsamic vinegar, 2 Tbsp. minced... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:56:32">http://salad-recipe.org/</link><title>Salad Recipes</title><description>* Salad Recipes (clueweb12-0302wb-16-23758) http://www.salad-recipe.org/sitemap/index.php Salad Recipes ...salad recipes | recipe tasty salads ravioli salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads spaghetti salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads spaghetti salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads three bean salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads three bean salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads cold curried rice salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads tortellini pesto salad recipe | pasta salad recipes | recipe tasty salads tortellini salad recipe | pasta salad recipes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:58:04">http://zonesef.fm.interia.pl/easy-szeb6/38.html</link><title>Recipes For Tortellini Salad. Off With A Warm Balsamic.</title><description>* Recipes For Tortellini Salad. Off With A Warm Balsamic. (clueweb12-1203wb-10-02066) http://zonesef.fm.interia.pl/easy-szeb6/38.html ...an entr e. Forums; recipes; the epicurious recipe swap; y meal solutions; healthy cooking ; cooking tortellini salad with walnuts and feta cheese posted:. Low fat recipes featured recipes with photo fabulous fruit salad fresh corn salad tortellini with saut vegetables. Find dozens of italian recipes for pasta dishes, pizza, salad dressings recipes soups, dinners, and desserts baked bruschetta; spinach tortellini salad; caprese salad; antipasti salad; antipasto party platter. Authentic italian pasta recipes &amp; cooking information for optimal flavor in refrigerated pasta... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-07"><link>http://chelsegj.fm.interia.pl/chicken-29/122.html</link><title>Tortellini And Broccoli Salad. Creamy Spinach Tortellini; Broccoli Salad; Roast Chicken.</title><description>* Tortellini And Broccoli Salad. Creamy Spinach Tortellini; Broccoli Salad; Roast Chicken. (clueweb12-0305wb-39-06731) http://chelsegj.fm.interia.pl/chicken-29/122.html ...food affair Turkey escallop chasseurs sp sh omelette midi potatoes broccoli mange tout tempura vegetables salad bar mixed choice of hot drinks lunch roast beef and gravy yorkshire puddings tortellini. Cold pasta salad with chicken, broccoli made with penne pasta from mini penne with chicken, broccoli and roasted peppers salad (mini penne con pollo, broccoli e. Sides includecole slaw, potato salad, fresh corn (seasonal),broccoli &amp; mushroom casserole with fried onions, cornbread, baked beans, tri-colored tortellini... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:00:31">http://www.gourmet.org/recipes/pasta/</link><title>Pasta Recipes</title><description>* Pasta Recipes (clueweb12-0202wb-42-21791) http://www.gourmet.org/recipes/pasta/ ...Daube De Boeufs Aux Champignons Et A L'orange Daube De Queue De Boeuf Deli-style Pasta Salad Delicate Homemade Pasta Deviled Eggs &amp; Noodles - Microwave Deviled Eggs&amp; Noodles Diabetic Linguine With Clam Sauce Dijon Pasta Salad Dill Pickled Eggs Dill Sauce With Scallops Over Angel Hair Pasta Ditalini With Zucchini Domatosoupa Me Spaghetti Dorothy's Mostaccioli Vegetarian Pasta With W Double Pesto Tortellini With Shrimp Dried Cherry Couscous Drunken Pioneers Dunbar Macaroni&amp; Cheese Durum-wheat Pasta For Pasta... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:36">http://thcbbs.com/food/category/0629-SALAD.HTM</link><title>THC BBS Food - Dishes :: Salad</title><description>* THC BBS Food - Dishes :: Salad (clueweb12-1114wb-69-29336) http://thcbbs.com/food/category/0629-SALAD.HTM ...salad dressing Charred Corn Salad Charred new potato and fennel salad Charred new potato &amp; fennel salad Charred steak pasta salad (mf) Char's pasta salad Char's potato salad Chayote Caviar Salad Chayote salad Cheddar Cheese Jello Salad Cheddar macaroni salad Cheese And Ham Tabbouleh Salad Cheese and potato salad Cheese mold Cheese &amp; potato salad Cheese salad Cheese salad dressings - great chefs Cheese tortellini with red pepper dressing Cheesy Pita Salad Sandwiches Chef Kurt Linsi's Queen Of Sheba Salad... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7120-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7120_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:03:47">http://sorrelfm.fm.interia.pl/how-to-b2b/205.html</link><title>Tortellini Bean Salad. Packaged Tortellini Make For A Delicious, 2007.</title><description>* Tortellini Bean Salad. Packaged Tortellini Make For A Delicious, 2007. (clueweb12-0007wb-65-16434) http://sorrelfm.fm.interia.pl/how-to-b2b/205.html ...Whole ChickenYellowstone Coffee MugsCoffee Mug Quilt Blocks Categorie Feeds Site Map my media Tortellini Bean Salad. Packaged Tortellini Make For A Delicious, 2007. Tortellini Bean Salad Meat tortellini baked ham baked chicken italian sausage in red sauce roast pork bean salad cucumber &amp; onion: all cocktail party, buffet, short thick spiral pasta y style, and sit down dinners. Tortellini salad a very simple yet surprisingly tasty salad, fish recipe tilapia perfect as a first course... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>