<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7122">horse dog pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:06:01" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:06:25">http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000272.htm</link><title>Pet Rock Star: Where Have You &lt;i&gt;Been&lt;/i&gt;?</title><description>* Pet Rock Star: Where Have You &lt;i&gt;Been&lt;/i&gt;? (clueweb12-1611wb-97-06231) http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000272.htm ...hentai rape RAPE SITES WAR RAPE. Rape pictures rape bondage JApanesE RapE. Family violence rape pics rape COmIX. Gang rape free rape movies workpLaCE vIoLeNCE. Domestic violence rape video BRUTAL RAPE...torture devices Posted by: fetish clothing at November 19, 2004 04:15 PM Zoo sex horse sex stories gay beastiality. Animal sex free free horse sex pictures zoofilia free bestiality pictures. Animal sex free free bestiality pics FREE BESTIALITY PICS. Beastiality sex horses having sex with women beAstIALity PoRN free BeastIaLITy ViDEOS. Sex with dog zoophilia stories bEASTIAliTY sex. Animal sex pics sex horse BEASTIALITY FORUMS. Animal sex pics beastiality pictures ANIMAL SEX VIDEO FREE ANIMAL SEX MOVIES. Beastiality... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:08:54">http://www.allivet.com/p-2602-pet-hair-pic-up-adhesive-refill.aspx</link><title>Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Refill , Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy</title><description>* Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Refill , Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy (clueweb12-0407wb-71-00316) http://www.allivet.com/p-2602-pet-hair-pic-up-adhesive-refill.aspx Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Refill , Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy Pic Up Adhesive Refill , Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy Horse Care Dog Care Cat Care Livestock Care Super Deal Account Account (0) view cart ...Super Deal Account Account (0) view cart Pic Up Adhesive Refill Horse CareHorse DewormersHorse Daily WormersHorse Oral Liquid WormersHorse Paste WormersHorse Digestive &amp; UlcerHorse Digestive MedicationsHorse Digestive SupplementsHorse Ear CareHorse Eye CareHorse... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:10:39">http://www.allivet.com/p-2601-pet-hair-pic-up-adhesive-roller.aspx</link><title>Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Roller, Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy</title><description>* Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Roller, Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy (clueweb12-0407wb-69-16852) http://www.allivet.com/p-2601-pet-hair-pic-up-adhesive-roller.aspx Pet Hair Pic Up Adhesive Roller, Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy Pic Up Adhesive Roller, Combs &amp; Brushes| Pet Grooming, | Allivet Trusted Pharmacy Horse Care Dog Care Cat Care Livestock Care Super Deal Account Account (0) view cart ...Super Deal Account Account (0) view cart Pic Up Adhesive Roller Horse CareHorse DewormersHorse Daily WormersHorse Oral Liquid WormersHorse Paste WormersHorse Digestive &amp; UlcerHorse Digestive MedicationsHorse Digestive SupplementsHorse Ear CareHorse Eye CareHorse... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:24">http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000277.htm</link><title>Pet Rock Star: The Saga Continues</title><description>* Pet Rock Star: The Saga Continues (clueweb12-1611wb-97-06233) http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000277.htm ...sEx WiTh ANIMals bEAstiAliTy PicTuReS. Animal sex movies girls having sex with dogs ZooFIlIA. Sex dog sex with horses FREE BESTIALITY. Beastiality pictures bestiality free SEX dog. Men having sex with animals free bestiality sex with horses. Women having sex with animals free beastiality stories horse sex. Free animal sex pics free bestiality movies free beastiality videos. Zoofilia women having sex with dogs stories of beastiality... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:56">http://www.medicalonline.com/medicaldiscussion/_disc2/000015af.htm</link><title>xbghUMtEFhgNnEAH</title><description>* xbghUMtEFhgNnEAH (clueweb12-0511wb-06-16227) http://www.medicalonline.com/medicaldiscussion/_disc2/000015af.htm ...bestiality animal fuck zoo sex dog zoo sex movies zoo sex girls zoo sex girl dog fucking girl zoo fucking animal fucking animal sex pictures animal sex clips animal sex women animal sex fuck animal sex movies sex animal sex fucking horse sex free horse sex sex horse sex with horse horse sex movies horse sex pics horse sex stories horse sex free free horse sex movies sex with a horse horse sex pictures horse sex movie free horse sex... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:13:06">http://www.domainnamesanity.com/pages/15.php</link><title>Domain Name Sanity</title><description>* Domain Name Sanity (clueweb12-0506wb-90-24844) http://www.domainnamesanity.com/pages/15.php ...american breeders bull pit terrier7587923 - american breeders dog eskimo standard6076566 - american buck skin horse4378948 - american bull dog2584127 - american bull history pit terrier7418210 - american bull kennel pit terrier5480965 - american bull...7338570 - andalusian impression7566022 - andalusian malaga region1551934 - andalusian mare7371824 - andalusian music2860400 - andalusian pic5990328 - andalusian picture4150711 - andalusian show horse8381494 - andalusian stallion3788727 - andalusian stallions9723772 - andalusian texas1130605 - andrew bird9495100 - angola horse thoroughbred2771871 - animal picture online5016417 - animated dog gif3376407 - anna horse morgan morgan morgan,and ranch richard7899599 - anna morgan horse6475285 - another chance english setter7394185 - anstamm scottish terrier1599886 - anti idiotarian rottweiler6819904 - antique... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:16:14">http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000706.htm</link><title>Pet Rock Star: &lt;strike&gt;Warping&lt;/strike&gt; Wrapping Presents</title><description>* Pet Rock Star: &lt;strike&gt;Warping&lt;/strike&gt; Wrapping Presents (clueweb12-1608wb-26-12204) http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000706.htm ...FREe BeAstiALiTY aNiMAl sEX. Zoophilia stories free bestiality pictures ANIMAL SEX MOVIES. Zoofilia zoo sex horse beastiality. Bestiality pictures beastiality tgp BeStIALity PoRN Free beasTIAlItY pICTURes. Zoophilia stories bestiality free ANIMAL FARM SEX. Animal farm sex gay bestiality free bestiality pics. Dog bestiality girls having sex with animals frEe horsE sex pIcTuREs sEX wITh dOgs. Horse sex sex with horses FREE DOG SEX MOVIES HORSES HAVING SEX WITH WOMEN. Free animal sex videos dog sex stories free beastiality movies. Zoo... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:17:59">http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000464.htm</link><title>Pet Rock Star: Living Vicariously...</title><description>* Pet Rock Star: Living Vicariously... (clueweb12-1606wb-54-20829) http://www.shannoncampbell.info/archives/000464.htm ...www.bestlowmortgagerates.com/homeloans/ Posted by: mortgage at November 17, 2004 01:52 PM Sex dog people having sex with animals free dog sex stories. Zoo sex sex animal FREE HORSE...at November 17, 2004 01:52 PM Sex dog people having sex with animals free dog sex stories. Zoo sex sex animal FREE HORSE SEX. Horse sex movies horse bestiality men having sex with animals. Beastiality movies gay beastiality ZOOPHILIA. Beastiality mpegs free horse sex pictures free HORsE SEX PicTURES. Bestiality videos dog sex free animal sex movies beastiality videos. Free bestiality pics dog sex BEAsTiALITy vIDeO dOG BestIAliTY. Beastiality pictures zoophilia BEASTiAliTy fORUmS. Horse sex stories bestiality free... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:20:34">http://www.allivet.com/c-37-combs-brushes.aspx</link><title>Combs &amp; Brushes, Pet Grooming | Pet Meds| Allivet Trusted Pet Pharmacy</title><description>* Combs &amp; Brushes, Pet Grooming | Pet Meds| Allivet Trusted Pet Pharmacy (clueweb12-0101wb-22-28745) http://www.allivet.com/c-37-combs-brushes.aspx ...Pharmacy Horse Care Dog Care Cat Care Livestock Care Super Deal Account Account (0) view cart Horse CareHorse DewormersHorse Daily WormersHorse Oral Liquid WormersHorse Paste WormersHorse Digestive &amp; UlcerHorse Digestive MedicationsHorse Digestive SupplementsHorse Ear CareHorse Eye CareHorse Eye AntibioticsHorse Eye InflammationHorse Eye Tears LubricantsHorse Fly Control... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7122-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7122_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:24:25">http://www.domainnamesanity.com/pages/28.php</link><title>Domain Name Sanity</title><description>* Domain Name Sanity (clueweb12-0506wb-55-26840) http://www.domainnamesanity.com/pages/28.php ...7686488 - samoyed puppy picture4958112 - samoyed rescue2234404 - sandra morgan quarter horse2739030 - saskatchewan paint horse club2838631 - sawyer creek appaloosa2437615 - scarlet chested parakeet4526556 - schipperke639323 - schipperke adoption7413883 - schipperke breeders2302350 - schipperke club3637940 - schipperke club of america768593 - schipperke dog1440492 - schipperke dog breed8328023 - schipperke dog breeders3540836 - schipperke for sale7801515 - schipperke gift4818320 - schipperke photo6678701 - schipperke pic6086301 - schipperke picture8756293 - schipperke pup7454935 - schipperke puppy2275907 - schipperke puppy for sale7958349... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>