<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:41:25" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:42:20">http://bikersusa.com/travel/ca/hotels/long-beach.html</link><title>Long Beach California CA Hotels|Motels|Inns|Attractions</title><description>* Long Beach California CA Hotels|Motels|Inns|Attractions (clueweb12-0306wb-19-22911) http://bikersusa.com/travel/ca/hotels/long-beach.html Long Beach California CA Hotels|Motels|Inns|Attractions CA Hotels and Motels Find Long Beach CA Hotels and Motels with the best accomodations, lowest priced, or most convenient to motorcycle events and local attractions. To find the hotel closest to your destination in Long Beach California, check out the Long Beach CA Hotels Map. Major Motorcycle Rally cities: Austin, Daytona Beach, Fayetteville AR, Galveston, Myrtle Beach, Ocean City, Phoenix, Sturgis Rally / Rapid City... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:43:49">http://www.usa-lodging.net/?f</link><title>Long Beach California CA hotels</title><description>* Long Beach California CA hotels (clueweb12-0305wb-34-07663) http://www.usa-lodging.net/motels/california/LongBeach.htm Long Beach California CA hotels ...98.99 - 200.99)   2 Star Visitors to Long Beach, California in addition appreciate the beach, Ocean Boulevard, &amp; the Aquarium of the Pacific. Stay at this recently renovated hotel in the heart of Long Beach, California. Hotel rooms feature deluxe pillow-top beds, free Wi-Fi ...more Los Angeles-Days Inn Long Beach/City Center 1500 E. Pacific Coast Highway Long Beach, CA 90806 Nightly Rates (80.01 - 80.01)   3 Star We offer features for the business... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-03"><link>http://www.qwikcast.com/hotelsearch/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html</link><title>Long Beach, CA, California hotels</title><description>* Long Beach, CA, California hotels (clueweb12-0604wb-44-00330) http://www.qwikcast.com/hotelsearch/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html Long Beach, CA, California hotels ...hotels Long Beach Find the best rates for hotels in Long Beach, CA. Get discounted rates for...Beach California offers exceptional service international flair and an elegant... Get more information on Hilton Long Beach Executive Meeting Center hotel CURRENT 5325 E Pacific Coast Hwy Long Beach, CA 90804 Nightly Rates: ( 112.50 - 112.50 ) Formerly known as the GuestHouse Hotel -Hotel CURRENT is the newest addition to the city of Long Beach. We embrace the Southern California beach lifestyle by hi... Get more information on hotel CURRENT Long Beach Marriott 4700 Airport Plaza... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-04"><link>http://www.traveltidingsusa.com/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html</link><title>Long Beach California CA Hotels - Long Beach Vacation and Hotel Guide - Travel Tidings USA</title><description>* Long Beach California CA Hotels - Long Beach Vacation and Hotel Guide - Travel Tidings USA (clueweb12-0302wb-04-29619) http://www.traveltidingsusa.com/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html ...California CA Hotels - Long Beach Vacation and Hotel Guide - Travel Tidings USA Long Beach, CA Hotels Welcome to Travel Tidings USA's selection of hotel accommodation in Long Beach, CA where...CA 90831-3102 Nightly Rates: ( 184.00 - 209.00 ) 4 Star The recently renovated Hilton Long Beach &amp; Executive Meeting Center hotel in Long Beach, California offers exceptional service, international flair and an elegant ambiance. Conveniently located adjacent to the World Trade Center and near bo...more Los Angeles-Days Inn Long Beach/City Center 1500 E. Pacific Coast Highway Long Beach, CA 90806 Nightly Rates: ( 85.34 - 96.01 ) 3 Star Welcome to the Days Inn Long... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:47:39">http://www.sanpedro.com/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html</link><title>Long Beach California CA hotels</title><description>* Long Beach California CA hotels (clueweb12-0211wb-66-10839) http://www.sanpedro.com/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html ...Inn Long Beach CA hotel, which is just a short shuttle ride from the Long Beach Airport. Our Long Beach extended stay hotel suites offer separate living and sle...see more hotel CURRENT 5325 E Pacific Coast Hwy Long Beach, CA 90804 Nightly Rates: ( 116.03 - 116.03 ) 2 Star Formerly known as the GuestHouse Hotel -Hotel CURRENT is the newest edition to the city of Long Beach. We embrace the Southern California beach lifestyle by highlighting hand painted artwork... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-06"><link>http://www.gusto.com/california/longbeach/hotels/City1666363Reservation.html</link><title>hotels in long beach | long beach, ca hotels and motels</title><description>* hotels in long beach | long beach, ca hotels and motels (clueweb12-0110wb-36-18098) http://www.gusto.com/california/longbeach/hotels/City1666363Reservation.html hotels in long beach | long beach, ca hotels and motels Long Beach, California CA Hotels and Motels gusto! top cities: South Padre Island, TX Cincinnati, OH Panama City Beach, FL Wildwood, NJ Wilmington, NC Austin, TX Charlotte, NC Arlington, VA Pittsburgh, PA Kansas City, MO Philadelphia, PA Albuquerque, NM Washington, DC Orlando, FL Boston, MA Columbus, OH Columbia, SC... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:51:10">http://octa-trails.org/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.php</link><title>Long Beach California CA Hotels :: Oregon-California Trails Association (OCTA)</title><description>* Long Beach California CA Hotels :: Oregon-California Trails Association (OCTA) (clueweb12-0008wb-60-07910) http://octa-trails.org/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.php ...access to both Orange and Los Angeles County. The hotel is located adjacent to the Long Beach Airport with easy freeway accessibility to major attractions and corporat...see more hotel CURRENT 5325 E Pacific Coast Hwy Long Beach, CA 90804 Nightly Rates: ( 100.00 - 112.50 ) 2 Star Formerly known as the GuestHouse Hotel -Hotel CURRENT is the newest addition to the city of Long Beach. We embrace the Southern California beach lifestyle by highlighting hand painted artwork featured...see... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-08"><link>http://https://www.octa-trails.org/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.php</link><title>Long Beach California CA Hotels :: Oregon-California Trails Association (OCTA)</title><description>* Long Beach California CA Hotels :: Oregon-California Trails Association (OCTA) (clueweb12-0610wb-32-19634) http://https://www.octa-trails.org/hotels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.php ...access to both Orange and Los Angeles County. The hotel is located adjacent to the Long Beach Airport with easy freeway accessibility to major attractions and corporat...see more hotel CURRENT 5325 E Pacific Coast Hwy Long Beach, CA 90804 Nightly Rates: ( 100.00 - 112.50 ) 2 Star Formerly known as the GuestHouse Hotel -Hotel CURRENT is the newest addition to the city of Long Beach. We embrace the Southern California beach lifestyle by highlighting hand painted artwork featured...see... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:54:15">http://www.roadsideamerica.com/hotels_motels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html</link><title>Long Beach, California CA - Motels, Hotels, Inns, Lodging</title><description>* Long Beach, California CA - Motels, Hotels, Inns, Lodging (clueweb12-0207wb-79-16918) http://www.roadsideamerica.com/hotels_motels/hotels/us-ca-long-beach.html Long Beach, California CA - Motels, Hotels, Inns, Lodging Long Beach, CA Hotels Navigation RoadsideAmerica.com US Hotels Canada Hotels FAQ Car Rentals Contact Us Privacy My...seen on the Pacific coast. Located in the heart of the entertainment district, our downtown Long Beach, California hotel is ... Click for More Info hotel CURRENT 5325 E Pacific Coast Hwy Long Beach, CA 90804 Rates Recently Found: ($88.33 - $155.67) 2 Star Formerly known as the GuestHouse Hotel -Hotel CURRENT is the newest edition to the city of Long Beach. We embrace the Southern California beach lifestyle by highlighting hand painted artwork featured ... Click for... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:56:16">http://www.vehicledonation101.com/car_donation/ca_long_beach_vehicle_donation_3.shtml</link><title>Vehicle Donation Long Beach, California: Car Donation</title><description>* Vehicle Donation Long Beach, California: Car Donation (clueweb12-1002wb-26-08819) http://www.vehicledonation101.com/car_donation/ca_long_beach_vehicle_donation_3.shtml Vehicle Donation Long Beach, California: Car Donation All you need to know about donating your car to a charity...4 Long Beach, CA Inter Community Care Centers Inc. Long Beach, CA Intercity Fellowship Hall Long Beach, CA Interdenominational Church of God of America Long Beach, CA Interdenominational Community Development Corporation Long Beach, CA Intermodal Infrastructure Partnership (Until December 2007) Long Beach, CA International Childrens Affair (Until December 2005) Long Beach, CA International Childrens Choir of Long Beach Long Beach, CA International City Racing Foundation (Until December 2007) Long Beach, CA International City Theatre Long Beach, CA International... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>