<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:42:44" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:43:29">http://www.visitnorman.com/events/location/sam-noble-oklahoma-museum-of-natural-history/</link><title>Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History</title><description>* Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History (clueweb12-1206wb-19-00426) http://www.visitnorman.com/events/location/sam-noble-oklahoma-museum-of-natural-history/ Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History ...Meeting Space Meeting Planning Services Museum of Natural History Search Events By Date Range Start Date: End Date: find function submitform() { document.supportform.submit(); } Loading Map.... Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History2401 Chautauqua Ave. - Norman, OKDetails 35.1946 -97.4485 Address 2401 Chautauqua Ave. Norman, OK... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:46:35">http://www.visitnorman.com/index.php</link><title>http://www.visitnorman.com/index.php</title><description>* http://www.visitnorman.com/index.php (clueweb12-1116wb-81-16242) http://www.visitnorman.com/index.php ...Jacobson House Native Art Center 03/25/2012 Discovery Days at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 03/27/2012 Free Admission to Fred Jones Jr. Museum of Art 03/27/2012 Toddler Time at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 03/29/2012 - 04/01/2012 The Sooner Theatre presents "Footloose" 03/30/2012 - 04... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:47:50">http://www.visitnorman.com</link><title>http://www.visitnorman.com</title><description>* http://www.visitnorman.com (clueweb12-1116wb-81-16232) http://www.visitnorman.com ...the Jacobson House Native Art Center 03/27/2012 Free Admission to Fred Jones Jr. Museum of Art 03/27/2012 Toddler Time at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 03/29/2012 - 04/01/2012 The Sooner Theatre presents "Footloose" 03/30/2012 - 04...30/2012 Concert - Doobie Brothers 03/31/2012 Toddler Time at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 03/31/2012 Discovery Days at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 04/01/2012 Discovery Days at the Sam Noble Oklahoma Museum of Natural History 04/01/2012 42nd Annual Festival of Spirituals 04/02/2012 - 04/03/2012 Oklahoma... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:49:34">http://www.cbel.com/science_museums/</link><title>579 manually selected sites about Science Museums</title><description>* 579 manually selected sites about Science Museums (clueweb12-0502wb-34-17549) http://www.cbel.com/science_museums/ ...Museum of Discovery and Science- Miami Museum of Science &amp; Planetariu...- Long Island Science Center- Water Museum Barcelona- Lawrence Hall of Science- Science East Science Centre- Museum of Life and Science- The Museum of Science and Industry in Ma...- Natural Science Center of Greensboro- National Museum of Science and Technolog...- National Museum of Emerging Science and ...- Museum of the History of Science, Univer...- Museum of Science &amp; History- The Nobel Museum- Museum of Science- The Danish Lake District Eco-Museum... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-05"><link>http://hoppa.com/Natural_History/</link><title>Hoppa - Natural History in the World</title><description>* Hoppa - Natural History in the World (clueweb12-0004wb-89-21193) http://hoppa.com/Natural_History/ Hoppa - Natural History in the World var OrigUrl = '/Natural_History/'; Natural History in the World Canadian Museum of Nature Canada, Nature, Museums, Natural History The Canadian Museum of Nature is your source for authoritative and credible information about the natural world. Increase your interest in nature while you learn about our exhibitions, programmes, activities, research... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-06"><link>http://www.nlbif.nl/browse_collections.php</link><title>NLBIF Biodiversity Portal : Browse all collections</title><description>* NLBIF Biodiversity Portal : Browse all collections (clueweb12-1803wb-43-23207) http://www.nlbif.nl/browse_collections.php ...info | Disclaimer | Credits Site developed by ETI BioInformatics Museum of Natural History Naturalis Leiden Aceraceae - Maple family PlantenTuin Esveld Boskoop Aceraceae - Sycamore or Maple family Botanical Gardens University of Utrecht: Von Gimborn Arboretum Doorn Aeonium [Crassulaceae, Sempervivens family] Botanical Gardens University of Utrecht: Fort Hoofddijk Utrecht Algae Museum of Natural History Rotterdam Rotterdam Alpine plants Botanical Gardens University of Utrecht: Fort Hoofddijk Utrecht Amorphophallus [Araceae - Arum... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:59:31">http://bhl.ala.org.au/bibliography/11915</link><title>Information about 'The American Museum journal.' - Biodiversity Heritage Library</title><description>* Information about 'The American Museum journal.' - Biodiversity Heritage Library (clueweb12-1207wb-33-05268) http://bhl.ala.org.au/bibliography/11915 Information about 'The American Museum journal.' - Biodiversity Heritage Library Museum journal. Summary Details MODS BibTeX Endnote Title The American Museum journal. Related Titles Succeeding: Natural history (New York, N.Y.) Supplement: Guide leaflets (American Museum of Natural History) By American Museum of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:01:23">http://biodiversitylibrary.org/bibliography/3494</link><title>Details - Annual report of the Director to the Board of Trustees for the year ... / Field Museum of Natural History - Biodiversity Heritage Library</title><description>* Details - Annual report of the Director to the Board of Trustees for the year ... / Field Museum of Natural History - Biodiversity Heritage Library (clueweb12-0001wb-92-04297) http://biodiversitylibrary.org/bibliography/3494 Details - Annual report of the Director to the Board of Trustees for the year ... / Field Museum of Natural History \- Biodiversity Heritage Library ...Spanish Swedish Swiss German Turkish, Ottoman Ukrainian Undetermined Urdu Yiddish For: (All Contributors) Academy of Natural Sciences, Philadelphia American Museum of Natural History Library California Academy of Sciences California Academy of Sciences Library Cambridge University Library Cornell University Library Field Museum Library Harvard University Botany Libraries Harvard University, MCZ, Ernst Mayr Library Institute of Botany, CAS... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:03:22">http://www.earthstation9.com/museum12.htm</link><title>Museums</title><description>* Museums (clueweb12-0409wb-99-12930) http://www.earthstation9.com/museum12.htm Museums Museums Museums of Natural History \- Worldwide      Navigation - Links    Navigation is accomplished by using the main menu on the left. Just...menu on the left. Just click on the red help book next to the word Museums and the index will fold/unfold.    78 Agder Museum of Natural History &amp; Botanical Garden - Denmark Alaska Museum of Natural History \- Alaska American Museum of Natural History - New York Anniston Museum of Natural History - Alabama Australian... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:04:39">http://www.my-edu2.com/EDU/museum5.htm</link><title>EDU2 : Level 4</title><description>* EDU2 : Level 4 (clueweb12-1410wb-13-22807) http://www.my-edu2.com/EDU/museum5.htm EDU2 : Level 4 EDU2 :MUSEUM SCITECH ABCentral . Search . Helpers MUSEUM SUBJECT : TITLE BIOLOGY GEOLOGY MATH NATURAL HISTORY NATURAL SCIENCE NATURE PHYSICS PSYCHOLOGY SCIENCE SCIENCE US TECH MUSEUM *BIOLOGY* Abiko City Museum of Bird Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum Arthropod Museum, Dept. of Entomology, University of Arkansas BOTANICAL MUSEUM, FINNISH MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY Biohistory Research Hall Bishop Museum, Honolulu Bohart :entomology museum Botanisk Have &amp; Museum - Křbenhavns Universitet... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>