<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:18:22" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-01"><link>http://citizensh.ist-in-hamburg.de/fine-rep27/lance-armstrong-bracelet.html</link><title>Lance Armstrong Bracelet</title><description>* Lance Armstrong Bracelet (clueweb12-0007wb-68-15893) http://citizensh.ist-in-hamburg.de/fine-rep27/lance-armstrong-bracelet.html ...iron basket :: lance armstrong bracelet :: Lance Armstrong Bracelet Related tags: cycling, buy bank homes reo lance armstrong, air pollution in canada bracelet, sams casino louisiana cancer, vera wang. The november issue of runner s world will feature tour de france winner and rubber bracelet manufacturer lance armstrong on its cover armstrong, who, in the spirit of diddy and oprah. Lance armstrong and the lance armstrong foundation little yellow rubber bracelets retailing through the livestrong website and nike retailers for a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-02"><link>http://www.newsalbum.com/Celebrity/3049-Lance-Armstrong/</link><title>Lance Armstrong Latest News, Interviews, Reviews, Downloads &amp; Celebrity Photos &amp; Profile - News Album</title><description>* Lance Armstrong Latest News, Interviews, Reviews, Downloads &amp; Celebrity Photos &amp; Profile - News Album (clueweb12-1806wb-41-02438) http://www.newsalbum.com/Celebrity/3049-Lance-Armstrong/ Lance Armstrong Latest News, Interviews, Reviews, Downloads &amp; Celebrity Photos &amp; Profile - News Album ...Profile - News Album Lance Armstrong Latest News, Interviews, Reviews, Downloads &amp; Celebrity Photos &amp; Profile ...For more information of this profile try these websites http://www.lancearmstrong.com or http://lance-armstrong.com http://www.Lance.com http://www.Armstrong.com Profile Visitors607 Lance Armstrong Sun SignVirgo Lance Armstrong Feng Shui Pet Pig Lance Armstrong Age41 years. Lance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:25:34">http://www.operationgadget.com/livestrong_program/</link><title>Operation Gadget | LiveStrong Program Archives</title><description>* Operation Gadget | LiveStrong Program Archives (clueweb12-0210wb-38-12002) http://www.operationgadget.com/livestrong_program/ ...Operation Gadget Main | LiveStrong Program Archives Lance Armstrong's New Commuter Bike Shop in Austin Chris Brewer, a long-time contributor to the Livestrong...Austin, TX. Chris writes: If I told you that 7-time Tour de France winner Lance Armstrong had opened a bike shop, I’ll bet you would imagine row up on row... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:26:39">http://www.operationgadget.com/livestrong_program/index.html</link><title>Operation Gadget | LiveStrong Program Archives</title><description>* Operation Gadget | LiveStrong Program Archives (clueweb12-0511wb-72-13986) http://www.operationgadget.com/livestrong_program/index.html ...Operation Gadget Main | LiveStrong Program Archives Lance Armstrong's New Commuter Bike Shop in Austin Chris Brewer, a long-time contributor to the Livestrong...Austin, TX. Chris writes: If I told you that 7-time Tour de France winner Lance Armstrong had opened a bike shop, I’ll bet you would imagine row up on row... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:29:43">http://www.babble.com/</link><title>Lance Armstrong - FameCrawler</title><description>* Lance Armstrong - FameCrawler (clueweb12-1412wb-65-12614) http://babble.com/CS/blogs/famecrawler/archive/tags/Lance+Armstrong/default.aspx Lance Armstrong \- FameCrawler Babble.com PREGNANCY BABY TODDLER KID FOOD CELEBRITY BLOGS BABY NAMES HEALTH PHOTO CONTEST...parents, pamela anderson, celebrity moms, Nicole Richie, Sheryl Crow, Perez Hilton, Victoria Beckham, milla jovovich, Lance Armstrong, jennifer lopez, Elle Macpherson, elizabeth hurley, wyatt, jessica simpson, jessica alba, tabloid, clothing line, musician...alba, tabloid, clothing line, musician, design, paula abdul, single moms, muppets, hillary duff, jacklyn smith Lance Armstrong Dishes On The Sheryl Crow Breakup  Three years after the infamous Lance and Sheryl fairytale came to an end, Lance is finally ready to talk about the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:30:54">http://www.rogerkramercycling.org/HTML/2010/01/oprah-takes-on-distracted-driving.php</link><title>Roger Kramer Cycling: The Blog Page</title><description>* Roger Kramer Cycling: The Blog Page (clueweb12-0210wb-23-26592) http://www.rogerkramercycling.org/HTML/2010/01/oprah-takes-on-distracted-driving.php ...and other topics of the day   Oprah UPDATED (JAN. 18): The parents of Matt Wilhelm. the Champaign-Urbana area cyclist who was...world team sprint record02/17/12 19:32 from VeloNews Lance Armstrong Google feeds Lance Armstrong \- Google News » Armstrong out to conquer new mountain - Herald Sun02/17/12 15:07 from Lance Armstrong \- Google News » Was the Lance Armstrong Doping Case Whitewashed by US Attorney While ... - AllGov02/17/12 12:45 from Lance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:32:25">http://www.famoustext.com/index/tweets/user/lancearmstrong</link><title>Lance Armstrong's Twitter Tweets on FamousText! Find out what Lance Armstrong is saying! Lance Armstrong the Celebrity</title><description>* Lance Armstrong's Twitter Tweets on FamousText! Find out what Lance Armstrong is saying! Lance Armstrong the Celebrity (clueweb12-1713wb-95-00103) http://www.famoustext.com/index/tweets/user/lancearmstrong Lance Armstrong's Twitter Tweets on FamousText! Find out what Lance Armstrong is saying! Lance Armstrong the Celebrity ...Check out my custom line of hand crafted surf jewelry. http://www.stricklyboarding.com   Explore Lance Armstrong's Tweets Today's Latest Tweets Tweets today (2)  | Tweets this week (21)  |  Tell a friend Lance Armstrong Famous Celebrity RT @ReillyRick: I respect new Browns QB Brandon Weeden for his service to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:34:55">http://marriage.about.com/cs/celebritymarriages/a/lancekristin_3.htm</link><title>Lance Armstrong and Sheryl Crow Relationship Profile -- Relationship of Sheryl Crow and Lance Armstrong</title><description>* Lance Armstrong and Sheryl Crow Relationship Profile -- Relationship of Sheryl Crow and Lance Armstrong (clueweb12-0005wb-04-23862) http://marriage.about.com/cs/celebritymarriages/a/lancekristin_3.htm Lance Armstrong and Sheryl Crow Relationship Profile -- Relationship of Sheryl Crow and Lance Armstrong Lance Armstrong and Sheryl Crow RelationshipBy Sheri &amp; Bob Stritof, About.com Guides See More About:lance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:38:43">http://www.biographyshelf.com/lance_armstrong_biography.html</link><title>Biography of Lance Armstrong - biography, autobiography &amp; memoir resources</title><description>* Biography of Lance Armstrong - biography, autobiography &amp; memoir resources (clueweb12-0101wb-84-21153) http://www.biographyshelf.com/lance_armstrong_biography.html Biography of Lance Armstrong \- biography, autobiography &amp; memoir resources ...Home Browse Biographies About BiographyShelf How to write a Biography Contact Me Add to Favorites Lance Armstrong ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7138-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7138_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:39:23">http://www.thecelebrityblog.com/category/lance-armstrong/</link><title>» Lance Armstrong  The Celebrity Blog, Celebrity gossip, celebrity rumors Hollywood gossip blog</title><description>* » Lance Armstrong  The Celebrity Blog, Celebrity gossip, celebrity rumors Hollywood gossip blog (clueweb12-1203wb-64-04297) http://www.thecelebrityblog.com/category/lance-armstrong/ Lance Armstrong  The Celebrity Blog, Celebrity gossip, celebrity rumors Hollywood gossip blog Lance Armstrong and Anna Hansen Expecting a Baby Lance Armstrong and girlfriend Anna Hansen are expecting their first child together. the 37-year-old... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>