<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:26:49" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:07">http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/k</link><title>List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with k 1</title><description>* List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with k 1 (clueweb12-0304wb-66-12879) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/k List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with k 1 Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Choose a local business in Cambridge Choose a local business beginning with the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-02"><link>http://www.djrichards.com/cambridge-soundworks.htm</link><title>Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGE</title><description>* Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGE (clueweb12-1100wb-28-24381) http://www.djrichards.com/cambridge-soundworks.htm Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGECambridge SoundworksCambridge Soundworks has home theater systems, award-winning speakers, MP3 Players, and more....award-winning speakers, MP3 Players, and more.cambridge soundworks , ambridge soundworks , cmbridge soundworks , cabridge soundworks , camridge soundworks , cambidge soundworks , cambrdge soundworks , cambrige soundworks... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:33:01">http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/i</link><title>List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with i 1</title><description>* List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with i 1 (clueweb12-0304wb-56-24240) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/i List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with i 1 Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Choose a local business in Cambridge Choose a local business beginning with the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:34:23">http://www.joinbusiness.co.uk/Cambridge_c45,1.html</link><title>Companies in Cambridge, Page 1 in Business Locator</title><description>* Companies in Cambridge, Page 1 in Business Locator (clueweb12-0201wb-81-07398) http://www.joinbusiness.co.uk/Cambridge_c45,1.html Companies in Cambridge, Page 1 in Business Locator Cambridge 1 | 2 | 3 | 4 | 5 | 6 | 7 | 8 | 1. The Cambridge Conservatory Centre Ltd.Cambridge / Cambridgeshire, Conservatories2. Cambridge Health TeamCambridge / CAMBRIDGESHIRE, Social Services3. Cambridge Multimedia ComputingCambridge... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:37:04">http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/u</link><title>List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with u 1</title><description>* List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with u 1 (clueweb12-0304wb-38-12405) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/u List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with u 1 Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Choose a local business in Cambridge Choose a local business beginning with the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:39:41">http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/o</link><title>List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with o 1</title><description>* List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with o 1 (clueweb12-0304wb-21-10266) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/o List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with o 1 Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Choose a local business in Cambridge Choose a local business beginning with the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:41:40">http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/v</link><title>List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with v 1</title><description>* List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with v 1 (clueweb12-0304wb-48-08463) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/names/letter/v List of businesses in Cambridge UK beginning with v 1 Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Choose a local business in Cambridge Choose a local business beginning with the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:44:06">http://www.surfy.com/hotels/CAMBRIDGE%20MA.html</link><title>CAMBRIDGE Massachusetts Hotels - Discount and Resort - MA</title><description>* CAMBRIDGE Massachusetts Hotels - Discount and Resort - MA (clueweb12-1712wb-09-25813) http://www.surfy.com/hotels/CAMBRIDGE%20MA.html CAMBRIDGE Massachusetts Hotels - Discount and Resort - MA   CAMBRIDGE, Massachusetts Hotels - Discount and Deals - MA               Hotels for CAMBRIDGE, Massachusetts     SHERATON COMMANDER HOTEL CAMBRIDGE, ,USRates from 129.00 to 495.00 HYATT REGENCY CAMBRIDGE CAMBRIDGE, ,USRates from 69.95 to 430.00 RADISSON HOTEL CAMBRIDGE CAMBRIDGE, ,USRates from 149.95 to 189.95 INN AT HARVARD-CAMBRIDGE CAMBRIDGE, ,USRates... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-09"><link>http://www.latergater.com/cambridge-soundworks.htm</link><title>Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGE</title><description>* Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGE (clueweb12-1104wb-08-17404) http://www.latergater.com/cambridge-soundworks.htm Cambridge Soundworks stereos and electronics.  CAMBRIDGE Cambridge SoundworksCambridge Soundworks has home theater systems, award-winning speakers, MP3 Players, and more. ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7141-10"><link>http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/popularsearches</link><title>Popular Searches in Cambridge</title><description>* Popular Searches in Cambridge (clueweb12-0305wb-35-16200) http://www.touchcambridge.com/business/popularsearches Popular Searches in Cambridge Cambridge Who or What? Where? Businesses: Register or Login Cambridge Business Directory Cambridge Business Reviews Cambridge Questions Cambridge Local Community Cambridge Local Networking Cambridge Social Network Popular Searches Here you can find a list of some of the most... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>