<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:21:03" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:21:28">http://hearingaidreport.com/types-of-hearing-loss.asp</link><title>Types of Hearing Losses and Hearing Impairments</title><description>* Types of Hearing Losses and Hearing Impairments (clueweb12-0504wb-11-17519) http://www.hearingaidreport.com/types-of-hearing-loss.asp ...otolaryngologist audiological physician (doctor specialising in hearing problems) audiologist (a specialist in the testing of hearing and fitting of hearing aids) When examining a person with hearing loss, a doctor will want to know how the hearing loss has developed and what sort of problems it causes. He or she will also perform a physical examination. Tuning forks and a special electronic device with headphones (an audiometer) are used to test the degree of hearing loss. Hearing tests An audiometer... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:23:44">http://hearingaidreport.com/types-of-hearing-loss.asp?Searched=</link><title>Types of Hearing Losses and Hearing Impairments</title><description>* Types of Hearing Losses and Hearing Impairments (clueweb12-0505wb-40-26132) http://www.hearingaidreport.com/types-of-hearing-loss.asp?Searched= ...otolaryngologist audiological physician (doctor specialising in hearing problems) audiologist (a specialist in the testing of hearing and fitting of hearing aids) When examining a person with hearing loss, a doctor will want to know how the hearing loss has developed and what sort of problems it causes. He or she will also perform a physical examination. Tuning forks and a special electronic device with headphones (an audiometer) are used to test the degree of hearing loss. Hearing tests An audiometer... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:25:50">http://www.healthyhearing.com/help/hearing-loss</link><title>Hearing Loss, Loss of Hearing, About Hearing Loss, What is Hearing Loss</title><description>* Hearing Loss, Loss of Hearing, About Hearing Loss, What is Hearing Loss (clueweb12-0110wb-03-15006) http://www.healthyhearing.com/content/Hearing-loss Hearing Loss, Loss of Hearing, About Hearing Loss, What is Hearing Loss ...Reviews Other Hearing Loss Protection Test Treatments Types Other ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:26:44">http://www.hear-it.org/Headphones-and-sports-a-dangerous-cocktail-2</link><title>Headphones and sports a dangerous cocktail - hear-it.org</title><description>* Headphones and sports a dangerous cocktail - hear-it.org (clueweb12-1212wb-49-16952) http://www.hear-it.org/Headphones-and-sports-a-dangerous-cocktail-2 ...Hear Youth Medical Political Press Languages: English Deutsch Español Français Português Hearing loss...hearing problems Noise induced hearing loss a risk for truck drivers Hearing with your skin Hearing-problems not the end of the world Tinnitus on the menu Parents do not know enough about middle ear inflammation A gene that can cause hearing impairment Healthier hearing in the baby boomers Chemotherapy for testicular cancer causes hearing loss Taking care of your hearing aids Headphones and sports a dangerous cocktail Work noise to be removed by design Hybrid hearing aid... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:27:26">http://healthbridges.info/?p=1081</link><title>Western Pennsylvania Health Information » Blog Archive » Music Induced Hearing Loss Is Becoming A Big Problem</title><description>* Western Pennsylvania Health Information » Blog Archive » Music Induced Hearing Loss Is Becoming A Big Problem (clueweb12-1116wb-12-20089) http://www.healthbridges.info/?p=1081 ...Is Becoming A Big Problem Posted in Hearing Loss (MIHL)? Music Induced Hearing Loss is a disorder in which a person has been exposed to high levels of music over a prolonged period of time. People of all ages, demographics and gender may be affected by MIHL. Music Induced Hearing Loss is caused from too much sound intensity going through and into the auditory system. First, a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:29:42">http://www.bioline.org.br/request?mj02013</link><title>Bioline International Official Site (site up-dated regularly)</title><description>* Bioline International Official Site (site up-dated regularly) (clueweb12-1002wb-45-05053) http://www.bioline.org.br/request?mj02013 ...Submitted-22.5.2001, Revised-21.8.2001, Accepted-16.11.2001 Code Number: mj02013 The use of headphone has been thought to cause infection in the ear canal and contribute to hearing loss. In this study, we examined 136 Customer Service Representative from Celcom (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd. who use headphone throughout their working hours. The purpose of this study was to determine the prevalence of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:31:07">http://www.healthyhearing.com/content/articles/Hearing-loss/Causes/47555-Hearing-loss-causes-mp3-teens</link><title>Hearing Loss Causes: MP3 &amp; iPods Raises Teen Hearing Loss</title><description>* Hearing Loss Causes: MP3 &amp; iPods Raises Teen Hearing Loss (clueweb12-0510wb-80-17717) http://www.healthyhearing.com/content/articles/Hearing-loss/Causes/47555-Hearing-loss-causes-mp3-teens Hearing Loss Causes: MP3 &amp; iPods Raises Teen Hearing Loss ...over half of college students in the urban environment are at risk for noise-induced hearing loss (NIHL). "Some people, especially those using their headphones in a noisy environment, like a city street or subway, do listen at levels high enough and for durations of time that pose a risk to hearing," Fligor tells Healthy Hearing. "This is an issue that won't cause a problem immediately as it takes years to do significant damage, but once it occurs... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:34:47">http://www.merckmanuals.com/home/ear_nose_and_throat_disorders/hearing_loss_and_deafness/hearing_loss_and_deafness.html?qt=&amp;sc=&amp;alt=</link><title>Hearing Loss and Deafness: Merck Manual Home Edition</title><description>* Hearing Loss and Deafness: Merck Manual Home Edition (clueweb12-0713wb-64-02869) http://www.merckmanuals.com/home/ear_nose_and_throat_disorders/hearing_loss_and_deafness/hearing_loss_and_deafness.html?qt=&amp;sc=&amp;alt= Hearing Loss and Deafness: Merck Manual Home Edition ...in the ears (tinnitus). Sometimes people notice the ringing sound before they fully recognize their hearing loss. Causes Hearing loss has many causes. The most common cause is exposure to noise. Usually damage results after long-term exposure to loud noise, but even brief exposure to extremely loud noise can permanently harm hearing. Listening to loud music through headphones has become a common cause of hearing loss, even as industrial exposure to loud noise has been reduced. Head trauma... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:35:23">http://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/ss/slideshow-causes</link><title>Slideshow: Top Causes of Severe Hearing Loss Including Loud Noise, Disease, and Injury</title><description>* Slideshow: Top Causes of Severe Hearing Loss Including Loud Noise, Disease, and Injury (clueweb12-1900tw-23-00232) http://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/severe-hearing-loss-10/slideshow-causes Slideshow: Top Causes of Severe Hearing Loss Including Loud Noise, Disease, and Injury ...tools:Symptoms|Doctors|Medical Dictionary Hearing Loss Its Causes and Treatments Email a FriendPrint Article if (pf_param == "true") { printElements(); } Severe Hearing Loss: Its Causes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7144-10"><link>http://www.hearinglossweb.com/Medical/Causes/nihl/nihl.htm</link><title>Noise Induced Hearing Loss</title><description>* Noise Induced Hearing Loss (clueweb12-0109wb-77-05122) http://www.hearinglossweb.com/Medical/Causes/nihl/nihl.htm Noise Induced Hearing Loss ...Texas Utah Vermont Virginia Washington West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming Hearing Loss?Hearing Aid AffordabilityHearing Aids Hearing Devices Hearing Aids Reviews Causes... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>