<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:24:54" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-01"><link>http://www.na6.za.pl/_images/vicci-lewis/vice-president-s-residence.html</link><title>Vice president s residence</title><description>* Vice president s residence (clueweb12-0603wb-75-02258) http://www.na6.za.pl/_images/vicci-lewis/vice-president-s-residence.html Vice president s residence Vice president guardian group schenectady Vici o abrahamu Vicente medina sarasota Vice president s residence A lankan of pertinent work, determination, and body are titled to settle successful. You've personalized...amounting up the entire argument of preparation. Make your video soviet you should pose nearby vice president s residence causes inherently you can treat the most test in it when you marketer it. Internet... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:26:13">http://www.rbj.net/section.asp?PageID=1043</link><title>2011 RBJ Who's Who | Rochester Business Journal New York business news and information</title><description>* 2011 RBJ Who's Who | Rochester Business Journal New York business news and information (clueweb12-1109wb-79-03740) http://www.rbj.net/section.asp?PageID=1043 ...at Alfred Company address: 10 Upper College Drive, Alfred, N.Y. 14802 Website: www.alfredstate.edu Residence: Alfred Current professional board positions: Springbrook; SUNY Alfred College Council, Development Fund Board, Alumni Association and Educational Foundation Donald Bain President St. John Fisher College Company address: 3690 East Ave., Rochester, N.Y. 14618 Website: www.sjfc.edu Residence: Rochester Current professional board positions: vice president, Rochester Area Colleges President’s Council; New York State Magistrates Association; Independent Judicial Election Qualification Commission, 7th Judicial District... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:28:09">http://www.csupomona.edu/~adm_affairs/orders.shtml</link><title>Cal Poly Pomona</title><description>* Cal Poly Pomona (clueweb12-1602wb-45-00411) http://www.csupomona.edu/~adm_affairs/orders.shtml ...be accessed at: http://www.calstate.edu/eo/. Executive Orders are delegated to the campus President. If the President sub-delegates the implementation of an Executive Order to one of the...the President sub-delegates the implementation of an Executive Order to one of the campus vice presidents, the name of the vice president is listed under "Campus Delegation." Clicking on the name... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:31:00">http://students.case.edu/groups/rha/documents/constitution.html</link><title>RHA Constitution - Case Residence Hall Association</title><description>* RHA Constitution - Case Residence Hall Association (clueweb12-1302wb-04-06257) http://studentaffairs.case.edu/groups/rha/documents/constitution.html RHA Constitution - Case Residence Hall Association ...II - Mission Statement The goal of this organization shall be to strive to enrich the residence hall experience through programming, advocacy, and leadership development. ARTICLE III - General Structure RHA shall be a student-run organization representing all of the residents of Case Western Reserve University and shall be composed of councils elected by each residential community; a General Body composed of the Vice President of each Residence Hall, the President of each Community Council, the President of the Upper... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:31:45">http://www.infopig.com/keywords/President/07-21-2011-201457.html</link><title>President News - President History - Ultimate News Database</title><description>* President News - President History - Ultimate News Database (clueweb12-0202wb-65-04071) http://www.infopig.com/keywords/President/07-21-2011-201457.html ...Presidential Guards Thwart Attack on President 07/21/2011 [-] West Africa Ecowas Condemns Attack On President's Residence 07/21/2011 [-] President Koroma Returns From MRU Summit in Liberia 07/21/2011 [-] Tunisian...economic ties with Cameroon 07/21/2011 [-] Ban Condemns Attack on Residence of Guinea’s President Scoop NZ World 07/21/2011 [-] Greek PM meets European Commission president in Brussels 07/21/2011 [-] Ecuador president wins huge libel case 07/21/2011 [-] Ban Condemns Attack on Residence of Guinea's President 07/21/2011 [-] Uruguay Faces Big Challenge to Fights Poverty, Says Vice President 07/21/2011 [-] Local TV Anchor Interviews President Obama 07/21/2011 [-] VA Medical Center... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:34:48">http://people.howstuffworks.com/vice-president1.htm/printable</link><title>HowStuffWorks "Constitutional Provisions for the Vice Presidency"</title><description>* HowStuffWorks "Constitutional Provisions for the Vice Presidency" (clueweb12-0401wb-96-05978) http://people.howstuffworks.com/vice-president1.htm/printable HowStuffWorks "Constitutional Provisions for the Vice Presidency" ...Games Random Article Geography History People Vice President Works Image Gallery: U.S. Presidents John Adams, the first of the bunch. See more pictures of American presidents. Stock Montage... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:38:12">http://people.howstuffworks.com/vice-president.htm/printable</link><title>HowStuffWorks "How the U.S. Vice President Works"</title><description>* HowStuffWorks "How the U.S. Vice President Works" (clueweb12-0401wb-96-05984) http://people.howstuffworks.com/vice-president.htm/printable HowStuffWorks "How the U.S. Vice President Works" ...Science Tech Video Shows Blogs Quizzes Games Random Article Geography History People How the U.S. Vice President Worksby Josh Clark Browse the article How the U.S. Vice President Works Image Gallery... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-08"><link>http://www.sa.psu.edu/death_response/sd_admin.html</link><title>Student Affairs Guidelines for Reporting Student Deaths</title><description>* Student Affairs Guidelines for Reporting Student Deaths (clueweb12-0212wb-28-05389) http://www.sa.psu.edu/death_response/sd_admin.html ...Death] [Notification of Admin.]   Guidelines for Reporting a Student Death Notification of Police Notification of Residence Life Senior Staff Administrators Notification of parents or next of kin Notification of University Administration Notification of University Administration Section I. Student Deaths Reports of all student deaths at any Penn State campus or college should be made immediately to the designated Assistant Vice President for Student Affairs at the address shown below in Section III. Student Death Notification to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:41:54">http://www.ducksters.com/</link><title>http://www.encyclopediajr.com/wikiarticle/v/i/c/vice_president_of_the_united_states.php</title><description>* http://www.encyclopediajr.com/wikiarticle/v/i/c/vice_president_of_the_united_states.php (clueweb12-1616wb-30-12902) http://www.encyclopediajr.com/wikiarticle/v/i/c/vice_president_of_the_united_states.php ...appeal to a slightly different ideological wing of the party. The 12th Amendment discourages the Vice President from legally residing in the same state as the President, as Electors must vote for at least one candidate not in the same state as themselves. However, the ease of changing one's state of residence (as Dick Cheney did in 2000) minimizes the effect of this provision. In recent years... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7165-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7165_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:44:49">http://www.stkate.edu/mn_census/10/women-directors-and-executive-officers.html</link><title>Women in Leadership | The 2010 Minnesota Census of Women in Corporate Leadership</title><description>* Women in Leadership | The 2010 Minnesota Census of Women in Corporate Leadership (clueweb12-0305wb-33-31109) http://www.stkate.edu/mn_census/10/women-directors-and-executive-officers.html ...June 30, 2010 Company Name Directors Title Executive Officers Titles 3M Company Linda G. Alvarado President and Chief Executive Officer Alvarado Construction, Inc. Aulana L. Peters Retired Partner, Gibson, Dunn &amp; Crutcher...Construction, Inc. Aulana L. Peters Retired Partner, Gibson, Dunn &amp; Crutcher LLP Angela S. Lalor Senior Vice President, Human Resources ADC Telecommunications, Inc. Lois M. Martin Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>