<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:19:25" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:19:49">http://www.aircraftfinishing.com/forums/t/4/ekobond-glue</link><title>Stewart Systems. EkoBond Glue</title><description>* Stewart Systems. EkoBond Glue (clueweb12-1906wb-12-18904) http://www.aircraftfinishing.com/forums/t/4/ekobond-glue Stewart Systems. EkoBond Glue Fabric Finishing / EkoBond Glue EkoBond Glue Reply 1 2 Next jason gerard Status: Moderator Total Posts: 77 Joined: 8/16/2011... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:22:16">http://yaji-tex.en.alibaba.com/productgrouplist-212048496/Coated_blackout_fabric_with_black_glue.html</link><title>Coated blackout fabric with black glue direct from</title><description>* Coated blackout fabric with black glue direct from (clueweb12-1709wb-26-05274) http://yaji-tex.en.alibaba.com/productgrouplist-212048496/Coated_blackout_fabric_with_black_glue.html Coated blackout fabric with black glue direct from Fabric Coated blackout fabric with black glue Coated blackout fabric with black glue View gallery View list Show 16 32 48 items per page ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:23:05">http://www.vintageimagecraft.com/fabric-box-craft.html</link><title>Fabric Box Craft: Make this Asian Treasure Box with vintage images and simple materials.</title><description>* Fabric Box Craft: Make this Asian Treasure Box with vintage images and simple materials. (clueweb12-0305wb-64-16859) http://www.vintageimagecraft.com/fabric-box-craft.html Fabric Box Craft: Make this Asian Treasure Box with vintage images and simple materials. ...Site All about VintageImageCraft [?] Subscribe To This Site This Asian Treasure Box is an easy fabric box craft. It begins with a discarded cardboard cigar box. With some rich fabric, bangles, glue \- and expert measuring skills - you can create a true keepsake. (click for a larger Fabric Box Craft image) We openly admit: this fabric box craft idea was inspired by a 1995 Martha Stewart project. But frankly, we think... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:26:19">http://gluegun.posterous.com/rss.xml</link><title>PVA Glue</title><description>* PVA Glue (clueweb12-1800tw-08-13851) http://gluegun.posterous.com/rss.xml ...dry quickly, and create a powerful and firm bond. Due to the compounds within CA glue, it requires moisture for the glue to adequately form lasting bonds, even the smallest amount of moisture will do. CA glue comes in a variety of different thicknesses, for big projects or small, making it applicable to a wide variety of materials - beauty products, clothing and fabrics, wood, and plastics, among many others. Although CA glue is slightly more expensive than other... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:28:52">http://www.dollardays.com/wholesale-craft-glue-pg5.html</link><title>Craft Glue Wholesale - Wholesale School Glue - Clear School Glue p5 - DollarDays</title><description>* Craft Glue Wholesale - Wholesale School Glue - Clear School Glue p5 - DollarDays (clueweb12-1611wb-21-23031) http://www.dollardays.com/wholesale-craft-glue-pg5.html Craft Glue Wholesale - Wholesale School Glue - Clear School Glue p5 - DollarDays ...Wholesale Foam Glue-4 Ounces Foam Glue-4 Ounces. FIBRE CRAFT-Creative Hands SmArt Foam Glue. This glue was specially designed to be used by the little ones. It is non-toxic; dries clear; cleans with soap and water while wet and can be used on foam; wood; plastic; beads; sequins and View Larger Image SKU: 654713 /* */ Compare Wholesale Aleene's No-Sew Fabric Glue-4 Ounce Aleene's No-Sew Fabric Glue-4 Ounce. DUNCAN-Aleene's No-Sew Fabric Glue... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:29:43">http://www.1stopsquare.com/glue.html</link><title>Glue - Marker &amp; Glitter, Fabric Glue and 3D Pop Up Dots</title><description>* Glue - Marker &amp; Glitter, Fabric Glue and 3D Pop Up Dots (clueweb12-1813wb-50-13097) http://www.1stopsquare.com/glue.html Glue \- Marker &amp; Glitter, Fabric Glue and 3D Pop Up Dots Glue Pens, Glitter Glue, Fabric Glue, Glue Stick and 3D Pop Up Dots                          Craft &amp; Office Home    Punches    Xyron Laminators    Heat Tools    Tons of Craft Supplies Glue Pens, Glitter Glue, Fabric Glue, Glue Stick and 3D Pop Up Dots Glue Pens, Glitter Glue, Fabric Glue, Glue Stick and 3 D Popup Dots for  decorating memory... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-07"><link>http://www.ithow.co.uk/l/How-can-I-get-glue-off-from-fabric.shtml</link><title>How can I get glue off from fabric Tips and advice - @7For.info</title><description>* How can I get glue off from fabric Tips and advice - @7For.info (clueweb12-0200wb-74-04241) http://www.ithow.co.uk/l/How-can-I-get-glue-off-from-fabric.shtml How can I get glue off from fabric Tips and advice - @7For.info glue off from fabric document.write('So you are searching for information and advice. Sometimes we need advice to be able to find advice,the information is out there it just needs locating. We specialise in finding information to help peoplesolve a problem that they are having.Another major problem is that they do not know where , or the right search engine to use to find theinformation that they are looking for. Take for instance the search term that brought you to this page: How can I get glue off from fabric .We have not only been able to find many results for you enquiry but we will be hereif you need the information again.')We have also found the following links related to How Can I Get Glue Off From Fabric [1] [2] [3] [4] [5] [6] [7] [8] [9] [10] [11] [12] [13] [14] [15... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:34:08">http://www.bizrate.com/glue/purple-office-supplies/</link><title>Purple office supplies Glue - Compare Prices, Read Reviews and Buy at Bizrate.</title><description>* Purple office supplies Glue - Compare Prices, Read Reviews and Buy at Bizrate. (clueweb12-0010wb-88-04489) http://printers.bizrate.com/glue/purple-office-supplies/ Purple office supplies Glue \- Compare Prices, Read Reviews and Buy at Bizrate. follow us:     Digital Cameras Home &amp; Garden Clothing...more related searches: purple office supplies, purple office supply, shoe tape dispenser office depot, office glue stick, extra office glue, extra strength office glue, finger tips office supply, black shoe tape... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:39:00">http://smallstuff-digest.com/cgi-bin/archives.cgi?cf=121&amp;category=cat_fabricneedle</link><title>Small Stuff Tips Archives</title><description>* Small Stuff Tips Archives (clueweb12-1304wb-61-06494) http://smallstuff-digest.com/cgi-bin/archives.cgi?cf=121&amp;category=cat_fabricneedle ...want. If it's a fancy parasol, you can wrap narrow silk ribbon around the shaft. Glue on a pretty bead or beads for handle. Cut out a circular piece of fabric, stick the end of the shaft through the middle, and glue to hold. Then pull the fabric up and twist it to hold it tight. Glue or take a stitch around the top to hold it in place. Gather lace all... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:42:25">http://www.e-merch.com/Sitemap/Sitemap_p_h_adhesives_ENG.html</link><title>Promotional Items Database -&gt; Sitemap_p_h_office_supplies_ENG.html office supplies -&gt; adhesives - promotional articles</title><description>* Promotional Items Database -&gt; Sitemap_p_h_office_supplies_ENG.html office supplies -&gt; adhesives - promotional articles (clueweb12-0504wb-72-24891) http://www.e-merch.com/Sitemap/Sitemap_p_h_adhesives_ENG.html ...transparent, 5000White Glue transparent, 5000 g, Glues fast and strong. For use on Wood Glue 100 g,Wood Glue 100 g, Water resistant Wood Glue for Laminate flooring, parquet. Wood Glue 200 g,Wood Glue 200 g, Water resistant Wood Glue for Laminate flooring, parquet. Gemstone Glue Pen DriesGemstone Glue Pen Dries clear. Solvent free. For exact sticking of designer Textile Adhesive Fabric adhesiveTextile Adhesive Fabric adhesive is a liquid thread for joining all types Spray Glue... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>