<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:56:00" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:56:32">http://www.rightdiagnosis.com/s/spinal_cord_injury/intro.htm</link><title>Spinal cord injury Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatments and Causes - RightDiagnosis.com</title><description>* Spinal cord injury Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatments and Causes - RightDiagnosis.com (clueweb12-1009wb-59-06283) http://www.rightdiagnosis.com/s/spinal_cord_injury/intro.htm ...cord injury Intro Symptoms Types Causes Tests Prognosis Treatment Misdiagnosis Deaths Videos var ts=String.fromCharCode(60); if(wdbigad) document.write(ts+'script type="text/javascript" src="http://ad.doubleclick.net/adj/'+wd_ad_map+'sz=300x250,250x250,300x600;tile=3;pos=abovecenter1;ord=' + cachebuster + '?"&gt;'+ts+'/script&gt;'); Spinal cord injury: Introduction Symptoms Causes Treatments Misdiagnosis Home Testing Types Deaths Complications Prognosis Videos Research Statistics Stories from Users Full Contents list Spinal cord injury: Introduction Spinal cord injury: Spinal cord injury (SCI) occurs when a traumatic event results in damage to cells within the spinal cord or severs the nerve tracts that ... more about Spinal cord injury. Spinal cord injury: Spinal cord injury... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:59:44">http://www.ewitness.com/lbct/420/spinal-cord-injury.htm</link><title>Ewitness.com - (spinal cord injury) - SPINAL CORD INJURY SPECIALISTS, EXPERTS, WITNESSES &amp; FORENSIC CONSULTANTS.</title><description>* Ewitness.com - (spinal cord injury) - SPINAL CORD INJURY SPECIALISTS, EXPERTS, WITNESSES &amp; FORENSIC CONSULTANTS. (clueweb12-0109wb-40-03196) http://www.ewitness.com/lbct/420/spinal-cord-injury.htm Ewitness.com - (spinal cord injury) - SPINAL CORD INJURY SPECIALISTS, EXPERTS, WITNESSES &amp; FORENSIC CONSULTANTS. Trauma : automobile accidents, falls, gunshots, diving accidents, etc. Disease : polio, spina bifida, tumors, Friedreichs ataxia, etc. It is important to note that the spinal cord does not have to be completely severed for there to be a loss of function. In fact, the spinal cord remains intact... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:01:54">http://ilru.org/html/publications/SCI/library/VRNEP_search_for_SCI_and_Exercise_Lit.htm</link><title>Scientific Abstracts: Part One</title><description>* Scientific Abstracts: Part One (clueweb12-0001wb-86-11142) http://ilru.org/html/publications/SCI/library/VRNEP_search_for_SCI_and_Exercise_Lit.htm ...to see this abstract as a 24 page Word document. | Pulmonary management following acute SCI. (spinal cord injury) Journal of Neuroscience Nursing; April 1, 1998; Lucke, Kathleen T. ... phase following spinal cord...doc1.asp?DOCID=1G1:15842389&amp;num=14&amp;ctrlnfo=Round9c%3AProd%3ASR%3AResult&amp;ao= Aging with spinal cord injury. Paraplegia News; April 1, 1991; Roth, Elliot J. ... of aging with a spinal cord injury. Thus, there ... bullet severed his spinal cord. He wasn't given ... one with such an injury was, at that time ... and his father exercised the boy's legs ... Midwest Regional Spinal Cord Injury Care System, Rehabilitation ... http://www.highbeam.com/library/doc1.asp?DOCID=1G1:10668672&amp;num... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:04:11">http://www.floridalawsuits.com/PersonalInjury/CatastrophicInjuries/SpinalCordInjuries.aspx</link><title>Spinal Cord Injuries Explained by Florida Medical Malpractice and Personal Injury Attorney</title><description>* Spinal Cord Injuries Explained by Florida Medical Malpractice and Personal Injury Attorney (clueweb12-1814wb-47-20985) http://www.floridalawsuits.com/PersonalInjury/CatastrophicInjuries/SpinalCordInjuries.aspx Spinal Cord Injuries Explained by Florida Medical Malpractice and Personal Injury Attorney ...can also result from various diseases present at birth or acquired later in life. Other spinal cord injuries results from tumors or electric shock. Also, accidents resulting in the loss of oxygen related to surgical or underwater mishaps can cause spinal cord injuries. How Spinal Cord Injuries Occur  It is not necessary for the spinal cord to be severed in order for symptoms to appear. Injuries can occur when the spinal cord is crushed... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:05:15">http://www.accident-injury-claim-compensation.org/spinal_injury/index.htm</link><title>Spinal Injury Web Directory</title><description>* Spinal Injury Web Directory (clueweb12-1904wb-13-18856) http://www.accident-injury-claim-compensation.org/spinal_injury/index.htm ...Scaffolding Accident Sexual Assault Silicosis Skin Disease Slip Fall Claim Small Claims Court Solicitor Online Spinal Cord Injury Sports Injury Train Accident Vibration Injury Claim Vibration White Finger Victim Support Link Whiplash...of the American Spinal Injury Association is: It was out of this group the American Spinal Injury Association (ASIA) was created in 1973. Spinal Cord Injury Functional ...   Understanding Spinal Cord Injury &amp; Functional Goals. Please take Rev. 1996. [Available from: American Spinal Injury Association. Online ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:06:44">http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/spinal%20cord%20injuries.html</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog</title><description>* Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog (clueweb12-0901wb-50-10803) http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/spinal%20cord%20injuries.html ...20 in the online edition of Nature Neuroscience, the findings suggest that the regeneration of severed nerve fibers is not required for paraplegic rats to learn to walk again. The finding may hold implications for human rehabilitation after spinal cord injuries."The spinal cord contains nerve circuits that can generate rhythmic activity without input from the brain to drive... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:09:22">http://www.stemcellnetwork.ca/index.php?page=spinal-cord-injury&amp;hl=fra</link><title>About Spinal Cord Injury - RĂŠseau de cellules souches</title><description>* About Spinal Cord Injury - RĂŠseau de cellules souches (clueweb12-1900wb-83-01853) http://www.stemcellnetwork.ca/index.php?page=spinal-cord-injury&amp;hl=fra About Spinal Cord Injury - RĂŠseau de cellules souches ...on a telephone wire speeds up the electrical signals and protects the nerves. If the spinal cord is injured, many nerve fibre bundles are severed. In a severed nerve, the proximal axon is still connected to the cell body, but the distal axon... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:11:15">http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/spinal%20cord.html</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog</title><description>* Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog (clueweb12-0901wb-50-10805) http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/spinal%20cord.html ...20 in the online edition of Nature Neuroscience, the findings suggest that the regeneration of severed nerve fibers is not required for paraplegic rats to learn to walk again. The finding may hold implications for human rehabilitation after spinal cord injuries."The spinal cord contains nerve circuits that can generate rhythmic activity without input from the brain to drive... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:13:15">http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/nerves.html</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog</title><description>* Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog (clueweb12-0900wb-14-16166) http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/nerves.html Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog ...Article. Posted here by Matthew at 12:47 PM Spinal Cord Injury A cure for spinal injuries that leave people paralyzed, currently incurable, is being developed by Researchers at Northwestern University in Chicago. They are looking into using new nanotechnology that could enable them to completely heal cut and severed spinal cords allowing the previously paralyzed to walk again.Spinal cord injury often leads to permanent... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:14:33">http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/scar%20tissue.html</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog</title><description>* Spinal Cord Injury Information Pages News Blog (clueweb12-0906wb-29-13948) http://www.sci-info-pages.com/labels/scar%20tissue.html ...Injury Information Pages News Blog Spinal Cord Injury News. Information and resources for those with spinal cord injuries. Spinal Cord Injury A cure for spinal injuries that leave people paralyzed, currently incurable, is being developed by Researchers at Northwestern University in Chicago. They are looking into using new nanotechnology that could enable them to completely heal cut and severed spinal cords allowing the previously paralyzed to walk again.Spinal cord injury often leads to... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>