<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:05:35" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:05:51">http://mysbfiles.stonybrook.edu/~levinger/publications.htm</link><title>http://mysbfiles.stonybrook.edu/~levinger/publications.htm</title><description>* http://mysbfiles.stonybrook.edu/~levinger/publications.htm (clueweb12-1812wb-63-21732) http://mysbfiles.stonybrook.edu/~levinger/publications.htm IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE Selected Evinger Lab Publications and Links Clicking on the underlined names will...J. Neurophysiol. 52: 323-339, 1984 PubMed             Manning, K.A. and Evinger, C.  Different forms of blinks and their two-stage control.  Exp. Brain Res. 64: 579-588, 1986 Pub Med             Evinger, C., Sibony, P.A., Manning, K.A. and Fiero, R.A.  A pharmacological distinction between the long and short latency pathways of the human blink reflex revealed with tobacco  Exp. Brain Res. 73: 477-480, 1988 PubMed Delgado-GarciaJM, Evinger C... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:06:35">http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blinked</link><title>blinked - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia.</title><description>* blinked - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. (clueweb12-0908wb-97-00468) http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blinked blinked \- Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. word='blink';WordListHost='w1.thefreedictionary.com';SAYT.Tab=1024 Printer Friendly Dictionary, Encyclopedia and Thesaurus - The...with Text Translate() Dictionary/thesaurusMedicaldictionaryLegaldictionaryFinancialdictionaryAcronyms IdiomsEncyclopediaWikipediaencyclopedia? blink (redirected from blinked)    Also found in: Dictionary/thesaurus, Medical, Encyclopedia, Wikipedia 0.01 sec. social.leftcol('This site:','This page:','Share:'); OnThisPage('On this page','Translations','Thesaurus','Word Browser') blink...unbowedbloodybloody but unbowedbloody mindedbloom  Bling-blingBlinged-Out CabbagebliniBlinisblinkblinkblinkblinkblinkBlink 182blink atblink atblink awayblink backblink backblink backBlink beerBlink comparatorBlink Microscopeblink of an eyeBlink of an Eye (Voyager episode)Blink reflexBlink reflexBlink reflexblink responseblink responseblink responseblink tears backBlink-eyedBlinkard blinkedblinked atblinked atblinked atblinked backblinked... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:08:51">http://jnnp.bmj.com/content/67/3/379.full</link><title>Unmasking of the trigemino-accessory reflex in accessory facial anastomosis -- Esteban and Prieto 67 (3): 379 -- Journal of Neurology, Neurosurgery &amp; Psychiatry</title><description>* Unmasking of the trigemino-accessory reflex in accessory facial anastomosis -- Esteban and Prieto 67 (3): 379 -- Journal of Neurology, Neurosurgery &amp; Psychiatry (clueweb12-1013wb-19-13986) http://jnnp.bmj.com/content/67/3/379.full Unmasking of the trigemino-accessory reflex in accessory facial anastomosis -- Esteban and Prieto 67 (3): 379 -- Journal of Neurology, Neurosurgery &amp; Psychiatry...January 1999 Accepted 5 March 1999 Â Next Section Abstract OBJECTIVE To evaluate the possible blink reflex responses in facial muscles reinnervated by the accessory nerve. METHOD Eleven patients with a complete facial palsy were submitted to a surgical repair by an accessory facial nerve anastomosis (AFA). In this pathological group, blink reflex was studied by means of percutaneous electrical stimulation of the supraorbital nerve and recording from... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:10:48">http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink+tears+back</link><title>blink tears back - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia.</title><description>* blink tears back - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. (clueweb12-0909wb-18-23210) http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink+tears+back blink tears back - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. word='blink tears back';WordListHost='w1.thefreedictionary.com';SAYT.Tab=1024 Printer Friendly Dictionary, Encyclopedia and...with Text Translate() Dictionary/thesaurusMedicaldictionaryLegaldictionaryFinancialdictionaryAcronyms IdiomsEncyclopediaWikipediaencyclopedia? blink tears back     0.01 sec. social.leftcol('This site:','This page:','Share:'); OnThisPage('On this page','Translations','Thesaurus','Word Browser') blink one's tears backFig. to try to keep from...mindedbloom  Bling blingBling ChainsBling-blingBling-blingBlinged-Out CabbagebliniBlinisblinkblinkblinkblinkblinkBlink 182blink atblink atblink awayblink backblink backblink backBlink beerBlink comparatorBlink Microscopeblink of an eyeBlink of an Eye (Voyager episode)Blink reflexBlink reflexBlink reflexblink responseblink responseblink response blink tears backBlink-eyedBlinkardblinkedblinkedblinkedblinkedblinked atblinked atblinked at... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:12:52">http://www.thefreedictionary.com/blink+of+an+eye</link><title>blink of an eye - definition of blink of an eye by the Free Online Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia.</title><description>* blink of an eye - definition of blink of an eye by the Free Online Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. (clueweb12-0303wb-04-24060) http://www.thefreedictionary.com/blink+of+an+eye blink of an eye - definition of blink of an eye by the Free Online Dictionary, Thesaurus...blink of an eye - definition of blink of an eye by the Free Online Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. word='blink of an eye';WordListHost='w1.thefreedictionary.com';SAYT.Tab=1 Printer Friendly Dictionary, Encyclopedia...BlingBlingBling blingBling ChainsBling-blingBling-blingBlinged-Out CabbagebliniBlinisblinkblinkblinkblinkblinkBlink 182blink atblink atblink awayblink backblink backblink backBlink beerBlink comparatorBlink Microscope blink of an eyeBlink of an Eye (Voyager episode)Blink reflexBlink reflexBlink reflexblink responseblink responseblink responseblink tears backBlink-eyedBlinkardblinkedblinkedblinkedblinkedblinked atblinked atblinked at... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:15:31">http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink</link><title>blink - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia.</title><description>* blink - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. (clueweb12-0909wb-18-23207) http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink ...BlingBlingBling blingBling ChainsBling-blingBling-blingBlinged-Out CabbagebliniBlinis blinkBlink 182blink atblink atblink awayblink backblink backblink backBlink beerBlink comparatorBlink Microscopeblink of an eyeBlink of an Eye (Voyager episode)Blink reflexBlink reflexBlink reflexblink responseblink responseblink responseblink tears backBlink-eyedBlinkardblinkedblinkedblinkedblinkedblinked atblinked atblinked atblinked backblinked back  Idioms and... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:17:43">http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink+at</link><title>blink at - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia.</title><description>* blink at - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. (clueweb12-0909wb-18-23208) http://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/blink+at blink at - Idioms - by the Free Dictionary, Thesaurus and Encyclopedia. word='blink at';WordListHost='w1.thefreedictionary.com';SAYT.Tab=1024 Printer Friendly Dictionary, Encyclopedia and Thesaurus...BlingBlingBling blingBling ChainsBling-blingBling-blingBlinged-Out CabbagebliniBlinisblinkblinkblinkblinkblinkBlink 182 blink atblink awayblink backblink backblink backBlink beerBlink comparatorBlink Microscopeblink of an eyeBlink of an Eye (Voyager episode)Blink reflexBlink reflexBlink reflexblink responseblink responseblink responseblink tears backBlink-eyedBlinkardblinkedblinkedblinkedblinkedblinked atblinked atblinked atblinked backblinked... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:19:03">http://www.biglist.com/lists/stella/archives/200409/maillist.html</link><title>Stella Archives by Date : Date Index</title><description>* Stella Archives by Date : Date Index (clueweb12-0100wb-87-20687) http://www.biglist.com/lists/stella/archives/200409/maillist.html ...-0000 Surround disassembly, Dennis Debro - 20 Sep 2004 15:59:51 -0000 BitHacker Updated, Edwin Blink \- 19 Sep 2004 20:50:42 -0000 Re: [stella] Jumpman: Beginner Levels, David Galloway - 19...Jumpman: Easy Does It, Manuel Rotschkar - 16 Sep 2004 16:26:09 -0000 RE: [stella] Reflex: Online level editor, Thomas Jentzsch - 16 Sep 2004 15:13:14 -0000 RE: [stella] Reflex... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-09"><link>http://www.blepharospasm.org/2002hallett.html</link><title>Pathophysiology of blepharospasm and hemifacial spasm</title><description>* Pathophysiology of blepharospasm and hemifacial spasm (clueweb12-0101wb-03-07683) http://www.blepharospasm.org/2002hallett.html ...inhibitory projections to the LP motoneurons, bilaterally. This is the appropriate circuitry for the trigeminal blink reflex, which should occur with orbicularis oculi contraction and levator inhibition. There has been a new...and voluntary blinking is not well known. There have been detailed investigations, however, of the blink reflex. Most commonly, the reflex is elicited with electrical stimulation of the supraorbital nerve. The OO blink reflex consists of two components: an early, first response (R1) and a late, second response (R2... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7180_10.ksh" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:22:32">http://pleiad.dcc.uchile.cl/_export/raw/research/software/reflex/documentation/behavioral_links_blinks</link><title>http://pleiad.dcc.uchile.cl/_export/raw/research/software/reflex/documentation/behavioral_links_blinks</title><description>* http://pleiad.dcc.uchile.cl/_export/raw/research/software/reflex/documentation/behavioral_links_blinks (clueweb12-1416wb-61-30262) http://pleiad.dcc.uchile.cl/_export/raw/research/software/reflex/documentation/behavioral_links_blinks ...relation between the hookset and the metaobject definition. Links are the most important element of Reflex. They have a serie of attributed related to: the cardinality of the relation, the protocol...behavioral link: control, scope, activation, mintypes, updatable, declared type and initialization. ===== Control ===== Description:\\\ The [[http://reflex.dcc.uchile.cl/svn/base/trunk/src/reflex/api/link/attribute/Control.java|Control]] attribute... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>