<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7194">hobcaw barony</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:38:42" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:38:58">http://www.elowcountry.com/events</link><title>Elowcountry - South Carolina</title><description>* Elowcountry - South Carolina (clueweb12-1716wb-37-20584) http://www.elowcountry.com/events ...6 ((Habitat for Humanity of Georgetown County)     May 12, 2012 Bike to the Boardwalk at Hobcaw Barony Bike through Hobcaw’s forest to the Reserves beautiful saltmarsh boardwalk on North Inlet. Meet Reserve staff in the Hobcaw Barony Discovery Center parking lot and bike 2.5 miles (each way) on gravel roads to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-02"><link>http://www.hobcawbarony.org/Tours.Programs.html</link><title>The Belle W. Baruch Foundation</title><description>* The Belle W. Baruch Foundation (clueweb12-1502wb-82-10941) http://www.hobcawbarony.org/Tours.Programs.html ...Horse Firefly Watch Program Earth Day Open House Southern Cemeteries Paint Out with Bill Griffin Hobcaw Photo Safari Hobcaw Beach Wildlife Landscaping SC Jews of Camden Wild Wednesday: Snakes, Gators, Skins...Beginners Series True Blue, An Indigo Workshop Nature Camp Are You Firewise? Boater Education Class Hobcaw Fly Fishing Adventure We offer many tours and programs throughout the year.  Please read below or click the links to the right to start your adventure today! Tours of Hobcaw Barony (Year Round) This three hour van tour requires little walking but includes highlights of Hobcaw's history. Once eleven plantations, the property was bought in 1905-07 by Bernard Baruch, native... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:41:35">http://artsandsciences.sc.edu/seoe/Research-3.php</link><title>School of Earth, Ocean and Environment - University of South Carolina</title><description>* School of Earth, Ocean and Environment - University of South Carolina (clueweb12-1604wb-43-23645) http://www.cas.sc.edu/seoe/Research-3.php ...Institutes Baruch Institute | ESRI-SC Faculty &amp; Staff Directory | Faculty Bylaws News &amp; Events RESEARCH HIGHLIGHT Hobcaw Barony Discovery Center Opens New Era Wendy B. Allen The Belle W. Baruch Institute for...educational opportunities. This is about to change with the recent opening of the new Hobcaw Barony Discovery Center on the Belle W. Baruch Foundation property near Georgetown, S.C.the location of USCs Baruch Marine Field Laboratory and the North InletWinyah Bay National Estuarine Research Reserve (NIWB NERR). The Hobcaw Barony Discovery Center is a 13,500-squarefoot, joint-use education facility of the NIWB... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:42:58">http://events.myrtlebeachonline.com/georgetown_sc/venues/show/827810-hobcaw-barony</link><title>Hobcaw Barony in Georgetown, SC 29440 - The Sun News</title><description>* Hobcaw Barony in Georgetown, SC 29440 - The Sun News (clueweb12-1504wb-30-02207) http://events.myrtlebeachonline.com/georgetown_sc/venues/show/827810-hobcaw-barony Hobcaw Barony in Georgetown, SC 29440 - The Sun News ...venuesrestaurantsperformers Home | Register | Log In Zvents.tracker.notifyAdView('venue:827810'); Hobcaw Barony Hobcaw Barony Hobcaw Rd, Georgetown, SC, 29440 (843) 546-4623 - Venue Website A... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:44:43">http://www.dailygamecock.com/news/item/2907-etv-airs-documentary-on-the-baruchs-of-hobcaw</link><title>ETV airs documentary on 'The Baruchs of Hobcaw'</title><description>* ETV airs documentary on 'The Baruchs of Hobcaw' (clueweb12-0806wb-75-12924) http://www.dailygamecock.com/news/item/2907-etv-airs-documentary-on-the-baruchs-of-hobcaw ETV airs documentary on 'The Baruchs of Hobcaw' ...Film highlights history of preserved coastland now vital to USC researchers Hobcaw Barony, a 17,500 acre nature preserve near Georgetown, South Carolina, is not...work is environmental success stories, and that is one part of the Hobcaw story because Belle Baruch saved Hobcaw Barony from development and preserved it for education and research. [She] was an... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-06"><link>http://www.hobcawbarony.org/Research.html</link><title>The Belle W. Baruch Foundation</title><description>* The Belle W. Baruch Foundation (clueweb12-1503wb-12-11185) http://www.hobcawbarony.org/Research.html ...ProposalMemorandum to Individuals Interested in Conducting Research on Hobcaw Barony Thank you for your interest in conducting research on Hobcaw Barony. As you may know, Hobcaw Barony has been a site for world class research since...proposal review process to better tract research activities on Hobcaw Barony. The process is designed to reduce the potential for... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:46:33">http://www.northinlet.sc.edu/education/programs.html</link><title>Public Programs: North Inlet-Winyah Bay National Estuarine Research Reserve</title><description>* Public Programs: North Inlet-Winyah Bay National Estuarine Research Reserve (clueweb12-1807wb-60-14017) http://www.northinlet.sc.edu/education/programs.html ...W. Baruch Foundationâs 17,500 acre wildlife preserve, Hobcaw Barony, near Georgetown, SC. Public access to the Reserve and Hobcaw Barony is limited, but much of the Reserve can be accessed by water and visitors are welcome to enjoy and help conserve the resources of North Inlet and Winyah Bay.Â  The Hobcaw Barony Discovery Center (located at the entrance to Hobcaw Barony... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7194_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:48:08">http://www.lfip.org/laws602s2012/withpropertyvisit.htm</link><title>Without property Visit</title><description>* Without property Visit (clueweb12-1708wb-84-16851) http://www.lfip.org/laws602s2012/withpropertyvisit.htm ...for Marine &amp; Coastal Sciences (Baruch Marine Lab) just outside Georgetown, SC on the Hobcaw Barony. A 17,500 acre research reserve, Hobcaw Barony is one of the few undeveloped tracts on the Waccamaw Neck. The Hobcaw Barony is a major protected area on the South Carolina coast, and as such... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-09"><link>http://www.hobcawbarony.org/History.HB.html</link><title>The Belle W. Baruch Foundation</title><description>* The Belle W. Baruch Foundation (clueweb12-1502wb-82-10940) http://www.hobcawbarony.org/History.HB.html The Belle W. Baruch FoundationHobcaw Barony A 17, 500 acre research reserve, Hobcaw Barony is one of the few undeveloped tracts on the Waccamaw Neck.  The Native Americans called it "hobcaw," meaning between the waters.  In 1718, the land became a colonial land grant, a barony.  Sold and subdivided into plantations extending from... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7194-10"><link>http://www.hobcawbarony.org/BWB.html</link><title>The Belle W. Baruch Foundation</title><description>* The Belle W. Baruch Foundation (clueweb12-1502wb-90-06175) http://www.hobcawbarony.org/BWB.html ...a sailor, equestrian and pilot. She called Hobcaw Barony the "friendliest woods in the world," and always wanted to have a home here. In 1935, Belle bought the first section of Hobcaw Barony and purchased portions continuously until she owned all 17,500 acres. Belle used Hobcaw much in the same way her father... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>