<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:28:12" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-01"><link>http://https://guttmacher.org/pubs/journals/2603600.html</link><title>Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey?</title><description>* Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? (clueweb12-0309wb-75-09673) http://https://guttmacher.org/pubs/journals/2603600.html Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? , , , Authors: " /&gt; ...STATE CENTERPUBLICATIONS  International Family Planning Perspectives Volume 26, Number 1, March 2000 Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? By Nuriye Ortayli, Aysen Bulut, Hacer Nalbant and Jane Cottingham Context: In Turkey, where contraceptive prevalence is about 65%, a large number of couples rely on withdrawal and the IUD... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:30:21">http://www.guttmacher.com/pubs/journals/2603600.html</link><title>Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey?</title><description>* Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? (clueweb12-0510wb-20-26189) http://www.guttmacher.com/pubs/journals/2603600.html Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? , , , Authors: " /&gt; ...STATE CENTERPUBLICATIONS  International Family Planning Perspectives Volume 26, Number 1, March 2000 Is the Diaphragm a Viable Option for Women in Turkey? By Nuriye Ortayli, Aysen Bulut, Hacer Nalbant and Jane Cottingham Context: In Turkey, where contraceptive prevalence is about 65%, a large number of couples rely on withdrawal and the IUD... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-03"><link>http://www.clarimed.com/medical-devices-categories/contraceptive-diaphragms-accessories</link><title>Overview of Contraceptive Diaphragms and Accessories</title><description>* Overview of Contraceptive Diaphragms and Accessories (clueweb12-1101wb-53-04377) http://www.clarimed.com/medical-devices-categories/contraceptive-diaphragms-accessories Overview of Contraceptive Diaphragms and Accessories Contraceptive Devices › Contraceptive Diaphragms &amp; Accessories Contraceptive Diaphragms &amp; Accessories ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:34:05">http://www.moondragon.org/obgyn/contraception/diaphragm.html</link><title>MoonDragon's ObGyn Health Information: Contraception: Diaphragm</title><description>* MoonDragon's ObGyn Health Information: Contraception: Diaphragm (clueweb12-1316wb-24-26107) http://www.moondragon.org/obgyn/contraception/diaphragm.html MoonDragon's ObGyn Health Information: Contraception: Diaphragm MoonDragon's Contraception Information DIAPHRAGM CONTRACEPTION For "Informational Use Only".For more detailed information, contact your...MoonDragon's ObGyn Health Information: Contraception: Diaphragm MoonDragon's Contraception Information DIAPHRAGM CONTRACEPTION For "Informational Use Only".For more detailed information, contact your health care provider about...trying to enter the uterus and killing sperm before they can fertilize an egg. When contraceptive spermicide gel or cream is used with the diaphragm, its efficiency is significantly increased since the spermicide kills any sperm that may get past the rim of the diaphragm. The spermicide is place around the rim and some is included in the dome part of the diaphragm, coating the diaphragm. Cervical Cap VS Diaphragm placement. Studies involving some 2,800 U.S. women... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:35:16">http://www.quickoverview.com/reproductive/diaphragm-contraceptive.html</link><title>Diaphragms - The contraceptive that is a cervical barrier creating a seal against the wall of the vagina.</title><description>* Diaphragms - The contraceptive that is a cervical barrier creating a seal against the wall of the vagina. (clueweb12-0916wb-97-26215) http://www.quickoverview.com/reproductive/diaphragm-contraceptive.html Diaphragms \- The contraceptive that is a cervical barrier creating a seal against the wall of the vagina. QuickOverview when there is no time to surf Home About Contribute Search Diaphragms diaphragm is a cervical barrier type of birth control. It is a soft latex or silicone...creates a seal against the walls of the vagina. Use Anyone inserting or removing a diaphragm should first wash their hands, to avoid introducing harmful bacteria into the vaginal canal. The... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-06"><link>http://https://www.dred.com/uk/contraceptive-diaphragm.html</link><title>The Contraceptive Diaphragm - Advantages &amp; Disadvantages</title><description>* The Contraceptive Diaphragm - Advantages &amp; Disadvantages (clueweb12-1302wb-15-03790) http://https://www.dred.com/uk/contraceptive-diaphragm.html The Contraceptive Diaphragm \- Advantages &amp; Disadvantages ...Travel MedicineOther Services Medicines dispensed by Regulated by CareQualityCommission Provider ID – 1-201500907 Contraceptive diaphragm Dr. Jasper Mordhorst DrEd Medical Director The contraceptive diaphragm is a small, dome-shaped cup made of rubber or silicone that covers the cervix... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:38:23">http://www.summitmedicalgroup.com/library/womens_health/diaphragm/</link><title>Summit Medical Group - Diaphragm</title><description>* Summit Medical Group - Diaphragm (clueweb12-0603wb-73-06032) http://www.summitmedicalgroup.com/library/womens_health/diaphragm/ Summit Medical Group - Diaphragm ...Page Digg Reddit LinkedIn Facebook Delicious StumbleUpon Twitter Live Well Library &gt;  Women's Health Advisor &gt;  Diaphragm View image What is a diaphragm? The diaphragm is a dome-shaped rubber cup with a flexible rim. It is used to help prevent pregnancy. Before intercourse the diaphragm is filled with a contraceptive cream or jelly and inserted into the vagina. The contraceptive cream or jelly contains a spermicide, a chemical that kills sperm. The diaphragm covers the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:40:36">http://www.childrenshealthnetwork.org/CRS/CRS/pa_diaphm_wha.htm</link><title>Pediatric Advisor 2011.4: Diaphragm: Teen Version</title><description>* Pediatric Advisor 2011.4: Diaphragm: Teen Version (clueweb12-0109wb-38-02537) http://www.cpnonline.org/CRS/CRS/pa_diaphm_wha.htm Pediatric Advisor 2011.4: Diaphragm: Teen Version Diaphragm: Teen Version diaphragm? The diaphragm is a dome-shaped rubber cup with a flexible rim. It is used to help prevent pregnancy. Before intercourse the diaphragm is filled with a contraceptive cream or jelly and put into the vagina. The contraceptive cream or jelly contains a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:43:04">http://www.ihacares.com/index.cfm/HealthAdvisors/WomensHealthAdvisor/crs-wha-hhg_diaphragm/</link><title>Diaphragm - IHACares</title><description>* Diaphragm - IHACares (clueweb12-1714wb-63-03248) http://www.ihacares.com/index.cfm/HealthAdvisors/WomensHealthAdvisor/crs-wha-hhg_diaphragm/ ...Office or Doctor Search DiaphragmPrintableDiaphragm \- IHACares crs-wha-hhg_diaphragm birth control contraception contraceptive diaphragm family planning intercourse pregnancy prevention sex sexual intercourse vaginal diaphragm Women's Health Advisor 2009.3 © 2009 RelayHealth and/or its affiliates. All Rights Reserved... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:44:21">http://www.merckmanuals.com/home/womens_health_issues/family_planning/contraception.html?qt=&amp;sc=&amp;alt=</link><title>Contraception: Family Planning: Merck Manual Home Edition</title><description>* Contraception: Family Planning: Merck Manual Home Edition (clueweb12-0713wb-94-07856) http://www.merckmanuals.com/home/womens_health_issues/family_planning/contraception.html?qt=&amp;sc=&amp;alt= ...Tooth Injury Wounds In This Topic Women's Health Issues Family Planning Contraception Hormonal Methods Oral Contraceptives Skin Patches and Vaginal Rings Contraceptive Implants Contraceptive Injections Emergency Contraception Barrier Contraceptives Spermicides Intrauterine...Women's Health Issues Family Planning Contraception Hormonal Methods Oral Contraceptives Skin Patches and Vaginal Rings Contraceptive Implants Contraceptive Injections Emergency Contraception Barrier Contraceptives Spermicides Intrauterine Devices Timing Methods Natural Family Planning... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>