<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7200">uss stennis</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:12:56" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:13:12">http://synergeez.com/military-art/s1.php</link><title>Synergeez Naval Art</title><description>* Synergeez Naval Art (clueweb12-0010wb-21-24657) http://synergeez.com/military-art/s1.php ...carrier USS Iowa USS Iowa USS Iowa BB61 USS Iowa BB61 USS Iowa BB 61 USS Iowa BB 61 USS Iowa pics USS Iowa pics USS Iowa picture USS Iowa picture USS Iowa pictures USS Iowa pictures USS Iowa photo USS Iowa photo USS Iowa photos USS Iowa photos USS Iowa photographs USS Iowa photographs USS Iowa battleship USS Iowa battleship USS John C Stennis USS John C Stennis USS John C Stennis CVN74 USS John C Stennis CVN74 USS... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:13:41">http://www.uscarriers.net/cvn74history.htm</link><title>USS John C. Stennis (CVN 74) history</title><description>* USS John C. Stennis (CVN 74) history (clueweb12-0702wb-96-13727) http://www.uscarriers.net/cvn74history.htm USS John C. Stennis (CVN 74) history USS JOHN C. STENNIS CVN 74    U.S. Carriers  |  Decommissioned  |  Links  |  Info  |  Deployments  |  History     On March 13, 1991, the keel for the seventh Nimitz-class aircraft carrier John C. Stennis was laid. The ship is named in honor of John Cornelius Stennis of Mississippi who served in the Senate from 1947 to 1989. No previous ships have... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:15:58">http://synergeez.com/military-art/ss-1-13.php</link><title>Synergeez Naval Art</title><description>* Synergeez Naval Art (clueweb12-0010wb-36-02424) http://synergeez.com/military-art/ss-1-13.php ...ships: USS Iowa USS Iowa USS Iowa BB61 USS Iowa BB61 USS Iowa BB 61 USS Iowa BB 61 USS Iowa pics USS Iowa pics USS Iowa picture USS Iowa picture USS Iowa pictures USS Iowa pictures USS Iowa photo USS Iowa photo USS Iowa photos USS Iowa photos USS Iowa photographs USS Iowa photographs USS Iowa battleship USS Iowa battleship USS John C Stennis USS John C Stennis USS John C Stennis CVN74 USS John C Stennis CVN74 USS... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:18:11">http://www.stennis.gov/programs/aircraft-carriers/37-connecting-carriers-and-congress-pco-program?showall=1</link><title>Connecting Carriers and Congress - PCO Program</title><description>* Connecting Carriers and Congress - PCO Program (clueweb12-0905wb-62-10263) http://www.stennis.gov/programs/aircraft-carriers/37-connecting-carriers-and-congress-pco-program?showall=1 ...have questions about the program please contact: Mary DewaldPhone: (202) 546-1837Email: mary@stennis.gov Other Programs Aircraft CarriersCivil Military Leadership ProgramCongress to CampusEmerging Congressional Staff...CarriersCivil Military Leadership ProgramCongress to CampusEmerging Congressional Staff Leaders ProgramLifting LeadersStennis Congressional Staff Fellows ProgramStennis Program for Congressional InternsStennis Student CongressTruman Scholars Day on Capitol HillStudent Public Service Leaders ProgramsWomen's Leadership InitiativesNational Issues Forums Search Sitemap &gt; Bookmark var addthis_pub = 'adlit'; Print E-mail Past Events USS EISENHOWER Award Winners Visit DC February 14, 2012 - February 15, 2012 Washington, D.C. PCO Luncheon... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:19:31">http://www.public.navy.mil/surfor/cds21/Pages/JCSSG.aspx</link><title>Strike Group Three</title><description>* Strike Group Three (clueweb12-0804wb-43-26181) http://www.public.navy.mil/surfor/cds21/Pages/JCSSG.aspx ...2011-2012 Commander, Carrier Strike Group (CCSG) 3, with its embarked air wing (CVW 9), USS Mobile Bay (CG 53), and Destroyer Squadron Twenty-one, which includes USS Pinckney (DDG 91), USS Kidd (DDG 100), USS Dewey (DDG 105) and USS Wayne E. Meyer (DDG 108).   Stennis CSG Deployment 2011 News Articles COMDESRON TWO ONEJohn C. Stennis Carrier Strike Group returns from deploymentSAN DIEGO â The John C. Stennis Carrier Strike Group... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:20:20">http://blog.seattlepi.com/thebigblog/2012/03/02/photo-gay-kiss-marks-homecoming-of-bremerton-aircraft-carrier/</link><title>PHOTOS: Gay kiss marks homecoming of Bremerton aircraft carrier | Seattle's Big Blog - seattlepi.com</title><description>* PHOTOS: Gay kiss marks homecoming of Bremerton aircraft carrier | Seattle's Big Blog - seattlepi.com (clueweb12-0600tw-00-15622) http://blog.seattlepi.com/thebigblog/2012/03/02/photo-gay-kiss-marks-homecoming-of-bremerton-aircraft-carrier/ ...Jewell, E5, with a kiss after Jewell returned from a seven month deployment aboard the USS Stennis on Friday, March 2, 2012 in Bremerton, Wash. The USS Stennis returned to its home port in Bremerton Friday, completing a seven-month deployment in which...more photos of the kiss and the return of the carrier. .hdn_slideshow { background: #848484; } .hdn_slideshow h2, .hdn_slideshow .extra { color: #FFF; } 1 of 29 | Share USS John C. Stennis aircraft carrier returns ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:22:19">http://www.stennis.gov/programs/aircraft-carriers/37-connecting-carriers-and-congress-pco-program?start=1</link><title>Connecting Carriers and Congress - PCO Program - Prospective Commanding Officers Program Participants</title><description>* Connecting Carriers and Congress - PCO Program - Prospective Commanding Officers Program Participants (clueweb12-0905wb-55-19240) http://www.stennis.gov/programs/aircraft-carriers/37-connecting-carriers-and-congress-pco-program?start=1 ...CarriersCivil Military Leadership ProgramCongress to CampusEmerging Congressional Staff Leaders ProgramLifting LeadersStennis Congressional Staff Fellows ProgramStennis Program for Congressional InternsStennis Student CongressTruman Scholars Day on Capitol HillStudent Public Service Leaders ProgramsWomen's Leadership InitiativesNational Issues Forums Search Sitemap &gt; Bookmark var addthis_pub = 'adlit'; Print E-mail Past Events USS EISENHOWER Award Winners Visit DC February 14, 2012 - February 15, 2012 Washington, D.C. PCO Luncheon... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:24:19">http://www.hullnumber.com/CVN-74</link><title>http://www.hullnumber.com/CVN-74</title><description>* http://www.hullnumber.com/CVN-74 (clueweb12-0506wb-71-14363) http://www.hullnumber.com/CVN-74 USS JOHN C. STENNIS (CVN-74) Deployments &amp; History USS JOHN C. STENNIS (CVN-74) Look Ahead Click to view crew list   USS John C. Stennis (CVN-74) keel was laid at Newport News Ship Building and Dry... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:25:21">http://www.synergeez.com/military-art/ss1-uss-John-C-Stennis-74-03.php</link><title>USS John C Stennis</title><description>* USS John C Stennis (clueweb12-0602wb-53-09106) http://www.synergeez.com/military-art/ss1-uss-John-C-Stennis-74-03.php USS John C Stennis John C Stennis If you are looking for more information on USS John C Stennis, you can find out more at the following link: USS John C Stennis. Another way to find information on USS John C Stennis is by going to the following related resources. USS John C Stennis Searching for USS... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7200-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7200_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:26:21">http://www.synergeez.com/military-art/ss1-uss-John-C-Stennis-carrier-74-13.php</link><title>USS John C Stennis carrier</title><description>* USS John C Stennis carrier (clueweb12-0602wb-53-09107) http://www.synergeez.com/military-art/ss1-uss-John-C-Stennis-carrier-74-13.php USS John C Stennis carrier USS John C Stennis carrier If you are looking for more information on USS John C Stennis carrier, you can find out more at the following link: USS John C Stennis carrier. Another way to find information on USS John C Stennis carrier is by going to the following related resources. USS John C Stennis carrier Searching... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>