<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:33:15" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:33:49">http://www.iie.tpu.ru/en/2_legalization_countries.php</link><title>List of countries. IIE&amp;LC TPU</title><description>* List of countries. IIE&amp;LC TPU (clueweb12-0203wb-23-29539) http://www.iie.tpu.ru/en/2_legalization_countries.php ...Legalization of educational documents &gt; List of countries List of countries Country Legalization Ground Australia Apostille Hague Convention Austria Apostille Hague Convention Azerbaijan No legalization Agreement on legal redress Albania No legalization Agreement on legal redress Algeria No legalization Agreement on legal redress Andorra Apostille Hague Convention Antigua and Barbuda Apostille Hague Convention Argentina Apostille Hague Convention Armenia No legalization Agreement on legal redress Bahamas Apostille Hague Convention Barbados Apostille Hague Convention... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-02"><link>http://www.haguedv.org/resources/bibliography-archive.html</link><title>Bibliography Archive - The Hague Domestic Violence Project</title><description>* Bibliography Archive - The Hague Domestic Violence Project (clueweb12-0911wb-45-22979) http://www.haguedv.org/resources/bibliography-archive.html Bibliography Archive - The Hague Domestic Violence Project Hague Domestic Violence Project Home The Hague Convention and domestic violence About the Hague Domestic Violence Project Domestic violence defined Our staff and volunteers Special thanks Mothers What Victims Should Know About The Hague Convention Information on the Hague Convention Attorneys who consult on Hague Convention cases Resources for survivors of domestic violence Using your computer to seek domestic violence... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:35:05">http://www.vitalcertificates.co.uk/browse-legalisation-services-by-country-29-c.asp</link><title>Browse Legalisation Services by Country</title><description>* Browse Legalisation Services by Country (clueweb12-1712wb-24-26021) http://www.vitalcertificates.co.uk/browse-legalisation-services-by-country-29-c.asp ...T U V W X Y Z Afghanistan Afghanistan is not a member of the Hague Convention and requires both UK and consular legalisation before documents can be presented in Afghanistan. To legalise documents for use in Afghanistan, please contact us for an individual quotation. Back to Top Albania Albania is a member of the Hague Convention and therefore will accept documents issued in the UK that have been legalised by adding... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-04"><link>http://www.haguedv.org/resources/bibliography.html</link><title>Bibliography - The Hague Domestic Violence Project</title><description>* Bibliography - The Hague Domestic Violence Project (clueweb12-0911wb-53-27962) http://www.haguedv.org/resources/bibliography.html Bibliography - The Hague Domestic Violence Project Hague Domestic Violence Project Home The Hague Convention and domestic violence About the Hague Domestic Violence Project Domestic violence defined Our staff and volunteers Special thanks Mothers What Victims Should Know About The Hague Convention Information on the Hague Convention Attorneys who consult on Hague Convention cases Resources for survivors of domestic violence Using your computer to seek domestic violence... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-05"><link>http://www.haguedv.org/resources/national-international.html</link><title>National and International Publications - The Hague Domestic Violence Project</title><description>* National and International Publications - The Hague Domestic Violence Project (clueweb12-0911wb-42-18634) http://www.haguedv.org/resources/national-international.html National and International Publications - The Hague Domestic Violence Project Hague Domestic Violence Project Home The Hague Convention and domestic violence About the Hague Domestic Violence Project Domestic violence defined Our staff and volunteers Special thanks Mothers What Victims Should Know About The Hague Convention Information on the Hague Convention Attorneys who consult on Hague Convention cases Resources for survivors of domestic violence Using your computer to seek domestic violence... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:38:26">http://www.ftia.org/faqs-hague.asp</link><title>Families Thru International Adoption</title><description>* Families Thru International Adoption (clueweb12-0111wb-71-03824) http://www.ftia.org/faqs-hague.asp ...Get Started Links Newsletter   China Hague Convention on Protection of Children andCo-operation in Respect of Intercountry Adoption Hague Convention on Protection of Children and Co-operation in Respect of Intercountry Adoption (Hague Convention) that is effective in the United States as of April 1, 2008. What is the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:39:31">http://www.cptech.org/ecom/jurisdiction/hague.html</link><title>CPTech's Page on the Hague Convention on Jurisdiction and Foreign Judgments in Civil and Commercial Law</title><description>* CPTech's Page on the Hague Convention on Jurisdiction and Foreign Judgments in Civil and Commercial Law (clueweb12-0103wb-23-10365) http://www.cptech.org/ecom/jurisdiction/hague.html CPTech's Page on the Hague Convention on Jurisdiction and Foreign Judgments in Civil and Commercial Law CPTech's Page on the Hague Conference on Private International Law's Convention on Jurisdiction and Foreign Judgments in Civil and Commercial Matters Convention of 30 June 2005 on choice of court agreement. Answers to frequently asked questions regarding Convention, as of November 8, 2005: Note: No country has signed it yet. Status of the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:40:07">http://referenceworks.brillonline.com/browse/foreign-law-guide</link><title>INTERNATIONAL CONVENTIONS AND TREATIES    International agreements</title><description>* INTERNATIONAL CONVENTIONS AND TREATIES    International agreements (clueweb12-1012wb-71-13857) http://www.foreignlawguide.com/sample/internationalconventionsandtreaties.htm ...reprinted at 16 International journal of marine and coastal law 335 (2001). Benelux intellectual property convention. Benelux convention on intellectual property. The Hague, 25 Feb 2005. In force 1 Sep 2006. Full text with explanatory notes at http://www.boip.int/. French text, with rules, at http://www.wipo.int/wipolex/. This is an entirely new convention governing designs and trademarks. Consolidates, replaces and repeals the Benelux designs convention of 1962. The... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:41:27">http://www.adoptiononline.com/intercountry_adoption_from_hague_convention_and_non-hague_convention_countries.html</link><title>Intercountry Adoption from Hague Convention and Non-Hague Convention Countries</title><description>* Intercountry Adoption from Hague Convention and Non-Hague Convention Countries (clueweb12-0304wb-50-05971) http://www.adoptiononline.com/intercountry_adoption_from_hague_convention_and_non-hague_convention_countries.html Intercountry Adoption from Hague Convention and Non-Hague Convention Countries Hague Convention and Non-Hague Convention Countries   Introduction Comparison of Adoptions From Convention vs. Non-Convention Countries Frequently Asked Questions Resources for further information Introduction The process for adopting a child... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7242-10"><link>http://https://www.legallanguage.com/resources/treaties/hague/hague-faq/</link><title>The Hague Conventions: FAQ</title><description>* The Hague Conventions: FAQ (clueweb12-0204wb-76-30224) http://https://www.legallanguage.com/resources/treaties/hague/hague-faq/ The Hague Conventions: FAQ ...Witnesses Find Private Investigators Find US Process Servers Hague Conventions » Frequently Asked Questions on Hague Conventions Frequently Asked Questions on Hague Conventions Q. What is the “Hague Conference on Private International Law”? A. The Hague Conference on Private International Law is an intergovernmental organisation, the purpose of which is “to... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>