<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:10:16" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:10:48">http://www.rocketswag.com/animal/reptile/alligator/Largest-Alligator-Ever-Recorded.html</link><title>Largest Alligator Ever Recorded</title><description>* Largest Alligator Ever Recorded (clueweb12-1415wb-05-11109) http://www.animalamigo.com/reptile/alligator/Largest-Alligator-Ever-Recorded.html Largest Alligator Ever Recorded Ever RecordedLargest Alligator Ever Recordedalligators are located in southeastern US, but they are also found in coastal regions of North...but typically grow to a length of thirteen feet. However, there have been reports of alligators growing longer than this. The largest alligator ever recorded was nineteen feet and two inches in length.alligator was found in Marsh Islands located in the state of Louisiana in the year 1890... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:11:35">http://simmonsholdings.com/created-what-is-a-alligator-pitbull/</link><title>Alligator stuffed animal :: alligator stuffed animal</title><description>* Alligator stuffed animal :: alligator stuffed animal (clueweb12-1615wb-21-13185) http://simmonsholdings.com/created-what-is-a-alligator-pitbull/ ...cut outbelarus alligator experience in ncalligator shoes new jerseypackers vs bears rivalry alligator tee shirtsalligator photosdiablo relays mother saves child from alligator crocodileamphibious tractor the alligatorfishing alligator alley floridawhite alligator stuttgartalligator jaws whipped creamthe largest alligator in the worldizod alligator logoalligator in flint creektransfusion reaction how to keep a alligator lizardrecord alligator gar in oklahomaalligator pepperalligator coloring sheetwhitworths sunny raisins how does an... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:13:08">http://www.public-criminal-records.org/Mississippi/Alligator/</link><title>Alligator Public Criminal Records</title><description>* Alligator Public Criminal Records (clueweb12-1700wb-80-09934) http://www.public-criminal-records.org/Mississippi/Alligator/ ...Alligator Public Records and Crimianl Search for people in the local Alligator area. ... Alligator Marriage Records: Alligator Divorce Records: Alligator Criminal Report http://www.recordsbase.com/resources/public-records/mississippi/bolivar/alligator...Safescreener Pre-Employment and Tenant Screening $$ http://recordsproject.com/county/florida/alachua.asp The Florida Alligator 1105 W University Ave Gainesville, FL ... Public Records; Court Records; Criminal Records; Birth Records; Death Records; Marriage Records http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alligator According to the 2005 Scholastic Book of World Records, Louisiana is the state with the largest alligator population. The majority of American alligators inhabit Florida ... http://www.public-criminal-records.org/Mississippi/Greenville/ Free Greenville, Texas public records... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:14:03">http://www.musicianguide.com/biographies/1608003272/Bruce-Iglauer.html</link><title>Bruce Iglauer Biography</title><description>* Bruce Iglauer Biography (clueweb12-0203wb-02-11936) http://www.musicianguide.com/biographies/1608003272/Bruce-Iglauer.html ...Born on July 10, 1947, in Cincinnati, OH. Education: Attended Lawrence College, Appleton, WI. Addresses: Record company--Alligator Records, P.O. Box 60234, Chicago, IL 60660, website: http://www.alligator.com. Alligator Records, Bruce Iglauer was a major force behind the American blues revival of the 1980s and 1990s. He made Alligator Records the world's largest independent blues music label, as well as one of the largest and most successful independent... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-05"><link>http://www.mushroommusic.com.au/catalogues/international/34/eyeball-music-small-scale-music</link><title>Mushroom Music Publishing :: Catalogues</title><description>* Mushroom Music Publishing :: Catalogues (clueweb12-0209wb-80-20428) http://www.mushroommusic.com.au/catalogues/international/34/eyeball-music-small-scale-music ...lined up to spread the word. NATIONAL RECOGNITION With a catalog of over 200 titles, Alligator Records is the largest independent blues label in the world. Its recordings have won more awards than any other contemporary blues label, including a total of 34 Grammy? nominations (two wins), 18 Indie Awards from the Association For Independent Music (AFIM) and three Grand Prix du Disque awards. Alligator and its artists have won a total of 70 W.C. Handy Blues Awards, the blues... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-06"><link>http://www.chacha.com/topic/crocodile</link><title>Crocodile Questions, Answers, News, Images and Info | ChaCha</title><description>* Crocodile Questions, Answers, News, Images and Info | ChaCha (clueweb12-0406wb-24-04136) http://www.chacha.com/topic/crocodile ...on ChaCha Mobile for Crocodile In the Last: Day | Week | Month What is bigger, an alligator or a crocodile? The crocodile is bigger than the alligator. The crocodile can... Which are bigger a crocodile or alligator? Crocodiles can reach over 15.9 ft long and weigh well over 2,... What is the largest crocodile on record? The only reliable record of length for the largest crocodile ... What is the biggest crocodile ever caught? The largest crocodile ever held is a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:17:43">http://www.rocketswag.com/animal/reptile/alligator/index.html</link><title>Difference Between A Crocodile And An Alligator , Alligator And Laws In Florida</title><description>* Difference Between A Crocodile And An Alligator , Alligator And Laws In Florida (clueweb12-1412wb-91-28429) http://www.animalamigo.com/reptile/alligator/index.html ...Pets alligator look very similar and often people mistake one for the other, there is a difference between them. For starters, crocodile belongs to the crocodylidae family, and the alligator along with the caiman belongs to the alligatoridae family. More... Alligator And Laws In Florida Largest Alligator Ever Recorded What Do Alligators Eat ? What Type Of Bird Does Alligators Eat ?   ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:19:30">http://es.willyfogg.com/d108/M/Blues/</link><title>Blues / Música</title><description>* Blues / Música (clueweb12-0002wb-44-03537) http://es.willyfogg.com/d108/M/Blues/ ...its origins from the Mississippi Delta to its amplification in Chicago rig ... USD 18.98 Alligator Records The Jazz &amp; Blues Lover's Guide To The U.S. Where did Charlie Parker first play with Dizzy Gillespie? What are the coolest clubs in Chicago? Which city has the largest jazz museum? Where is Howlinâ Wolf buried? The answers can be found in The... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-09"><link>http://www.myakkariver.org/index.php/wildlife/alligator-faq</link><title>Myakka River State Park - Alligator FAQ</title><description>* Myakka River State Park - Alligator FAQ (clueweb12-0201wb-63-13530) http://www.myakkariver.org/index.php/wildlife/alligator-faq Myakka River State Park - Alligator FAQ ...Fishing Hiking Horse Trail Camping &amp; Cabins Tram Safari Picnics &amp; Pavilions Wildlife Myakka Animals Myakka Plants Alligator FAQ Animal List Plant List Ecology About the River Invasive Plants Cogongrass Study Cogongrass Links... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:22:00">http://de.willyfogg.com/d108/Musik/Blues/</link><title>Blues / Musik</title><description>* Blues / Musik (clueweb12-0002wb-44-03525) http://de.willyfogg.com/d108/Musik/Blues/ ...categories. They're all here, including Delta ... USD 16.98Preis: USD 16.98Versand: Frei Alligator Records Blues with a Feeling The Little Walter Story Blues with a Feeling explores the life...in modern blues. Beginning in th ... USD 24.98Preis: USD 24.98Versand: Frei Alligator Records All Music Guide to the Blues Designed for devoted blues lovers and newcomers alike, this... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>