<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:47:18" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-01"><link>http://gpvdb.nl/forum/cache/image/comment-131.htm</link><title>Elvish Lyrist (Core Set - Eighth Edition)</title><description>* Elvish Lyrist (Core Set - Eighth Edition) (clueweb12-1815wb-39-15290) http://gpvdb.nl/forum/cache/image/comment-131.htm Elvish Lyrist (Core Set - Eighth Edition) Elvish Linguistic Fellowship There a new Elvish is Linguistics email list, PBIS Website called, amazingly enough, business Local the Elvish. If you are trying Phuket to figure out how to say Indian your name in Elvish,. - Similar pages The languages were the first thing Tolkien created for his mythos, starting with what he originally called... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-02"><link>http://sci-fi.lovetoknow.com/fantasy-literature/lord-rings-elvish-dictionary</link><title>Lord of the Rings Elvish Dictionary</title><description>* Lord of the Rings Elvish Dictionary (clueweb12-1101wb-77-23420) http://sci-fi.lovetoknow.com/fantasy-literature/lord-rings-elvish-dictionary ...a J. R. R. Tolkien fan in the market for a Lord of the Rings Elvish dictionary, you may be surprised to learn there are a variety of resources to choose from. Even with the aid of a dictionary, whether or not the language can be used as a spoken language is a debated topic. Elvish Language While Tolkien is attributed with writing several languages as part of developing his fictional worlds, the Elvish languages developed for his stories includes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:49:35">http://www.elvish.org/gwaith/faq.htm</link><title>FAQ</title><description>* FAQ (clueweb12-0109wb-25-01839) http://www.elvish.org/gwaith/faq.htm ...tattoo or wedding ring "translated" in the "runes" of the One Ring. What about the Elvish letters? What are the Tengwar? How do I learn the Elvish scripts? How can I write Elvish on my PC? How do I write with the fonts? The result doesn't look right! Where can I learn how to say basic phrases? (Hello, Goodbye...) What languages did Tolkien use as his model? How are those words pronunced? Where can I find... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:51:11">http://masterman535.hubpages.com/hub/Learn-to-Speak-Elvish</link><title>Learn to Speak Elvish</title><description>* Learn to Speak Elvish (clueweb12-1911wb-71-32276) http://masterman535.hubpages.com/hub/Learn-to-Speak-Elvish ...or flag jq(document).ready(function() {displaySocialButtons({'pagepath' : '/hub/education-and-science/linguistics/applied-linguistics/Learn-to-Speak-Elvish'});});By Masterman535 See all 2 photos An Elf Â So you're curious about Elvish?Â  Well, then you've come to the right place to learn to speak Elvish.Â  This is the Elvish based on J.R.R. Tolkien's Middle Earth, so don't complain that this isn't Elvish as you know it.Â  There are countless authors who try to make a language, but none are as complete as the linguistic picture that J.R.R. Tolkien provides us. Here... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:52:41">http://www.classbrain.com/artmovies/publish/article_83.shtml</link><title>Exploring Elvish with Tolkien</title><description>* Exploring Elvish with Tolkien (clueweb12-0111wb-71-24474) http://www.classbrain.com/artmovies/publish/article_83.shtml ...Student Film Opportunities The History Channel Language   Exploring Elvish with Tolkien By Cynthia Kirkeby Aug 25, 2006, 12:24 PST Email this article  Printer friendly page Elvish writing (ďż˝ 2001 New Line Productions, photograph courtesy New Line Cinema) Subject  - Foreign Language Keywords  - Learning elvish, Tolkien languages, Tolkien's elvish language, elvish pronunciation guide, Quenya, Amanye Tenceli, writing Elvish, Tengwar, Elvish... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:53:50">http://folk.uib.no/hnohf/artlang.htm</link><title>Artificial Languages</title><description>* Artificial Languages (clueweb12-0608wb-87-21664) http://www.uib.no/People/hnohf/artlang.htm Artificial Languages Artificial Languages by Robert Isenberg taH pagh taHbe'. DaH mu'tlheghvam vIqelnIS. quv'a', yabDaq San vaQ...type of system is strictly artificial as long as no one speaks it, and a language as soon as people do.           For the sake of itself does not mean that the language has no purpose, but that its goal is not first and foremost an ideological one. Languages generated for ideological purposes are similar but ultimately different. In the case of Klingon and Elvish, they initially serve literary purposes, but in both cases their roles are often self-serving... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:55:06">http://www.tolkien-archives.com/library/essays/introduction-the-artificial-language-in-context.html</link><title>The Tolkien Archives - Artificial Languages by Robert Isenberg</title><description>* The Tolkien Archives - Artificial Languages by Robert Isenberg (clueweb12-0300wb-41-23942) http://www.tolkien-archives.com/library/essays/introduction-the-artificial-language-in-context.html The Tolkien Archives - Artificial Languages by Robert Isenberg ...type of system is strictly artificial as long as no one speaks it, and a language as soon as people do.           For the sake of itself does not mean that the language has no purpose, but that its goal is not first and foremost an ideological one. Languages generated for ideological purposes are similar but ultimately different. In the case of Klingon and Elvish, they initially serve literary purposes, but in both cases their roles are often self-serving... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7261_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:55:57">http://www.ambar-eldaron.com/ardalambion/artlang.htm</link><title>Artificial Languages</title><description>* Artificial Languages (clueweb12-1309wb-31-17228) http://www.ambar-eldaron.com/ardalambion/artlang.htm Artificial Languages Langages artificiel par Robert Isenberg   taH pagh taHbe'. DaH mu'tlheghvam vIqelnIS. quv'a', yabDaq San vaQ...type of system is strictly artificial as long as no one speaks it, and a language as soon as people do.           For the sake of itself does not mean that the language has no purpose, but that its goal is not first and foremost an ideological one. Languages generated for ideological purposes are similar but ultimately different. In the case of Klingon and Elvish, they initially serve literary purposes, but in both cases their roles are often self-serving... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-09"><link>http://www.all-science-fair-projects.com/science_fair_projects_encyclopedia/Elvish_language</link><title>Science Fair Projects - Elvish language</title><description>* Science Fair Projects - Elvish language (clueweb12-1600wb-22-22534) http://www.all-science-fair-projects.com/science_fair_projects_encyclopedia/Elvish_language Science Fair Projects - Elvish language ...choosing any of the categories below. Science Fair Project Encyclopedia Contents Page languages Elvish languages (Redirected from Elvish language) Elvish languages are constructed languages used typically by elves in a fantasy setting. Contents showTocToggle("show","hide") 1 Elvish languages of Middle-earth 1.1 Pronunciation 2 Other Elvish languages 3 External links Elvish languages of Middle-earth Author J. R. R. Tolkien created many languages for Elves to complement... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7261-10"><link>http://www.warofthering.net/forums/archive/index.php/t-10637.html</link><title>Master's degree [Archive] - War of the Ring Community</title><description>* Master's degree [Archive] - War of the Ring Community (clueweb12-0711wb-31-23342) http://www.warofthering.net/forums/archive/index.php/t-10637.html Master's degree [Archive] - War of the Ring Community War of the Ring Community &gt; Bag End &gt; Language &gt; Master's degree PDA View Full Version : Master's degree AlectoMarch 18th,2011, 08:06 PM...personal definition of the words ;) NB: in the following questionnaire, I will use the word Ť Elvish ť for the Elvish languages. 1  If you know a foreign language: did studying a foreign language help you with the learning of Elvish? 2  Compared to the foreign languages that you may have learnt, what are the differences and the similarities with Elvish? 3  Do you think Elvish can be compared to Esperanto concerning invented languages? Why? 4  Sociolinguists talk about blank language... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>