<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:53:37" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:54:03">http://www.johndclare.net/cold_war1_answer.htm</link><title>Who was to blame for the Cold War?</title><description>* Who was to blame for the Cold War? (clueweb12-1111wb-09-09323) http://www.johndclare.net/cold_war1_answer.htm Who was to blame for the Cold War? Causes of the Cold War is an examination topic, and you can read about The Causes of the Cold War in a dispassionate kind of way in your textbooks.    IF YOU ARE BORING, that is... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:55:01">http://www.netessays.net/viewpaper/5154.html</link><title>Free Essays</title><description>* Free Essays (clueweb12-0603wb-01-00761) http://www.netessays.net/viewpaper/5154.html ...Religion   Science   Sports   Technology   Message Board   Link To NetEssays.net Login:   Login Here! Featured Papers causes of the cold war" target=_blank&gt;the causes of the cold war 3123 Causes of the Cold War" target=_blank&gt;Causes of the Cold War 601 Cold War" target=_blank&gt;Cold War 2250 Cold war" target=_blank&gt;Cold war 507 Cold War and Post Cold War Worlds" target=_blank&gt;Contrast the Cold War and Post Cold War Worlds 1527 Causes of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:56:00">http://www.factbites.com/topics/Cold-War</link><title>Cold war - Factbites</title><description>* Cold war - Factbites (clueweb12-0406wb-09-27924) http://www.factbites.com/topics/Cold-War Cold war - Factbites Where results make senseAbout us   |   Why use us?   |   Reviews   |   PR   |   Contact us...Union and the United States, supported by their military alliance partners. This period began the Cold War in 1947 and continued until the change in leadership for both superpowers in 1953 - from Presidents Truman to Eisenhower for the United States and from Stalin to Khrushchev in the Soviet Union. However, the proximate cause for the end of the Cold War was ultimately Mikhail Gorbachev's decision, publicized in 1988, to repudiate the Brezhnev doctrine. en.wikipedia... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:57:04">http://www.johndclare.net/cold_warA1.htm</link><title>Origins of the Cold War 1945-49</title><description>* Origins of the Cold War 1945-49 (clueweb12-1111wb-00-25995) http://www.johndclare.net/cold_warA1.htm ...Truman Doctrine and the Marshall Plan; the Berlin Blockade and its immediate consequences.       Contents: Hot War/ Cold War Causes Yalta and Potsdam Hiroshima Salami tactics Fulton Truman Doctrine/ Marshall Plan Berlin Blockade Self-test 1945-1949 Korean War  Khrushchev and Peaceful Co-existence     Plus: Revision sheet Hard-copy booklet Exemplar AQA Assessment Exemplar... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:57:43">http://www.essaygalaxy.com/topics/history/c.htm</link><title>Essay Galaxy - World History: C</title><description>* Essay Galaxy - World History: C (clueweb12-0111wb-92-18590) http://www.essaygalaxy.com/topics/history/c.htm ...David Accord13215Canada 28013Canada And Nato6913Canada At War9974Canada In WWI24049Canada- Facts And Figures956335Canadian And...Of The American Civil W17567Causes Of The American Civil W7373Causes Of The American Revolut10504Causes Of The Civil War7683Causes Of The Civil War19628Causes Of The Civil War19568Causes Of The Civil War 215996Causes Of The Civil War 317207Causes Of The Cold War6153Causes Of The First World War280611Causes Of The French Revolutio... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-06"><link>http://org.newtrier.k12.il.us/library/teacher_assignments/worldwar2coldwar.htm</link><title>World War II &amp; Cold War</title><description>* World War II &amp; Cold War (clueweb12-0007wb-32-14328) http://org.newtrier.k12.il.us/library/teacher_assignments/worldwar2coldwar.htm World War II &amp; Cold War ...World War II &amp; Cold War War II &amp; Cold War Mr. Kaifez   BOOKS--also use New Trier Library Catalog Reference Books WW...1947-1997), Paul Auster (b. 1947). See Literature Resource Center and Gale Virtual Ref Library COLD WAR 1\. Explain how the Korean War showed the escalation so characteristic of the Cold War?  Escalation is when one side's action causes a heightened or more intense response from the other side. Post War America: see section on Containment see also: U.S. Enters the Korean Conflict 2. Explain how... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 00:02:19">http://www.infojug.com/history-articles/summary-of-the-cold-war-causes-and-effects.html</link><title>Summary of the Cold War - Causes and Effects</title><description>* Summary of the Cold War - Causes and Effects (clueweb12-0102wb-00-25546) http://www.articleswave.com/history-articles/summary-of-the-cold-war-causes-and-effects.html Summary of the Cold War - Causes and Effects Wars  Summary of the Cold War - Causes and Effects Cold War - Causes and Effects The wars end but the story of malevolence continues! As history says, the aftermaths of the First... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-08"><link>http://www.podshow411.net/stories/176992/Cold_War_L_multilanguage_2006.html</link><title>Untitled document</title><description>* Untitled document (clueweb12-0709wb-49-07090) http://www.podshow411.net/stories/176992/Cold_War_L_multilanguage_2006.html PodShow411 - Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) Cold War (L) [multilanguage] (2006) ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-09"><link>http://alartecnica.pt/seguranca/uploadfiles/media/article1515.html</link><title>The Civil War</title><description>* The Civil War (clueweb12-0306wb-96-30729) http://alartecnica.pt/seguranca/uploadfiles/media/article1515.html The Civil War of civil war exploration of one of the bloodiest and most costly Videos Top Speed...Abubakar A. Atofarati of the Nigerian Twist Top Short Sleeve - Women's Army, examining the causes of the war, the strategies employed SongMeanings | lyrics | Queen - Keep Passing The Open Windows by the belligerents,. The issues that caused the Civil War had been brewing since the United States was formed. The most important causes Southerners listed for the war were. In post-Cold War era, civil wars' causes misunderstood Post-colonial conflicts in small, weak states more to blame... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 00:04:43">http://www.bestrussiantour.com/cold_war_faq</link><title>BiG FAQ about Cold War - who won the cold war, what caused the cold war, who was involved in the cold war and etc.</title><description>* BiG FAQ about Cold War - who won the cold war, what caused the cold war, who was involved in the cold war and etc. (clueweb12-0104wb-26-26977) http://www.bestrussiantour.com/cold_war_faq BiG FAQ about Cold War \- who won the cold war, what caused the cold war, who was involved in the cold war and etc. ...Jet FAQ about North Pole Facts about North Pole Russian battlefield tours FAQ FAQ about Cold War Team Building in Russia For Agencies Impressions of our 小lients Contact Us ... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>