<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:07:55" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-01"><link>http://vibiv.com/img/custom/thumbs/icons/raccnae.html</link><title>\- Garlic Reduces Acne - Acne-n-Redness Pimples &amp; Tricks</title><description>* \- Garlic Reduces Acne - Acne-n-Redness Pimples &amp; Tricks (clueweb12-0011wb-10-00757) http://vibiv.com/img/custom/thumbs/icons/raccnae.html Garlic Reduces Acne - Acne-n-Redness Pimples &amp; Tricks Redness In Pimples Red Alert - Measures To How Get Rid Jumpman23.com: The official You are here: Minimally Pimples.com.sg Forum Home &gt; Discussion Forums &gt; Redness of face. Redness of face. Topic Title, Replies, Views, Latest Post Info. How to reduce redness and pimples... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-02"><link>http://homeremediesforacneonline.com/how-to-reduce-the-redness-of-pimples</link><title>How To Reduce The Redness Of Pimples</title><description>* How To Reduce The Redness Of Pimples (clueweb12-0500tw-35-05600) http://homeremediesforacneonline.com/how-to-reduce-the-redness-of-pimples How To Reduce The Redness Of Pimples AcneAcne Remdies InfoContactAboutPrivacy PolicyDisclamerHome Remedies For Acne Subscribe by: RSS Acne RemediesHow To Get Rid Of BlackheadsHow To Get Rid Of AcneHow To Get Rid Of PimplesHome Remedies For Red Inflamed AcneAcne Scar RemovalAcne Scar TreatmentHow To Get Rid Of Acne ScarsHome Remedies... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:09:49">http://www.typef.com/acne-redness/rss/</link><title>How to Be Confident With Acne</title><description>* How to Be Confident With Acne (clueweb12-1019wb-12-10866) http://www.typef.com/acne-redness/rss/ typeF.com Acne Redness http://www.typef.com/acne-redness/ en-US Is Toner Good for Red Acne Scars...typeF.com Acne Redness http://www.typef.com/acne-redness/ en-US Is Toner Good for Red Acne Scars? http://www.typef.com/article/toner...you could just use something in your home to free yourself from blemishes.]]&gt; How to Reduce Redness From Acne in Less Than 10 Minutes http://www.typef.com/article/reduce-redness-acne-less-10-minutes/ Mon, 31 Oct 2011 09:08:13 -0700 http://www.typef.com/article/reduce-redness-acne-less-10-minutes/ Redness from acne can be seriously maddening, especially if you have major face time coming up at work... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:10:48">http://www.acnemagazine.com/how-to-reduce-the-redness-of-a-pimple-fast/</link><title>How to Reduce the Redness of a Pimple Fast | Acne Magazine</title><description>* How to Reduce the Redness of a Pimple Fast | Acne Magazine (clueweb12-1201tw-23-10763) http://www.acnemagazine.com/how-to-reduce-the-redness-of-a-pimple-fast/ How to Reduce the Redness of a Pimple Fast | Acne Magazine Acne Magazine All About Acne and How to Treat This Skin Condition Home Acne Cosmetics Acne Home Remedies Acne News var _gaq = _gaq || []; _gaq.push(['_setAccount', 'UA-30380921-1']); _gaq.push(['_trackPageview']); (function() { var ga = document.createElement('script'); ga.type = 'text/javascript'; ga.async = true; ga.src = ('https:' == document.location.protocol ? 'https://ssl' : 'http://www') + '.google-analytics.com/ga.js'; var s = document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0]; s.parentNode.insertBefore(ga, s); })(); Red Acne Lesion How to Reduce the Redness of a Pimple Fast If You Drink Coffee, Drink Lemon Water to Counteract... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:11:36">http://www.natural-homeremedies.org/blog/how-to-reduce-acne-redness/</link><title>How To Reduce Acne Redness - Ways To Reduce Acne Redness | Home Remedies, Natural Remedy</title><description>* How To Reduce Acne Redness - Ways To Reduce Acne Redness | Home Remedies, Natural Remedy (clueweb12-0204wb-61-03607) http://www.natural-homeremedies.org/blog/how-to-reduce-acne-redness/ How To Reduce Acne Redness \- Ways To Reduce Acne Redness | Home Remedies, Natural Remedy...Treatment Options Diet Diet For Six Packs Abs The Best Vitamins For Toddlers How To Reduce Cellulite Through Diet Thanksgiving Appetizers For Kids Appetizer Ideas For Easter Natural Cures Treatment Options... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-06"><link>http://www.acnetreatment-s.us/how-to-reduce-redness-of-pimples/</link><title>How To Reduce Redness Of Pimples | Get Rid of Pimples</title><description>* How To Reduce Redness Of Pimples | Get Rid of Pimples (clueweb12-1008wb-53-22375) http://www.acnetreatment-s.us/how-to-reduce-redness-of-pimples/ How To Reduce Redness Of Pimples | Get Rid of Pimples ...with warm water. Aloe Vera. An aloe vera has its components that are excellent in reducing the redness of pimples. It has an “astringent” ingredient as well as antibacterial properties that combats the [...] Organic Acne Treatment | Treat Skin Conditions | Control Sebum Production | acnetreatment-s.us 9 [...] Red clover is the second herb that is proven to treat skin conditions such as eczema, acne and rashes. It has genistein, the ingredient that modifies androgen that can control sebum production... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:13:12">http://www.healthy-skin-guide.com/reducing-pimple-redness.html</link><title>Reducing Pimple Redness And Eliminating Acne</title><description>* Reducing Pimple Redness And Eliminating Acne (clueweb12-0202wb-53-05652) http://www.healthy-skin-guide.com/reducing-pimple-redness.html Reducing Pimple Redness And Eliminating Acne PIMPLE REDNESS Reducing pimple redness is very important. It is the first step in treating and preventing acne. Many people believe squeezing pimples will make them go away faster. Unfortunately squeezing pimples can...the healing process to take longer, and it makes you more likely to get additional acne in the future. The key to eliminating acne to use an effective treatment. An effective treatment is good at reducing pimple redness, eliminating acne, and preventing future breakouts. The most common places to get acne are on face, neck... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:14:13">http://www.fithealthyliving.com/2010/06/how-to-get-rid-of-acne-redness/</link><title>Best Anti Acne Products for Treating Acne Redness</title><description>* Best Anti Acne Products for Treating Acne Redness (clueweb12-1912wb-87-20433) http://www.fithealthyliving.com/2010/06/how-to-get-rid-of-acne-redness/ Best Anti Acne Products for Treating Acne Redness ...It is important to experiment to see what works for you. Phototherapy People suffering from acne and the inflammation that leads to acne redness have practiced do it yourself phototherapy for years whether it is sunbathing outdoors or using indoor tanning salons. Phototherapy produces a substance called porphyrin which reduces the presence of Langerhans cells in the skin responsible for producing the inflamed acne lesions which cause acne redness and red acne scars. Intense pulsed light, blue light therapy... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-09"><link>http://www.usaizdelki.com/theproducts.cfm?owner=1192&amp;subcat=171&amp;cat=52</link><title>All nutritional supplements and personal care products in one place</title><description>* All nutritional supplements and personal care products in one place (clueweb12-1217wb-37-29099) http://www.usaizdelki.com/theproducts.cfm?owner=1192&amp;subcat=171&amp;cat=52 ...00   Liquid Neutrogena face cleaner comes in 8 oz, 236 ml) Pimple Patch (4 patches) reduces redness from pimples in 30 minutes for acne USD $ 0.00 / USD $ 0.00   Pimple Patch Reduces Redness in 30 minutes for Acne, The worst thing about acne and pimples is the redness of the pimple and how to get rid of the redness quickly. redness can now be taken away in just a few minutes. Neutrogena On-the-spot Acne... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:16:07">http://www.typef.com/article/way-lighten-scars/</link><title>Tips to Reduce a Scar's Redness | typeF.com</title><description>* Tips to Reduce a Scar's Redness | typeF.com (clueweb12-1019wb-79-27865) http://www.typef.com/article/tips-reduce-scars-redness/ Tips to Reduce a Scar's Redness | typeF.com ...before making the final decision to go ahead with this procedure. ad_order_1 = (typeof ad_order_1 === "undefined") ? "1" : ad_order_1; ad_client = "ca-tyra_js"; num_ads = "4"; type = "text"; channels = "art_bottom_beauty"; class_name = "adsense_afc"; print_google_ad(ad_order_1, num_ads, type, channels, ad_client , class_name ); Related Videos   Tips to Reduce Scars Makeup Colors That Reduce Redness How to Reduce Visibility of Acne Scars on the Face: Peach Skin How to Reduce Visibility of Acne Scars on the Face: Fair Skin How to Reduce Visibility of Acne Scars on the Face: Caramel Skin How to Reduce Visibility of Acne Scars on the Face: Tan Skin How to Reduce Visibility of Acne Scars on the... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>