<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:37:26" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:37:53">http://www.lawresearchservices.com/firms/trials/kobe-statutue.htm</link><title>Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch</title><description>* Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch (clueweb12-0512wb-32-09719) http://www.lawresearchservices.com/firms/trials/kobe-statutue.htm Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch LAW RESEARCH Mainstreet Attorney Directory LawResearch Library Membership Sherlock Be Your Own Investigator Lawfirm Index Lawfirm Search Lawfirm by Practice Area Lawfirm by State Lawfirm by Country Kobe Trial - Colorado Court System Kobe Trial Lawyer Profiles Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial Colorado Criminal Code related to Charges of Rape Colorado Criminal Code 18-3-407... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:38:52">http://www.lawresearchservices.com/firms/trials/kobe-statute.htm</link><title>Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch</title><description>* Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch (clueweb12-0203wb-57-03945) http://www.lawresearchservices.com/firms/trials/kobe-statute.htm Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch LAW RESEARCH Mainstreet Attorney Directory LawResearch Library Membership Sherlock Be Your Own Investigator Lawfirm Index Lawfirm Search Lawfirm by Practice Area Lawfirm by State Lawfirm by Country Kobe Trial - Colorado Court System Kobe Trial Lawyer Profiles Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial Colorado Criminal Code related to Charges of Rape Colorado Criminal Code 18-3-407... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:39:47">http://www.justlawlinks.com/TRIALS/kobe-statute.htm</link><title>Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch</title><description>* Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch (clueweb12-0507wb-46-10367) http://www.justlawlinks.com/TRIALS/kobe-statute.htm Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial - LawResearch ...Refer An Associate Bookmark Us Contact Us About Us Kobe Trial - Colorado Court System Kobe Trial Lawyer Profiles Lawyers for the Kobe Bryant Trial Colorado Criminal Code related to Charges of Rape Colorado Criminal Code 18-3-407... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:41:06">http://bestplayerontheplanet.com/sitemap/</link><title>Kobe Bryant Blog with News, Stats, Highlights | Bestplayerontheplanet.com</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Blog with News, Stats, Highlights | Bestplayerontheplanet.com (clueweb12-1415wb-97-01328) http://bestplayerontheplanet.com/sitemap/ Kobe Bryant Blog with News, Stats, Highlights | Bestplayerontheplanet.com Kobe Bryant Wallpapers Lebron James Wallpapers Kobe Bryant Video Library Kobe Bryant Vs. Lebron James Sitemap Home » Sitemap Authors Chaseckirkhamgoofycancooknsorensonsimpixelated Pages About Contact Kobe Bryant Video Library Kobe Bryant Vs. Lebron James Kobe Bryant Wallpapers Lebron James Wallpapers Sitemap The Gallery Where Amazing Happens Posts ArtworkKobe Bryant... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-05"><link>http://www.sccards.com/bryant.htm</link><title>Basketball Cards - Kobe Bryant</title><description>* Basketball Cards - Kobe Bryant (clueweb12-1310wb-57-00785) http://www.sccards.com/bryant.htm Basketball Cards - Kobe Bryant Bryant, Kobe Camby, Marcus Carter, Vince Daniels, Antonio Davis, Baron Delk, Tony Dickerson, Michael Drexler, Clyde Duncan... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:43:12">http://www.basketwallpapers.com/USA/Kobe-Bryant/</link><title>Kobe Bryant - Basketball Wallpapers</title><description>* Kobe Bryant - Basketball Wallpapers (clueweb12-0101wb-79-14875) http://www.basketwallpapers.com/USA/Kobe-Bryant/ Kobe Bryant \- Basketball Wallpapers Can't find wallpapers of your favorite player or team? Click HERE for BasketWallpapers.com Site Map (links to all categories).   Home - Upload Wallpapers Contribute - Contact Me Online Basketball Games Bookmark Us, Press "Ctrl + D" Last Update: Jan. 30th 2012. Kobe Bryant Chinese New Year 2012 Wallpaper One more request i got, this one was at site... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:45:08">http://www.senatciis.org/dating/kobe-bryant-marriage.html</link><title>Get Free kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage) possibilities here</title><description>* Get Free kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage) possibilities here (clueweb12-0211wb-13-17667) http://www.senatciis.org/dating/kobe-bryant-marriage.html Get Free kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage) possibilities here ...latin singles connectionlatin woman datinglatin women for marriagelatin women marriage     Free www.kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage).com dating mega site This dating site offers various possibilities for kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage) , finding new friends and much more! For one of the best dating site offering free membership kobe bryant marriage (kobebryantmarriage) - ENTER HERE This page could help also if in search for okbe, kbe... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:45:38">http://www.demosproject.org/demos/bryant.aspx</link><title>Project Options Including bryant And Related Accessories</title><description>* Project Options Including bryant And Related Accessories (clueweb12-0412wb-32-31085) http://www.demosproject.org/demos/bryant.aspx Project Options Including bryant And Related AccessoriesDemo Shopping!    bryant And More Project Ideas $1.99Ervin Magic Johnson, Kobe Bryant, Thomas with Michael Jordan Rookie Card$1,499.99POP 1 PSA 10 KOBE BRYANT 1999 UD OVATION STANDING OVATION 16/50 ONLY 1 PSA 10$22.27Lot of Kobe Bryant Cards(1996-2000)$12.99Lane Bryant Plus Size Skirt 26/28 3X Coral Brown... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-09"><link>http://www.wecsky.com/kobe-bryant-shoes-c-210.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant Shoes,Cheap Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 4,Top Quality Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 5 for you</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Shoes,Cheap Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 4,Top Quality Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 5 for you (clueweb12-1002wb-77-16365) http://www.wecsky.com/kobe-bryant-shoes-c-210.html Kobe Bryant Shoes,Cheap Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 4,Top Quality Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 5 for you ...Plus 60+ (8)Jordan Team Strong (9)Jordan Trunner Q4 (5)Kids Jordan Shoes (6)Kobe Bryant Shoes-&gt; (17)Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 4 (4)Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 5 (5)Kobe Bryant Zoom Shoes 6 (8)Lebron James Shoes-&gt; (8)Nike Air Yeezy (24)Women Jordan Shoes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:47:22">http://www.demosproject.org/demos/bryant+los+angeles+lakers.aspx</link><title>Project Options Including bryant los angeles lakers And Related Accessories</title><description>* Project Options Including bryant los angeles lakers And Related Accessories (clueweb12-0502wb-51-07377) http://www.demosproject.org/demos/bryant+los+angeles+lakers.aspx Project Options Including bryant los angeles lakers And Related AccessoriesDemo Shopping!    bryant los angeles lakers And More Project Ideas $19.99Kobe Bryant Los Angeles Lakers Black New Era 59Fifty 'Black Mamba' Fitted cap$60.00Authentic Kobe Bryant Lakers jersey$3.52AWESOME 1996-97 FLEER ULTRA KOBE BRYANT ROOKIE #52 GEM MINT 10$49.99Kobe Bryant â NBA Los Angeles Lakers Adidas... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>