<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:55:24" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:55:56">http://www.changbioscience.com/bio/careerlinks.htm</link><title>Biology Career Job Links</title><description>* Biology Career Job Links (clueweb12-0106wb-20-06231) http://www.changbioscience.com/bio/careerlinks.htm ...Physician and Scientist - US academic scientist and physician positions. Adsumo: Biotech and pharmaceutical jobs. Biocareer: Biotech jobs. Bioexchange: Biotech jobs. Biofind: Biotech jobs, rumors, and events. Bionet: Bionet Jobs group, posting jobs...National Laboratory. Pharmaceutical/Biotech San Diego Biolink: Positions in the San Diego Area. PostDocJobs.com: Postdocs and young scientists. Science: Positions advertized on Science. ScienceJobs.com: Academic, biotech and pharmaceutical jobs. Southwestern: UT Southwestern job opportunities. The New Scientist Jobs: Job positions in US, Canada, Australia, and Europe. TIGR: TIGR career opprtunites. UCSF: UCSF career center. Career Links for Individual University and Biotech/Pharmaceutical Company ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:56:56">http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_magazine/previous_issues/articles/2008_05_02/caredit.a0800063</link><title>Structuring Academic Careers in Europe - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers</title><description>* Structuring Academic Careers in Europe - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers (clueweb12-0309wb-69-13174) http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_magazine/previous_issues/articles/2008_05_02/caredit.a0800063 Structuring Academic Careers in Europe \- Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers ...see as Europe's flawed academic career structure as a major reason for the migration of European researchers to the United States. Each country has its own academic job titles and--often unwritten--career paths, making an international job search thorny and opaque. Also, European universities often offer junior positions without any consideration of whether there will be another position when... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:57:30">http://www.changbioscience.com/bio/career.html</link><title>Biology Career Job Links</title><description>* Biology Career Job Links (clueweb12-0106wb-84-03242) http://www.changbioscience.com/bio/career.html ...Instructionsupplierprotocol...Career Links AACC Onlin - American Association of Clinical Chemistry career center. Academia : Job listings in academia, major US universities, and positions in Australia, Canada, and Europe. Academic Employment Network: US academic positions. Academic network : Jobs in higher education. Academic, Physician and Scientist - US academic scientist and physician positions. Adsumo: Biotech and pharmaceutical jobs. Biocareer: Biotech jobs. Bioexchange: Biotech jobs. Biofind: Biotech jobs, rumors, and events. Bionet: Bionet Jobs group, posting jobs and jobs wanted. Bio-jobs: Biotech... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:58:14">http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_magazine/previous_issues/articles/2011_10_21/science.opms.r1100110</link><title>Academic Opportunities in European Science - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers</title><description>* Academic Opportunities in European Science - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers (clueweb12-0311wb-95-23299) http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_magazine/previous_issues/articles/2011_10_21/science.opms.r1100110 Academic Opportunities in European Science - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers ...also numerous differences that exist between the members states and their higher education systems. The postdoc appointment is one such illustration: âAlthough the concept of postdoctoral researchers is well understood, there is considerable variability in job titles and in the practical organization of this stage in Europe,â according to the 2010 European Science Foundation (ESF) Report, âResearch Careers in Europe: Landscape and Horizonsâ (http://scim.ag/qrFZHZ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:59:23">http://web.udl.es/usuaris/k4371596/employ.htm</link><title>Employment Links for the Biomedical Scientist</title><description>* Employment Links for the Biomedical Scientist (clueweb12-1716wb-53-03053) http://web.udl.es/usuaris/k4371596/employ.htm ...large and ever-increasing volume of information can be a time-consuming task for the job-seeker with specialized career options. This set of links is being compiled by a fellow...postings- Job postings in biotechnology and biotechnology related companies from the Biospace Career Center. NISS Job Vacancies - Job opening in United Kingdom and commonwealth universities advertized through the National Information Service and Systems. The New Scientist Planet Recruitment Database - A most comprehensive listing of current scientific, technological and academic vacancies from the New Scientist. Mostly positions in the United Kingdom, but includes some European and Australasian listings - definitely worth a visit. Academic Employment Network Job Listings - Employment positions accessed... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:00:13">http://www.eurosciencejobs.com/jobs/biotechnology_and_genetics</link><title>EuroScienceJobs.com - Biotechnology and Genetics Research Jobs or Postdocs in Europe</title><description>* EuroScienceJobs.com - Biotechnology and Genetics Research Jobs or Postdocs in Europe (clueweb12-1604wb-67-09461) http://www.eurosciencejobs.com/jobs/biotechnology_and_genetics EuroScienceJobs.com - Biotechnology and Genetics Research Jobs or Postdocs in Europe job listings from EuroScienceJobs, enter your email address and press subscribe. $(document).ready(function(){ var image = new Image(); image.onload = function() { $("body").css("background", "url('images/site_background.jpg') repeat-x fixed center bottom #FFFFFF"); }; image.src = 'images/site_background.jpg'; }); ...yet? To receive weekly job listings from EuroScienceJobs, enter your email address and press subscribe. $(document).ready(function(){ var image = new Image(); image.onload = function() { $("body").css("background", "url('images/site_background.jpg') repeat-x fixed center bottom #FFFFFF"); }; image.src = 'images/site_background.jpg'; }); Job Search Upload CV Career Guides Recruiters ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:01:00">http://www.biotechnologist2020.com/2012/03/ncl-pune-phd-biotechnology-engineering.html</link><title>Biotechnologist2020: NCL-Pune PhD Biotechnology Engineering admissions for BTech</title><description>* Biotechnologist2020: NCL-Pune PhD Biotechnology Engineering admissions for BTech (clueweb12-1200tw-87-21774) http://www.biotechnologist2020.com/2012/03/ncl-pune-phd-biotechnology-engineering.html ...Internship / Summer training on Stem Cell TechnologyNIT-Rourkela recruits @BT2020-Orissa MSc/MTech Biotechnology jobManipal University MSc/MTech Medical Biotechnology admissionsPune, Ahmedabad, Hyderabad &amp; Chennai - ABS-BT2020- UGC-CSIR...Job Tamil Nadu Marine Biology Job IARI Delhi BSc/MSc Biotechnology Job Delhi Plant Biotechnology Job University of Pune Plant Biotechnology job Uttrakhand MSc/ PhD Microbiology job IIT Roorkee MTech/ MSc Biotechnology Job JNU Delhi PhD Biotechnology job Kolkatta MSc/ PhD Biotechnology Jobs Andhra Pradesh MSc Biotechnology job IISER Pune PhD admissions in Biological Sciences Italy Research Jobs in Computational/ Systems Biol... Portugal Postdoc position in Cell Biology Tamilnadu MSc Biotechnology fresher job UP Plant Biotechnology research job Chennai... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:01:48">http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_magazine/previous_issues/articles/2008_08_01/caredit.a0800114</link><title>Taken for Granted: The Fat Lady Sings - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers</title><description>* Taken for Granted: The Fat Lady Sings - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers (clueweb12-0310wb-78-10342) http://sciencecareers.sciencemag.org/career_development/previous_issues/articles/2008_08_01/caredit_a0800114 Taken for Granted: The Fat Lady Sings - Science Careers - Biotech, Pharmaceutical, Faculty, Postdoc jobs on Science Careers ...Careers Contact My Science Career My Account My RĂŠsumĂŠs My Cover Letters My Applications My Jobs My Searches My Job Alerts Find a Job Job Search Browse All Jobs By Employer... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:02:22">http://www.bsdpostdoc.uchicago.edu/publications-past-bulletin.shtml</link><title>The University of Chicago Biological Sciences Division Postdoctoral Association</title><description>* The University of Chicago Biological Sciences Division Postdoctoral Association (clueweb12-1607wb-05-16728) http://www.bsdpostdoc.uchicago.edu/publications-past-bulletin.shtml The University of Chicago Biological Sciences Division Postdoctoral Association ...The University of Chicago Biological Sciences Division Postdoctoral Association University of Chicago BSD Postdoctoral Association Postdocs Personal Welfare Chicago Jobs Job resources Career Advice Job postings - NEW! Events Seminars Seminar Archive Social Events Postdoc Symposium Publications Weekly Bulletin Weekly Bulletin... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7423-10"><link>http://www.marine-genomics-europe.org/index2.php?mode=news&amp;quoi=all</link><title>REX Marine Genomics Europe</title><description>* REX Marine Genomics Europe (clueweb12-1909wb-69-21427) http://www.marine-genomics-europe.org/index2.php?mode=news&amp;quoi=all REX Marine Genomics Europe ...projects INTERNATIONAL MARINE GENOMICS CONFERENCE 2006 Miscellaneous Diaporama News Europe &amp; useful links Up coming events Job opportunities Other networks European seas", Gothenburg University, Department of Marine Ecology at Tjärnö, Strömstad (Sweden). September 21-26, 2009. Read... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>