<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:05:10" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:05:40">http://www.astheromansdo.com</link><title>Fine art &amp; travel photography journeys, cultural &amp; historical tours in Rome, Italian cooking courses, Incentive Travel Programs in Italy, photographs of Italy, private tours in Rome &amp; Florence; photo journeys in Rome &amp; Italy, culinary tours in Rome, pictures of Italy, photos of Rome, hstorical tours, English speaking photographer in Rome, creative coach in Rome, food &amp; wine, cooking in Italy, Roman cooking, cooking classes in Rome, cooking schools in Rome, Italy, Roman cooking, food in Rome, private photography journeys and in Rome, .</title><description>* Fine art &amp; travel photography journeys, cultural &amp; historical tours in Rome, Italian cooking courses, Incentive Travel Programs in Italy, photographs of Italy, private tours in Rome &amp; Florence; photo journeys in Rome &amp; Italy, culinary tours in Rome, pictures of Italy, photos of Rome, hstorical tours, English speaking photographer in Rome, creative coach in Rome, food &amp; wine, cooking in Italy, Roman cooking, cooking classes in Rome, cooking schools in Rome, Italy, Roman cooking, food in Rome, private photography journeys and in Rome, . (clueweb12-1515wb-29-03088) http://www.astheromansdo.com ...school, cooking lessons in Italy, Italian food, cooking in Italy, Italian cuisine, culinary schools in Italy, Italian cooking classes in Rome, Roman cooking, Roman cuisine, cooking in Rome, cooking lessons in Rome, Roman Holiday, cappucinno, wine tours in italy, cooking in rome, roman cuisine, cooking lessons in rome, cooking classes in Italy, Italian food, italy, Rome food, authentic Italian cuisine, the best cooking classes in Rome, best cooking classes in Italy, Rome, Italy, culinary, gourmet food in... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:06:19">http://www.astheromansdo.com/index.htm</link><title>Fine art &amp; travel photography journeys, cultural &amp; historical tours in Rome, Italian cooking courses, Incentive Travel Programs in Italy, photographs of Italy, private tours in Rome &amp; Florence; photo journeys in Rome &amp; Italy, culinary tours in Rome, pictures of Italy, photos of Rome, hstorical tours, English speaking photographer in Rome, creative coach in Rome, food &amp; wine, cooking in Italy, Roman cooking, cooking classes in Rome, cooking schools in Rome, Italy, Roman cooking, food in Rome, private photography journeys and in Rome, .</title><description>* Fine art &amp; travel photography journeys, cultural &amp; historical tours in Rome, Italian cooking courses, Incentive Travel Programs in Italy, photographs of Italy, private tours in Rome &amp; Florence; photo journeys in Rome &amp; Italy, culinary tours in Rome, pictures of Italy, photos of Rome, hstorical tours, English speaking photographer in Rome, creative coach in Rome, food &amp; wine, cooking in Italy, Roman cooking, cooking classes in Rome, cooking schools in Rome, Italy, Roman cooking, food in Rome, private photography journeys and in Rome, . (clueweb12-1515wb-72-06666) http://www.astheromansdo.com/index.htm ...school, cooking lessons in Italy, Italian food, cooking in Italy, Italian cuisine, culinary schools in Italy, Italian cooking classes in Rome, Roman cooking, Roman cuisine, cooking in Rome, cooking lessons in Rome, Roman Holiday, cappucinno, wine tours in italy, cooking in rome, roman cuisine, cooking lessons in rome, cooking classes in Italy, Italian food, italy, Rome food, authentic Italian cuisine, the best cooking classes in Rome, best cooking classes in Italy, Rome, Italy, culinary, gourmet food in... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:06:59">http://www.placestravel.com/europe/italy/index.html</link><title>Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates</title><description>* Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates (clueweb12-1306wb-43-07707) http://www.placestravel.com/europe/italy/index.html ...by over over 16 feet. Venice is also a very popular tourist area. It is best known as the city built on water. It is famous for its canals and gondolas used as transportation around the city.   Search Italy Hotels and Resort by Location Rome | Milan | Venice | Naples | Capri | Genoa | Bologna | Asisi | Alensandria | Ascoli Piceno | Asolo | Bari Bergamo | Biela | Bologna... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:07:50">http://www.sevenseastourism.com/europe/italy/index.html</link><title>Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates</title><description>* Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates (clueweb12-0210wb-47-30428) http://www.sevenseastourism.com/europe/italy/index.html ...by over over 16 feet. Venice is also a very popular tourist area. It is best known as the city built on water. It is famous for its canals and gondolas used as transportation around the city. Italy Featured Hotels &amp; Beach Resorts St Regis Grand Hotel Italy Via Vittorio Emanuele Orlando 3 Rome Italy Hotel Rating: 5 Star Hotel Boscolo Hotel Exedra Italy Piazza della Repubblica, 47, 00185 Rome, Italy Hotel Rating: 5 Star Hotel Intercontinental De La... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:08:42">http://www.sevenseastour.com/europe/italy/index.html</link><title>Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates</title><description>* Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates (clueweb12-0303wb-73-31053) http://www.sevenseastour.com/europe/italy/index.html ...city of the eastern region.   Italy Featured Hotels and Beach Resorts St Regis Grand Hotel Italy Rome, Italy Hotel Rating : 5 Star Hotel Boscolo Hotel Exedra Italy Rome, Italy Hotel Rating : 5...Italy Amadeus Hotel Venice Italy Ambassador Tre Rose Hotel Venice Italy Andreola Central Hotel Milan Italy Antares Hotel Accademia Milan Italy Antares Hotel Concorde Milan Italy Antares Hotel Rubens Milan Italy Ara Pacis Hotel Rome Italy Ariston Hotel Rome Italy Atlantic Hotel Milan Italy Atlantic Palace Hotel Florence Italy Augustus Hotel Rome Italy Bellevue Hotel Syrene Sorrento Italy Berna Hotel Milan Italy Best Western Abner's Hotel Rimini Italy Best Western Ai Cavalieri Hotel Sicily Best Western Albergo Roma... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:09:27">http://www.sevenseashotels.com/europe/italy/index.html</link><title>SearchBox</title><description>* SearchBox (clueweb12-0304wb-97-03291) http://www.sevenseashotels.com/europe/italy/index.html Italy Hotels - List of Italy Hotels and Resorts with affordable Hotel Rates ...destinations around the world" "Always growing Hotel Inventory to provide you more hotel options" "Our Best Rates gives Value to your Money" "Simple and User Friendly Interface" Italy Hotels by Destinations Rome | Milan | Venice | Naples | Capri | Genoa | Bologna | Asisi | Alensandria | Ascoli Piceno | Asolo | Bari Bergamo | Biela | Bologna... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:10:14">http://goitaly.about.com/popular.htm</link><title>About.com Italy Travel: Most Popular Articles</title><description>* About.com Italy Travel: Most Popular Articles (clueweb12-0000wb-66-04186) http://goitaly.about.com/popular.htm ...city in the heart of Tuscany, is one of the most popular travel cities in Italy. Florence has some of Italy's best museums, beautiful cathedrals and churches, and interesting streets and squares with elegant buildings and shops.Amalfi Coast Map and Travel InformationAmalfi Coast map and tourism information. Plan your vacation to the Amalfi Coast.Rome Three Day ItineraryRome attractions - Rome is a popular travel city in Italy with many tourist attractions. What to see and... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:11:14">http://www.foodloversodyssey.typepad.com/my_weblog/page/7/</link><title>Food Lover's Odyssey</title><description>* Food Lover's Odyssey (clueweb12-1911wb-44-19356) http://www.foodloversodyssey.typepad.com/my_weblog/page/7/ ...Europe are Changing the Way We Understand "Vintage" - Great photos from various grape harvests in Italy, and links to many more - Do Bianchi Guida alle Migliori Dieci Pizzerie Napoletane - Guide to the 10 Best Pizzerie in Naples and Campania - Luciano Pignataro (in Italian) Budget Dining in Rome, Revised - Katie updates her budget dining recommendations - Parla Food Mercato (via Gregorio VII) - Elizabeth Minchilli in Rome Rome Gelato Tour: Il Gelato di Claudio Torce - An American in Rome Rome: Neve di Latte... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:11:59">http://www.astheromansdo.com/special_events.htm</link><title>Roman Holiday Culinary Adventures, food &amp; wine in Rome, cooking inItaly, Roman cooking, cooking lessons in Rome, coooking schools in Rome, shopping in the outdoor markets, Rome markets, Roman cooking, food in Rome, Campo dei Fiori, hidden markets, Rome</title><description>* Roman Holiday Culinary Adventures, food &amp; wine in Rome, cooking inItaly, Roman cooking, cooking lessons in Rome, coooking schools in Rome, shopping in the outdoor markets, Rome markets, Roman cooking, food in Rome, Campo dei Fiori, hidden markets, Rome (clueweb12-1515wb-72-06686) http://www.astheromansdo.com/special_events.htm ...school, cooking lessons in Italy, Italian food, cooking in Italy, Italian cuisine, culinary schools in Italy, Italian cooking classes in Rome, Roman cooking, Roman cuisine, cooking in Rome, cooking lessons in Rome, Roman Holiday, cappucinno, wine tours in italy, cooking in rome, roman cuisine, cooking lessons in rome, cooking classes in italy, italian food, italy, rome food, authentic italian cuisine, the best cooking classes in rome, best cooking classes in italy, rome, italy, culinary, gourmet food in... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:12:52">http://boards.independenttraveler.com/archive/index.php/f-109.html</link><title>Italy [Archive] - Travel Message Board Forums - IndependentTraveler.com</title><description>* Italy [Archive] - Travel Message Board Forums - IndependentTraveler.com (clueweb12-1614wb-79-11216) http://boards.independenttraveler.com/archive/index.php/f-109.html Italy [Archive] - Travel Message Board Forums - IndependentTraveler.com Travel Message Board Forums - IndependentTraveler.com &gt; European Traveler...Italy Train Travel by KDavies Finding "Pensions"? Which Tuscan hilltown? Sicily villa/house rentals in Italy Rome and Naples Rome Hotels How Many Days Do I Need? Airport transpers in Milan Milan...trip to Italy, please help us plan Moving to Bari Cinque terra package deals to italy Tripman42 First Trip To Italy Italy \- First Time - Need Help beach apt wanted? Best restaurant in San Gimignano (Tuscany) and Sorrento? Anniversary visit to Italy Senior travel Food/ wine/ resturant prices.... Aeolian Islands I will travel to Rome at this Friday.please help Travel to Italy Jan 2010 Hey everyone... Me and My Wife are planning for our next honeymoon Cinque... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>