<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:17:28" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:18:07">http://ticketwebsitehq.com/bruno-mars-concert-tickets/index.php</link><title>Bruno Mars Concert Tickets - Bruno Mars Tickets</title><description>* Bruno Mars Concert Tickets - Bruno Mars Tickets (clueweb12-1910wb-76-03459) http://ticketwebsitehq.com/bruno-mars-concert-tickets/index.php Bruno Mars Concert Tickets \- Bruno Mars Tickets Mars Concert Tickets \- Bruno Mars Tickets Bruno Mars Concert Tickets • Bruno Mars Tickets Bruno Mars Concert Tour • Bruno Mars Tour Dates 2012   Tickets Sports Tickets Theater Tickets   Mars Top Cities Bruno Mars Atlanta Bruno Mars Boston Bruno Mars Charlotte Bruno Mars Chicago Bruno Mars Cleveland Bruno Mars Dallas Bruno Mars Denver Bruno Mars... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-02"><link>http://tickets.oakwebworks.com/CONCERTS/POPROCK/BrunoMars/BrunoMarsTickets.asp</link><title>Bruno Mars Tickets</title><description>* Bruno Mars Tickets (clueweb12-0011wb-31-23238) http://tickets.oakwebworks.com/CONCERTS/POPROCK/BrunoMars/BrunoMarsTickets.asp Bruno Mars Tickets Mars Tickets here at Oak Web Works Tickets More Cities Bruno Mars will be Visiting: Bruno Mars Coachella TicketsBruno Mars Las Vegas TicketsBruno Mars Montgomery TicketsBruno Mars Paris TicketsBruno Mars Universal City TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Atlanta TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Boston TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Broomfield TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Camden... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:19:51">http://www.excite.com/events/concert-tickets/Bruno-Mars/index.php</link><title>Bruno Mars Tickets - Cheapest Tickets For Bruno Mars</title><description>* Bruno Mars Tickets - Cheapest Tickets For Bruno Mars (clueweb12-0804wb-35-29581) http://www.excite.com/events/concert-tickets/Bruno-Mars/index.php Bruno Mars Tickets \- Cheapest Tickets For Bruno Mars Tickets Concert Tickets Theater Tickets Cities Venues Top Events FAQ Use Discount Code EXCITED on Checkout and Get an Immediate Discount Categories: Sports Auto Racing Tickets College Basketball Tickets College Football Tickets Cricket Tickets Golf Tickets Miscellaneous Tickets MLB Tickets NBA Tickets NFL Tickets NHL Tickets Olympics Tickets Rodeo Tickets Tennis... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:20:52">http://ticketwebsitehq.com/30-seconds-to-mars-concert-tickets/index.php</link><title>30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tickets - 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets</title><description>* 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tickets - 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets (clueweb12-1910wb-86-27350) http://ticketwebsitehq.com/30-seconds-to-mars-concert-tickets/index.php 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tickets \- 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets Mars Concert Tickets \- 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tickets • 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tour • 30 Seconds To Mars Tour Dates 2012   Tickets Sports Tickets Theater Tickets   ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:21:31">http://www.authoritytickets.com/error.php</link><title>Tickets to Bruno Mars</title><description>* Tickets to Bruno Mars (clueweb12-0100wb-08-28101) http://www.authoritytickets.com/concerts/poprock/brunomars/brunomarstickets.php Tickets to Bruno Mars   Bruno Mars POP / ROCK Concert Tour Schedule and Tickets Search Tickets Concert Tickets Theater Tickets Las Vegas Shows Tickets Blog Bruno Mars Tour Bruno Mars Coachella TicketsBruno Mars Essex Junction TicketsBruno Mars Las Vegas TicketsBruno Mars Paris TicketsBruno Mars Universal City TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Del Mar TicketsBruno Mars &amp; Janelle Monae Phoenix... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:22:01">http://www.barrystickets.com/losangeles/gibson-amphitheatre/30-seconds-to-mars-tickets.php</link><title>30 Seconds to Mars Tickets Gibson Amphitheatre | 30 Seconds to Mars Gibson Amphitheatre Los Angeles</title><description>* 30 Seconds to Mars Tickets Gibson Amphitheatre | 30 Seconds to Mars Gibson Amphitheatre Los Angeles (clueweb12-1310wb-13-26335) http://www.barrystickets.com/losangeles/gibson-amphitheatre/30-seconds-to-mars-tickets.php 30 Seconds to Mars Tickets Gibson Amphitheatre | 30 Seconds to Mars Gibson Amphitheatre Los Angeles Mars Tickets function validation() { ByZipCode=document.getElementById('form2').elements['ByZipCode'].value; daterange=document.getElementById('form2').elements['daterange'].value; //if(ByZipCode=='' || daterange=='') if(ByZipCode=='' || ByZipCode=='By City or Zip Code') { //alert("Please complet all search values"); document.getElementById("zip1_err").innerHTML ='Please enter a value to search for'; return false; } return true; } Select a Date Today This Weekend Next Weekend AprilMayJuneJulyAugustSeptemberOctober... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:23:11">http://www.frontrowking.com/buy-bruno-mars-concert-tickets/index.html</link><title>Bruno Mars Tickets - Bruno Mars Concert Tickets 2012 - 2013</title><description>* Bruno Mars Tickets - Bruno Mars Concert Tickets 2012 - 2013 (clueweb12-0107wb-24-29843) http://www.frontrowking.com/buy-bruno-mars-concert-tickets/index.html Bruno Mars Tickets \- Bruno Mars Concert Tickets 2012 - 2013       Buy Bruno Mars Concert Tickets   Front Row King » Bruno Mars Tickets   Home Concerts Sports Theater Comedy Bruno Mars Concerts Atlanta, Georgia Atlantic City, New Jersey Austin, Texas Boston, Massachusetts Charlotte, North Carolina Chicago...San Francisco, California Seattle, Washington Toronto, Ontario Washington, District Of Columbia Buy With Confidence Bruno Mars Concert Tickets Bruno Mars Tickets Bruno Mars tickets is well known for entertaining concerts! Pick your seats for the Bruno Mars tickets concert near you to see Bruno Mars tickets live. We strive providing excellent ticket selections... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:23:58">http://www.awesomeseating.com/alternative-tickets/30-Seconds-To-Mars-Tickets.aspx</link><title>30 Seconds To Mars Tickets â Cheap 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tour Tickets at AwesomeSeating!</title><description>* 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets â Cheap 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tour Tickets at AwesomeSeating! (clueweb12-0404wb-30-17574) http://www.awesomeseating.com/alternative-tickets/30-Seconds-To-Mars-Tickets.aspx 30 Seconds To Mars Tickets â Cheap 30 Seconds To Mars Concert Tour Tickets at AwesomeSeating! TICKETSMLB BASEBALL TICKETSNBA BASKETBALL TICKETSNHL HOCKEY TICKETSNCAA FOOTBALL TICKETSNCAA BASKETBALL TICKETSPGA GOLF TICKETSNASCAR TICKETSBOXING TICKETSWWE TICKETSTENNIS TICKETSOLYMPICS TICKETSOTHER TICKETSCONCERTSALTERNATIVE TICKETSCOUNTRY MUSIC TICKETSPOP... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:25:08">http://www.thelasttickets.com/concerts/bruno-mars-tickets</link><title>http://www.thelasttickets.com/concerts/bruno-mars-tickets</title><description>* http://www.thelasttickets.com/concerts/bruno-mars-tickets (clueweb12-1612wb-97-18779) http://www.thelasttickets.com/concerts/bruno-mars-tickets ...Code "TLTix" Tickets I Bruno Mars Tickets Quick Search :    Cheap Bruno Mars Tickets   The Last Tickets offer you the Bruno Mars tickets that you are looking for! We are providing the cheap Bruno Mars tickets over the Internet. You can buy Bruno Mars tickets online through TheLastTickets's safe and secure server. On-time delivery is our guarantee. Click to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7432-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7432_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:25:47">http://www.ticketspresto.com/concert-tickets/the-mars-volta.html</link><title>The Mars Volta Tickets | Tickets for The Mars Volta | Cheap The Mars Volta Tickets</title><description>* The Mars Volta Tickets | Tickets for The Mars Volta | Cheap The Mars Volta Tickets (clueweb12-1615wb-60-24082) http://www.ticketspresto.com/concert-tickets/the-mars-volta.html The Mars Volta Tickets | Tickets for The Mars Volta | Cheap The Mars Volta Tickets Presto Brings You Top-Quality, Cheap The Mars Volta Tickets! Tickets Presto... Your Top Source for Cheap Tickets Online! Search: Home Sports Tickets Concert Tickets Theater Tickets Family Tickets Comedy Tickets Ticket Search Enter an Event or City: Top Concerts Britney Spears Elton John Keith Urban Taylor... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>