<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7435">trendy bar Berlin</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:44:59" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:45:40">http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/berlin/entertainment/bars/</link><title>Bars « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog</title><description>* Bars « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog (clueweb12-0701wb-43-12340) http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/category/berlin/entertainment/bars/ Bars « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog ...Bars « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog Berlin Apartments Navigation: Home Apartments Locations Checkin-Info Blog Gallery About Us ...berlin, panorama bar, panorama bar berlin, rote rose, rote rose berlin, things to do in berlin, wilde renate Posted in Articles by Evo Lucian, Bars, Berlin, Berlin Culture, Berlin Tourist Attractions, Berlin Youth Culture, Clubbing, Culture, DJing in Berlin, Drinking in Berlin, Electronic Music in Berlin, Entertainment, Party, Things to do in Berlin | No Comments » Whatâs on in Berlin? – Trendy Christmas Markets â by OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog contributor Diana de Nobrega Sunday, December 18th, 2011... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:46:26">http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/berlin/entertainment/drinking-in-berlin-berlin/</link><title>Drinking in Berlin « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog</title><description>* Drinking in Berlin « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog (clueweb12-0701wb-26-05409) http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/category/berlin/entertainment/drinking-in-berlin-berlin/ ...throughout the city, especially in the areas more dubbed for tourists, [...] Continue Reading… Tags: Berlin, berlin ausgehen, berlin bars, berlin in winter, berlin nachtleben, berlin nightlife, brian williams, christmas culture berlin, christmas in berlin...berlin, panorama bar, panorama bar berlin, rote rose, rote rose berlin, things to do in berlin, wilde renate Posted in Articles by Evo Lucian, Bars, Berlin, Berlin Culture, Berlin Tourist Attractions, Berlin Youth Culture, Clubbing, Culture, DJing in Berlin, Drinking in Berlin, Electronic Music in Berlin, Entertainment, Party, Things to do in Berlin | No Comments » Whatâs on in Berlin? – Trendy Christmas Markets â by OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog contributor Diana de Nobrega Sunday, December 18th, 2011... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:47:10">http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/berlin/entertainment/electronic-music-in-berlin/</link><title>Electronic Music in Berlin « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog</title><description>* Electronic Music in Berlin « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog (clueweb12-0701wb-81-10218) http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/category/berlin/entertainment/electronic-music-in-berlin/ ...Clubs’ of the moment. Sitting on a dock on [...] Continue Reading… Tags: Berlin, berlin ausgehen, berlin bars, berlin club, berlin clubbing, berlin nachtleben, berlin nightlife, Club der Visionaere, Club der Visionaere - Berlin, Club der Visionaere open, club der visionaire, club der visionaire berlin, Club der VisionĂ¤re, clubbing berlin, germany, Ms Cindy Su, nightlife berlin, spree river, techno, techno berlin, things to do in berlin, trendy club berlin Posted in Articles by Cindy Su, Bars, Berlin, Clubbing, Electronic Music in Berlin... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:48:04">http://www.elegant-lifestyle.com/berlin.htm</link><title>Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin (city guide for Berlin's hotels, restaurants, entertainment, theatres exhibitions, guide books, shops)</title><description>* Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin (city guide for Berlin's hotels, restaurants, entertainment, theatres exhibitions, guide books, shops) (clueweb12-0109wb-57-26426) http://www.elegant-lifestyle.com/berlin.htm ...special occasions (up to 120 guests, EUR 500 per hour), almost legendary 'Harry's New York Bar' and gourmet restaurant 'Harlekin'; Tel: +49-30-25478-0; Fax: +49-30-265-1171; Luetzowufer 15; 10785 Berlin ; Open: Restaurant 'Harlekin': Tue-Sat 6pm-midnight; Tube: Nollendorfplatz; e-mail: info@esplanade.de; website...chef Franz Raneburger, no credit cards accepted; Tel: +49-30-805 4000; Koenigstrasse 36; 14109 Berlin-Wannsee ; Open: Wed-Sun noon-midnight; Tube: Wannsee; website: www.schloss-glienicke.de (42) Schwarzenraben; Restaurants: Trendy; Decoration of the 1990s with chocolate, pistachio and coconut colours, the Cocktail bar 'Engelspalast' is draped with velour, original new Italian cuisine is served in the like of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:48:52">http://www.pongu-travel.com/index.html?country=Germany&amp;func=hotel&amp;city=berlin&amp;partner=bk</link><title>Pongü's Germany Hotel Guide - Hotels in berlin, Germany</title><description>* Pongü's Germany Hotel Guide - Hotels in berlin, Germany (clueweb12-0705wb-09-23742) http://www.pongu-travel.com/index.php?country=Germany&amp;func=hotel&amp;city=berlin&amp;partner=bk ...starting at EUR 136This 5-star hotel has a large spa and pool overlooking Berlin, stylish restaurants, and bars with live music. It lies in the lively Potsdamer Platz district, 300 metres from the...84This 4-star design hotel offers modern accommodation beside the lovely Friedrichshain park in Berlins trendy Prenzlauer Berg district. It lies just one kilometre from famous Alexanderplatz square and Hackescher Markt... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-06"><link>http://www.europeanrailguide.com/thingstodo/bars.html</link><title>Bars in Europe - Looking for somewhere to drink on your European trip? Try these - European Rail Guide</title><description>* Bars in Europe - Looking for somewhere to drink on your European trip? Try these - European Rail Guide (clueweb12-0201wb-05-31421) http://www.europeanrailguide.com/thingstodo/bars.html ...that hangs on the walls, all of which is for sale.Pussy Galore's Flying Circus (Bar)Copenhagen (Denmark)Worth a visit for the name alone, there's an enticing cocktail selection and outdoor seating for warmer days.The Porter (Pub)Bath (England)A colourful and popular local pub catering to the alternative and student crowdThe Met Bar (Bar)London (England)One of London's top trendy night spots - pricey drinks but worth it for the atmosphere.The Ordnance Arms (Pub)London... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:50:01">http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/10/18/clubbing-berlin-%e2%80%93-%e2%80%98berghain%e2%80%99-door-policy-how-to-get-in-%e2%80%93-%e2%80%98ota-berlin-constituency-blog%e2%80%99-contributor-evo-lucien-tells-you-how/</link><title>Clubbing « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog</title><description>* Clubbing « OTA-Berlin Constituency Blog (clueweb12-0700wb-52-17565) http://www.ota-berlin.de/blog/category/berlin/entertainment/clubbing/ ...Clubs’ of the moment. Sitting on a dock on [...] Continue Reading… Tags: Berlin, berlin ausgehen, berlin bars, berlin club, berlin clubbing, berlin nachtleben, berlin nightlife, Club der Visionaere, Club der Visionaere - Berlin, Club der Visionaere open, club der visionaire, club der visionaire berlin, Club der VisionĂ¤re, clubbing berlin, germany, Ms Cindy Su, nightlife berlin, spree river, techno, techno berlin, things to do in berlin, trendy club berlin Posted in Articles by Cindy Su, Bars, Berlin, Clubbing, Electronic Music in Berlin... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-08"><link>http://www.vamostravel.com/city_breaks/berlin/nightlife.asp</link><title>The best guide to nightlife &amp; stag do's in Berlin</title><description>* The best guide to nightlife &amp; stag do's in Berlin (clueweb12-0705wb-84-26740) http://www.vamostravel.com/city_breaks/berlin/nightlife.asp ...Its a great place to find a non-stop party spirit, great for those Berlin stag nights and meet a friendly crowd on the dancefloor. A-lounge is another popular bar-club with its on DJ &amp; dancefloor, found in the Mitte district. The music policy changes throughout the week, but the clientele is usually a nice mix of locals, short break foreigners and trendy students. Green Door bar is known to be one of the nicest bars to try... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-09"><link>http://hotels.swissinfo.com/hotels-prenzlauer-berg</link><title>Hotels Berlin Prenzlauer Berg cheaper</title><description>* Hotels Berlin Prenzlauer Berg cheaper (clueweb12-0005wb-75-33561) http://hotels.swissinfo.com/hotels-prenzlauer-berg ...MAP Berlin Inspired by Tsarist Russia, this 4-star hotel occupies an historic Art Nouveau building in Berlin's trendy Prenzlauer Berg district. It offers modern accommodation, free Wi-Fi, and bike rental. The Hotel...00 Lettestr. 7, Berlin This hostel is located in one of the most popular and trendy districts of Berlin, in the Prenzlauer Berg district. Letteâm Sleep offers a friendly and relaxed place to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7435-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7435_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:54:03">http://www.elegant-lifestyle.com/berlin_restaurants.htm</link><title>Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin Guide: Restaurants</title><description>* Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin Guide: Restaurants (clueweb12-0110wb-34-25443) http://www.elegant-lifestyle.com/berlin_restaurants.htm Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin Guide: Restaurants Best 100 City Guides: Berlin Guide: Restaurants HOME |  ADVERTISE | NEWSLETTER | BEST 100 CITY...Elegant-Lifestyle.com: Best 100 City Guide: Berlin Guide: Restaurants Best 100 City Guides: Berlin Guide: Restaurants HOME |  ADVERTISE | NEWSLETTER | BEST 100 CITY GUIDES | CONTACT US | ABOUT US | HELP Berlin... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>