<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:01:58" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:02:32">http://www.gotsmallanimalsonline.com/sitemap.shtml</link><title>Small Animals - Pictures, Breeders, Babies, Rescue, Photos</title><description>* Small Animals - Pictures, Breeders, Babies, Rescue, Photos (clueweb12-0111wb-45-24584) http://www.gotsmallanimalsonline.com/sitemap.shtml ...an animal for sale with photos and ask for a picture of the breeding stock. Animals For Sale - Find animals for sale, evaluate the babies, and make sure the breeders are experienced. Buy Animal \- To buy animal, view pictures and evaluate the babies. Buy Animals \- To buy animals, contact a breeder and view a photo. Pet Classifieds - Pet classifieds usually have contacts of the farms and pictures of the pets. Pet For Sale - Find a pet for sale and view... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:03:36">http://www.gotfarmanimalsonline.com/sitemap.shtml</link><title>Farm Animals - Pictures, Breeders, Rescue, Photos</title><description>* Farm Animals - Pictures, Breeders, Rescue, Photos (clueweb12-0110wb-48-00023) http://www.gotfarmanimalsonline.com/sitemap.shtml ...of that hard lifestyle. Brahma Bull - The brahma bull baby can be found on most farms that raise exotic animals. Animal Breeders - Animal breeders may work on a farm and raise babies. farms; in some instances, a breeder will maintain them personally. Buy Animal \- You can buy animal pictures, posters, and photos on the web; many times, they're available for free. ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:04:11">http://www.teambio.org/team/animals+stamps+art.aspx</link><title>Find the fun in politics with animals stamps art and more here!</title><description>* Find the fun in politics with animals stamps art and more here! (clueweb12-0612wb-44-18016) http://www.teambio.org/team/animals+stamps+art.aspx Find the fun in politics with animals stamps art and more here!  ...BannersCampaign FlagsCampaign Yard SignsCampaign MedalsCampaign Stampsanimals stamps art!FARM ANIMALS art impressions rubber stamps Current Price: $5.59 Buy it now: n/aRED Frame FISH ART Print "Timothy Got Stamped" DIY Ready to Display Current Price: $6.99 Buy it now: $12.99Nail Art: Nail Stamp Plate: Flower, Firework, Animal Current Price: $5.99 Buy it now: $6.99GRIZZLY BEAR Clear Unmounted Rubber Stamp... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:04:56">http://theanimalfarm.greedbag.com/products.xml</link><title>Roxy&amp;#39;s Wardrobe : Chemicals.Perfume.Burn. - Download Single</title><description>* Roxy&amp;#39;s Wardrobe : Chemicals.Perfume.Burn. - Download Single (clueweb12-0700tw-23-21610) http://theanimalfarm.greedbag.com/products.xml New from The Animal Farm New from The Animal Farm http://theanimalfarm.greedbag.com 5806875110142 Violet Bones : Chemicals - Download Single http://theanimalfarm.greedbag.com/buy/chemicals-5/ 0.79 GBP Violet Bones : Chemicals - Download Single - new 5055453639821 The Animal Farm TAFDIGI081-greed_wav http://mog.state51.co.uk/tid/8657bca099e8a7921a6443b53fe875792f1fd859/eicibjs/bbuzpubbgo/5806877220054.jpeg Media... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-05"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0452277507-Animal_Farm_A_Fairy_Story.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm: A Fairy Story</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm: A Fairy Story (clueweb12-0401wb-83-00421) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0452277507-Animal_Farm_A_Fairy_Story.html ...Swiss Mountain Dog Quality Books, Gear, Training, and GiftsAnimal Farm: A Fairy Story Author:George Orwell   Creator:Russell Baker   Brand:Penguin Group USA   Category:Book List Price: $13.00 Buy New: $6.55 as of 2/26/2012 01:35 MST details You Save: $6.... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-06"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0452284244-Animal_Farm_Centennial_Edition.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm: Centennial Edition</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm: Centennial Edition (clueweb12-0311wb-20-22994) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0452284244-Animal_Farm_Centennial_Edition.html ...Swiss Mountain Dog Quality Books, Gear, Training, and GiftsAnimal Farm: Centennial Edition Author:George Orwell   Creator:Ann Patchett   Publisher:Plume   Category:Book List Price: $14.00 Buy New: $7.49 as of 2/24/2012 10:35 MST details You Save: $6....Condition: New Notes: BRAND NEW FROM PUBLISHER! 100% Satisfaction Guarantee. Tracking provided on most orders. Buy with Confidence! Millions of books sold! Also Available In: Hardcover - Animal Farm Hardcover - Animal Farm Paperback - Animal Farm Hardcover - ANIMAL FARM Paperback - Animal Farm Paperback - Animal Farm Hardcover - Animal Farm (Transaction Large Print Books) Hardcover - Animal Farm Library Binding - Animal Farm: A Fairy Story Paperback... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-07"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0451526341-Animal_Farm.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm (clueweb12-0401wb-83-00420) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0451526341-Animal_Farm.html ...Swiss Mountain Dog Quality Books, Gear, Training, and GiftsAnimal Farm Author:George Orwell   Creator:Russell Baker   Publisher:Signet Classics   Category:Book List Price: $9.99 Buy New: $3.63 as of 2/25/2012 23:30 MST details You Save: $6....Condition: New Notes: BRAND NEW FROM PUBLISHER! 100% Satisfaction Guarantee. Tracking provided on most orders. Buy with Confidence! Millions of books sold! Also Available In: Hardcover - Animal Farm Hardcover - Animal Farm Paperback - Animal Farm Hardcover - ANIMAL FARM Paperback - Animal Farm Paperback - Animal Farm: Centennial Edition Paperback - Animal Farm Hardcover - Animal Farm (Transaction Large Print Books) Hardcover - Animal Farm Library Binding - Animal Farm... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-08"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0786102535-Animal_Farm.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm (clueweb12-0402wb-11-28613) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0786102535-Animal_Farm.html Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm ...Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm Animal Farm ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-09"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0451501217-Animal_Farm.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm (clueweb12-0401wb-95-29379) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0451501217-Animal_Farm.html Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm ...Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm Animal Farm ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7451-10"><link>http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0786119241-Animal_Farm.html</link><title>Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm</title><description>* Swiss Mountain Dog: Swiss Mountain Dog Books: Animal Farm (clueweb12-0401wb-95-29386) http://greater.swiss.mountain.dog.dogtraining-books.com/Books-1000-0786119241-Animal_Farm.html ...Swiss Mountain Dog Quality Books, Gear, Training, and GiftsAnimal Farm Author:George Orwell   Creator:Richard Brown   Publisher:Blackstone Audiobooks   Category:Book List Price: $21.95 Buy Used: $5.53 as of 2/26/2012 01:39 MST details You Save: $16...and exhausted, no better off than in the days when humans ran the farm. Satire Animal Farm may be, but it's a stony reader who remains unmoved when the stalwart workhorse, Boxer, having given his all to his comrades, is sold to the glue factory to buy booze for the pigs. Orwell's view of Communism is bleak indeed, but given the history... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>