<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:13:30" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:13:53">http://pcdandf.com/cms/magazine/192/3620-modeling-frequency-dependent-conductor-losses-in-serial-data-channel-interconnects--parts-1-and-2</link><title>Printed Circuit Design &amp; Fab Magazine Online</title><description>* Printed Circuit Design &amp; Fab Magazine Online (clueweb12-1508wb-07-23352) http://pcdandf.com/cms/magazine/192/3620-modeling-frequency-dependent-conductor-losses-in-serial-data-channel-interconnects--parts-1-and-2 ...Online Interconnects Ă˘âŹâ Parts 1 and 2 User Rating: / 3 PoorBest  Written by Yuriy Shlepnev...instance, are being optimized for analysis of relatively narrow-band systems and for frequencies where skin effect is well developed. Such models are not valid at low and intermediate frequencies where there is no skin effect or skin effect is not developed yet, and the models have to include those frequencies for digital applications. As a result, a broadband model of interconnects may show non-physical behavior of extracted inductance and resistance at low and intermediate frequencies... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:14:56">http://pcdandf.com/cms/magazine/95/3620</link><title>Printed Circuit Design &amp; Fab Magazine Online</title><description>* Printed Circuit Design &amp; Fab Magazine Online (clueweb12-0401wb-54-30200) http://pcdandf.com/cms/magazine/95/3620 ...Online Interconnects Ă˘âŹâ Parts 1 and 2 User Rating: / 3 PoorBest  Written by Yuriy Shlepnev...instance, are being optimized for analysis of relatively narrow-band systems and for frequencies where skin effect is well developed. Such models are not valid at low and intermediate frequencies where there is no skin effect or skin effect is not developed yet, and the models have to include those frequencies for digital applications. As a result, a broadband model of interconnects may show non-physical behavior of extracted inductance and resistance at low and intermediate frequencies... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:15:59">http://www.audioholics.com/audio-video-cables/interview-with-dr-howard-johnson-about-skin-effect</link><title>Skin Effect Interview with Dr. Howard Johnson — Reviews and News from Audioholics</title><description>* Skin Effect Interview with Dr. Howard Johnson — Reviews and News from Audioholics (clueweb12-0411wb-88-22847) http://www.audioholics.com/education/cables/interview-with-dr-howard-johnson-about-skin-effect ...Entertainment Cables &amp; Power Furniture &amp; Accessories DIY Install Interconnects → Skin Effect Interview with Dr. Howard Johnson Skin Effect Interview with Dr. Howard Johnson skin effect and "strand jumping" on speaker cables and interconnects. I am attempting to disprove the relevance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:16:36">http://www.audioholics.com/audio-video-cables/skin-effect-relevance-in-speaker-cables</link><title>Skin Effect Relevance in Speaker Cables — Reviews and News from Audioholics</title><description>* Skin Effect Relevance in Speaker Cables — Reviews and News from Audioholics (clueweb12-0411wb-85-21030) http://www.audioholics.com/education/cables/skin-effect-relevance-in-speaker-cables Skin Effect Relevance in Speaker Cables — Reviews and News from Audioholics ...Controls Speakers Televisions &amp; Displays AV University Acoustics Principles Amplifier Technology Audio Formats &amp; Technology Cables and Interconnects Display Formats &amp; Technology Frequently Asked Questions Loudspeaker Basics Surround Sound What to Buy Recommended Systems...Entertainment Cables &amp; Power Furniture &amp; Accessories DIY Install Interconnects → Skin Effect Relevance in Speaker Cables Skin Effect Relevance in Speaker Cables Skin Effect can cause deleterious effects on your audio performance. While Skin Effect is a real world problem in high frequency applications such as RF Power and Transmission... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:17:08">http://www.cardas.com/content.php?area=faqs&amp;content_id=4&amp;pagestring=Cable+Design</link><title>Cardas Audio</title><description>* Cardas Audio (clueweb12-1908wb-59-07468) http://www.cardas.com/content.php?area=faqs&amp;content_id=4&amp;pagestring=Cable+Design ...Quadlink vs Golden Cross capacitance Q.) Dear Mr. Cardas, may I ask a question? Quadlink interconnect capacitance is higher than Golden Cross, but in the case of loudspeaker cable the Golden...matched set. Which ever storage medium is dominant establishes the "Q" of the cable. In interconnects, the capacitance is the most relative because signal is transferred as voltage fluctuation with little... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:17:36">http://www.calce.umd.edu/articles/abstracts/2009/Skin_Effect_Detection_Interconnect_Degrad_abstract.html</link><title>Use of the Skin Effect for Detection of Interconnect Degradation</title><description>* Use of the Skin Effect for Detection of Interconnect Degradation (clueweb12-0407wb-06-13413) http://www.calce.umd.edu/articles/abstracts/2009/Skin_Effect_Detection_Interconnect_Degrad_abstract.html ďťż Use of the Skin Effect for Detection of Interconnect Degradation IMAPS 42nd Int. Symposium on Microelectronics, San Jose, CA, Nov. 1-5, 2009 Use of the Skin Effect for Detection of Interconnect Degradation Michael H. Azarian1, Daeil Kwon1, and Michael Pecht...between a short and an open, such as a partially degraded interconnect. Under cyclic loading conditions, interconnect degradation is caused by fatigue cracking... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-07"><link>http://www.iec.org/newsletter/aug06_2/design_eng_1.html</link><title>IEC Newsletter</title><description>* IEC Newsletter (clueweb12-0201wb-55-31876) http://www.iec.org/newsletter/aug06_2/design_eng_1.html ...The T-line waveforms in Figure 1 lack rounding in the edge transitions, since the skin effect and dielectric losses are not modeled. The W-line waveforms exhibit rounded edge transitions at...through the 50% crossing point). This effect is exacerbated by etch length and narrow lines. Skin effect is the inductive effect that causes a large proportion of the current carried in a conductor at high frequency to be carried in the outer part (skin) of a wire or conductor. The simulation results for transmission lines less than three inches illustrate that lossy interconnect models are generally not required, even with extremely fast rise times; while lossy models are... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:18:52">http://www.blackdahlia.com/tipindex/tip_25/tip_25.html</link><title>tip_25</title><description>* tip_25 (clueweb12-1910wb-16-17049) http://www.blackdahlia.com/tipindex/tip_25/tip_25.html ...minor  in nature, except for the addition of MAC wireand Kimber Kable Select KS 1030 interconnect to the recommended list. The notion of cable as a high-end component, so contentious...not 6N) silver and that other factors beyond materials come into play (see discussion on skin effect). However, OFC and even 6N copper are easily outdistanced by 4N silver in terms of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:19:29">http://referencefidelitycomponents.co.uk/design-of-interconnects/</link><title>What are great hifi interconnects and hifi loudspeaker cable |</title><description>* What are great hifi interconnects and hifi loudspeaker cable | (clueweb12-1000tw-33-17996) http://referencefidelitycomponents.co.uk/design-of-interconnects/ ...transfer impedance of the shield will equal its DC resistance. Â At frequencies above 100KHz skin effect will increase transfer impedance but we do not have to consider that for audio frequencies...is sometimes argued) the degree of “realism” on the timbre of some musical notes. Â Skin effect causes phase lag, and phase lag affects wave harmonics, so the components of harmonic series waveforms that extend well beyond audio frequency thresholds can be affected, and in turn (it is argued) can affect how that sound is perceived. Â How does this relate to interconnect design? Â Well minimising phase shift is simply a matter of designing signal conductors to... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:20:08">http://www.homegrownaudio.com/what-is-litz-wire/</link><title>Litz Wire</title><description>* Litz Wire (clueweb12-0411wb-34-25960) http://www.homegrownaudio.com/litz-wire/ ...cable used in electronics to carry alternating current. The wire is designed to reduce the skin effect and proximity effect losses in conductors used at frequencies up to about 1 MHz.[1] It consists of...stranded wire[3] or woven wire[4]. Contents  [hide]  1 Principle of operation 1.1 Skin effect 1.2 Proximity effect 2 Effectiveness 3 Applications 3.1 WWVB transmitting station 4 Notes 5 References 6 See also 7 External links Principle of operation Litz wire reduces the impact of the skin effect and the proximity effect. Skin effect The resistance of an isolated conductor at DC (0 Hz) depends on its cross sectional... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>