<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:27:56" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-01"><link>http://www.brakemasters.com/blog/category/car-fluids-info/</link><title>Car Fluids Info « Brake Buddy's Auto Repair &amp; Maintenance Blog</title><description>* Car Fluids Info « Brake Buddy's Auto Repair &amp; Maintenance Blog (clueweb12-0905wb-15-24296) http://www.brakemasters.com/blog/category/car-fluids-info/ ...auto repair shop nearby. Common causes of engine overheating include: low engine coolant, a cracked radiator, broken fans or a broken water pump. Ignoring a rising engine temperature gauge is the worst thing that you can do.Â  This can lead to tons of costly repairs including fixing a blown head gasket. Tags: broken radiator, car temperature, engine temperature, overheating car Posted in Car Fluids Info, Car Repair | Comments Off Selecting The Right Engine Coolant Wednesday, November 17th, 2010 With... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:28:49">http://www.freeonlineautorepair.com/sitemap.html</link><title>Site Map</title><description>* Site Map (clueweb12-0106wb-46-25489) http://www.freeonlineautorepair.com/sitemap.html ...System - Troubleshooting &amp; Repair Tips Automotive Electrical Troubleshooting- Troubleshooting &amp; Tips Fix Electrical Shorts in Your Own Car How to Change the Starter on a Dodge Neon How To Check For Bad Spark Plug Wires How...Tips Acura Integra Repair - How to Tips Acura Integra Maintenance Required Light Acura Integra Oil Change Acura Manual Transmission Fluid Change Acura Manual Transmission Fluid Change Acura TL Repair Acura TL 2006 iPhone 3GS Audio Video... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:30:03">http://www.wikihow.com/Change-Radiator-Fluid</link><title>How to Change Radiator Fluid: 11 steps - wikiHow</title><description>* How to Change Radiator Fluid: 11 steps - wikiHow (clueweb12-0704wb-44-11605) http://www.wikihow.com/Change-Radiator-Fluid How to Change Radiator Fluid: 11 steps - wikiHow Cars &amp; Other Vehicles » Cars » Car Maintenance and Repair » Vehicle Fuels and Fluids How to Change Radiator Fluid Edited byFlickety and 5 others ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:31:02">http://www.trustmymechanic.com/30.html</link><title>Car Maintenance Schedule for 30,000 Mile Service Interval</title><description>* Car Maintenance Schedule for 30,000 Mile Service Interval (clueweb12-0300wb-71-24692) http://www.trustmymechanic.com/30.html ...emission gases. Fram filters offers air, fuel, oil, pcv and interior cabin filters for most cars and trucks. We have been using Fram filters in my shop for years and they are probably one of the most recognizable aftermarket filter brands on the market. Antifreeze/Coolant Inspect: Check the fluid level in the plastic "overflow reservoir" and the actual level of coolant inside the radiator. You should be able to visually see the coolant level inside the radiator when the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:31:44">http://www.flypark.co.nz/vehicleservicing.jsp</link><title>Check our services while your car parking at Flypark near Auckland airport</title><description>* Check our services while your car parking at Flypark near Auckland airport (clueweb12-1012wb-59-06781) http://www.flypark.co.nz/vehicleservicing.jsp Check our services while your car parking at Flypark near Auckland airport ...up to $16 retail) - extra oil and some filters will be an additional charge 1. Change engine oil 2. Change engine oil filter 3. Check / Fill brake fluid 4\. Check brake fluid condition 5. Check / fill / test clutch fluid level 6. Check / fill / test coolant/radiator fluid level 7. Visual check of radiator cap 8. Visual check of cooling system hoses 9. Check / Fill power steering fluid 10... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:33:01">http://www.trustmymechanic.com/maint_schedule.html</link><title>Auto repair maintenance schedules, car repair troubleshooting, online manuals</title><description>* Auto repair maintenance schedules, car repair troubleshooting, online manuals (clueweb12-0301wb-11-31602) http://www.trustmymechanic.com/maint_schedule.html Auto repair maintenance schedules, car repair troubleshooting, online manuals Trust My Mechanic .com - Home of the Honest Auto Mechanic   ...or the brake pedal goes to the floor slowly while brakes are applied. 6.      Differential Fluid – (A rear differential is only found on rear wheel drive cars and trucks.) Inspect: The rear differential (commonly referred to as the rear end) fluid or grease should be checked during each routine oil change and topped off as needed with the fluid prescribed in the owner’s manual. Replace: Drain and flush the rear end fluid periodically... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:33:31">http://www.flypark.co.nz/data.html</link><title>http://www.flypark.co.nz/data.html</title><description>* http://www.flypark.co.nz/data.html (clueweb12-1012wb-59-06779) http://www.flypark.co.nz/data.html ...Diesel Platinum change with up to 4 litres of quality oil and standard oil filter (up to $16...up to $16 retail) - extra oil and some filters will be an additional charge 1. Change engine oil 2. Change engine oil filter 3. Check / Fill brake fluid 4\. Check brake fluid condition 5. Check / fill / test clutch fluid level 6. Check / fill / test coolant/radiator fluid level 7. Visual check of radiator cap 8. Visual check of cooling system hoses 9. Check / Fill power steering fluid 10... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:34:01">http://www.carinsurance.org/car-maintenance</link><title>Basic Car Maintenance - Car Insurance.org</title><description>* Basic Car Maintenance - Car Insurance.org (clueweb12-1310wb-92-15795) http://www.carinsurance.org/car-maintenance/ ...the level of the transmission fluid. If additional fluid is need your only approved transmission fluid. Change transmission fluid every 24,000 miles, two years or has instructed by your owners manual. How to...check oil light may symbolize the need for more oil a need for an oil change. The temperature light reacts to the radiator fluids temperature. It will come on if the temperature is too high. The service light can mean several things such as the car needs a tune up or service. Dashboard Warning Lights 101 How to Interpret Your Car's Warning Lights -- powered by eHow.com Inspections In many states inspections are required. In 18... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:34:40">http://www.autohub360.com/index.php/different-fluid-levels-that-need-to-be-checked-on-a-vehicle-2596/</link><title>Different fluid levels that need to be checked on a vehicle - by Anthony Megna - Helium</title><description>* Different fluid levels that need to be checked on a vehicle - by Anthony Megna - Helium (clueweb12-0301tw-18-03519) http://www.helium.com/items/2065448-different-fluid-levels-that-need-to-be-checked-on-a-vehicle Different fluid levels that need to be checked on a vehicle - by Anthony Megna - Helium ...where it's level is at that moment. To be on the safe side, check the fluid once per month.  Cars today don't need to have their oil changed nearly as much as in the past, but checking the level of the oil can't hurt. GA_googleFillSlotWithSize(HELAD_publishercode, "ArticleATFMiddleArticle300x250", 300, 250); The next important fluid to check is the water/antifreeze level.  There is a cap for this on the radiator of the vehicle and/or a dipstick as well. Don't check this after the car... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:35:24">http://denverexpresscare.com/category/car-maintenance/page/3</link><title>Car Maintenance | Express Car Care of Denver - Part 3</title><description>* Car Maintenance | Express Car Care of Denver - Part 3 (clueweb12-1714wb-97-28456) http://denverexpresscare.com/category/car-maintenance/page/3 Car Maintenance | Express Car Care of Denver - Part 3 Change Automatic Transmission Fuel System Cleaning Radiator Flush Service Wiper Blades Air Filter Cabin Air Filter Gearbox Service Brake Service Clutches CV Boots Tune-Up Steering &amp; Suspension Tires Products Motor Oil Auto Transmission Fluid Antifreeze Fuel System Products Other Products Shop Specials Blog About Us ... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>