<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7485">bachelor party jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:14:55" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:15:14">http://www.partypractical.com/search/iowa/event/bachelor-party.html</link><title>Iowa Bachelor Party, Iowa Bachelor Party Planning, Iowa Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors</title><description>* Iowa Bachelor Party, Iowa Bachelor Party Planning, Iowa Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors (clueweb12-0814wb-12-10502) http://www.partypractical.com/search/iowa/event/bachelor-party.html Iowa Bachelor Party, Iowa Bachelor Party Planning, Iowa Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors Party Store | FAQs | Advertise With Us | Link To Us | Downloads | Contact Us           Party Practical USA Party - Bachelor Party in Iowa - Iowa Bachelor Party Planning Home -&gt; Iowa Party Events and Vendors -&gt; Bachelor Party   Select Your City   Iowa Ackley Bachelor PartyIowa Ackworth Bachelor Party Iowa Adair Bachelor Party... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:15:55">http://www.centralconnector.com/central/girl+playing+cards.aspx</link><title>Hobby Supplies Including girl playing cards.</title><description>* Hobby Supplies Including girl playing cards. (clueweb12-0507wb-49-32109) http://www.centralconnector.com/central/girl+playing+cards.aspx ...LegosMarblesVintage GamesUsed GamesPC GamesRobotsLeap FrogFamily GamesMonopoly GamesParty GamesAdult GamesWar GamesWord GamesLearning GamesDVD GamesTravel GamesAngry BirdsJoke Deck Poker Game Party Naked Gag Bachelor Gift$4.95NUDE Playing cards NAKED WOMEN POLISH GIRLS COLLECTION!!! ADULT$12.99NUDE... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:16:32">http://www.partypractical.com/search/louisiana/event/bachelor-party.html</link><title>Louisiana Bachelor Party, Louisiana Bachelor Party Planning, Louisiana Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors</title><description>* Louisiana Bachelor Party, Louisiana Bachelor Party Planning, Louisiana Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors (clueweb12-0814wb-64-10118) http://www.partypractical.com/search/louisiana/event/bachelor-party.html Louisiana Bachelor Party, Louisiana Bachelor Party Planning, Louisiana Bachelor Party Ideas and Favors Party Store | FAQs | Advertise With Us | Link To Us | Downloads | Contact Us           Party Practical USA Party - Bachelor Party in Louisiana - Louisiana Bachelor Party Planning Home -&gt; Louisiana Party Events and Vendors -&gt; Bachelor Party   Select Your City   Louisiana Abbeville Bachelor PartyLouisiana Abita Springs Bachelor Party Louisiana Addis Bachelor... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:16:58">http://www.centralconnector.com/central/girls+playing+cards+deck.aspx</link><title>Hobby Supplies Including girls playing cards deck.</title><description>* Hobby Supplies Including girls playing cards deck. (clueweb12-0505wb-67-32204) http://www.centralconnector.com/central/girls+playing+cards+deck.aspx ...LegosMarblesVintage GamesUsed GamesPC GamesRobotsLeap FrogFamily GamesMonopoly GamesParty GamesAdult GamesWar GamesWord GamesLearning GamesDVD GamesTravel GamesAngry Birds...card deck antique ART DECO PIN UP GIRL$12.34FULL NUDE GIRL PLAYING CARDS Joke Deck Poker Game Party Naked Gag Bachelor Gift$4.95Double Deck Mac Tharson Vargas Pin Up Girls Playing Cards in Box 1945 USA$9.99Bachelor Gift JUMBO NUDE GIRL PLAYING CARDS Joke Deck Poker Game Dirty Female$3.99Toronto Sun Newspaper Sunshine Girls 8th Edition Deck... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:17:48">http://www.mypartyplanner.com/search/event/Bachelor-or-Bachelorette/select_state.html</link><title>Bachelorette Party Ideas, Bachelor Party Games, Pics &amp; Invitations</title><description>* Bachelorette Party Ideas, Bachelor Party Games, Pics &amp; Invitations (clueweb12-0602wb-94-28515) http://www.mypartyplanner.com/search/event/Bachelor-or-Bachelorette/select_state.html Bachelorette Party Ideas, Bachelor Party Games, Pics &amp; Invitations ...Party Retirement Party Reunion School Event Senior Events Sporting Event Valentines Day Bachelor Party PlanningParty \- Bachelor Party... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:18:16">http://www.blog.hr/print/id/1629651912/download-bachelor-party-vegas-movie.html</link><title>Download BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS Movie - Hermina Ellyn - Blog.hr</title><description>* Download BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS Movie - Hermina Ellyn - Blog.hr (clueweb12-0710wb-48-18863) http://www.blog.hr/print/id/1629651912/download-bachelor-party-vegas-movie.html Download BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS Movie - Hermina Ellyn - Blog.hr BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS Movie Download BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS MovieYear: 2006Country: USAGenre: Adventure, ComedyDirectors &amp; Writers: Eric Bernt, Dennis Dugan...Penn, Barry Diamond, Lin Shaye, Barbara Stuart, Deborah Harmon, Bob BarkerDownload Movie:orDownload BACHELOR PARTY VEGAS Movie - Click Here &gt;&gt;&gt;Download Others Movies: - Download MURDER PARTY Movie - Download THE GHOST GOES WEST Movie - Download A PAIN IN THE PULLMAN Movie - Download... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-07"><link>http://www.ideacenter.com/5/idea66.html</link><title>Bachelor Party Ideas</title><description>* Bachelor Party Ideas (clueweb12-1116wb-28-06571) http://www.ideacenter.com/5/idea66.html ...version with our easy to follow Quick Start Guide. Click Here Right Now The best bachelor party ideas : Bachelor Party Fun Bachelor gifts and party planning tips, jokes, models, playmates, condoms, and more. Bachelor Party - Bachelor Parties &amp; Bachelor Party Ideas - BachelorBlowOut.com Searching for the perfect Bachelor Party Idea? Plan a bachelor party in Las Vegas? BachelorBlowOut.com is the premier bachelor and bachelorette party planning service in Las Vegas. ... If you already have bachelor party ideas in mind for... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-08"><link>http://www.partypop.com/v/4000850/Bachelor-Party-Fun</link><title>Bachelorparty Fun - Bachelor Party Serving Nationwide</title><description>* Bachelorparty Fun - Bachelor Party Serving Nationwide (clueweb12-0208wb-80-17373) http://www.partypop.com/v/4000850/Bachelor-Party-Fun Bachelorparty Fun - Bachelor Party Serving Nationwide ...Bachelor Party Fun is your number one source for planning a bachelor party or fraternity party. Add to My FavoritesShare Profile Gallery Bachelor Party Fun (www.bachelorpartyfun.com) is the one stop shop for bachelor party ideas, supplies, games and bachelor party gifts and they offer a FREE gift with every order. Their site has free bachelor party content including bachelor party jokes, e-cards, game ideas, drink ideas, links to valuable bachelor party resources as well as... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7485_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:20:32">http://www.centralconnector.com/central/playing+cards+full+deck.aspx</link><title>Hobby Supplies Including playing cards full deck.</title><description>* Hobby Supplies Including playing cards full deck. (clueweb12-0501wb-73-16154) http://www.centralconnector.com/central/playing+cards+full+deck.aspx ...Tilt Poker Playing Cards - 6 Decks!! - Brand New!!$5.00FULL NUDE GIRL PLAYING CARDS Joke Deck Poker Game Party Naked Gag Bachelor Gift$4.95Gypsy Witch Fortune-Telling Playing Cards - Full 52 Card Deck, Instructions$9....gold-plated playing cards – unique status collectible!$79.9954 FULL NUDE GIRL PLAYING CARDS Bachelor Party Joke 1 Deck Poker Game Naked Gag$4.95MANNY PACQUIAO PAC-MAN POKER PLAYING CARDS... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7485-10"><link>http://chengdu.craigslist.com.cn/eve/2410804142.html</link><title>Cleveland Bachelor Party stripper 216 370 7990 Akron Canton Strippers</title><description>* Cleveland Bachelor Party stripper 216 370 7990 Akron Canton Strippers (clueweb12-0709wb-75-10686) http://chengdu.craigslist.com.cn/eve/2410804142.html Cleveland Bachelor Party stripper 216 370 7990 Akron Canton Strippers email this posting to a friend chengdu craigslist &gt; event &gt; events please flag with care: [?] miscategorized prohibited spam/overpost best of craigslist 5/30-6/13: Cleveland Bachelor Party stripper 216 370 7990 Akron Canton Strippers (Cleveland Bachelor Party stripper 216 37) Date: 2011-05-31, 1:16AM CST Reply to: dbghz-2410804142@event... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>