<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:27:59" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:28:27">http://sillybeans.com/free-april-fools-prank-ideas.php/</link><title>free april fools prank ideas Resources</title><description>* free april fools prank ideas Resources (clueweb12-0603wb-55-00301) http://www.sillybeans.com/free-april-fools-prank-ideas.php free april fools prank ideas Resources April Fools Prank Ideas Resources ...12] [13] [14] [15] &gt;&gt; Joke, Comedy and Humorous Websites! 50) this.border=1" alt="free april fools prank ideas" width="120" height="90"&gt; April Fools Practical Jokes Gag Gifts Contains a list of pranks from 1990 to present day. Also includes ideas for gag pranks. [ Click To Open In A New Window ] ... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:29:01">http://www.altiusdirectory.com/Society/april-fools-day-ideas.html</link><title>April Fools Day Ideas 2012 April Fools Ideas Tricks Ideas for April Fools Day.</title><description>* April Fools Day Ideas 2012 April Fools Ideas Tricks Ideas for April Fools Day. (clueweb12-0400wb-73-16935) http://www.altiusdirectory.com/Society/april-fools-day-ideas.html April Fools Day Ideas 2012 April Fools Ideas Tricks Ideas for April Fools Day. April Fools Day Ideas Day Ideas Ideas of April Fools Day A day, get pleasure from shame and fraud is called ‘All Fools Day’. ‘All Fools Day’ is started in Europe at first. ‘All Fools Day’ is known as ‘April Fools... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-03"><link>http://www.toytokyo.com/htmlarea/online/april-fools/</link><title>april day fool idea origin of april fool day april fool open snowmobile video water</title><description>* april day fool idea origin of april fool day april fool open snowmobile video water (clueweb12-0303wb-46-05248) http://www.toytokyo.com/htmlarea/online/april-fools/ april day fool idea origin of april fool day april fool open snowmobile video water april day fool idea april day fool idea, origin of april fool day, april fool open snowmobile video water april day fool ideaapril day fool idea origin of april fool day april fool open snowmobile video water celebrate april fool day april fool trick april fool kid prank... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:30:16">http://www.humsurfer.com/april-fool-pranks-and-sms-messages</link><title>April Fool Pranks and SMS Messages: Humsurfer</title><description>* April Fool Pranks and SMS Messages: Humsurfer (clueweb12-0502wb-10-02951) http://www.humsurfer.com/april-fool-pranks-and-sms-messages April Fool Pranks and SMS Messages: Humsurfer ...Fool SMS | April Fool Pranks | April Fool Gags | April Fool Tricks | Love Anniversary SMS | Hindi April Fool SMS | Urdu April Fool SMS | Cute April Fool SMS | Cool April Fool SMS | English April Fool SMS | April Fool SMS Messages | April Fool S M S | April Fool Msgs | April Fool Mobile Messages | Romantic April Fool SMS | April Fool Messages | April Fool Ideas | Bengali April Fool SMS | Punjabi April Fool SMS Send these April Fool SMS Messages to your friend, boss... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:30:49">http://smsheat.com/category/april-fool-sms/page/4/</link><title>April Fool Pranks - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages</title><description>* April Fool Pranks - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages (clueweb12-0210wb-68-08003) http://www.smsheat.com/sms-messages/april-fool-pranks.htm April Fool Pranks - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages April Fool Jokes | Funny April Fool SMS | April Fool Pranks | April Fool Tricks | April Fool Ideas | April Fool Gags | April Fool E Cards | April Fool Cards | April Fool Messages |  Love April Fool SMS | Hindi April Fool SMS | Urdu April Fool SMS | Cute... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:31:18">http://www.mijnwinstmethode.com/?A=4746&amp;SubAffiliateID=18945660&amp;sid=20140425183118af816a0ed99fef04d5</link><title>April Fools Pranks, April Fools Tricks, April Fools Joke | April Fools Jokes 2012</title><description>* April Fools Pranks, April Fools Tricks, April Fools Joke | April Fools Jokes 2012 (clueweb12-0700tw-82-22838) http://aprilfools-jokes.com/april-fools-pranks-april-fools-tricks-april-fools-joke April Fools Pranks, April Fools Tricks, April Fools Joke | April Fools Jokes 2012 April Fools Jokes – April Fools Day Joke Ideas Pranks, April Fools Tricks, April Fools Joke Posted in Main | March 8th, 2012 April Fools Pranks for school listed here will make april fools day one of the best holidays of the year. April fools is just a few weeks away and its always fun to get someone a surprise whether you love them. April fools is a special... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:31:50">http://smsheat.com/category/april-fool-sms/page/3/</link><title>April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages \- April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages</title><description>* April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages \- April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages (clueweb12-0210wb-61-34206) http://www.smsheat.com/sms-messages/april-fool-jokes.htm April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages April Fool Jokes | Funny April Fool SMS | April Fool Pranks | April Fool Tricks | April Fool Ideas | April Fool Gags | April Fool E Cards | April Fool Cards | April Fool Messages |  Love April Fool SMS | Hindi April Fool SMS | Urdu April Fool SMS | Cute April... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:32:22">http://smsheat.com/category/april-fool-sms/page/5/</link><title>April Fool Messages - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages</title><description>* April Fool Messages - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages (clueweb12-0210wb-61-34207) http://www.smsheat.com/sms-messages/april-fool-messages.htm April Fool Messages - April Fool Jokes - April Fool Messages - Cute April Fool SMS Messages - April Fool Pranks - April Fool Gags - Text SMS Messages April Fool Messages | Funny April Fool SMS | April Fool Pranks | April Fool Tricks | April Fool Ideas | April Fool Gags | April Fool E Cards | April Fool Cards | April Fool Messages |  Love April Fool SMS | Hindi April Fool SMS | Urdu April Fool SMS | Cute... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:32:50">http://www.mijnwinstmethode.com/?A=4746&amp;SubAffiliateID=18945660&amp;sid=2014042518325098ba08dfd28b9a594a</link><title>April Fool Prank Ideas for 1st April 2012 | April Fools Jokes 2012</title><description>* April Fool Prank Ideas for 1st April 2012 | April Fools Jokes 2012 (clueweb12-0700tw-75-08873) http://aprilfools-jokes.com/april-fool-prank-ideas-for-1st-april-2011 April Fool Prank Ideas for 1st April 2012 | April Fools Jokes 2012 April Fools Jokes – April Fools Day Joke Ideas Prank Ideas for 1st April 2012 Posted in Main | March 7th, 2012 April Foolâs Day is celebrated on 1st April in Western world every year. sometimes called as All Foolâs Day, it is not any legal holiday however is celebrated and recognized widely as the day that tolerates foolishness and practical jokes. This day is also marked by commission of hoaxes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7487-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7487_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:33:28">http://journalbuddies.com/tag/journal-topics/</link><title>Journal Topics | Journal BuddiesÂŽ | Journaling, Kids Writing, Writing Ideas, Writing Prompts, Creative Writing, Girl Diary, Boy Diary and more</title><description>* Journal Topics | Journal BuddiesÂŽ | Journaling, Kids Writing, Writing Ideas, Writing Prompts, Creative Writing, Girl Diary, Boy Diary and more (clueweb12-1806wb-57-25063) http://journalbuddies.com/tag/journal-topics/ ...or not it’s necessary for people to ownâŚ more 53 Journal Writing Topics about April Fool’s Day Journal Writing Topics: April Fool’s Day– This April holiday is a fun...coming soon!). With this list of new journal prompts, students can reminisce about their favorite April Fool’s jokes and think about ideas for their latest pranks. They’ll consider whether they prefer funny or scary jokes, while also thinking about how they feel when they get tricked by someone else. Help your students get inspired this April Fool’s Day with these silly journal writing topics â just watch out that they don’t... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>