<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:58:35" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-01"><link>http://www.free-software-programs.com/freeware/wav-to-mp3-converter.html</link><title>Free Wav to mp3 converter</title><description>* Free Wav to mp3 converter (clueweb12-0502wb-24-21319) http://www.free-software-programs.com/freeware/wav-to-mp3-converter.html Free Wav to mp3 converter ...2 WAV files. Crystal MP3 Converter Crystal MP3 Converter can digitally convert wav to mp3 and support normalizing. ImTOO MP3 WAV Converter A great MP3 WAV converter and supports converting for video or audio file format Convert your favorite MP3 files into WAV files and vice versa. With this program you can convert MP3s to Wav files with just a single right click of the... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:59:51">http://www.sharewareconnection.com/titles/wav.htm</link><title>Software Download: Wav</title><description>* Software Download: Wav (clueweb12-0609wb-77-01266) http://www.sharewareconnection.com/titles/wav.htm ...to mp3 Visual MP To Wav Converter License: Shareware Price: $19.95 Convert MP3 to Wav, including normal PCM wav and 10 compressed wav formats Visual MP3 To Wav Converter can convert your MP3 files to more than 10 different compressed WAV formats including Microsoft ADPCM Wav, Compressed CD-Quality and Computer Telephony format for burning audio CD or keeping of human speech. The program is very easy to use, just select the files to be converted and go. You... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:00:50">http://popular.softlandmark.com/mp3_to_wav_converter.html</link><title>mp3 To Wav Converter Downloads and Reviews</title><description>* mp3 To Wav Converter Downloads and Reviews (clueweb12-0401wb-82-17694) http://popular.softlandmark.com/mp3_to_wav_converter.html mp3 To Wav Converter Downloads and Reviews ...Software Shareware and Freeware Software Downloads: mp3 to wav converter Show: All Free #1 Smart MP3 to WAV Converter 2.12 MP3 to WAV Converter is one of the quickest and easiest to use audio tools of its kind. The program completes conversions in seconds, decoding MP3 files to burnable and editable WAV files.It is ideal for converting batches of MP3 files thus saving your precious time. The program works on all Windows systems. When it... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-04"><link>http://www.downloadfreetrial.com/audio/audio_file_conversion.html</link><title>Download FreeTrial - MP3 &amp; Audio | Audio File Conversion</title><description>* Download FreeTrial - MP3 &amp; Audio | Audio File Conversion (clueweb12-0111wb-10-28900) http://www.downloadfreetrial.com/audio/audio_file_conversion.html ...Web Scripts Directory|      |Submit Software|    |Advertise|   Categories Utilities Business Desktop MP3 &amp; Audio Multimedia Tools Internet Programs Games Web Authoring Web Scripts Development Educational Hobbies Miscellaneous Marketplace Products E-Books Directory Authors Submit Software Offers to Developers Affiliate Programs Site Map MP3 &amp; Audio | Audio File Conversion This page contains MP3 &amp; Audio conversion software, and cd rippers var ranNum= Math.floor(Math.random()*1)+1; if (ranNum==1) { document.write("") } Featured Software TitlesAbyssMedia MP3 to WAV Converter 1.10 - Batch MP3 to WAV conversion utility License: Shareware Advanced WMA Workshop 2.... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-05"><link>http://www.get-software.info/quick_easy_free/gr/grabber-739.html</link><title>grabber software</title><description>* grabber software (clueweb12-1313wb-19-25758) http://www.get-software.info/quick_easy_free/gr/grabber-739.html ...iPod: AudioTo iPod saves different audio files &amp; tracks from audioCD to Apple iPod WinXMedia CD MP3/WAV/WMA Converter: An advanced CD ripper and audio format converter with user-friendly interface. Fast...Converter: Fast Audio Converter - a supreme converter for the popular audio, video formats. Audio To MP3 Converter: Convert audio files to MP3 format with high quality. ImTOO Audio Encoder: Super easy... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:04:17">http://top.softlandmark.com/Bell_Church_Wav.html</link><title>Bell Church Wav Software Free Download</title><description>* Bell Church Wav Software Free Download (clueweb12-1516wb-25-31516) http://top.softlandmark.com/Bell_Church_Wav.html ...Password Recovery Pdf Page Split Merge Extract Pro Related Mp3 To Wav #1 Cd To Mp3 Wav Maker Cd To Wav Wav #1 Wav Mp3 Converter Wav Recorder A Wav Tuning Abc...Harmonious Bells system sounds for your desktop come packaged with the same rich featured ChurchBells program used by many churches as their belltower ministry to outreach into their communities. 05-Aug-2010 8.2 MB Freeware Screenshot Download More Info MP3 WAV Maker 1.04 CD to MP3 WAV Maker is an extremely easy and fast-speed tool to convert your audio CD to MP3, WAV, WMA and OGG files. It copies the audio digitally... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-07"><link>http://www.cuteapps.com/good_free_software/wa/wav_encoder-1179.html</link><title>wav encoder software</title><description>* wav encoder software (clueweb12-0108wb-62-02472) http://www.cuteapps.com/good_free_software/wa/wav_encoder-1179.html wav encoder software     Categories Last searches Companies Info ...encoder LAME ASPI cd ripper CD to...)Download AltoMP3 Gold An attractive CD ripper that converts CD to MP3 or wave files easily Jesterware DVD Audio Ripper 2.13- DVD Audio Ripper is the ultimate DVD Audio converter program[ Get it - More information and user's reviews about Jesterware DVD Audio Ripper ] (This utility is related to: dvd to mp3 audio ripper dvd to wav dvd to aac dvd to ogg dvd audio ripper...)Download Jesterware DVD Audio Ripper DVD... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:05:47">http://top.softlandmark.com/Answering_Wav.html</link><title>Answering Wav Software Free Download</title><description>* Answering Wav Software Free Download (clueweb12-1512wb-64-06156) http://top.softlandmark.com/Answering_Wav.html ...freedb function. 06-Aug-2010 2.8 MB Shareware Screenshot Download More Info MP3 to WAV Converter 2.12 MP3 to WAV Converter is one of the quickest and easiest to use audio tools of its kind. The program completes conversions in seconds, decoding MP3 files to burnable and editable WAV files.It is ideal for converting batches of MP3 files thus saving your precious time. The program works on all Windows systems. When it... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:06:38">http://top.softlandmark.com/Recycle_Ben_Wav.html</link><title>Recycle Ben Wav Software Free Download</title><description>* Recycle Ben Wav Software Free Download (clueweb12-0010wb-95-26966) http://top.softlandmark.com/Recycle_Ben_Wav.html ...freedb function. 06-Aug-2010 2.8 MB Shareware Screenshot Download More Info #1 Smart MP3 to WAV Converter 2.12 MP3 to WAV Converter is one of the quickest and easiest to use audio tools of its kind. The program completes conversions in seconds, decoding MP3 files to burnable and editable WAV files.It is ideal for converting batches of MP3 files thus saving your precious time. The program works on all Windows systems. When it... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7491-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7491_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:07:16">http://pcwin.com/downloads/Wav.htm</link><title>Wav - Free Software Downloads and Reviews</title><description>* Wav - Free Software Downloads and Reviews (clueweb12-0403wb-45-10790) http://pcwin.com/downloads/Wav.htm ...Wall Photo Maker TriceraSoft CDG Ripper Atomic Mail Sender FolderHighlight Yesterdata Photo Recovery Wav Wav Files To Numbers Wav File - Split Wav File Into Smaller Wav Files - Convert Wav...can convert mp3 to Wav, so you can burn your own cd audio with the Wav file. Very easy to use ,You only click a button! Select all files you want to convert. Category: Audio / Rippers &amp; Encoders Publisher: one click, License: Shareware, Price: USD $18.00, File Size: 819.0 KB Platform: Unknown MP3 WAV Converter MP3 WAV Converter program is designed to convert between MP3 format and WAV format, you can convert WAV music... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>