<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:14:40" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:15:11">http://www.timizzer.com/</link><title>Timizzer</title><description>* Timizzer (clueweb12-1900tw-13-21716) http://www.timizzer.com/money-2/social-media-and-islamic-finance-practical-partners/ ...Guest Lists Staff Lists Events Investors Cut Business Solutions Education Resources Partners Social Media and Islamic Finance: Practical Partners? 22/04/2012 by Hayden Richards ...Media and Islamic Finance: Practical Partners? 22/04/2012 by Hayden Richards Social Media and  Islamic finance have in common?. Are there synergies between retail Islamic finance and Social Media?. Should... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:16:10">http://friendfeed.com/social-media-enthusiasts</link><title>Social Media Enthusiasts - FriendFeed</title><description>* Social Media Enthusiasts - FriendFeed (clueweb12-0310wb-67-07149) http://friendfeed.com/social-media-enthusiasts Social Media Enthusiasts - FriendFeed Sign in or Join FriendFeed FriendFeed is the easiest way to share...FriendFeed is the easiest way to share online. Learn more » Join FriendFeed 1,344 subscribers Social Media Enthusiasts A room for people to discuss Social Media,New Media &amp; Online Meida Subscribe to Social Media Enthusiasts About 2 posts per day Ana Hoffman to Ana's feed, Blogging and Business Success Collaboration, The Bloggers Discussions, Twitter, Twitter Apps, Social Media Enthusiasts, Social Media 2535 Words on How to Turn sCRAPed Content into Link Building Goldmine - http://www.trafficgenerationcafe... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:16:31">http://www.oxfordbibliographies.com/view/document/obo-9780195390155/obo-9780195390155-0116.xml</link><title>Oxford Bibliographies - Islam and the Internet</title><description>* Oxford Bibliographies - Islam and the Internet (clueweb12-1406wb-17-20638) http://www.oxfordbibliographiesonline.com/view/document/obo-9780195390155/obo-9780195390155-0116.xml ...PagesPublicationsPagesAdvanced SearchMedia StudiesVictorian LiteratureIslamic StudiesLinguisticsRenaissance and ReformationBrowse All SubjectsCloseIn This Article Islam and the...and Online ResourcesText CollectionsMuslim GroupsSexualityMusicRadicalism and Political ViolenceOnline FatawaSocial Media and BlogsOnline Computer GamesIslam and the Internet by Göran Larsson Introduction The development of the global system of interconnected... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-04"><link>http://www.blackwell-compass.com/subject/sociology/article_view?article_id=soco_tr_bpl160</link><title>Teaching and Learning Guide for: Media, Racism and Islamophobia: The Representation of Islam and Muslims in the Media : Sociology Compass</title><description>* Teaching and Learning Guide for: Media, Racism and Islamophobia: The Representation of Islam and Muslims in the Media : Sociology Compass (clueweb12-0811wb-65-10390) http://www.blackwell-compass.com/subject/sociology/article_view?article_id=soco_tr_bpl160 Teaching and Learning Guide for: Media, Racism and Islamophobia: The Representation of Islam and Muslims in the Media : Sociology Compass Social and Personality Psychology Compass Language and Linguistics Compass   Home | My Compass | Help | Content Alerts | Contact... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:17:34">http://www.arabwestreport.info/subjects-we-select</link><title>Subjects we select | Arab West Report</title><description>* Subjects we select | Arab West Report (clueweb12-0914wb-04-02346) http://www.arabwestreport.info/subjects-we-select ...between churches. * Traditions and feasts such as: Holy Family, mulids, and apparitions. 15. Political and Social Context in the Arab World Articles that fall under this category deal with:  * Arab or Egyptian nationalism, Egyptian government, political parties, foreign relations of Egypt (if related to Islam), Arab-West relations, and Muslim-Christian relations. * Discussions about human rights, specific human rights organizations, or activists in Arab media. * Advocacy for democratization. * Ibn Khaldoun Center and court rulings in relation to it. * Claims that... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-06"><link>http://lass.calumet.purdue.edu/cca/gmj/fa06/graduatefa06/gmj_grad_fa06_talib.htm</link><title>Global Media Journal</title><description>* Global Media Journal (clueweb12-0006wb-94-12114) http://lass.calumet.purdue.edu/cca/gmj/fa06/graduatefa06/gmj_grad_fa06_talib.htm Global Media Journal ...Muslim discourse community.  Introduction Since 9/11 violence associated with Muslims has raised questions about Islam’s values and ideals.  While the Western media daily represent Islam as steeped in “fundamentalism” and “terrorism” many Muslims and their allies have challenged the accurateness of these claims.  One of the foci of this discussion about Islam has been Muslim women, their roles, their rights and their oppressions. Mass media are replete... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-07"><link>http://https://lass.calumet.purdue.edu/cca/gmj/fa06/graduatefa06/gmj_grad_fa06_talib.htm</link><title>Global Media Journal</title><description>* Global Media Journal (clueweb12-0400wb-44-32021) http://https://lass.calumet.purdue.edu/cca/gmj/fa06/graduatefa06/gmj_grad_fa06_talib.htm Global Media Journal ...Muslim discourse community.  Introduction Since 9/11 violence associated with Muslims has raised questions about Islam’s values and ideals.  While the Western media daily represent Islam as steeped in “fundamentalism” and “terrorism” many Muslims and their allies have challenged the accurateness of these claims.  One of the foci of this discussion about Islam has been Muslim women, their roles, their rights and their oppressions. Mass media are replete... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:18:54">http://www.resetdoc.org/story/00000000459</link><title>Press and Tv: The role of religion in the Arab new media - Patricia Kubala | Reset Dialogues on Civilizations</title><description>* Press and Tv: The role of religion in the Arab new media - Patricia Kubala | Reset Dialogues on Civilizations (clueweb12-0601wb-35-17875) http://www.resetdoc.org/story/00000000459 Press and Tv: The role of religion in the Arab new media \- Patricia Kubala | Reset Dialogues on Civilizations ...public sphere. This alternative description of the public sphere as a space of embodied, visual social practice and representation helps us to understand why the Egyptian government, for instance, has gone to great lengths to control not only discussions about, but also the representations of Islam and Islamism that appear in state-controlled media. Indeed, contests over the symbolic, the public display of Islam, were of central concern to nationalists in the early twentieth century who circulated images of... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-09"><link>http://www.centerforsocialmedia.org/future-public-media/documents/field-reports/public-media-20-field-report-new-muslim-cool-engaging-st</link><title>Public Media 2.0 Field Report: New Muslim Cool: Engaging Stakeholders in the Filmmaking Process | Center for Social Media</title><description>* Public Media 2.0 Field Report: New Muslim Cool: Engaging Stakeholders in the Filmmaking Process | Center for Social Media (clueweb12-0109wb-49-11865) http://www.centerforsocialmedia.org/future-public-media/documents/field-reports/public-media-20-field-report-new-muslim-cool-engaging-st Public Media 2.0 Field Report: New Muslim Cool: Engaging Stakeholders in the Filmmaking Process | Center for...2.0 Field Report: New Muslim Cool: Engaging Stakeholders in the Filmmaking Process | Center for Social Media ...0 Field Report: New Muslim Cool: Engaging Stakeholders in the Filmmaking Process The Center for Social Media's field reports profile innovative media for public knowledge and action. Published as part of the Center’s Ford Foundation-supported... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:20:11">http://www.islamnewsroom.com/news-we-need/1284-muslim-media-in-the-west/</link><title>Islam News Room .com</title><description>* Islam News Room .com (clueweb12-1610wb-31-02285) http://www.islamnewsroom.com/news-we-need/1284-muslim-media-in-the-west/ Muslim Media (sister report) Islam News Room .com Islam \- Donate For Islam - Islam News Room Main Menu HomeEarthquake UpdatesSearch by keywordsLife...Mosques, web-missions of communities had been launched. Internet has provided a new opportunity for media consumers to become media producers and disseminators. And consequently now we see lots of personal pages of users in the Web. The community of Muslim-bloggers is growing, Islamic groups in the popular social networks are launched. The Islamic social websites that offer similar services organized in accordance with Shariah are also created. But for... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>