<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:35:34" name="CMU ClueWeb" id="FW14-e055"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:35:53">http://www.ilsa.org/listings/llm.php</link><title>International Law Students Association - the future of international law</title><description>* International Law Students Association - the future of international law (clueweb12-0200wb-59-08733) http://www.ilsa.org/listings/llm.php ...Geneva University Law Faculty Switzerland (Geneva) International Dispute Settlement Grotius Centre for International Legal Studies, Leiden University, The Hague Campus Netherlands (The Hague) Public International Law Hamline University School of Law USA (Saint Paul) LL.M. for International Lawyers Heidelberg Universität - Universidad de Chile Chile (Santiago de Chile) International Law Hofstra University School of Law USA (Hempstead) LL.M. in American Legal Studies Hofstra University School of Law... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:36:31">http://law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/howtobecomephdcandidate.html</link><title>How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School</title><description>* How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0004wb-17-06394) http://law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/howtobecomephdcandidate.html How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School \- Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School University Leiden Law School Research Leiden Law School Nederlands Law Education Research Organisation Library Contact How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School Doing a PhD at Leiden Law School is an excellent way to increase your own expertise in a certain field, to advance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:37:03">http://www.law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/howtobecomephdcandidate.html</link><title>How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School</title><description>* How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0601wb-03-17613) http://www.law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/howtobecomephdcandidate.html How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School \- Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School University Leiden Law School Research Leiden Law School Nederlands Law Education Research Organisation Library Contact How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School Doing a PhD at Leiden Law School is an excellent way to increase your own expertise in a certain field, to advance... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:37:44">http://www.research.leiden.edu/partnerships-collaborations/research-schools-with-leiden-university-as-partner.html</link><title>Research Schools - Partnerships &amp; Collaborations - Research</title><description>* Research Schools - Partnerships &amp; Collaborations - Research (clueweb12-1001wb-96-15592) http://www.research.leiden.edu/partnerships-collaborations/research-schools-with-leiden-university-as-partner.html Research Schools \- Partnerships &amp; Collaborations - Research Leiden University Research Portal Partnerships &amp; Collaborations Nederlands Research About Research Research Profiles Institutes Libraries Contact Research Schools Research Schools in which Leiden University participates or acts as coordinating partner. Research Schools Leiden University as the coordinating partner Research Schools in which Leiden participates Research Schools The Leiden research programmes are concentrated in university research institutes. These institutes are often part... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-05"><link>http://law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/cooperationfaculties.html</link><title>Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School</title><description>* Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0004wb-17-06392) http://law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/cooperationfaculties.html Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School \- Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School University Leiden Law School Research Leiden Law School Nederlands Law Education Research Organisation Library Contact Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School The Leiden Law School has a number of partnerships for scientific research, both nationally and internationally. Ghent â Leiden Thorbecke lecture LERU School of Human Rights Research Law and Society SARFaL Cooperation in a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-06"><link>http://www.law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/cooperationfaculties.html</link><title>Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School</title><description>* Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School - Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0601wb-03-17612) http://www.law.leiden.edu/research-leiden-law-school/cooperationfaculties.html Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School \- Research Leiden Law School - Leiden Law School University Leiden Law School Research Leiden Law School Nederlands Law Education Research Organisation Library Contact Cooperation outside the Leiden Law School The Leiden Law School has a number of partnerships for scientific research, both nationally and internationally. Ghent â Leiden Thorbecke lecture LERU School of Human Rights Research Law and Society SARFaL Cooperation in a... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:39:07">http://www.research.leiden.edu/find/research/research-schools-with-leiden-university-as-partner.html</link><title>Research Schools - Research Areas - Research</title><description>* Research Schools - Research Areas - Research (clueweb12-1001wb-37-14539) http://www.research.leiden.edu/find/research/research-schools-with-leiden-university-as-partner.html Research Schools \- Research Areas - Research Leiden University Research Portal Find Research Research Areas Nederlands Find Research Research About Research Research Profiles Institutes Libraries Contact Research Schools Research Schools in which Leiden University participates or acts as coordinating partner. Research Schools Leiden University as the coordinating partner Research Schools in which Leiden participates Research Schools The Leiden research programmes are concentrated in university research institutes. These institutes... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:39:33">http://www.llm-guide.com/university/219/leiden-university-leiden-law-school</link><title>LLM GUIDE - Leiden University - Leiden Law School</title><description>* LLM GUIDE - Leiden University - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0500wb-45-00742) http://www.llm-guide.com/university/219/leiden-university-leiden-law-school LLM GUIDE - Leiden University - Leiden Law School time(); My Account · Advanced Search · Board · Login Home USA Americas UK ˇ IRL Europe Africa Asia AUS...Poland · Portugal · Romania · Russia · Serbia · Slovenia · Spain · Sweden · Switzerland · Turkey · Ukraine   Featured Programs China-EU School of Law Beijing LL.M. in European &amp; Int. Law and Chinese Law Institute for Law... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-09"><link>http://arthistoryclub.com/art_history/University_of_Leiden</link><title>University of Leiden - Art History Online Reference and Guide</title><description>* University of Leiden - Art History Online Reference and Guide (clueweb12-0000wb-74-13011) http://arthistoryclub.com/art_history/University_of_Leiden University of Leiden \- Art History Online Reference and Guide ...University of Leiden - Art History Online Reference and Guide Leiden \- Your Art History Reference Guide! Art History Search        Art History Browse             News        Gallery        Forums        Articles...from all over the world. Contents showTocToggle("show","hide") 1 The institution 2 History 3 Education 4 Research schools and affiliated institutes 5 Alumni and other people associated with the Leiden University 6 See also 7 External links The institution The university has no central campus; its buildings are spread over the city. Some buildings like the Gravensteen (which currently houses the Leiden School of Management) are very old, while buildings like Plexus and Gorlaeus are much more modern... [cached version]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e055-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e055/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:41:05">http://law.leiden.edu/research/phdprogramme/how-to-become/howtobecomephdcandidate.html</link><title>How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - How to become a PhD candidate - Leiden Law School</title><description>* How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School - How to become a PhD candidate - Leiden Law School (clueweb12-0004wb-17-06398) http://law.leiden.edu/research/phdprogramme/how-to-become/howtobecomephdcandidate.html How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School \- How to become a PhD candidate - Leiden Law School University Leiden Law School Research PhD candidates How to become a PhD candidate Nederlands PhD students Law Research at Leiden University Dutch research page Contact Graduate School How to become a external PhD candidate at Leiden Law School Doing a PhD at Leiden Law School is an excellent way to increase... [cached version]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>