<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-11 22:58:35" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-01"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/article/4104550</link><title>Exhaled breath condensate: methodological recommendations and unresolved questions</title><description>Collection of exhaled breath condensate (EBC) is a noninvasive method for obtaining samples from the lungs. EBC contains large number of mediators including adenosine, ammonia, hydrogen peroxide, isoprostanes, leukotrienes, nitrogen oxides, peptides and cytokines. Concentrations of these mediators are influenced by lung diseases and modulated by therapeutic interventions. Similarly EBC pH also changes in respiratory diseases. The aim of the American Thoracic Society/European Respiratory Society Task Force on EBC was to identify the important methodological issues surrounding EBC collection and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-02"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/article/2111646</link><title>J. Neville and D. Jensen (2002). Supporting relational knowledge discovery: Lessons in architecture and algorithm design.</title><description>This paper discusses a few of the lessons we have learned developing a relational knowledge discovery system. The relationships among data instances in relational data provide extra information for "mining." This additional information has the potential to greatly improve the quality of learned models. However, the dependencies among instances in the data also introduce new statistical challenges for learning algorithms. Relational data provide an ideal environment in which to examine ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-03"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12576581</link><title>New insights into visceral hypersensitivity--clinical implications in IBS.</title><description>A subset of patients with IBS have visceral hypersensitivity and/or somatic hypersensitivity. Visceral hypersensitivity might have use as a clinical marker of IBS and could account for symptoms of urgency for bowel movements, bloating and abdominal pain. The mechanisms that lead to chronic visceral hypersensitivity in patients who have IBS are unclear. However, several working models may be considered, including: nociceptive input from the colon ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-04"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/4118847</link><title>Review of rifaximin as treatment for SIBO and IBS.</title><description>Rifaximin is a broad-range, gastrointestinal-specific antibiotic that demonstrates no clinically relevant bacterial resistance. Therefore, rifaximin may be useful in the treatment of gastrointestinal disorders associated with altered bacterial flora, including irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) and small intestinal bacterial overgrowth (SIBO). To review rifaximin for treatment of IBS and SIBO. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-05"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/Rohdium/article/4482599</link><title>The effects of melatonin on colonic transit time in normal controls and IBS patients.</title><description>The role of melatonin in regulating gut motility in human subjects is not clear. The aim of this study was to investigate the effects of exogenous melatonin on colonic transit time (CTT) in healthy subjects and in patients with irritable bowel syndrome (IBS). Colonic transit time was measured in 17 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-06"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/sophiec/article/10114909</link><title>Therapeutic mechanisms of a mindfulness-based treatment for IBS: effects on visceral sensitivity, catastrophizing, and affective processing of pain sensations.</title><description>Irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) is a prevalent functional disorder characterized by abdominal pain and hypervigilance to gastrointestinal sensations. We hypothesized that mindfulness training (MT), which promotes nonreactive awareness of emotional and sensory experience, may target underlying mechanisms of IBS including affective pain processing and catastrophic appraisals of gastrointestinal sensations. Seventy five female IBS patients were randomly assigned to participate in either 8 weeks of MT or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-07"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/Amazoness/article/2671064</link><title>Elevated exhaled nitric oxide in newborns of atopic mothers precedes respiratory symptoms.</title><description>RATIONALE: Exhaled nitric oxide (NO) is a well-known marker of established airway inflammation in asthma. Its role in the disease process before the onset of respiratory symptoms remains unclear. Objectives: To examine whether elevated NO in newborns with clinically naive airways is associated with subsequent respiratory symptoms in infancy. METHODS: We measured exhaled NO concentration and output after birth and prospectively assessed respiratory symptoms during infancy in a birth cohort of 164 unselected healthy neonates. We examined a possible association between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-08"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/michaelbussmann/article/3015301</link><title>IBS for Ion Distribution Under Electron Cooling</title><description>Standard models of the intra-beam scattering (IBS) are based on the growth of the rms beam parameters for a Gaussian distribution. As a result of electron cooling, the core of beam distribution is cooled much faster than the tails, producing a denser core. In this paper, we compare various approaches to IBS treatment for such distribution. Its impact on the luminosity is also discussed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-09"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/slack---line/article/7960299</link><title>Reconciling the analysis of IBD and IBS in complex trait studies</title><description>Identity by descent (IBD) is a fundamental concept in genetics and refers to alleles that are descended from a common ancestor in a base population. Identity by state (IBS) simply refers to alleles that are the same, irrespective of whether they are inherited from a recent ancestor. In modern applications, IBD relationships are estimated from genetic markers in individuals without any known relationship. This can lead to erroneous inference because a consistent base population is not used. We argue that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7002-10"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/tiagoj/article/3339803</link><title>Symptoms, spirometry, exhaled nitric oxide, and asthma exacerbations in clinical practice.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Patient symptoms, spirometry measurements, exacerbation rates, and exhaled nitric oxide (FE(NO)) levels have all been used to quantify asthma severity. OBJECTIVE: To determine the relationships among these disease surrogates in clinical practice. METHODS: Data were collected from 5 primary care asthma clinics on patient symptoms, reliever use, spirometry measurements, maintenance pharmacotherapy, disease severity (British Thoracic Society treatment step), and FE(NO) level. Exacerbation data (asthma-related unscheduled health care contact or rescue oral corticosteroid therapy) for the 12 months before and 3 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>