<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-15 08:46:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-01"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/11141037</link><title>Male Circumcision</title><description>Male circumcision consists of the surgical removal of some, or all, of the foreskin (or prepuce) from the penis. It is one of the most common procedures in the world. In the United States, the procedure is commonly performed during the newborn period. In 2007, the American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) convened a multidisciplinary workgroup of AAP members and other stakeholders to evaluate the evidence regarding male circumcision and update the AAP’s 1999 recommendations in this area. The Task Force included ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-02"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/david_r_whiting/article/215423</link><title>Pathologizing male sexuality: Lallemand, spermatorrhea, and the rise of circumcision.</title><description>Although spermatorrhea as a disease entity and an episode in nineteenth-century medical history has received significant scholarly attention over the past decade, many aspects of its nature, origins, and consequences remain obscure. The aim of this article is to indicate its origins in and links with medical anxiety about masturbation and to discuss the therapies devised to treat the condition. Particular attention is given to the work of Claude-Francois Lallemand and his influence on English doctors, especially William Acton, and the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-03"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/avivagabriel/article/9406096</link><title>Life satisfaction, anxiety, depression and resilience across the life span of men</title><description>Objective.?To determine (a) the relationship between life satisfaction, anxiety, depression and ageing in the male community and (b) to identify the impact of vulnerability factors, personal and social resources on life satisfaction and distress. Design.?A stratified random sample of the German male population (N?=?2144) was investigated by standardized questionnaires of life satisfaction (FLZM), depression, anxiety (PHQ), resilience (RS-11) and self-esteem (RSS). Results.?No age-related change was found regarding overall life satisfaction. Satisfaction with health decreased in midlife (51?60 years), while the importance ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-04"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/achinerarias/article/10443077</link><title>Circumcision and the risk of prostate cancer</title><description>BACKGROUND: Several lines of evidence support a role for infectious agents in the development of prostate cancer (PCa). In particular, sexually transmitted infections (STIs) have been implicated in PCa etiology, and studies have found that the risk of acquiring a STI can be reduced with circumcision. Therefore, circumcision may reduce PCa risk. METHODS: Participant data collected as part of 2 population-based case-control studies of PCa were analyzed. Self-reported circumcision status, age at circumcision, and age at first sexual intercourse were recorded ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-05"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/emisacco/article/12099600</link><title>[Circumcision: history, religion and law].</title><description>The aim of this article is to describe the circumcision procedure during history, its therapeutic and preventive goals, with focus on bioethical, economic and law issues. The origins of this practice are lost in antiquity. It was performed since 3000 BC by the Egyptians for hygienic and religious reasons. Moreover, male circumcision is a religious commandment in Judaism and Islam, and it is customary in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-06"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/cyclopoietes/article/12819948</link><title>Anthropology and Circumcision</title><description>This chapter reviews the anthropology of male and female circumcision over the past century. After surveying classic sociocultural and psychodynamic interpretations of male circumcision, I shift to the biblical and Jewish rite, focusing on gender symbolism and counter-hegemonic practice within European-Christian society. The chapter then reviews the relationship between male circumcision in sub-Saharan Africa and reduced rates of HIV. Next, I address female circumcision, focusing again on symbolism but especially on highly impassioned debates over cultural relativism and human rights, medical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-07"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/david_r_whiting/article/1257885</link><title>Does circumcision harm your sex life?</title><description>Does circumcision harm your sex life? This question has become more pressing than ever with the recent endorsement by the World Health Organization of circumcision as a means of reducing HIV infection in Africa (New Scientist, 31 March, p 7). But as two new studies show, it's proving tricky to resolve. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-08"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/achinerarias/article/10883216</link><title>Male circumcision and sexual function in men and women: a survey-based, cross-sectional study in Denmark</title><description>Background One-third of the world’s men are circumcised, but little is known about possible sexual consequences of male circumcision. In Denmark (∼5% circumcised), we examined associations of male circumcision with a range of sexual measures in both sexes. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-09"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/achinerarias/article/11172705</link><title>Male Circumcision: Pain, Trauma and Psychosexual Sequelae</title><description>Infant male circumcision continues despite growing questions about its medical justification. As usually performed without analgesia or anaesthetic, circumcision is observably painful. It is likely that genital cutting has physical, sexual and psychological consequences too. Some studies link involuntary male circumcision with a range of negative emotions and even post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD). Some circumcised men have described their current feelings in the language of violation, torture, mutilation and sexual assault. In view of the acute as well as long-term risks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7003-10"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/david_r_whiting/article/1102125</link><title>The effect of male circumcision on sexuality</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>