<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7007">Allen Ginsberg Howl review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:15" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amromeo/article/1451991</link><title>Integrin modulation and signaling in leukocyte adhesion and migration</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/AlmondCookie/article/10383988</link><title>Counterfactuals</title><description>Counterfactuals are a form of common-sense nonmonotonic inference that has been of long-term interest to philosophers. In this paper, we begin by describing some of the impact counterfactuals can be expected to have in artificial intelligence, and by reviewing briefly some of the philosophical conclusions which have been drawn about them. We continue by presenting a formal description of counterfactual implication and discussing the issues involved in implementing it. Specific applications in the domains of planning and the automated diagnosis of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3578213</link><title>Chris Allen</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shimi002/article/9414177</link><title>Regulation of Integrin Activation.</title><description>Regulation of cell-cell and cell-matrix interaction is essential for the normal physiology of metazoans and is important in many diseases. Integrin adhesion receptors can rapidly increase their affinity (integrin activation) in response to intracellular signaling events in a process termed inside-out signaling. The transmembrane domains of integrins and their interactions with the membrane are important in inside-out signaling. Moreover, integrin activation is tightly regulated by a complex network of signaling pathways. Here, we review recent progress in understanding how the membrane ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shua/article/5399763</link><title>Mindful emotion regulation: An integrative review</title><description>This review aims to integrate the constructs of mindfulness and emotion regulation. Research into both of these areas is relatively new, and while several reviews have emerged for each area independently, none has directly proposed a conceptual integration. The current review explores how key axioms and assumptions of traditional psychological models of emotion regulation and the psychological interventions that are derived from them (e.g., cognitive behavior therapy) differ fundamentally from mindfulness-based approaches in terms of the underlying processes they address. Accordingly, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pwais/article/3137738</link><title>Limited discrepancy search</title><description>Many problems of practical interest can be solved using tree search methods because carefully tuned successor ordering heuristics guide the search toward regions of the space that are likely to contain solutions. For some problems, the heuristics often lead directly to a solution---but not always. Limited discrepancy search addresses the problem of what to do when the heuristics fail. Our intuition is that a failing heuristic might well have succeeded if it were not for a small number of &amp;quot;wrong turns ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amoore88/article/505266</link><title>Views from Inside: Memoirs concerning the Yugoslav Breakup and War</title><description>Recent memoirs published in Zagreb, Ljubljana, Sarajevo, and Podgorica offer glimpses into how the principals would like their roles in the events connected with the Yugoslav breakup and war to be remembered. The most indispensable of the ten memoirs under review are those by Janez Drnovsek and Janez Jansa, who have differing perspectives on developments in Slovenia between 1988 and 1991; by Martin Spegelj, who outlines in detail his argument that Croatia should have laid siege to the Yugoslav Army barracks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276023</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1986 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276020</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1983 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7007-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7007_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:41:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276018</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1981 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>