<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7008">jesse van ruller solo transcriptions</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:29:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:29:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thithu/article/10048206</link><title>Een nieuwe verzuiling van de eerste lijn</title><description>In maart 2007 hield dr. Toon Voorham een openbare les getiteld ‘Een nieuwe verzuiling van de eerste lijn’ aan de Hogeschool Rotterdam. Hij stelde dat onze laagdrempelige, generalistische eerste lijn wordt bedreigd door specialistische centra. De huidige eerstelijnszorg garandeert continuïteit van de aangeboden zorg en is naast lichamelijke en geestelijke aspecten ook gericht op de omgeving van de patiënt. In de Tranzo Zorgsalon stond de vraag centraal of deze vorm van zorg door de toenemende veranderingen wordt bedreigd? Toon Voorham hield ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:30:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thithu/article/8488361</link><title>Nonlocal van der Waals density functional: The simpler the better</title><description>We devise a nonlocal correlation energy functional that describes the entire range of dispersion interactions in a seamless fashion using only the electron density as input. The new functional is considerably simpler than its predecessors of a similar type. The functional has a tractable and robust analytic form that lends itself to efficient self-consistent implementation. When paired with an appropriate exchange functional, our nonlocal correlation model yields accurate interaction energies of weakly-bound complexes, not only near the energy minima but also ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:31:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yennesitPalacios/article/8331169</link><title>Exclusion Financiera en America Latina o el costo social de la no bancarizacion de los sectores pobres urbanos</title><description>This article is currently available as a free download on ingentaconnect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:31:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dakeller/article/2421042</link><title>Foundations of IT Service Management Based on ITIL® V3 (English version)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Foundations of IT Service Management&lt;/i&gt; based on ITIL has become the industry classic guide on the topic of ITIL. Over the years this authoritative itSMF guide has earned its place on the bookshelves and in the briefcases of industry experts as they implement best practices within their organizations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This 2007 version has now been upgraded to reflect ITIL V3. Written in the same concise way and covering all the facts, readers will find that this title succinctly covers the key aspects ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:32:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrvaidya/article/11236183</link><title>Publication of descriptions of novel bacterial taxa in Antonie van Leeuwenhoek</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:33:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12889448</link><title>Distinct neural stem cell tropism, early immune activation, and choroid plexus pathology following coxsackievirus infection in the neonatal central nervous system</title><description>Distinct neural stem cell tropism, early immune activation, and choroid plexus pathology following coxsackievirus infection in the neonatal central nervous system Laboratory Investigation advance online publication, December 30 2013. doi:10.1038/labinvest.2013.138 Authors: Jenna M Puccini, Chelsea M Ruller, Scott M Robinson, Kristeene A Knopp, Michael J Buchmeier, Kelly S Doran &amp; Ralph Feuer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:34:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bhengeveld/article/11156325</link><title>De keuze van Vincent : Van Goghs Musée imaginaire</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:35:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ttaga/article/8059088</link><title>Fail or Flourish? Cognitive Appraisal Moderates the Effect of Solo Status on Performance</title><description>When everyone in a group shares a common social identity except one individual, the one who is different from the majority has solo status. Solo status increases one's visibility and performance pressure, which may result in stress. Stress has divergent effects on performance, and individuals' response to stressful situations is predicted by their cognitive appraisal (challenge or threat) of the situation. Two experiments test the hypothesis that cognitive appraisal moderates the effect of solo status on performance. Experiment 1 finds that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:36:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dakeller/article/11821138</link><title>Foundations of ITIL 2011 Edition (Best Practice (Van Haren Publishing))</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7008-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7008_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:37:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/flips/article/4962175</link><title>Likelihood functions for multivariate point processes with coincidences.</title><description>Existing work on scalar and multivariate point process models assumes a no-simultaneity condition i.e. no more than one event of any kind can occur in a small time interval. But there is now strong interest from a number of fields such as neuro-physiology in being able to construct models that allow simultaneity. Here we construct such models and associated likelihood (ratios) for the first time. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>