<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:51:27" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:51:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cisevol/article/10861696</link><title>Is the changing precipitation regime of Manchester, United Kingdom, driven by the development of urban areas?</title><description>Precipitation measurements made at three weather stations and one composite record from the Manchester region and the Isle of Man have been analysed over the period 1899–2008. Large positive trends over the last 40 years were identified for the three records within 50 km of Manchester whilst the Isle of Man measurements revealed no such trend. The recent increase in rainfall at the urban or urban-influenced sites was significantly and negatively correlated with NOx emissions recorded in Manchester whilst local temperature ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:53:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kenjimyzk/article/9843131</link><title>Nationality preferences for labour in the international football industry</title><description>This paper tests consumer and co-worker nationalistic preferences by measuring the effect of team nationality composition on fan attendance and overall team quality using professional football teams in the world's five largest football leagues. Little evidence is found to support the hypothesis that fans or co-workers discriminate based upon the player's nationality. Thus, the under-representation of various nationalities can be concluded to originate from a club's ownership and/or management. These results are similar to the racial bias revealed by English club ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:54:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Pedro_Martins/article/3759923</link><title>How predictable are the FIFA worldcup football outcomes? An empirical analysis</title><description>Since 1993 the Federation of International Football Association's (FIFA) monthly world ranking system for senior national football teams has become a reliable source to judge a team's potentiality in football. In the past four FIFA worldcup football tournaments from 1994 to 2006, the top seeded team never won the FIFA worldcup except in 1994 when Brazil won as the number one team. This article examines the strength of this element of uncertainty in FIFA worldcup using two empirical models. We find ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:55:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/betting/article/157312</link><title>Forecasting football results and the efficiency of fixed-odds betting</title><description>An ordered probit regression model estimated using 10 years' data is used to forecast English league football match results. As well as past match results data, the significance of the match for end-of-season league outcomes, the involvement of the teams in cup competition and the geographical distance between the two teams' home towns all contribute to the forecasting model's performance. The model is used to test the weak-form efficiency of prices in the fixed-odds betting market. A strategy of selecting end-of-season ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:57:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kenjimyzk/article/7137052</link><title>Income, leisure and proficiency: an economic study of football performance</title><description>The influence of income, across countries, on the proficiency of leisure, as measure by international football achievement is addressed. It is widely concluded that leisure is a normal good, however; little research has been conducted on the influences of efforts to become proficient at a specific leisure activity. While the law of diminishing marginal productivity indicates that leisure proficiency will increase at a decreasing rate with increases in time allocated toward the leisure activity, the second-order effect of income on neither ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:58:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kenjimyzk/article/3993521</link><title>Technology transfer and convergence of performance: an economic study of FIFA football ranking</title><description>The seminal work of Gerschenkron (1962) stated that latecomers borrow advanced technology from their predecessors, resulting in convergence of productivity among nations. Additionally, the diffusion of technology among developing nations has been fulfilled not only directly from developed nations but also from surrounding nations through local spillovers such as learning from others. Recently, the disparity in national football performance among the nations appears to have improved, and it is evident that talented players are mobilized from developing nations to developed ones. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:59:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kenjimyzk/article/10150409</link><title>Effect of Linguistic Heterogeneity on Technology Transfer: An Economic Study of FIFA Football Rankings</title><description>This paper used Fédération Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) world ranking points data to examine how linguistic heterogeneity has an impact on technology transfer from the most developed countries. The major findings were that the learning effect from the most developed countries on team performance is larger for developing countries than for developed ones and that linguistic heterogeneity has a detrimental effect on technology transfer for developed, but not developing countries. The results presented here are interpreted to imply that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:00:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/satbiod/article/1030335</link><title>One Planet Many People: Atlas of our Changing Environment</title><description>&lt;b&gt;One Planet, Many People&lt;/b&gt; is intended for environmental policy makers, non-governmental organizations, the private sector, academics, teachers and citizens. This colorful and approachable atlas contains photographs, satellite images, maps and narratives that provide insights into the many ways people around the world have changed, and continue to change, the environment. &lt;b&gt;Objectives:&lt;/b&gt; The main purpose of this hard-cover, 332-page, large-format atlas is to document visual evidence of global environmental changes resulting from natural processes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:01:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hhhannes/article/3823804</link><title>Least Developed Countries Report 2008 The: Growth, Poverty and the Terms of Development Partnership</title><description>This report assesses recent trends in growth and poverty in the least developed countries (LDCs), as well as changes in terms of development partnership. It discusses the fact that rapid economic growth in the LDCs has been associated with a slow rate of poverty reduction and slow progress towards the Millennium Development Goals. The report also considers progress towards country-owned development strategies in LDCs and the role of recipient- led aid management policies at the country level as a practical policy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7010-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7010_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:02:23">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10570/article/10107717</link><title>Manchester hiring</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>