<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7011">Vera Pavlova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:03:22" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:03:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9817436</link><title>First finding of deepwater &lt;i&gt;profunda&lt;/i&gt; morph of quagga mussel &lt;i&gt;Dreissena bugensis&lt;/i&gt; in the European part of its range</title><description>The deepwater profunda morph of quagga mussel Dreissena bugensis was found for the first time in the European part of its range. The mussels of this morph were found in the Cheboksary Reservoir situated in the midstream of the Volga River (Russian Federation). Traditional and geometric morphometrics confirm the similarity of studied specimens to profunda mussel described from the Great Lakes of North America. In the Cheboksary Reservoir the deepwater mussels live at depth of 26.5 m on sandy-pebbled substrate at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:05:00">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10935/article/5840116</link><title>Sensitivity of the Russian agriculture to changes in climate, CO2 and tropospheric ozone concentrations and soil fertility</title><description>Russian agriculture sensitivity to changes in climate, soil and atmosphere chemistry were analyzed. Calculated data are presented on crop productivity of grain crops and grasses (C3) under arid and humid scenarios of climate taking account of one-, two-, three and four-factor natural environment impacts. All four factors under studies (climatic parameters, CO2 and tropospheric ozone concentrations, soil degradation extent) greatly impact agriculture productivity. The effect of interaction between all considered factors on agroecosystem productivity is studied. It is established that a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:06:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ajwdewit/article/13051577</link><title>Modelling the effects of climate variability on spring wheat productivity in the steppe zone of Russia and Kazakhstan</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:08:09">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5884854</link><title>An asset-pricing view of external adjustment☆</title><description>Recent literature has argued that conventional measures of external sustainability—the trade balance and current account—are misleading because they omit capital gains on net foreign asset positions. We adjust the definition of the current account to include the capital gains and discuss how this may affect our thinking about external adjustment and sustainability. We do so in the context of a two-country macro-finance model of Pavlova and Rigobon (2008a) that allows to explore the interconnections between equilibrium portfolios and external accounts' dynamics. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:10:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RobHayward/article/10808254</link><title>Asset Prices and Exchange Rates</title><description>Author contact info: Anna Pavlova London Business School Regents Park London NW1 4SA UK Tel: 617/253-7159 E-Mail: apavlova@london.edu Roberto Rigobon MIT Sloan School of Management 100 Main Street, E62-516 Cambridge, MA 02142 Tel: 617/258-8374 Fax: 617/258-6855 E-Mail: rigobon@mit.edu This paper develops a simple two-country, two-good model, in which the real exchange rate, stock and bond prices are jointly determined. The model predicts that stock market prices are correlated internationally even though their dividend processes are independent, providing a theoretical argument in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:12:37">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13972/article/13041970</link><title>Sole Smooth Muscle States Determine Gliding Rate in the Freshwater Snail Lymnaea stagnalis.</title><description>The sole of crawling gastropods is a unique model for studying the function of smooth muscles and ciliated epithelium. The gastropod snail Lymnaea stagnalis glides over the substratum without visible muscular contraction in its sole; consequently, the gliding was thought to be due to sole cilia. However, we have shown that the sole muscles in Lymnaea are phasic smooth muscles. They contribute extensively to gliding ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:14:31">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6476417</link><title>Answer to “comment on individual ion activities of Na+ and Cl− by Arce, Wilczek-Vera and Vera” by F. Malatesta</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:17:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nailest/article/12028303</link><title>MicroRNA-Regulated Networks: The Perfect Storm for Classical Molecular Biology, the Ideal Scenario for Systems Biology</title><description>MicroRNAs (miRNAs) are involved in many regulatory pathways some of which are complex networks enriched in regulatory motifs like positive or negative feedback loops or coherent and incoherent feedforward loops. Their complexity makes the understanding of their regulation difficult and the interpretation of experimental data cumbersome. In this book chapter we claim that systems biology is the appropriate approach to investigate the regulation of these miRNA-regulated networks. Systems biology is an interdisciplinary approach by which biomedical questions on biochemical networks are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:18:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/beacham/article/3613492</link><title>Conceptualisation of technology education within the paradigm of sustainable development</title><description>Abstract  This article addresses the issue of how sustainable development might be conceptualised and used to advance technology education practice. It is argued that a conceptualisation of sustainable development based on a combination of weak anthropocentrism and value based approaches within particular social, environmental and economic contexts provides the basis for establishing education for sustainable development (ESD) through technology education. It is argued that such an approach is in accord with the general push for a paradigm shift in curriculum development to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7011-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7011_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 00:21:01">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3613495</link><title>Introduction</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>