<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ooshenghui/article/10042510</link><title>Chinese Opera in Singapore: Negotiating Globalisation, Consumerism and National Culture</title><description>While it is conventionally argued that global culture homogenises local cultures, very little attention is paid to the strategies that local cultures deploy to survive. This article looks at Chinese opera in Singapore and explores strategies such as apprenticeship schemes, coopting consumerist culture and amateur opera. It argues that the relationship between global and local cultures is one of continuous contestation and refutes the notion that national culture protects or elevates local cultures. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/krzysztofwojciecholszewski/article/11461464</link><title>Tools of culture : Japan's cultural, intellectual, medical, and technological contacts in East Asia, 1000-1500s</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/10017798/article/8061496</link><title>Growing up with TV : Asian children's experience</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amandaalders/article/9049456</link><title>Asian Americans and Alzheimer's disease: Assimilation, culture, and beliefs</title><description>Because most successful interventions for Alzheimer's disease (AD) rely upon early diagnosis and implementation, it is important to understand the factors influencing dementia treatment-seeking behaviors. These include perceptions, beliefs, values, and feelings relating to AD, which may vary among and within ethnic groups according to the strength of culturally-based explanatory models and individual group members' ages and experiences. This study used ten focus groups drawn from Asian American communities representing different national origins (Chinese, Japanese, and Korean) to examine the factors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:17">http://www.citeulike.org/article/483720</link><title>The Impact of Asian Drivers on the Developing World</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/katerina_pekarkova/article/3206578</link><title>Action, Culture and Development: Points of Convergence</title><description>Based on Boesch's contributions to cultural psychology, prospects as well as problems of connecting the theoretical perspectives of action, culture and development are explored in this paper. Cultural systems maintain and regenerate themselves through the regulation and control of development over the life-span. Within the matrix of sociocultural constraints, developing subjects select and construe their own developmental ecologies and create their personal cultures. Development over life-span is thus formed by intentional action; potentialities and intentional contents of action are in turn ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kevin/article/2919562</link><title>Traces of Ancient Iranian Culture in Boysun District, Uzbekistan</title><description>Despite the beginnings made during the Soviet period, there are still isolated regions of Central Asia outside the nominally "Iranian" republic (Tajikistan) where material and societal evidence of pre-Turkic Iranian culture has yet to be collected and studied systematically. Dr. Rahmonī, as yet one of only a few Tajik folklorists actively collecting and publishing such material, presents here a sample of contemporary folk traditions from a rural area of southern Uzbekistan. These include mourning customs; various instances of the veneration of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lindahirsch/article/5636900</link><title>Culture</title><description>Culture is considered as a key term in anthropology, now in critical mode, and to be worked through powerful tropes that lead to issues in politics, interpretation, translation, stereotype and racism. Anthropology is described as a cultural system itself, with a large supporting institutional apparatus, not unlike the culture industry as critiqued by Adorno and the Frankfurt School. The high mass culture/high culture distinction is considered and some distortions explained (away). Street culture and culture as (development) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/marianap/article/1220003</link><title>Visual essentialism and the object of visual culture</title><description>The double question whether visual culture studies is a discipline or an interdisciplinary movement, and which methods are most suited to practice in this field, can only be addressed by way of the object. This article probes the difficulty of defining or delimiting the object of study without the reassuring and widespread visual essentialism that, in the end, can only be tautological. 10.1177/147041290300200101 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rayoulike/article/43318</link><title>Conceptualizing an East Asian popular culture</title><description>Since the 1980s, popular cultural products have criss-crossed the national borders of East Asian countries, enabling a discursive construction of an 'East Asian Popular Culture' as an object of analysis. The present essay is a preliminary attempt to provide some conceptual and analytic shape to this object, delineated by its three constitutive elements of production, distribution and consumption. Each East Asian location participates in different and unequal levels in each of these component processes. Production can either be located entirely in ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>