<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:11:30" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:11:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12823267</link><title>How sexual harassment changed the way I work</title><description>As a flurry of interest in workplace discrimination subsides, efforts to raise awareness and eliminate abuses continue, says Kathleen Raven. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:12:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EGCKing/article/3113525</link><title>The Business of Books: Booksellers and the English Book Trade 1450-1850</title><description>In 1450 very few English men or women were personally familiar with a book; by 1850, the great majority of people daily encountered books, magazines, or newspapers. This book explores the history of this fundamental transformation, from the arrival of the printing press to the coming of steam. James Raven presents a lively and original account of the English book trade and the printers, booksellers, and entrepreneurs who promoted its development. Viewing print and book culture through the lens of commerce, Raven offers a new interpretation of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:13:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EGCKing/article/3113538</link><title>London Booksellers and American Customers: Transatlantic Literary Community and the Charleston Library Society, 1748-1811</title><description>James Raven's history of the Charleston Library Society's book purchasing activities offers both a window into the transatlantic book trade during the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries and a chronicle of this early library's influence on southern culture. Founded in 1748 and still flourishing today, the Charleston Library Society occupies a position of historical significance comparable to that of the Library Company of Philadelphia, the New York Library Society, and the Boston Athenaeum. Its members provided the initiative for the founding of the Charleston Museum, the College of Charleston, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:14:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bcl/article/7373197</link><title>Inorganic carbon acquisition by eukaryotic algae: four current questions</title><description>The phylogenetically and morphologically diverse eukaryotic algae are typically oxygenic photolithotrophs. They have a diversity of incompletely understood mechanisms of inorganic carbon acquisition: this article reviews four areas where investigations continue. The first topic is diffusive CO2 entry. Most eukaryotic algae, like all cyanobacteria, have inorganic carbon concentrating mechanisms (CCMs). The ancestral condition was presumably the absence of a CCM, i.e. diffusive CO2 entry, as found in a small minority of eukaryotic algae today; however, it is likely that, as is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:15:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2109800</link><title>Full Text</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:17:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8126641</link><title>Why are mycorrhizal fungi and symbiotic nitrogen-fixing bacteria not genetically integrated into plants?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:18:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3748006</link><title>Problems for Testimonial Acquaintance</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:19:51">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3722705</link><title>The Bases of Power and the PowerInteraction Model of Interpersonal Influence</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:21:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5757784</link><title>Horsetails get the wind up</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:22:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9178033</link><title>The cost of photoinhibition</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>