<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:02:52" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:02:57">http://www.citeulike.org/group/946/article/4746523</link><title>MR imaging of lumbar facet joint synovial cysts</title><description>Abstract.   The increasing application of magnetic resonance (MR) imaging of the spine has raised the awareness of lumbar facet synovial cysts (LFSC). This well recognised, yet uncommon condition, presents with low back pain and radiculopathy due to the presence of an extradural mass. The commonest affected level is L4/5 with a mild degenerative spondylolisthesis a frequent associated finding. MR imaging is the technique of choice to detect and diagnose a LFSC. This pictorial essay, drawing on experience of 43 cases seen ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:04:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Schopfel/article/9078726</link><title>UK higher education libraries and the role of JISC, the Joint Information Systems Committee</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:05:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/darthglader/article/10694817</link><title>Uncommon synovial cysts in children</title><description>Popliteal synovial cysts (Baker’s cysts) are a common occurrence in children and adults. Synovial cysts in other locations and/or with atypical extension are less common and may be confounded with tumors or other medical conditions. In this article we describe the underlying disease, clinical presentation and clinical course in six children with a sudden onset of paraarticular soft tissue masses or non-specific chronic pain. Ultrasound was the initial imaging method used in all cases; this was supplemented by MRI in three ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:06:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thsutton/article/696965</link><title>Computing curricula 2001</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:07:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12666878</link><title>Trends in biological joint resurfacing</title><description>The treatment of osteochondral lesions and osteoarthritis remains an ongoing clinical challenge in orthopaedics. This review examines the current research in the fields of cartilage regeneration, osteochondral defect treatment, and biological joint resurfacing, and reports on the results of clinical and pre-clinical studies. We also report on novel treatment strategies and discuss their potential promise or pitfalls. Current focus involves the use of a scaffold providing mechanical support with the addition of chondrocytes or mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs), or the use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:09:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/JohnLichtenberger/article/8278519</link><title>Primary cardiac synovial sarcoma</title><description>Synovial sarcoma is a rare entity and accounts for &lt;1% in all primary cardiac tumors. This is typically a highly aggressive tumor and survival is usually less than nine months in this location, even with surgery and adjuvant chemoradiation. Primary cardiac synovial sarcoma has rarely been reported in the literature. We report a recent case from the Mayo Clinic, Rochester, Minnesota. The patient is still alive and with some recurrence of tumor but without significant symptoms 22 months after primary surgery. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:10:31">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5178406</link><title>Recent trends in authentication and national information management policy in the UK</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:11:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4480788</link><title>Choosing between print or digital collection building in times of financial constraint</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:13:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4918120</link><title>The Google Book settlement and academic libraries: ANTAEUS</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:14:33">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3957690</link><title>Managing the implementation of a federated search tool in an academic library</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>