<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:28:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:28:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/2733742</link><title>On automorphism groups of the Hermitian codes</title><description>We determine the exact automorphism groups of the Goppa geometric codes from the Hermitian curves over GF(q&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:29:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/3735256</link><title>Hermitian codes as generalized Reed-Solomon codes</title><description>Hermitian codes obtained from Hermitian curves are shown to be concatenated generalized Reed-Solomon codes. This interpretation of Hermitian codes is used to investigate their structure. An efficient encoding algorithm is given for Hermitian codes. A new general decoding algorithm is given and applied to Hermitian codes to give a decoding algorithm capable of decoding up to the full error correcting capability of the code. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:30:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/12360331</link><title>The characterization of Hermitian surfaces by the number of points</title><description>The nonsingular Hermitian surface of degree $\sqrtq +1$ is characterized by its number of $\BbbF_q$-points among the irreducible surfaces over $\BbbF_q$ of degree $\sqrtq +1$ in the projective 3-space. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:31:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/radokirov/article/6527887</link><title>Minimum distance of Hermitian two-point codes</title><description>Abstract  We prove a formula for the minimum distance of two-point codes on a Hermitian curve. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:32:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/12181701</link><title>The Ekedahl-Oort type of Jacobians of Hermitian curves</title><description>The Ekedahl-Oort type is a combinatorial invariant of a principally polarized abelian variety $A$ defined over an algebraically closed field of characteristic $p &gt; 0$. It characterizes the $p$-torsion group scheme of $A$ up to isomorphism. Equivalently, it characterizes (the mod $p$ reduction of) the Dieudonné module of $A$ or the de Rham cohomology of $A$ as modules under the Frobenius and Vershiebung operators. There are very few results about which Ekedahl-Oort types occur for Jacobians of curves. In this paper, we consider the class of Hermitian curves, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:33:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/3887675</link><title>Improvements on Parameters of Algebraic-Geometry Codes From Hermitian Curves</title><description>Using the Vladut-Xing method, we refine a construction of Xu to improve the parameters of algebraic-geometry codes based on Hermitian curves. The parameters of these Hermitian codes are arbitrarily close to the Singleton bound, provided that the length of the code is sufficiently large. We also exhibit a class of Hermitian codes over any finite field BBFq 2 (q &gt; 2) with good parameters. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:34:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/1265731</link><title>Implementation of a Hermitian decoder IC in 0.35 μm CMOS</title><description>This paper presents the first integrated circuit implementation of a Hermitian decoder thereby proving its practical viability. Hermitian codes provide much larger block lengths (n=4080) compared to that of the popular Reed-Solomon (RS) codes (n=256) over the same field (GF(256)). This translates to a coding gain of 0.6 dB for the same rate. However, Hermitian codes were deemed to be too complex to implement until the emergence of a recent algorithmic breakthrough which made the complexity of Hermitian decoders comparable to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:36:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/radokirov/article/881672</link><title>On Semigroups Generated by Two Consecutive Integers and Improved Hermitian Codes</title><description>Analysis of the Berlekamp-Massey-Sakata algorithm for decoding one-point codes leads to two methods for improving code rate. One method, due to Feng and Rao, removes parity checks that may be recovered by their majority voting algorithm. The second method is to design the code to correct only those error vectors of a given weight that are also geometrically generic. In this work, formulae are given for the redundancies of Hermitian codes optimized with respect to these criteria as well as the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:37:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/2734778</link><title>A note on Hermitian codes over GF(&lt;e1&gt;q&lt;/e1&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;)</title><description>Properties of codes defined by Goppa's algebraic-geometric method using Hermitian curves are discussed. Generator and parity check matrices for such codes are derived explicitly. Results concerning the minimum distance and the weight distribution of the codes are provided ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7022-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7022_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:37:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielaugot/article/3735261</link><title>A serial-in-serial-out hardware architecture for systematic encoding of Hermitian codes via Gröbner bases</title><description>When a nontrivial permutation of a Hermitian code is given, the code will have a module structure over a polynomial ring of one variable. By exploiting the theory of Gröbner bases for modules, a novel and elegant systematic encoding scheme for Hermitian codes is proposed by Heegard et al. (1995). The goal of this paper is to develop a serial-in-serial-out hardware architecture, similar to a classical cyclic encoder, for such a systematic encoding scheme. Moreover, we demonstrate that under a specific ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>