<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7023">calculate jordan normal form</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:38:43" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:38:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tianbingxu/article/239196</link><title>Learning in Graphical Models (Adaptive Computation and Machine Learning)</title><description>"The state of the art presented by the experts in the field." -- Ross D. Shachter, Department of Engineering-Economic Systems and Operations Research, Stanford University &lt;P&gt;Graphical models, a marriage between probability theory and graph theory, provide a natural tool for dealing with two problems that occur throughout applied mathematics and engineering--uncertainty and complexity. In particular, they play an increasingly important role in the design and analysis of machine learning algorithms. Fundamental to the idea of a graphical model is the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:39:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dbirmajer/article/6922069</link><title>Computing diagonal form and Jacobson normal form of a matrix using Gröbner bases</title><description>In this paper we present two algorithms for the computation of a diagonal form of a matrix over non-commutative Euclidean domain over a field with the help of Gröbner bases. This can be viewed as the pre-processing for the computation of Jacobson normal form and also used for the computation of Smith normal form in the commutative case. We propose a general framework for handling, among other, operator algebras with rational coefficients. We employ special "polynomial" strategy in Ore localizations of non-commutative $G$-algebras and show its merits. In ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:40:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bizzylizzy/article/2486094</link><title>THE GULLIFORD LECTURE: Autistic spectrum disorders: a challenge and a model for inclusion in education</title><description>Rita Jordan, Professor in Autism Studies at the School of Education, University of Birmingham, gave last year's Gulliford Lecture at the University of Birmingham on 4 October 2007. This article is based upon that lecture. In it, Professor Jordan discusses the role of education in the lives of people with autistic spectrum disorders. She traces the growth in our knowledge about autistic spectrum disorders and the development of a variety of ways of responding to autism, from the highly specialised, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:42:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kaihoeffner/article/4009869</link><title>The GS algorithm for exact linearization to Brunovsky normal form</title><description>An algorithm utilizing the minimal number of integrations for the exact linearization of nonlinear systems to Brunovsky normal form under nonlinear feedback is presented. The tools which are involved are based on classical constructions appearing in the theory of exterior differential systems ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:43:08">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3690344</link><title>Partial orders and Jordan normal form</title><description>Abstract  Consideration is given to the relation between the structure of the acyclic binary relation and the adjacency matrix of its corresponding graph. In this case, the existing methods for studying the binary relations and their corresponding graphs in terms of the spectrum, that is, the set of eigenvalues, of the adjacency matrix are inapplicable because for the acyclic relations this matrix is nilpotent and its spectrum is identically zero. Therefore, a more refined characteristic of the matrix is required. The present ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:44:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/2226033</link><title>Mutual Entropy</title><description>F10.94&gt; I(X; Y ) = H(X) +H(Y ) H(X;Y ) The mutual entropy I(X; Y ) expresses the amount of information given by image Y on image X. A value of 1:0 would reect perfect agreement and 0:0 complete disagreement between the two images X and Y . Guido Gerig, 21st April 1999 2 reference volume. The second term is the entropy of the part of the test volume into which the reference volume projects. It encourages transformations that project u into complex parts of v. The third term, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:45:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tianbingxu/article/9386386</link><title>Beta processes, stick-breaking, and power laws</title><description>The beta-Bernoulli process provides a Bayesian nonparametric prior for models involving collections of binary-valued features. A draw from the beta process provides an infinite collection of probabilities in the unit interval, and a draw from the Bernoulli process turns these into binary-valued features. Recent work has shown how to derive stick-breaking representations for the beta process, by analogy to Sethuraman's derivation of a stick-breaking representation for the Dirichlet process. We show how to derive one such stick-breaking representation directly from the characterization of the beta process as a completely ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:46:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tianbingxu/article/4850787</link><title>Graphical Models, Exponential Families, and Variational Inference</title><description>The formalism of probabilistic graphical models provides a unifying framework for capturing complex dependencies among random variables, and building large-scale multivariate statistical models. Graphical models have become a focus of research in many statistical, computational and mathematical fields, including bioinformatics, communication theory, statistical physics, combinatorial optimization, signal and image processing, information retrieval and statistical machine learning. Many problems that arise in specific instances — including the key problems of computing marginals and modes of probability distributions — are best studied in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:47:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/niahm/article/1699166</link><title>Shut up and calculate</title><description>I advocate an extreme "shut-up-and-calculate" approach to physics, where our external physical reality is assumed to be purely mathematical. This brief essay motivates this "it's all just equations" assumption and discusses its implications. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7023-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7023_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:48:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tianbingxu/article/4303227</link><title>On Spectral Clustering: Analysis and an algorithm</title><description>Despite many empirical successes of spectral clustering methods -- algorithms that cluster points using eigenvectors of matrices derived from the distances between the points -- there are several unresolved issues. First, there is a wide variety of algorithms that use the eigenvectors in slightly different ways. Second, many of these algorithms have no proof that they will actually compute a reasonable clustering. In this paper, we present a simple spectral clustering algorithm that can be implemented ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>