<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:51:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:51:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arnisigurdur/article/944613</link><title>Influence of MgO nano-crystals on the thermodynamics, hydrogen uptake and kinetics in Mg films</title><description>Hydrogen uptake in thin sputtered magnesium films covered with a Palladium layer was studied by resistance measurements. During growth, oxygen was introduced into the chamber in small amounts and the effect on the resistance, measured in situ, while growing, was monitored. This resulted in the formation of a mixture of MgO nanocrystals and layers in the Mg films. The measurements were made in situ in the sputtering chamber where the samples were grown. The aim of the study was to study ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:52:54">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18283/article/12688084</link><title>The gas response behavior of spin-coated phthalocyanine films to NO2</title><description>The spin-coated films of 2,9,16,23-tetra(heptyloxy)phthalocyanine showed very good gas sensing properties to NO2 at room temperature. The response and recovery are rapid and complete with good reproducibility and high sensitivity. The magnitude of response of the film to NO2 are enhanced by irradiation with light. This may be ascribed to the decrease in the activation energy for the charge transfer interaction between the phthalocyanine donor and the gas acceptor by light excitation. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:54:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pajer/article/1158619</link><title>Obliquely deposited metal films for polarizers</title><description>The performance of obliquely deposited metal films as polarizers, which can be used for normally incident light, was improved. The relation between microscopic columnar structures and dichroism of the films was investigated by depositing various kinds of metals with changing deposition angles. The influence of substrate materials was also examined. It was revealed that enlargement of the spacing between the neighboring columns is the most significant to attain a good extinction ratio and a low insertion loss. For the best performance, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:55:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rdf/article/4255531</link><title>Simulation of structure evolution in Cu films</title><description>The Monte Carlo method was used to simulate grain growth in thin Cu films. The model, based on energetic principles, was compared with the evolution of measured film structures. Surface, interface, grain boundary, and elastic strain energies were applied to determine the preferred microstructure in terms of different annealing conditions and film thicknesses. Four microstructural cases, relating to different film thicknesses, were developed in this paper. Twinning in the Cu films is simulated by arbitrary re-assignment of randomly selected crystallite lattice ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:56:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/atenrok/article/841992</link><title>Fabrication of NaxCoO2 thin films by pulsed laser deposition</title><description>In this paper, we report the growth of NaxCoO2 thin films by pulsed laser deposition. Single [beta]-NaxCoO2 phase films showing metallic conducting behavior were obtained. The surface morphology of these films showed granular features. The films were stable in vacuum or in the pure oxygen environment, but were not stable in air, causing their resistivity to increase exponentially with time and become semiconductors or insulators. X-ray diffraction measurements confirmed that the (00l) orientation of the films did not change during this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:57:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/OlivierL/article/1619388</link><title>Study of the optical and structural properties of GaN films grown on Si substrates with a SiC layer</title><description>GaN films were grown on Si(100) substrates by molecular beam epitaxy employing an RF activated N-plasma source. The substrates were coated with a thin SiC layer to reduce the reaction of N with Si. The substrate temperature was set at 750 [degree sign]C, and the flux of Ga atoms was varied by changing the Ga-Knudsen cell temperature (TGa) from 950 to 1100 [degree sign]C. The effects of the different growth conditions on the optical and structural characteristics of the films were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:58:42">http://www.citeulike.org/group/7272/article/9779514</link><title>Composition and structure of vapour-deposited cryolite films</title><description>Vapour-deposited cryolite films were studied by reflection electron diffraction. It was found that the films generally did not consist exclusively of cryolite but also of dissociation products. At a higher evaporation rate even Na(AlF4) was formed on the substrate. Because of dissociation and fractionating during evaporation, the chemical composition of the condensed films depends strongly on the temperature of the evaporation source. The films showed differences in micro- structure caused by the growth mechanism, sorption of water vapour and recrystallisation. The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:59:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/AlbertoBarone/article/3211527</link><title>The nanoindentation behaviour of hard and soft films on silicon substrates</title><description>Carbon nitride and copper films of thickness 550 and 400 nm, respectively have been sputter deposited on silicon substrates. The indentation behaviour of these films is investigated by analysis of the load-displacement curves and by imaging of the residual indents. The Oliver and Pharr method is used to calculate the hardness from the load-displacement curve, while the contact area measured by atomic force microscopy is used in the traditional hardness equation: H=P/A. The carbon nitride films exhibited neither pile-up nor sink-in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:01:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rodney/article/3046619</link><title>The microstructure of thin films observed using atomic force microscopy</title><description>Atomic force microscopy was used to study the microstructure and nanostructure of sputtered and evaporated columnar thin films. The atomic force microscope was shown to be a useful tool for studying the surface topography of these technologically interesting surfaces. Two structure zone transitions were studied: the substrate-temperature dependent, zone 2 to zone 3 transition and the sputter-pressure dependent zone 1 to T transition. Columns of zone 1 films were found to occur in a number of different shapes; rounded domed columns, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7026-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7026_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:02:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/osos/article/6494313</link><title>Lead-Free Piezoelectric Thin Films of Mn-doped NaNbO3–BaTiO3 Fabricated by Chemical Solution Deposition</title><description>Lead-free piezoelectric thin films of NaNbO 3 –BaTiO 3 were fabricated on Pt/TiO x /SiO 2 /Si substrates by chemical solution deposition. Perovskite NaNbO 3 –BaTiO 3 single-phase thin films with improved leakage current and ferroelectric properties were prepared at 650 ºC by doping with a small amount of Mn. The 1.0 and 3.0 mol% Mn-doped 0.95NaNbO 3 –0.05BaTiO 3 thin films showed slim ferroelectric P – E hysteresis and field-induced strain loops at room temperature. The 1.0 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>