<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:03:00" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:03:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tictacgo/article/11295830</link><title>Gravity with a dynamical preferred frame</title><description>We study a generally covariant model in which local Lorentz invariance is broken "spontaneously" by a dynamical unit timelike vector field $u^a$---the "aether". Such a model makes it possible to study the gravitational and cosmological consequences of preferred frame effects, such as “variable speed of light" or high frequency dispersion, while preserving a generally covariant metric theory of gravity. In this paper we restrict attention to an action for an effective theory of the aether which involves only the antisymmetrized derivative $∇_[au_b]$. Without matter this theory is equivalent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:04:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kriskrogh/article/5848084</link><title>Non-Prefered Reference Frames and Anomalous Earth Flybys</title><description>Let us consider a reference frame Sigma prime in which the pseudo-Euclidean geometry holds. Einstein assumed that the principle of special relativity is valid, i.e. the reference frame of any uniformly moving observer is also described by the pseudo-Euclidean geometry. The transformation formulae from one reference frame to the other one are therefore given by the well-known Lorentz-transformations. But Einsteins assumption contradicts the observed dipole anisotropy of the cosmic microwave background (CMB) in the universe. The transformation formulae of the prefered reference frame Sigma prime in which the pseudo-Euclidean ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:05:02">http://www.citeulike.org/group/664/article/7263048</link><title>Preferred analysis methods for Affymetrix GeneChips. II. An expanded, balanced, wholly-defined spike-in dataset</title><description>BACKGROUND:Concomitant with the rise in the popularity of DNA microarrays has been a surge of proposed methods for the analysis of microarray data. Fully controlled "spike-in" datasets are an invaluable but rare tool for assessing the performance of various methods.RESULTS:We generated a new wholly defined Affymetrix spike-in dataset consisting of 18 microarrays. Over 5700 RNAs are spiked in at relative concentrations ranging from 1- to 4-fold, and the arrays from each condition are balanced with respect to both total RNA amount ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:06:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ffcloud/article/2839560</link><title>Bottom-up and top-down dynamics in visual cortex.</title><description>A key emergent property of the primary visual cortex (V1) is the orientation selectivity of its neurons. Recent experiments demonstrate remarkable bottom-up and top-down plasticity in orientation networks of the adult cortex. The basis for such dynamics is the mechanism by which orientation tuning is created and maintained, by integration of thalamocortical and intracortical inputs. Intracellular measurements of excitatory and inhibitory synaptic conductances reveal that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:07:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RMaitra/article/13127931</link><title>Including robustness in multi-criteria optimization for intensity-modulated proton therapy.</title><description>We present a method to include robustness in a multi-criteria optimization (MCO) framework for intensity-modulated proton therapy (IMPT). The approach allows one to simultaneously explore the trade-off between different objectives as well as the trade-off between robustness and nominal plan quality. In MCO, a database of plans each emphasizing different treatment planning objectives, is pre-computed to approximate the Pareto surface. An IMPT treatment plan that strikes the best balance between the different objectives can be selected by navigating on the Pareto ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:08:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mdreid/article/3079477</link><title>On preferred point geometry in statistics</title><description>A brief synopsis of progress in differential geometry in statistics is followed by a note of some points of tension in the developing relationship between these disciplines. The preferred point nature of much of statistics is described and suggests the adoption of a corresponding geometry which reduces these tensions. Applications of preferred point geometry in statistics are then reviewed. These include extensions of statistical manifolds, a statistical interpretation of duality in Amari's expected geometry, and removal of the apparent incompatibility between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:09:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/egcavalcanti/article/7296649</link><title>Defining the moving preferred basis</title><description>There are many formalisms to describe quantum decoherence. However, many of them give a non general and ad hoc definition of "pointer basis" or "moving preferred basis", and this fact is a problem for the decoherence program. In this paper we will consider quantum systems under a general theoretical framework for decoherence and present a very general definition of the moving preferred basis. In addition, this definition is implemented in a well known model and the time of decoherence and the relaxation time are defined and compared with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:11:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dborrajo/article/8387915</link><title>Specifying and computing preferred plans</title><description>In this paper, we address the problem of specifying and computing preferred plans using rich, qualitative, user preferences. We propose a logical language for specifying preferences over the evolution of states and actions associated with a plan. We provide a semantics for our first-order preference language in the situation calculus, and prove that progression of our preference formulae preserves this semantics. This leads to the development of PPlan, a bounded best-first search planner that computes preferred plans. Our preference language is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:12:09">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10262794</link><title>Preferred states of the apparatus</title><description>A simple one-dimensional model for the system–apparatus interaction is analysed. The system is a spin-1/2 particle, and its position and momentum degrees constitute the apparatus. An analysis involving only unitary Schrödinger dynamics illustrates the nature of the correlations established in the system–apparatus entangled state. It is shown that even in the absence of any environment-induced decoherence, or any other measurement model, certain initial states of the apparatus – like localized Gaussian wavepackets – are preferred over others, in terms of measurementlike ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:13:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Mjczek/article/12604361</link><title>Preferred orientation of chondrules in chondrites</title><description>Twenty H- and L-group chondrites, showing various degrees of recrystallization, were examined for preferred chondrule orientation. All of the samples but three possess a foliation, which is poorly developed in two chondrites and pronounced in the others. Most of the strongly foliate samples also possess a lineation in the plane of foliation. As the foliation in these chondrites shows no systematic change in intensity with the degree of recrystalization, it is interpreted as a relict sedimentary fabric which was imposed during ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>