<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:15:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:15:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davide_caldo/article/11610598</link><title>Percutaneous treatment of intervertebral disc herniation.</title><description>Interventional radiology plays a major role in the management of symptomatic intervertebral disc herniations. In the absence of significant pain relief with conservative treatment including oral pain killers and anti-inflammatory drugs, selective image-guided periradicular infiltrations are generally indicated. The precise control of needle positioning allows optimal distribution of steroids along the painful nerve root. After 6 weeks of failure of conservative treatment including periradicular infiltration, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:16:26">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13714/article/7560350</link><title>Integrating spatial multi-criteria evaluation and expert knowledge for GIS-based habitat suitability modelling</title><description>GIS data processing and spatial analysis, together with modern decision analysis techniques, were used in this study to improve habitat suitability evaluation over large areas. Both empirical evaluation models and models based on expert knowledge can be applied in this approach. The habitat requirements of species were described as map layers within GIS so that each map layer represented one criterion. GIS was used as the platform in managing, combining and displaying the criterion data and also as a tool for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:17:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saranshchoudhury/article/10733922</link><title>The Theory of Constraints and the Make-or-Buy Decision: An Update and Review</title><description>The make-or-buy decision has traditionally been made using standard cost accounting methods. In this Journal, Gardiner and Blackstone (1991) made a strong case for incorporating the bottleneck capacity into the decision. However, their method did not guarantee the best solution for the more complicated make-or-buy problem. Additionally, their approach in some cases allowed organizations to forego opportunities for profit improvement. Since the publication of the Gardiner and Blackstone research, spreadsheets with in-built Linear Programming (LP) based optimizers allow for quick “what-if” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:18:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lispler/article/5137960</link><title>Clock synchronization for wireless sensor networks: a survey</title><description>Recent advances in micro-electromechanical (MEMS) technology have led to the development of small, low-cost, and low-power sensors. Wireless sensor networks (WSNs) are large-scale networks of such sensors, dedicated to observing and monitoring various aspects of the physical world. In such networks, data from each sensor is agglomerated using data fusion to form a single meaningful result, which makes time synchronization between sensors highly desirable. This paper surveys and evaluates existing clock synchronization protocols based on a palette of factors like precision, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:19:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/7954/article/6870131</link><title>Using GIS-based multicriteria evaluation and path optimization for effective forest field inventory</title><description>The inventory practices concerning non-industrial privately owned forests are undergoing significant changes in Finland. In the future, the collection of information will be increasingly carried out by the means of remote sensing technologies, which is bound to have strong implications for the traditional and extensive field inventory practices. This study presents a new method for determining the importance of individual forest stands to the field inventory, including a technique for using this information to calculate efficient field inventory tours. The proposed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:20:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/AntoniaL/article/3106700</link><title>The Right to Buy: Analysis and Evaluation of a Housing Policy (Real Estate Issues)</title><description>An evaluation of the most enduring privatisation of the Thatcher era …_ Written in an accessible style, this is a key reference for students and researchers in housing and planning; geography; and social policy. The book analyses the operation and impact of the right to buy policy (RTB). It includes a critique of the Housing Act and the 2001 Housing (Scotland) Act. The enactment of these changes under a Labour government affirms the continuance of the RTB. The authors take stock of its profound effect on housing policy, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:21:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/3102586</link><title>More Damned Lies and Statistics: How Numbers Confuse Public Issues</title><description>In this sequel to the acclaimed _Damned Lies and Statistics, _which the _Boston Globe _said "deserves a place next to the dictionary on every school, media, and home-office desk," Joel Best continues his straightforward, lively, and humorous account of how statistics are produced, used, and misused by everyone from researchers to journalists. Underlining the importance of critical thinking in all matters numerical, Best illustrates his points with examples of good and bad statistics about such contemporary concerns as school shootings, fatal hospital errors, bullying, teen suicides, deaths at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:22:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dlouzeck/article/606941</link><title>Random Violence : How We Talk about New Crimes and New Victims</title><description>&lt;i&gt;Random Violence&lt;/i&gt; is a deft and thought-provoking exploration of the ways we talk about--and why we worry about--new crimes and new forms of victimization. Focusing on so-called random crimes such as freeway shootings, gang violence, hate crimes, stalking, and wilding, Joel Best shows how new crime problems emerge and how some quickly fade from public attention while others spread and become enduring subjects of concern. Best's original and incisive argument illuminates the fact that while these crimes are in actuality ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:23:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jklugman/article/1542141</link><title>Flavor of the Month: Why Smart People Fall for Fads</title><description>While fads such as hula hoops or streaking are usually dismissed as silly enthusiasms, trends in institutions such as education, business, medicine, science, and criminal justice are often taken seriously, even though their popularity and usefulness is sometimes short-lived. Institutional fads such as open classrooms, quality circles, and multiple personality disorder are constantly making the rounds, promising astonishing new developments--novel ways of teaching reading or arithmetic, better methods of managing businesses, or improved treatments for disease. Some of these trends prove ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:24:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/euclid/article/8361690</link><title>Evidence Examples &amp; Explanations, 6e</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>