<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:26:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:26:51">http://www.citeulike.org/group/8440/article/3981030</link><title>Test process optimization: closing the gap in the defect spectrum</title><description>This paper describes our methodology of tuning the test process of the Motorola Operations and Maintenance Center product to systematically reduce field defects. The benefits include improved test cases, reduced defects and the availability of up to date field data for feature verification ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:27:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10149589</link><title>Thomas Kuhn</title><description>Thomas Kuhn (1922-1996), the author of The Structure of Scientific Revolutions, is probably the best-known and most influential historian and philosopher of science of the last 25 years, and has become something of a cultural icon. His concepts of paradigm, paradigm change and incommensurability have changed our thinking about science. This volume offers an introduction to Kuhn's life and work and considers the implications of his work for philosophy, cognitive psychology, social studies of science and feminism. More than a retrospective ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:28:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NickGasson/article/3484636</link><title>A model and methodology for hardware-software codesign</title><description>A behavioral model of a class of mixed hardware-software systems is presented. A codesign methodology for such systems is defined. The methodology includes hardware-software partitioning, behavioral synthesis, software compilation, and demonstration on a testbed consisting of a commercial central processing unit (CPU), field-programmable gate arrays, and programmable interconnections. Design examples that illustrate how certain characteristics of system behavior and constraints suggest hardware or software implementation are presented ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:30:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vplagnol/article/3731361</link><title>Commentary: The concept of ‘Mendelian Randomization’</title><description>10.1093/ije/dyh048 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:31:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/HelenBe/article/8588098</link><title>The pyramids and palm trees test</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:32:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jhibbits/article/2709712</link><title>Embedded deterministic test for low cost manufacturing test</title><description>This paper introduces embedded deterministic test (EDT) technology, which reduces manufacturing test cost by providing one to two orders of magnitude reduction in scan test data volume and scan test time. The EDT architecture, the compression algorithm, design flow, experimental results, and silicon implementation are presented. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:33:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dwei98/article/2326353</link><title>Genesys-Pro: innovations in test program generation for functional processor verification</title><description>Functional verification is widely recognized as the bottleneck of the hardware design cycle. With the ever-growing demand for greater performance and faster time to market, coupled with the exponential growth in hardware size, verification has become increasingly difficult. Although formal methods such as model checking and theorem proving have resulted in noticeable progress, these approaches apply only to the verification of relatively small design blocks or to very focused verification goals. Current industry practice is to use separate, automatic, random stimuli ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:34:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PolymeraseI/article/8904644</link><title>Regulatory networks seen as asynchronous automata: A logical description</title><description>The aim of this paper is to provide a compact answer to the questions: why treat complex biological systems in logical terms? how can one do it conveniently? Our initial description (Thomas, R. J. theor. Biol. 1973, 42, 563) is what we now call the “naive” logical description. After recalling the essential elements of this asynchronous description, the present paper introduces the use of logical variables with more than two values the notion of logical parameters the logical identification of all ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:35:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Giulio/article/10717284</link><title>Medical beam monitor—Pre-clinical evaluation and future applications</title><description>Future medical ion beam applications for cancer therapy which are based on scanning technology will require advanced beam diagnostics equipment. For a precise analysis of beam parameters we want to resolve time structures in the range of microseconds to nanoseconds. A prototype of an advanced beam monitor was developed by the University of Applied Sciences Wiener Neustadt and its research subsidiary Fotec in co-operation with CERN RD42, Ohio State University and the JoÅ¾ef Stefan Institute in Ljubljana. The detector is based ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:36:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/primerplus/article/3278993</link><title>Multiple scan tree design with test vector modification</title><description>In this paper, we propose a method of test compression for multiple scan designs. Instead of the conventional serial scan chains, the proposed method constructs scan trees in which scan flip-flops are placed and routed in a tree structure. Inputs of the scan trees drive several scan trees of different lengths (height). Since test data volume and test application time are dominated by the scan tree with the maximum height among the constructed scan trees, the proposed method distributes the scan ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>