<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:50:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:50:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eguaus/article/1913513</link><title>Why a laptop orchestra?</title><description>In 2005, the Princeton Laptop Orchestra (PLOrk), an ensemble of fifteen laptop-based meta-instruments, began its first season. In this article, the author explores the motivations for starting a laptop orchestra, both in musical and cultural terms, and some of the aesthetic, technical, and compositional issues that face those interested in working with such an ensemble. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:51:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/falkowata/article/8981845</link><title>Laptop Configurations in Offices: Effects on Posture and Discomfort</title><description>This study investigates a variety of laptop configurations and their effects on posture and discomfort. There are several benefits to using laptops in an office setting. They conserve space and allow greater computing flexibility in meetings or business travel. One potential drawback of laptops is that the keyboard and monitor cannot be adjusted independently, which may lead to constrained postures and musculoskeletal discomfort. In this study, 14 users experienced six laptop configurations. The configurations varied in terms of laptop placement and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:51:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/falkowata/article/8981819</link><title>Disruption of meetings by laptop use: is there a 10-second solution?</title><description>We have conducted a study of meetings to gain an understanding of the sources of disruption when laptops are present. We videotaped five workplace meetings in which over 600 information tasks were performed by participants using paper or laptops. We saw evidence that people preferred task durations not to exceed approximately 10 seconds. Tasks performed by laptop users were more likely to exceed this limit, and this could contribute to disruptions. We suggest that laptop software may need to assist users ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:53:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/falkowata/article/8981814</link><title>A comparison of the postures assumed when using laptop computers and desktop computers</title><description>This study evaluated the postural implications of using a laptop computer. Laptop computer screens and keyboards are joined, and are therefore unable to be adjusted separately in terms of screen height and distance, and keyboard height and distance. The posture required for their use is likely to be constrained, as little adjustment can be made for the anthropometric differences of users. In addition to the postural constraints, the study looked at discomfort levels and performance when using laptops as compared with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:54:21">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13715/article/432139</link><title>Doing Cultural Studies: The Story of the Sony Walkman (Culture, Media &amp; Identities, Vol. 1) (Culture, Media and Identities series)</title><description>This book introduces the substantive and theoretical strands of contemporary cultural studies through the medium of a particular case study: that of the Sony Walkman. Through the Walkman example, Doing Cultural Studies shows how and why cultural practices and institutions have come to play such a crucial part in our lives, and introduces the central ideas, concepts, and methods of analysis involved in doing cultural studies. The authors of this unique work show how the Walkman is a typical cultural artifact ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:55:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mchinen/article/4233540</link><title>Live coding in laptop performance</title><description>Seeking new forms of expression in computer music, a small number of laptop composers are braving the challenges of coding music on the fly. Not content to submit meekly to the rigid interfaces of performance software like Ableton Live or Reason, they work with programming languages, building their own custom software, tweaking or writing the programs themselves as they perform. Often this activity takes place within some established language for computer music like SuperCollider, but there is no reason to stop ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:56:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gemturfer/article/6905701</link><title>The impact of laptop provision on teacher attitudes towards ICT</title><description>The use of information and communication technologies (ICTs) in Finnish primary and secondary schools has been increasing for the last decade, but the full potential of the new technology has not been achieved; pedagogical thinking in educational institutes has not advanced in parallel with technological advances. Teachers attitudes towards the use of ICTs in schools are significant factors in determining how technology is used in schools. The aim of this study is to investigate if there is a difference in attitudes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:57:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3105541</link><title>Micro-politics of social protection: examining the effectiveness of 'employment rights' for the informal sector in rural Maharashtra</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:58:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1461681</link><title>Editorial Introduction</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7034-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7034_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:59:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4818</link><title>Ethyl 5-amino-3-methyl­isoxazole-4-carboxyl­ate</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>