<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7036">holiday houses ardennes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:10:55" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:10:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sougnez/article/2397813</link><title>Sediment budget and tectonic evolution of the Meuse catchment in the Ardennes and the Roer Valley Rift System</title><description>The Meuse river system is located in the northeastern part of the Paris Basin, the Ardennes, and the Roer Valley Rift System (RVRS). The Meuse river system developed during the uplift of the Ardennes since the Eocene and it was affected by renewed rifting of the RVRS starting in the Late Oligocene. In response to the uplift of the Ardennes, the river system incised and a terrace sequence developed during the Plio-Pleistocene. The sediments generated by erosion in the catchment were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:11:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/benjaminopperman/article/4945621</link><title>Spectrophotometry of proteins: Absorption spectra of tyrosine, tryptophan and their mixtures. II. Estimation of tyrosine and tryptophan in proteins.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:13:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jpkalin/article/6190050</link><title>In[ter]vention: Locating Rhetoric's &lt;i&gt;Ethos&lt;/i&gt;</title><description>Rhetorical invention is the principal source of politics and ethics as contemporary theories from various disciplines demonstrate. The complex reflexive relationship among politics, ethics, and invention demands ethical responsibility, requiring rhetoricians (who hold a key to this subject) to acknowledge and attend to their &lt;i&gt;ethos&lt;/i&gt;, used here in the classical sense of &lt;i&gt;ethos&lt;/i&gt; as gathering place. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:14:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12365284</link><title>Effects of exercise during the holiday season on changes in body weight, body composition and blood pressure</title><description>Effects of exercise during the holiday season on changes in body weight, body composition and blood pressure European Journal of Clinical Nutrition advance online publication, May 22 2013. doi:10.1038/ejcn.2013.98 Authors: J L Stevenson, S Krishnan, M A Stoner, Z Goktas &amp; J A Cooper ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:15:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jforest443/article/6045089</link><title>Why did FDR's Bank Holiday Succeed?</title><description>After a month-long run on American banks, Franklin Delano Roosevelt proclaimed a Bank Holiday, beginning March 6, 1933, that shut down the banking system. When the banks reopened on March 13, depositors stood in line to return their hoarded cash. This article attributes the success of the Bank Holiday and the remarkable turnaround in the public’s confidence to the Emergency Banking Act, passed by Congress on March 9, 1933. Roosevelt used the emergency currency provisions of the Act to encourage the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:16:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1141692</link><title>Slavery and denial</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:17:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rrbarb/article/548960</link><title>Knowledge and networks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:18:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bjbraams/article/12652743</link><title>Linear versus cyclic sixteen electron triatomics: P2S and SiS2</title><description>Ab initio theoretical methods have been used to determine the geometries, energies and vibrational frequencies of linear, cyclic singlet and cyclic triplet isomers of P2S and SiS2. Although it has not been observed, the cyclic singlet structure for P2S has been previously predicted theoretically to be the ground state. In the present study both the cyclic singlet and the cyclic triplet isomers of P2S are found to lie below the experimentally observed linear isomer. The linear SiS2 isomer, however, is the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:20:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/10422970</link><title>Environmental impacts of the UK residential sector: Life cycle assessment of houses</title><description>This paper presents for the first time the results of a full life cycle assessment (LCA)1 study for the three most common types of house in the UK: detached, semi-detached and terraced. All life cycle stages are considered, including house construction, use and demolition after 50 years. The results indicate that the use stage has the largest contribution to most environmental impacts. For example, the global warming potential (GWP)2 over the 50-year lifetime of the detached house is 455 t of CO2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7036-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7036_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:21:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/renreff/article/2164130</link><title>It's a Holiday!!</title><description>Summary This article studies various holiday distributions, the most interesting one being Easter. Gauss’ Easter algorithm and Microsoft Excel are used to determine that the Easter distribution can be closely approximated by the convolution of two well-known uniform distributions. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>