<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:22:16" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:22:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/goncalojustino/article/1242600</link><title>How to write consistently boring scientific literature</title><description>Although scientists typically insist that their research is very exciting and adventurous when they talk to laymen and prospective students, the allure of this enthusiasm is too often lost in the predictable, stilted structure and language of their scientific publications. I present here, a top-10 list of recommendations for how to write consistently boring scientific publications. I then discuss why we should and how we could make these contributions more accessible and exciting. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:23:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/12480261</link><title>From the Editors: How to write a high-quality review</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:24:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/4067136</link><title>Write to the Top!: How to Become a Prolific Academic</title><description>This concise guide to writing is designed to help any academic become not only productive but truly prolific. It is a pithy, no-nonsense, no-excuses guide to maximizing the quality and quantity of scholarly output. Johnson and Mullen__offer an accessible overview of the art of writing efficiently andeffectively, provide a one-stop source for the nuts and bolts of success ingetting things written and into print, and advise academics on how to navigatethe turbulent waters of professional stress along the way. This is the firstbook that explicitly summarizes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:25:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/1641851</link><title>How to Write a Lot: A Practical Guide to Productive Academic Writing</title><description>All students and professors need to write, and many struggle to finish their stalled dissertations, journal articles, book chapters, or grant proposals. Writing is hard work and can be difficult to wedge into a frenetic academic schedule. In this practical, light-hearted, and encouraging book, Paul J. Silvia explains that writing productively does not require innate skills or special traits but specific tactics and actions. Drawing examples from his own field of psychology, he shows ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:26:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/reconnie/article/791402</link><title>How to write a proof</title><description>In their &lt;em&gt; The mathematical experience&lt;/em&gt; [Birkhäuser, Boston, MA, 1980], P. J. Davis and R. Hersh are right to point out that "In being exposed to the scrutiny and judgement of a new audience, the proof is subject to a constant process of criticism and revalidation. Errors, ambiguities, and misunderstandings are cleared by constant exposure" (p. 151). However, the most illuminating aspect of their discussion of the role of proving theorems in mathematics is that theorem proving, in the best instances, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:27:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akollmar/article/7202861</link><title>How to write a systematic review.</title><description>Evidence-based medicine (EBM) is the combination of the best available research evidence with clinical experience and patient needs. The concept of EBM as a part of clinical decision making has become increasingly popular over the last decade. In the hierarchy of studies meta-analysis and systematic reviews occupy the highest levels. A systematic review of a clinical question can be performed by following a relatively standard form. These techniques as described here can be performed without formal training. Systematic reviews conducted in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:28:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/reconnie/article/2199619</link><title>How to write consistently boring scientific literature</title><description>Although scientists typically insist that their research is very exciting and adventurous when they talk to laymen and prospective students, the allure of this enthusiasm is too often lost in the predictable, stilted structure and language of their scientific publications. I present here, a top-10 list of recommendations for how to write consistently boring scientific publications. I then discuss why we should and how we could make these contributions more accessible and exciting. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:29:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/williamharris/article/1643685</link><title>How to read a paper</title><description>Researchers spend a great deal of time reading research papers. However, this skill is rarely taught, leading to much wasted effort. This article outlines a practical and efficient three-pass method for reading research papers. I also describe how to use this method to do a literature survey. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:30:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/els2006/article/5205598</link><title>How to write an evidence-based clinical review article.</title><description>Traditional clinical review articles, also known as updates, differ from systematic reviews and meta-analyses. Updates selectively review the medical literature while discussing a topic broadly. Non-quantitative systematic reviews comprehensively examine the medical literature, seeking to identify and synthesize all relevant information to formulate the best approach to diagnosis or treatment. Meta-analyses (quantitative systematic reviews) seek to answer a focused clinical question, using rigorous statistical analysis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:31:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chvlyl/article/5842862</link><title>How To Choose a Good Scientific Problem</title><description>Choosing good problems is essential for being a good scientist. But what is a good problem, and how do you choose one? The subject is not usually discussed explicitly within our profession. Scientists are expected to be smart enough to figure it out on their own and through the observation of their teachers. This lack of explicit discussion leaves a vacuum that can lead to approaches such as choosing problems that can give results that merit publication in valued journals, resulting ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>