<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7040">vom fass gent</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:52:25" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:52:28">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7761477</link><title>The Gent–Mcwilliams parameterization: 20/20 hindsight</title><description>It has now been 20 years since the Gent and McWilliams paper on “Isopycnal Mixing in Ocean Circulation Models” was published in January 1990 issue of the Journal of Physical Oceanography. That paper was highlighted at the CLIVAR Working Group on Ocean Model Development “Workshop on Ocean Mesoscale Eddies” which was held at the UK Meteorological Office in April 2009, and this review paper is based on the talk given at that Workshop. It contains some hindsights on how the parameterization of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:53:19">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5347490</link><title>Non-linear stresses in a rubber cylinder sheared by pressure at one end</title><description>Normal stresses are set up by shearing a rubber block or tube. They depend strongly on the end conditions, even for relatively long specimens [A.N. Gent, J.B. Suh, S.G. Kelly III, Mechanics of rubber shear springs, Int. J. Non-Linear Mech. 42 (2007) 241–249; J.B. Suh, A.N. Gent, S.G. Kelly III, Shear of rubber tube springs, Int. J. Non-Linear Mech. 42 (2007) 1116–1126]. We have now examined a solid rubber cylinder bonded within a rigid cylindrical tube and subjected to pressure at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:54:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4244975</link><title>Scapegoating Strategically: Reselection, Strategic Interaction, and the Diversionary Theory of War</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:55:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9385056</link><title>Relative Rebel Strength and Power Sharing in Intrastate Conflicts</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:56:44">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4243908</link><title>The Inner Life of Mestizo Nationalism by Estelle Tarica</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:57:41">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3633050</link><title>State Infrastructural Power and Nationalism: Comparative Lessons from Mexico and Argentina</title><description>Abstract  This article focuses on the nexus between state infrastructural power and legitimacy. A comparative case study of nationalism in mid-twentieth-century Mexico and Argentina provides the basis for theorizing the impact of state infrastructural power on transformations of official understandings of nationhood. Both countries experienced a transition from liberal to popular nationalism. The extent to which popular nationalism became a regular product of state organizations varied between the two cases, depending on the timing of state development. The temporal congruence between the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:58:40">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3829338</link><title>Notiz</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:59:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/541922</link><title>The body as interactive display: examining bodies in a public exhibition</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:00:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8922510</link><title>Nutzung von Markersystemen in der Behandlung des Harnblasenkarzinoms</title><description>Für das Harnblasenkarzinom sind die derzeit akzeptierten Prognosefaktoren der Differenzierungsgrad des Tumors, die Infiltrationstiefe (T-Kategorie) und im Falle eines muskelinvasiven Karzinoms der Lymphknotenstatus. Diese morphologischen Kriterien korrelieren grundsätzlich mit dem klinischen Verlauf der betroffenen Patienten. Dennoch ist man bestrebt Prognosefaktoren zu identifizieren, die unabhängig vom histopathologischen Befund prognostische Relevanz besitzen. Dies scheint v. a. für die frühinvasiven Tumoren der Kategorie T1 aber auch für den Verlauf organbegrenzter muskelinvasiver Karzinome von Bedeutung zu sein, da die Progressionsneigung durchaus heterogen ist. Hierzu führten wir eine ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7040-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7040_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:01:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/timleslie/article/6817641</link><title>The Gent–McWilliams Skew Flux</title><description>This paper formulates tracer stirring arising from the Gent–McWilliams (GM) eddy-induced transport in terms of a skew-diffusive flux. A skew-diffusive tracer flux is directed normal to the tracer gradient, which is in contrast to a diffusive tracer flux directed down the tracer gradient. Analysis of the GM skew flux provides an understanding of the physical mechanisms prescribed by GM stirring, which is complementary to the more familiar advective flux perspective. Additionally, it unifies the tracer mixing operators arising from Redi isoneutral ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>