<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:12:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:12:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rblake/article/7035369</link><title>Two tetrahedral C1 cubic macro elements</title><description>We propose two tetrahedral C1 cubic macro elements that are constructed locally on one tetrahedron without any knowledge of the geometry of neighboring tetrahedra. Among such geometrically unconstrained local polynomial tetrahedral C1 schemes requiring only first order derivative data, our macro elements have the smallest number of coefficients. The resulting macro element spaces are stable and provide full approximation power. We give explicit formulae that can be used to implement our schemes. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:13:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dkoveal/article/6662815</link><title>Taxonomy and function of C1 protein kinase C homology domains.</title><description>C1 domains are compact alpha/beta structural units of about 50 amino acids which tightly bind two zinc ions. These domains were first discovered as the loci of phorbol ester and diacylglycerol binding to conventional protein kinase C isozymes, which contain 2 C1 domains (C1A and C1B) in their N-terminal regulatory regions. We present a comprehensive list of 54 C1 domains occurring singly or doubly in 34 different proteins. Many C1 domains and C1 domain-containing proteins bind phorbol esters, but many others ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:14:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Svea/article/8951880</link><title>Characterization of the transcription activator protein C1 of bacteriophage P22.</title><description>We cloned, expressed, and purified the positive regulatory protein C1 of the temperate phage P22 of Salmonella typhimurium. The purified protein was characterized as to its amino acid composition, protein sequence, molecular weight, and antigenicity. P22 C1 was shown to be a tetrameric protein composed of four identical subunits with M(r) = 10,000. Moreover, we identified and characterized two P22 C1-dependent phage promoters, P(RE) and Pa23, whose function was completely dependent on C1 both in vitro and in vivo. These two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:15:26">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2944/article/2392971</link><title>Highly divergent genes for methanopterin-linked C1 transfer reactions in Lake Washington, assessed via metagenomic analysis and mRNA detection.</title><description>The origins and the evolutionary history of tetrahydromethanopterin-linked C1 transfer reactions that are part of two environmentally important biotransformations, methylotrophy and methanogenesis, are still not well understood. In previous studies, we have expanded the known phylogenetic diversity of these reactions by identifying genes highly diverging from the ones associated with cultivated Proteobacteria, Planctomycetes, or Archaea (M. G. Kalyuzhnaya, M. E. Lidstrom, and L. Chistoserdova, Microb. Ecol. 48:463-472, 2004; M. G. Kalyuzhnaya, O. Nercessian, M. E. Lidstrom, and L. Chistoserdova, Environ. Microbiol. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:16:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kinestetika/article/7343721</link><title>Chloromethane-Induced Genes Define a Third C1 Utilization Pathway in Methylobacterium chloromethanicum CM4</title><description>Methylobacterium chloromethanicum CM4 is an aerobic alpha-proteobacterium capable of growth with chloromethane as the sole carbon and energy source. Two proteins, CmuA and CmuB, were previously purified and shown to catalyze the dehalogenation of chloromethane and the vitamin B12-mediated transfer of the methyl group of chloromethane to tetrahydrofolate. Three genes located near cmuA and cmuB, designated metF, folD and purU and encoding homologs of methylene tetrahydrofolate (methylene-H4folate) reductase, methylene-H4folate dehydrogenase-methenyl-H4folate cyclohydrolase and formyl-H4folate hydrolase, respectively, suggested the existence of a chloromethane-specific ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:17:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Svea/article/8953354</link><title>ban Operon of bacteriophage P1Mutational analysis of the c1 repressor-controlled operator</title><description>The repressor of bacteriophage P1, encoded by the c1 gene, represses the phage lytic functions and is responsible for maintaining the P1 prophage in the lysogenic state. The c1 repressor interacts with at least 11 binding sites or operators widely scattered over the P1 genome. From these operators, a 17 base-pair asymmetric consensus sequence, ATTGCTCTAATAAATTT, was derived. Here, we show that the operator, Op72 of the P1ban operon consists of two overlapping 17 base-pair sequences a and b forming an incomplete ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:18:46">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2944/article/1734155</link><title>Archaea-like genes for C1-transfer enzymes in Planctomycetes: phylogenetic implications of their unexpected presence in this phylum.</title><description>The unexpected presence of archaea-like genes for tetrahydromethanopterin (H4MPT)-dependent enzymes in the completely sequence geiome of the aerobic marine planctomycete Pirellula sp. strain 1 ("Rhodopirellula baltica") and in the currently sequenced genome of the aerobic freshwater planctomycete Gemmata obscuriglobus strain UQM2246 revives the discussion on the origin of these genes in the bacterial domain. We compared the genomic arrangement of these genes in Planctomyetes and methylotrophic proteobacteria and perormed a phylogenetic analysis of the encoded protein sequences to address the question ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:20:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kinestetika/article/7343723</link><title>A methenyl tetrahydromethanopterin cyclohydrolase and a methenyl tetrahydrofolate cyclohydrolase in Methylobacterium extorquens AM1</title><description>Recently it was found that Methylobacterium extorquens AM1 contains both tetrahydromethanopterin (H4MPT) and tetrahydrofolate (H4F) as carriers of C1 units. In this paper we report that the aerobic methylotroph contains a methenyl H4MPT cyclohydrolase (0.9 U·mg-1 cell extract protein) and a methenyl H4F cyclohydrolase (0.23 U·mg-1). Both enzymes, which were specific for their substrates, were purified and characterized and the encoding genes identified via the N-terminal amino acid sequence. The purified methenyl H4MPT cyclohydrolase with a specific activity of 630 U·mg-1 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:21:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/GermanErlenkamp/article/4516347</link><title>Design, Synthesis, and Biological Activity of Isophthalic Acid Derivatives Targeted to the C1 Domain of Protein Kinase C</title><description>Protein kinase C (PKC) is a widely studied molecular target for the treatment of cancer and other diseases. We have approached the issue of modifying PKC function by targeting the C1 domain in the regulatory region of the enzyme. Using the X-ray crystal structure of the PKC δ C1b domain, we have discovered conveniently synthesizable derivatives of dialkyl 5-(hydroxymethyl)isophthalate that can act as potential C1 domain ligands. Structure−activity studies confirmed that the important functional groups predicted by modeling were indispensable for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7042-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7042_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:22:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10838477</link><title>Therapeutische Strategien gegen die Progression der Niereninsuffizienz</title><description>Die chronische Niereninsuffizienz ist eine häufige Entität. Unabhängig von der Behandlung der Grunderkrankung sind Maßnahmen identifiziert worden, die das Fortschreiten zur dialysepflichtigen Niereninsuffizienz verlangsamen können. Die wichtigsten Maßnahmen sind dabei die Senkung des Blutdrucks und der Proteinurie. Nachdem die mögliche Gefährdung der Patienten durch eine zu starke Blutdrucksenkung in verschiedenen Studien offensichtlich wurde, werden die bisher formulierten niedrigen Blutdruckziele in Zweifel gezogen. Es ist daher eine individualisierte Therapie notwendig, im Rahmen derer kardiovaskuläre Vorschädigungen und die Gefahr einer Progression der Niereninsuffizienz ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>