<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7043">rhapsody in blue sheet piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:23:27" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:23:34">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10716115</link><title>Blue Gene/Q: by co-design</title><description>Blue Gene/Q represents the third generation in the IBM Blue Gene line of supercomputer systems. Architecturally, BG/Q installations can scale to over 100 PetaFLOPS. Blue Gene/Q follows the same philosophy as the earlier Blue Gene/L and Blue Gene/P systems, namely to build a massively parallel and highly reliable High Performance Computing (HPC) system out of power-efficient processor chips. Such power-efficient chips, in turn, allow dense packaging, which consequently results in power efficient, cost efficient, and floor-space efficient systems. A focus on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:24:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/8860201</link><title>Physical modeling of the piano</title><description>A project aimed at constructing a physical model of the piano is described. Our goal is to calculate the sound produced by the instrument entirely from Newton’s laws. The structure of the model is described along with experiments that augment and test the model calculations. The state of the model and what can be learned from it are discussed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:25:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/9635579</link><title>Piano hammers and their force compression characteristics: Does a power law make sense?</title><description>We have studied the force characteristics of a collection of piano hammers, through studies of the acceleration of the hammer head, the force due to the compression of the hammer felt, Fh, and the associated bending of the hammer shank which occurs when a hammer strikes a rigid object. By integration of the acceleration one can estimate the compression of the felt, and thus obtain a force-compression Fh(z) relationship; our results for this function are compared with previous experiments and theoretical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:26:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/10751945</link><title>Interferometric studies of a piano soundboard</title><description>Electronic speckle pattern interferometry has been used to study the deflection shapes of a piano soundboard. A design for an interferometer that can image such an unstable object is introduced, and interferograms of a piano soundboard obtained using this interferometer are presented. Deflection shapes are analyzed and compared to a finite-element model, and it is shown that the force the strings exert on the soundboard is important in determining the mode shapes and resonant frequencies. Measurements of resonance frequencies and driving-point ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:27:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/10214366</link><title>Coupled piano strings</title><description>The admittance of the piano bridge has a crucial effect on piano tone by coupling together the strings belonging to one note into a single dynamical system. In this paper, we first develop theoretical expressions that show how the rate of energy transmission to the bridge as a function of time (including the phenomena of beats and ’’aftersound’’) depends on bridge admittance, hammr irregularities, and the exact state in which the piano is tuned. We then present experimental data showing the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:28:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/10214363</link><title>Dispersion of waves in piano strings</title><description>A recent survey of piano acoustics literature revealed an apparent lack of attention to various aspects of dispersion in piano strings, apart from some information on its effect on inharmonicity of piano tone partials. In this article, it will be shown how group velocity of transverse waves in piano strings can be measured as a function of frequency with the aid of a short‐time spectral analysis method. Examples of group velocity measurements appear to be essentially in agreement with the theoretical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:29:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/8860195</link><title>Simple model of a piano soundboard</title><description>The vibrational properties of a simple finite-element model of a piano soundboard are considered. The main focus is on the behavior of the mechanical impedance in the musically important frequency range ~ 50104 Hz. The model includes the effects of elastic anisotropy and the ribs. It is argued that the ribs are an essential ingredient for producing the behavior of the impedance which is observed experimentally. ©1997 Acoustical Society of America. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:30:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardo/article/4015938</link><title>A dynamic assertion-based verification platform for UML statecharts over rhapsody</title><description>For quite some time, the Unified Modeling Language (UML) has been adopted by designers of safety critical control systems such as automotive and aviation control. This has led to an increased emphasis on setting up a validation flow over UML that can be used to guarantee the correctness of UML models. In this paper, we propose a dynamic Assertion-based verification (ABV) framework for validation of UML Statecharts over the Rhapsody platform of I-logix. We present an extension of Linear Temporal Logic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:31:57">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13568/article/12368988</link><title>Decay Rates of Piano Tones</title><description>Decay curves were recorded for an upright piano, a baby grand, and an electronic spinet. For some tones the partials were recorded separately. Decay rates for the electronic piano were measured at different levels of piano amplification. Analysis of the data reveals the degree of control exerted by the sounding board upon decay rate, particularly in the initial stage of decay. The significance of this control by the sounding board is discussed, in relation to the problem of electrical amplification of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7043-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7043_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:33:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/12355243</link><title>Dynamical properties of piano soundboards</title><description>In pianos, the transfer of energy from strings to soundboard and the radiation of sound are highly dependent on the dynamical properties of the soundboard. In this paper, a numerical study is conducted for various rib configurations, showing that even slight irregularities in rib spacing can induce a strong localization of the soundboard velocity pattern. The effective vibrating area can be further reduced due to the spatial filtering effect of the bridge. Numerical predictions of modal shapes and operating deflection shapes ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>