<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:34:19" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:34:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7711006</link><title>A Multi-Grid Model for Evacuation Coupling with the Effects of Fire Products</title><description>In the study, influences of fire products on pedestrians are introduced into a multi-grid evacuation model, in which the space is discretized into small grids with the size of 0.1Â mÂ ÃÂ 0.1Â m and each pedestrian occupies 5Â ÃÂ 5 grid sites. The fire products affect two walking parameters of pedestrians: the desired movement direction and the step frequency. The data of fire products are obtained from the simulation results of the Fire Dynamics Simulator (FDS), a well-founded computational fluid dynamic (CFD) program, developed by the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:35:28">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11498633</link><title>Evaluation of Fire Protection Performance of Eight Countries Based on Fire Statistics: An Application of Data Envelopment Analysis</title><description>To provide a view of countries’ relative fire protection efficiency from an international perspective, this study conducted an evaluation of fire protection performance of eight countries (i.e. Denmark, Japan, Norway, Singapore, Slovenia, Sweden, United Kingdom, and United States) based on the fire statistics from 2000 to 2008 released by the World Fire Statistic Center. Three inputs and two undesirable outputs were determined. After applying a transformation to both undesirable outputs, the overall efficiency and pure technical efficiency were acquired using two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:36:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xlfanustc/article/11082227</link><title>The fire situation and progress in fire safety science and technology in China</title><description>Since the 1950s, the direct property damage due to fire has increased with the development of industrialization and urbanization in China. The number of fire casualties has come down significantly since the 1980s while fire incidents with high casualties has occurred occasionally. Research on fire safety science and technology and its application have advanced, encouraged by Government at all levels, the Fire Service Department of the Ministry of Public Security and all of society. In recent years, the fire situation in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:37:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9336755</link><title>A numerical study of gypsum plasterboard behaviour under standard and natural fire conditions</title><description>Abstract Gypsum plasterboards are the most widely used passive fire protection for timber structures, especially in the case of light timber frame construction. Understanding the complex thermo-physical behaviour of plasterboard at elevated temperature is vital in the performance-based design of any structure adopting gypsum as passive fire protection (PFP). Numerous heat transfer studies have been conducted over the years where attempts have been made to simulate the fire performance of gypsum-protected assemblies, subject to standard fire exposure. However, contradictory thermal properties ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:38:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9472926</link><title>Chemical–analytical investigation of fire products in intermediate storages of recycling materials</title><description>SUMMARY Organic materials like paper, cardboard, textiles or plastics are mostly flammable. In intermediate storages for recycling products, these materials are stored in large amounts. If fire occurs in these stores, large emissions of smoke and other potentially harmful products are likely. In the present study, the gaseous products released from fires of such materials—for example, because of self-ignition—were investigated. Different fractions (paper/cardboard, textiles and plastics) were crushed at low temperatures (about 80 K) and subsequently allowed to smoulder at different temperatures ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:39:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xlfanustc/article/10284411</link><title>Numerical and theoretical evaluations of the propagation of smoke and fire in a full-scale tunnel</title><description>Most CFD tunnel fire simulations have so far focused on the thermal field and the critical velocity for suppression of the hot backlayering flow. However, there is a great need in understanding the characteristics of a real-scale tunnel fire in terms of the flame propagation and the toxic gas generation. In this study, an extension of the eddy dissipation concept incorporating two chemical reaction steps is integrated into an internationally recognised CFD fire simulation code. A full-scale over-ventilated tunnel fire is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:41:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SUNYGeneseo/article/9906674</link><title>Spatially Heterogeneous Estimates of Fire Frequency in Ponderosa Pine Forests of Washington, USA</title><description>Many fire history studies have evaluated the temporal nature of fire regimes using fire interval statistics calculated from fire scars. More recently, researchers have begun to evaluate the spatial properties of past fires as well. In this paper, we describe a technique for investigating spatio-temporal variability using a geographic information system (GIS). We used a dataset of fire-scarred trees collected from four sites in eastern Washington, USA, ponderosa pine (Pinus ponderosa C. Lawson) forests. The patterns of past fires recorded by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:42:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bnuwzj/article/7572078</link><title>Using the Community of Inquiry Survey Instrument to Inform Online Learning Outcomes</title><description>Although it was originally developed as the conceptual foundation for content analyses of online discussion, researchers with an interest in the model have developed survey instruments based on CoI content indicators, and most recently several researchers have joined together to create and validate a common CoI survey that measures student perceptions of the three presences across classes and institutions (Arbaugh, Cleveland-Innes, Diaz, Garrison, D. R., Ice, Richardson, Shea, &amp; Swan, 2008). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:42:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xlfanustc/article/10480769</link><title>Smoke control in case of fire in a large car park: CFD simulations of full-scale configurations</title><description>Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) simulation results are presented of full-scale car park fire experiments with smoke and heat control (SHC) by forced mechanical horizontal ventilation. A well-controlled liquid pool fire heat release rate (HRR) is set as an input parameter. The effect of the SHC system on the smoke movement in fire conditions is examined. The following parameters are varied: fire HRR; smoke extraction flow rate; openings for incoming air (so that different flow patterns have been created); presence of beams. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:43:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/skeeley/article/9834461</link><title>Applications of SHEBA/FIRE data to evaluation of snow/ice albedo parameterizations</title><description>Climate models use a wide variety of parameterizations for surface albedos of the ice-covered ocean. These range from simple broadband albedo parameterizations that distinguish among snow-covered and bare ice to more sophisticated parameterizations that include dependence on ice and snow depth, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>