<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:44:53" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:45:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/JCooke/article/10370388</link><title>Natural products as sources of new drugs over the 30 years from 1981 to 2010.</title><description>This review is an updated and expanded version of the three prior reviews that were published in this journal in 1997, 2003, and 2007. In the case of all approved therapeutic agents, the time frame has been extended to cover the 30 years from January 1, 1981, to December 31, 2010, for all diseases worldwide, and from 1950 (earliest so far identified) to December 2010 for all approved antitumor drugs worldwide. We have continued to utilize our secondary subdivision of a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:46:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/auvietphat/article/472092</link><title>Natural Products as Sources of New Drugs over the Period 1981−2002</title><description>This review is an updated and expanded version of a paper that was published in this journal in 1997. The time frame has been extended in both directions to include the 22 years from 1981 to 2002, and a new secondary subdivision related to the natural product source but applied to formally synthetic compounds has been introduced, using the concept of a ?natural product mimic? or ?NM? to join the original primary divisions. From the data presented, the utility of natural ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:47:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rossmounce/article/7947340</link><title>Treatise on Invertebrate Paleontology: Mollusca 4, Cephalopoda : Ammonoidea</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:48:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/JCooke/article/8978477</link><title>Natural Standard herbal pharmacotherapy : an evidence-based approach</title><description>With all of the essential information you need on herbal pharmacotherapy for the pharmacy setting, this complete reference provides practical guidance on the use of herbal therapies for medical conditions. The text's unique expanded outline format allows you to quickly review facts and identify important information. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:49:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/drshephe/article/200844</link><title>Cultures In Orbit: Satellites And The Televisual (Console-Ing Passions)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:50:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/artal/article/6008960</link><title>Defining the Sustainable Park: A Fifth Model for Urban Parks</title><description>How can parks contribute to the overarching project of helping cities become more ecologically sustainable? The history of urban parks in America reveals more concern with social problems than with ecological sustainability. Four types of city parks have been identified--the Pleasure Ground, the Reform Park, the Recreation Facility, and the Open Space System--and each of them respond to social issues, not ecological ones. Yet today, ecological problems are becoming one of our biggest social concerns, so a new urban park type ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:51:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Kyaita/article/6912690</link><title>Clinical practice guidelines for Clostridium difficile infection in adults: 2010 update by the society for healthcare epidemiology of America (SHEA) and the infectious diseases society of America (IDSA).</title><description>Since publication of the Society for Healthcare Epidemiology of America position paper on Clostridium difficile infection in 1995, significant changes have occurred in the epidemiology and treatment of this infection. C. difficile remains the most important cause of healthcare-associated diarrhea and is increasingly important as a community pathogen. A more virulent strain of C. difficile has been identified and has been responsible for more-severe cases ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:52:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vprieto/article/12819097</link><title>Analysis of generalized linear mixed models in the agricultural and natural resources sciences</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:54:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brainsman2000/article/9193281</link><title>Clinical practice guidelines for the management of sporotrichosis: 2007 update by the Infectious Diseases Society of America.</title><description>Guidelines for the management of patients with sporotrichosis were prepared by an Expert Panel of the Infectious Diseases Society of America and replace the guidelines published in 2000. The guidelines are intended for use by internists, pediatricians, family practitioners, and dermatologists. They include evidence-based recommendations for the management of patients with lymphocutaneous, cutaneous, pulmonary, osteoarticular, meningeal, and disseminated sporotrichosis. Recommendations are also provided for the treatment of sporotrichosis in pregnant women and in children. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:55:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nathanstrait/article/11961097</link><title>Perú : Yaguas-Cotuhé</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>