<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:56:10" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:56:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ab3279/article/10124173</link><title>High-speed force sensor for force microscopy and profilometry utilizing a quartz tuning fork</title><description>Force sensors are key elements of atomic force microscopes and surface profilometers. Sensors with an integrated deflection meter are particularly desirable. Here, quartz tuning forks as used in watches are utilized as force sensors. A novel technique is employed which simplifies the interpretation of the data and increases the imaging speed by at least one order of magnitude compared to previous implementations. The variation of the imaging signal with distance fits well to a Hertzian contact model. Images of compact discs ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:57:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stonest/article/1414576</link><title>The ATR pathway: Fine-tuning the fork</title><description>The proper detection and repair of DNA damage is essential to the maintenance of genomic stability. The genome is particularly vulnerable during DNA replication, when endogenous and exogenous events can hinder replication fork progression. Stalled replication forks can fold into deleterious conformations and are also unstable structures that are prone to collapse or break. These events can lead to inappropriate processing of the DNA, ultimately resulting in genomic instability, chromosomal alterations and cancer. To cope with stalled replication forks, the cell ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:58:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dpo/article/10802338</link><title>Software Automatic Tuning</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:59:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7240645</link><title>Arthropod Assemblages on Native and Nonnative Plant Species of a Coastal Reserve in California</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:00:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bmduggan/article/1808144</link><title>Arrested replication fork processing: Interplay between checkpoints and recombination</title><description>The arrest of DNA replication by DNA damage, nucleotide depletion, DNA-protein complexes or following clashes between transcription and replication factors all have the capacity to promote genome instability. In this review, we discuss how DNA replication is regulated by the checkpoint pathways that stabilise arrested replication forks and the recombination factors that process specific DNA structures resulting from fork arrest. We examine what is known about the interplay between the checkpoints and the recombination apparatus and review the evidence for a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:01:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4261254</link><title>Accuracy of endoscopic measurements</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:02:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dcoates/article/2153263</link><title>Dynamics of orientation tuning in macaque primary visual cortex.</title><description>Orientation tuning of neurons is one of the chief emergent characteristics of the primary visual cortex, V1. Neurons of the lateral geniculate nucleus, which comprise the thalamic input to V1, are not orientation-tuned, but the majority of V1 neurons are quite selective. How orientation tuning arises within V1 is still controversial. To study this problem, we measured how the orientation tuning of neurons evolves with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:03:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/champak/article/7347139</link><title>Broad tuning of whispering-gallery modes in silicon microdisks</title><description>Silicon microdisks with dynamically-tunable resonance spectra are achieved with nanoscale, in-plane silicon electrical contacts in a single lithographic step. Electrical current is passed through the devices to enable thermal tuning via joule heating. A 14nm wavelength shift is demonstrated with 1.6mW power consumption in devices with &gt;20nm free spectral ranges and quality factors exceeding 20,000. Spectral shifts equal to a full width at half maximum can be achieved with ~10μW tuning power for a mode with quality factor of 20,000. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:04:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rsabouni/article/821772</link><title>Tuning photonic nanocavities by atomic force microscope nano-oxidation</title><description>The authors demonstrate a technique to achieve high-precision tuning of photonic crystal nanocavities by atomic force microscope nano-oxidation of the cavity surface. Relative tuning between two nanocavity modes is achieved though careful choice of the oxide pattern, allowing them to restore the spectral degeneracy conditions necessary to create polarization-entangled quantum states. Tuning steps less than the linewidth (1 Å) of the high quality factor modes are obtained, allowing for virtually continuous tuning ability. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7046-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7046_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:05:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/champak/article/7022760</link><title>Tuning the cavity modes of a Fabry?Perot resonator using gold nanoparticles</title><description>We study the interaction between a planar Fabry–Perot microcavity and a single embedded gold nanoparticle. We record spatially resolved white-light transmission spectra and show that the interaction between microcavity and nanoparticle gives rise to a redshift of the cavity modes, in accordance with the Bethe–Schwinger cavity perturbation formula. The spectral tuning of cavity modes by discrete nanoparticles can be exploited for applications such as optical and micromechanical sensing. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>