<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:17:24" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:17:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kay0702/article/8061217</link><title>Flood! : a novel in pictures</title><description>A semi-autobiographical story in pictures about a city dweller in the last days of the twentieth century, based on events in New York in the late 1980s and early 1990s. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:18:32">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13427/article/7194491</link><title>Physiological responsivity to emotional pictures in schizophrenia.</title><description>Schizophrenic patients are known to experience difficulties in emotional information processing, yet knowledge of their physiological responsivity to emotional stimuli is limited. The purpose of this study was to investigate the physiological reactions of schizophrenic patients to emotional stimuli. We presented pictures selected from the International Affective Picture System (IAPS) to patients and controls, while assessing their subjective evaluations in terms of valence and arousal scores and measuring their responses of heart rate (HR), breathing rate (BR), skin conductance level (SCL) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:19:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mammabear/article/354931</link><title>Pictures for Language Learning (Cambridge Handbooks for Language Teachers)</title><description>A comprehensive resource demonstrating the vital role of visuals in the classroom. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:20:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RachelO/article/9164666</link><title>Phonological Activation of Ignored Pictures: Further Evidence for a Cascade Model of Lexical Access</title><description>Four experiments are reported exploring whether distractor pictures activate their phonological properties in the course of speech production. In Experiment 1, participants were presented with two pictures and were asked to name one while ignoring the other. Distractor pictures were phonologically related, semantically related or unrelated to the target picture. Naming latencies were faster in the phonologically related condition (the phonological facilitation effect--PFE) than in the unrelated condition. No difference between semantically related and unrelated distractors was observed. In Experiment 2, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:22:01">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4689206</link><title>Explicit formulation of delays in CMOS data paths</title><description>An explicit formulation of the transient response of general combinational CMOS structures is presented, including load conditions and driving waveforms. Based on data-path decomposition in unidirectional elementary cells, timing models developed here allow an analytic formulation of the real temporal behaviour of inverters, transmission gate arrays, and general CMOS gates. Validation is obtained through a comparison between delay times, calculated following this formulation, and values deduced from SPICE simulations, for a large range of inverters and gate structures with different configuration ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:23:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/evahara/article/588359</link><title>From emotion perception to emotion experience: emotions evoked by pictures and classical music.</title><description>Most previous neurophysiological studies evoked emotions by presenting visual stimuli. Models of the emotion circuits in the brain have for the most part ignored emotions arising from musical stimuli. To our knowledge, this is the first emotion brain study which examined the influence of visual and musical stimuli on brain processing. Highly arousing pictures of the International Affective Picture System and classical musical excerpts were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:24:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sharilyn/article/9357075</link><title>Predicting memory for pictures from rankings of interestingness, pleasingness, complexity, figure-ground and clarity.</title><description>Pictures used in the test phase of a picture-recognition task were ranked by 10 university students for interestingness, pleasingness, complexity, figure-ground, and clarity. The scale values obtained from these rankings were then correlated with the errors made by other subjects in the test phase of the picture-recognition task. Figure-ground and clarity were found, for the most part, to be reliable predictors of the errors made to both the "old" and "new" subsets of pictures in two experiments. Complexity, while not as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:24:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RachelO/article/7425161</link><title>Words, pictures, and priming: on semantic activation, conscious identification, and the automaticity of information processing.</title><description>We investigated the encoding mechanisms involved in the perceptual recognition of words and pictures. Latencies in naming word and picture targets were analyzed as a function of several characteristics of a preceding prime, including whether it was a word or a picture, its duration of exposure, the interval between the prime and target onset, and whether or not the prime was consciously identified and reported by the subject. Results indicated that a common semantic code is available that can represent the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:26:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jefkun/article/1320439</link><title>Use of the Hough transformation to detect lines and curves in pictures</title><description>Hough has proposed an interesting and computationally efficient procedure for detecting lines in pictures. This paper points out that the use of angle-radius rather than slope-intercept parameters simplifies the computation further. It also shows how the method can be used for more general curve fitting, and gives alternative interpretations that explain the source of its efficiency. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:27:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4362719</link><title>2005 and 2006 seasonal influenza vaccination coverage rates in 10 countries in Africa, Asia Pacific, Europe, Latin America and the Middle East</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>