<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7050">spotvps review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:37:19" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:37:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amoore88/article/505266</link><title>Views from Inside: Memoirs concerning the Yugoslav Breakup and War</title><description>Recent memoirs published in Zagreb, Ljubljana, Sarajevo, and Podgorica offer glimpses into how the principals would like their roles in the events connected with the Yugoslav breakup and war to be remembered. The most indispensable of the ten memoirs under review are those by Janez Drnovsek and Janez Jansa, who have differing perspectives on developments in Slovenia between 1988 and 1991; by Martin Spegelj, who outlines in detail his argument that Croatia should have laid siege to the Yugoslav Army barracks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:38:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276023</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1986 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:39:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276020</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1983 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:40:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brian/article/276018</link><title>Annual Review of Neuroscience: 1981 (Annual Review of Neuroscience)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:41:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/booker/article/3662354</link><title>Patients' preferences within randomised trials: systematic review and patient level meta-analysis</title><description>Objective To systematically review fully randomised patient preference trials and to explore the impact of preferences on attrition and outcome by meta-analysis of patient level data. Data sources Citation search using Science Citation Index and Google Scholar and search of the main electronic databases (Medline, CINAHL, Embase, and AMED) with a combination of key words. Study selection Fully randomised patient preference trials that compared treatments for any clinical condition were included. Other types of preference trials and crossover trials ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:42:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pshab/article/12028291</link><title>Harvard Business Review on work and life balance.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:43:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bpipitone/article/9860104</link><title>Compete to win final report June 2008</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:43:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stefanomasini2001/article/5080109</link><title>Learning With Computer-Based Learning Environments: A Literature Review of Computer Self-Efficacy</title><description>Although computer-based learning environments (CBLEs) are becoming more prevalent in the classroom, empirical research has demonstrated that some students have difficulty learning with these environments. The motivation construct of computer-self efficacy plays an integral role in learning with CBLEs. This literature review synthesizes research that has empirically examined factors related to computer self-efficacy and the relationship between computer self-efficacy, learning outcomes, and learning processes with CBLEs. Results indicate that behavioral and psychological factors are positively related to computer self-efficacy. Students who ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:45:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/srl/article/500271</link><title>History and Imperialism: A Century of Theory, from Marx to Postcolonialism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7050-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7050_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:46:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EsmeAnderson/article/6998976</link><title>Review: [The Dew Breaker]</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>