<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7052">hotel bruges</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:57:38" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:57:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kailuettger/article/3347693</link><title>Hotel Sales-and-Marketing Management: A Snapshot of Current Practice and Technology Use</title><description>This study of 200 hotels looked at eight areas of hotel sales-and-marketing management: advertising, department finances, franchise-affiliation benefit, human resources, revenue management, sales-contract terms, technology use, and third-party reservations. Approximately 60 percent of the hotels used both total revenue and room-nights sold as sales-performance measures, and 78 percent used room revenue to calculate bonuses. It seems that franchise-affiliated hotels receive greater benefit from the national reservation system than from the national sales offices. Close to 80 percent of the hotels use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chr_love/article/4186612</link><title>Impact of Information on Customer Fairness Perceptions of Hotel Revenue Management</title><description>Despite the prospective benefits of a revenue management (RM) program, some hotel managers remain concerned that customers perceive RM as being unfair. Studies have shown that offering customers information on a hotel's pricing practices can enhance their perceptions of fairness. To determine how much and what type of information hotels should provide in this context, researchers administered a scenario-based survey to 120 travelers. The study found that giving would-be guests relatively complete information about how a hotel's RM policies operate increases ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:00:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/HTWBibliothek/article/1443711</link><title>Best practices in hotel architecture</title><description>By making their rooms as home-like as possible, the best hotels are using architecture and design to add value to the guests' experience. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:01:20">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18129/article/10500671</link><title>Environmental performance in the hotel sector: the case of the Western Canary Islands</title><description>The appropriate management of environmental factors in the business world is a question of considerable interest to the scientific world, since studies increasingly reveal that such management has important competitive implications for the firm. One of the questions on which there does not yet exist sufficient consensus in the literature is how to evaluate the environmental behavior of companies, as a prior step of being able to establish the implications of such behavior for other aspects of management such as efficiency, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:02:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kailuettger/article/4702874</link><title>Strategic Hotel Development and Positioning: The Effects of Revenue Drivers on Profitability</title><description>A study of more than nineteen hundred U.S. hotels for the years 2002 and 2003 found that a hotel's net operating income percentage is most closely tied to its occupancy, although average daily rate (ADR) has a strong influence, as does market segment (also known as chain scale), the age of the property, and brand affiliation. A hotel's size (that is, number of rooms) and location (e.g., urban or highway) also influence net operating income (NOI), but a hotel's region does ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:03:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cindy2601/article/7897457</link><title>Hotel Management and Marketing on the Internet</title><description>10.1177/001088049603700322 Many hotel managers and hotel-operating companies are attempting to use the internet and worldwide web as an effective management and marketing tool. An exploratory survey finds thousands of hotel-related sites. Most such sites are hotel guides, chain hotels, and individual hotels, in that order. Current WWW hotel sites vary tremendously. Available functions of a web page include: travel information, reservations and payment, special promotions, links to partners, direct consumer feedback, employment opportunities, audio and video ads, gift certificates, shareholder information, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:04:27">http://www.citeulike.org/group/12110/article/8531024</link><title>Evoking Emotion: Affective Keys to Hotel Loyalty</title><description>The emotions a guest feels during a hotel stay are critical components of satisfaction and loyalty. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:05:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3510921</link><title>HLA-A polymorphisms in four ethnic groups from Guinea-Bissau (West Africa) inferred from sequence-based typing</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:06:48">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2374286</link><title>Participatory approaches for sustainable agriculture: A contradiction in terms?</title><description>Abstract  This paper examines the adoption and application of a participatory approach to the transfer of scientific research to farmers with the objective of supporting government policies for sustainable agriculture. Detailed interviews with scientists and farmers in two case studies in New Zealand are used to identify the potential and constraints of such an approach. One case study involves Māori growers wishing to develop organic vegetable production; the other involves commercial wheat farmers who want to improve their profitability and face major ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7052-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7052_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:07:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nicoara/article/4186712</link><title>Hotel Technology At the Start of the New Millennium</title><description>By the beginning of the new millennium, hotel technology will be entrenched in every phase of hotel management, marketing, and operations. Powerful new microchips will provide dramatic increases in power perdollarinvested. High-speed, high-capacity fiber-optic cable will link the world for faster, less costly telecommuni cations and will help change how hotels communicate with their guests and with headquarters. New hotel PBXs, telephone sets, and voice messaging systems will improve guest service, while the arrival of wireless pocket phones will mean that ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>