<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7053">nintendo 3ds hack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:09:04" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:09:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wellnair/article/3703047</link><title>Hacking the Nintendo Wii Remote</title><description>Since its introduction, the Nintendo Wii remote has become one of the world's most sophisticated and common input devices. Combining its impressive capability with a low cost and high degree of accessibility make it an ideal platform for exploring a variety of interaction research concepts. The author describes the technology inside the Wii remote, existing interaction techniques, what's involved in creating custom applications, and several projects ranging from multiobject tracking to spatial augmented reality that challenge the way its developers meant ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:10:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/8785534</link><title>Capability reconfiguration of incumbent firms: Nintendo in the video game industry</title><description>The importance of incumbent firms' ability to transform themselves according to the changing technological environment has been underlined by several scholars and practitioners. Yet, how incumbents leverage on commercial capabilities in order to develop such technological reconfiguration abilities in the midst of fierce competition from new entrants has not gained enough attention. To address the above research issue, our study investigated the case of Nintendo, an incumbent firm in the video game industry, using the dynamic capability perspective. Our study relied ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:11:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/textoris/article/480399</link><title>Tissue factor pathway of coagulation in sepsis.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To review the role of the tissue factor pathway of coagulation in experimental sepsis. DATA SOURCES: Studies published in biomedical journals. STUDY SELECTION: Studies on the role of the tissue factor pathway in animal or human models for sepsis. DATA EXTRACTION AND SYNTHESIS: Variables reflecting tissue factor pathway activation in the various models are discussed; the effects of administration of tissue factor pathway inhibitors on these and inflammatory variables, as well as on the course and outcome, are analyzed. CONCLUSION: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:12:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/764312</link><title>Use of the Esophageal Doppler Machine to help guide the intraoperative management of two children with pheochromocytoma</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:13:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10652461</link><title>Measurement uncertainty of Carré-type phase-stepping algorithms</title><description>Phase retrieval techniques are powerful tools used in interferometry, fringe projection, and other methods of image and signal analysis. The popular linear phase stepping algorithms combine weighted sums of signal values to obtain sine and cosine parts of the phase of interest. The coefficients and phase step angles are chosen to minimize the measurement uncertainty due to some experimental influence quantities. While a general treatment of measurement uncertainty for linear phase stepping algorithms has been given elsewhere, in this article a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:14:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jverdu/article/11239332</link><title>Geschäftsprozessmanagement und Serviceorientierte Architekturen (SOA) – Erfahrungen beim Aufbau von Geschäftsprozessplattformen – Projektbeispiele und Vorgehen transformIT</title><description>Geschäftsprozesse sind im übertragenen Sinn die DNS, die genetische Information, eines Unternehmens. Ihre Leistungsfähigkeit sowie die Fähigkeit des jeweiligen Unternehmens, seine Geschäftsprozesse flexibel an sich verändernde Wettbewerbs- und Marktgegebenheiten anzupassen, entscheiden über den wirtschaftlichen Unternehmenserfolg. Voraussetzung und Erfolgskriterium hierfür sind ein konsequentes Geschäftsprozessmanagement (Business Process Management – BPM) als eine Managementdisziplin genauso wie moderne Softwarearchitekturen, die eine flexible Anpassung der Geschäftsanwendungen ermöglichen. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:15:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/barbaraciteulike/article/10527046</link><title>Decidability Questions for Petri Nets</title><description>An understanding of the mathematical properties of Petri Nets is essential when one wishes to use Petri Nets as an abstract model for concurrent systems. The decidability of various problems which arise in this context is an important aspect of this question. The fact that these problems also arise in the context of other mathematical theories, such as commutative semigroups, closure under linear relations, Matrix Context-Free grammars, or Weak Counter Automata, provides further motivation. The Reachability Problem for Vector Addition Systems ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:16:15">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2892115</link><title>Beyond the Big Test: Noncognitive Assessment in Higher Education By William E. Sedlacek</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:17:15">http://www.citeulike.org/article/37335</link><title>Pediatric Bupropion-Induced Serum Sicknesslike Reaction</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7053-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7053_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:18:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/adriandefroment/article/3458882</link><title>Assessment strategies in the contests of male crickets,Acheta domesticus(L.)</title><description>Game theoretical models predict that the assessment of relative fighting ability and motivation is a process fundamental to resolving most contests. Demonstrations of assessment must (1) identify characters associated with fighting success and (2) establish a correlation between opponent asymmetry in these characters and the costs of fighting. Pair-wise contests between male house crickets revealed that winners were generally heavier than their opponents, although this effect varied with the degree of asymmetry in mass and the presence or absence of burrows. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>