<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7054">yarra valley sightseeing</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:19:43" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:19:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pbrannon/article/9099220</link><title>The coachman was a lady; the story of the life of Charley Parkhurst.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:20:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eimaj42jdp/article/149998</link><title>Mechanisms of Up-Valley Winds</title><description>The basic physical mechanisms governing the daytime evolution of up-valley winds in mountain valleys are investigated using a series of numerical simulations of thermally driven flow over idealized three-dimensional topography. The three-dimensional topography used in this study is composed of two, two-dimensional topographies: one a slope connecting a plain with a plateau and the other a valley with a horizontal floor. The present two-dimensional simulations of the valley flow agree with results of previous investigations in that the heated sidewalls produce ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:22:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gniebler/article/3424717</link><title>Valley filter and valley valve in graphene</title><description>The potential of graphene for carbon electronics rests on the possibilities offered by its unusual band structure to create devices that have no analogue in silicon-based electronics1, 2. Conduction and valence bands in graphene form conically shaped valleys, touching at a point called the Dirac point. There are two inequivalent Dirac points in the Brillouin zone, related by time-reversal symmetry. Intervalley scattering is suppressed in pure samples3, 4, 5. The independence and degeneracy of the valley degree of freedom suggests that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:23:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kas/article/2891541</link><title>Fully Valley-Polarized Electron Beams in Graphene</title><description>We propose a device to break the valley degeneracy in graphene and produce fully valley-polarized currents that can be either split or collimated to a high degree in a experimentally controllable way. The proposal combines two recent seminal ideas: negative refraction and the concept of valleytronics in graphene. The key new ingredient lies in the use of the specular shape of the Fermi surface of the two valleys when a high electronic density is induced by a gate voltage (trigonal warping). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:24:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rakeshspatel/article/7814427</link><title>Learning styles and courseware design</title><description>In this paper we examine how (courseware) can accommodate differences in preferred learning style. A review of the literature on learning styles is followed by a discussion of the implications of being able to accurately classify learners, and key issues that must be addressed are raised. We then present two courseware design solutions that take into account individual learning-style preference: the first follows on from traditional research in this area and assumes that learners can be classified in advance. The second ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:25:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fujitat/article/7224265</link><title>Valley filter in strain engineered graphene</title><description>We propose a simple, yet highly efficient and robust device for producing valley polarized current in graphene. The device comprises of two distinct components; a region of uniform uniaxial strain, adjacent to an out-of-plane magnetic barrier configuration formed by patterned ferromagnetic gates. We show that when the amount of strain, magnetic field strength, and Fermi level are properly tuned, the output current can be made to consist of only a single valley contribution. Perfect valley filtering is achievable within experimentally accessible parameters. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:26:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rmonteneg/article/5814992</link><title>Erase rates in photorefractive materials with two photoactive species</title><description>Erase rates for uniformly illuminated refractive-index gratings are derived for a model of photorefractivity in which two photoactive ions participate as donors and acceptors. The model leads naturally to decay of gratings at two separate rates. In some conditions the amplitudes of the components that decay at each rate are nearly equal, while the rates are substantially different. These conditions should be readily observable in crystals with two photoactive species. In other conditions, one amplitude greatly exceeds the other or the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:27:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andryacrossland/article/6975189</link><title>Significant characteristics of democratic presidential nomination acceptance speeches</title><description>Democratic presidential nomination acceptance speeches have become part of American tradition. Beginning as relatively unimportant supplements to letters of acceptance, the speeches have evolved into major political addresses. After conducting both an historical review of the period involved1832-1972and a content analysis of the speeches, the author identifies some of the principal rhetorical traditions surrounding such speeches. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:28:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pmunozm/article/4405841</link><title>Photonic analog-to-digital converters</title><description>This paper reviews over 30 years of work on photonic analog-to-digital converters. The review is limited to systems in which the input is a radio-frequency (RF) signal in the electronic domain and the output is a digital version of that signal also in the electronic domain, and thus the review excludes photonic systems directed towards digitizing images or optical communication signals. The state of the art in electronic ADCs, basic properties of ADCs and properties of analog optical links, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7054-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7054_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:30:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rroldan/article/11172048</link><title>Valley Dependent Optoelectronics from Inversion Symmetry Breaking</title><description>Inversion symmetry breaking allows contrasted circular dichroism in different k-space regions, which takes the extreme form of optical selection rules for interband transitions at high symmetry points. In materials where band-edges occur at noncentral valleys, this enables valley dependent interplay of electrons with light of different circular polarizations, in analogy to spin dependent optical activities in semiconductors. This discovery is in perfect harmony with the previous finding of valley contrasted Bloch band features of orbital magnetic moment and Berry curvatures from inversion symmetry breaking [Phys. Rev. Lett. 99, 236809 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>