<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:32:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:32:16">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16440/article/13076602</link><title>Quantum Communications in Reconfigurable Optical Networks: DWDM QKD through a ROADM</title><description>We demonstrate coexistence of classical and quantum signals for quantum key distribution in a DWDM reconfigurable networking environment using a ROADM. We show how the limiting noise mechanism can depend on the link configuration. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:33:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chaotron/article/6612045</link><title>Novel No-Guard-Interval PDM CO-OFDM Transmission in 4.1 Tb/s (50 x 88.8-Gb/s) DWDM Link over 800 km SMF Including 50-GHz Spaced ROADM Nodes</title><description>We demonstrated spectrally efficient (1.65-b/s/Hz) DWDM transmission of 88.8 Gb/s polarization division multiplexed coherent OFDM signals without guard interval. The record 18-concatenated 50-GHz-spaced ROADM transmission and high DGD tolerance over 120 ps were experimentally confirmed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:34:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kristgy/article/4170976</link><title>A Hybrid Electrooptic Microring Resonator-Based &lt;formula formulatype="inline"&gt;&lt;tex&gt;$1 times 4times 1$&lt;/tex&gt;&lt;/formula&gt; ROADM for Wafer Scale Optical Interconnects</title><description>&lt;para&gt; Pairing high-quality factor &lt;formula formulatype="inline"&gt;&lt;tex&gt;$(Q)$&lt;/tex&gt; &lt;/formula&gt; silicon-on-insulator microring resonators with rapidly tunable organic electrooptic claddings has allowed the first demonstration of a silicon-organic hybrid electrooptic reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexer (ROADM). A coplanar electrode geometry provides up to 0.36 GHz/V of electrooptic voltage tuning for each channel, corresponding to an electrooptic coefficient of &lt;formula formulatype="inline"&gt;&lt;tex&gt;$r_33=64 hboxpm/V$&lt;/tex&gt;&lt;/formula&gt; at wavelengths around 1550 nm. Individual ring resonator devices have 40-&lt;formula formulatype="inline"&gt; &lt;tex&gt;$muhbox m$&lt;/tex&gt;&lt;/formula&gt; ring radii, 2.7-nm free spectral range, and tuning ranges of 180 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:35:35">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7066367</link><title>An integrated reconfigurable optical add-drop multiplexer based on using an opto-VLSI processor and a 4-f imaging system</title><description>Abstract  A novel integrated reconfigurable optical add-drop multiplexer (ROADM) structure is proposed and demonstrated experimentally. The ROADM employs an interface substrate that enables the integration of a fiber-lens collimator array and an Opto-VLSI processor to realise a 4-f imaging system through optical beam steering. Phase hologram optimization of the Opto-VLSI processor is investigated, for maximizing the number of wavelength channels while keeping adequate insertion loss and crosstalk levels. Experimental results are shown, which demonstrate a broadband operation and the principle of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:36:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5315957</link><title>Experimental demonstration of layer-1 multicast for WDM networks using reconfigurable OADM</title><description>The feasibility of multicast-capable-reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexer (MC-ROADM) based on broadcast-and-select switch is experimentally demonstrated. The MC-ROADM can support unicast connection as well as multicast connection, and can provide directionless switching and low insertion loss in path-through channel. We implement fully-reconfigurable multi-degree MC-ROADM based on wavelength selective switch, and evaluate multicasting performances by fully loading 40 × 10 Gbit/s wavelength division multiplexed (WDM) signals. For unicast and multicast operation, measured spectrum and bit-error-rate (BER) show good uniformity and no power penalty. After 1040 km transmission ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:37:46">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9198817</link><title>Design of flexible and reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexer</title><description>We present a two-way hitless reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexer (ROADM) and an Optical Cross Connect (OXC) structures based on microring resonators (MRRs). The OXC is simulated by the transfer matrix compound with Finite-Different Time-Domain method, and the results show that optical signals can be carried out to any destination in this structure. The two-way hitless ROADM is suit for two-way network and the OXC can be used as core node in mesh network. It is shown the port number can be ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:39:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9617427</link><title>Design of equalized holographic ROADMs for application in CWDM METRO networks</title><description>In this paper a design for an equalized holographic ROADM (Reconfigurable Optical Add-Drop Multiplexer) is done. This device can address several wavelengths at the input to different output fibers, according to the holograms stored in a SLM (Spatial Light Modulator), where all the outputs are equalized in power. All combinations of the input wavelengths are possible at the different output fibers. These type of ROADMs are designed for application in CWDM (Coarse Wavelength Division Multiplexing) networks, where the distance between the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:40:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9651887</link><title>Wavelength switching technologies and requirements for agile optical networks at line rates of 100Gb/s and beyond</title><description>Future optical networks will have to support DWDM line rates beyond 100 Gb/s and transport data with much higher spectral efficiency than today’s networks, so as to meet the rapidly increasing demand for transmission capacity. At the same time, these networks need to provide increased flexibility at the optical layer to allow fast and automated provisioning of capacity wherever and whenever it is demanded. In this contribution we describe the different requirements that such high-speed agile optical networks pose on wavelength-selective switches ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:41:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/farouk_kh/article/6906469</link><title>40 Gb/s DBPSK and DQPSK formats for transparent 50 GHz DWDM transmission</title><description>Today's dense wavelength division multiplexed (DWDM) long haul and metropolitan networks are being upgraded from 10 Gb/s to 40 Gb/s, to support the growing traffic demands. Reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexers (ROADMs) allow for transparent networking at 50 GHz channel spacing. This paper addresses the challenges to support 40 Gb/s by examining two promising modulation formats, namely, differential binary and quadrature phase shift keying (DBPSK and DQPSK). We investigated several variants for reception of the two formats and present performances under optical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7056-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7056_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:42:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/javiersierrac/article/11131150</link><title>Transmission Impairments in DWDM Networks With Reconfigurable Optical Add-Drop Multiplexers</title><description>Reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexers (ROADMs) based on 1 X N wavelength-selective switches (WSS) are evolving to support DWDM networks with higher capacity and increased flexibility in wavelength routing. Different WSS technologies can be employed to provide colorless and steerable functionality for ring, or meshed architectures. Improvements in specifications of WSS modules operating on the 50 GHz wavelength grid have enabled 40 Gb/s transmission rates through extensive ROADM networks. The same ROADMs are also expected to support 100 Gb/s transmission in the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>