<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:43:34" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:43:37">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2118/article/2306906</link><title>A survey of trust in computer science and the Semantic Web</title><description>Trust is an integral component in many kinds of human interaction, allowing people to act under uncertainty and with the risk of negative consequences. For example, exchanging money for a service, giving access to your property, and choosing between conflicting sources of information all may utilize some form of trust. In computer science, trust is a widely used term whose definition differs among researchers and application areas. Trust is an essential component of the vision for the Semantic Web, where both ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:44:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/diogomartins/article/2020805</link><title>A Framework for Web Science</title><description>This text sets out a series of approaches to the analysis and synthesis of the World Wide Web, and other web-like information structures. A comprehensive set of research questions is outlined, together with a sub-disciplinary breakdown, emphasising the multi-faceted nature of the Web, and the multi-disciplinary nature of its study and development. These questions and approaches together set out an agenda for Web Science, the science of decentralised information systems. Web Science is required both as a way to understand the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:45:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/acstest/article/1841140</link><title>Creating a Science of the Web</title><description>Understanding and fostering the growth of the World Wide Web, both in engineering and societal terms, will require the development of a new interdisciplinary field. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:46:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rdelgado28/article/2629447</link><title>Steve Lawrence. Context in Web Search, IEEE Data Engineering Bulletin, Volume 23, Number 3, pp. 25--32, 2000.</title><description>Web search engines generally treat search requests in isolation. The results for a given query are identical, independent of the user, or the context in which the user made the request. Nextgeneration search engines will make increasing use of context information, either by using explicit or implicit context information from users, or by implementing additional functionality within restricted contexts. Greater use of context in web search may help increase competition and diversity on ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:47:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yoelabreu84/article/2439238</link><title>Ease of interaction plus ease of integration: Combining Web2.0 and the Semantic Web in a reviewing site</title><description>Web2.0 has enabled contributions to the Web on an unprecedented scale, through simple interfaces that provide engaging interactions. This wealth of data has spawned countless mashups that integrate heterogenous information, but using techniques that will not scale beyond a handful of sources. In contrast, the Semantic Web provides the key to large-scale data integration, yet still lacks approachable interfaces allowing contributions from non-specialists. In this paper we present Revyu, a reviewing and rating site in the Web2.0 mould that is built ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:48:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cuiyh_bit/article/2439228</link><title>Collective knowledge systems: Where the Social Web meets the Semantic Web</title><description>What can happen if we combine the best ideas from the Social Web and Semantic Web? The Social Web is an ecosystem of participation, where value is created by the aggregation of many individual user contributions. The Semantic Web is an ecosystem of data, where value is created by the integration of structured data from many sources. What applications can best synthesize the strengths of these two approaches, to create a new level of value that is both rich with human ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:50:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/piyakorn/article/4069449</link><title>So Much More to Know</title><description>From the nature of the cosmos to the nature of societies, the following 100 questions span the sciences. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:51:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/IngridRichardson/article/2439236</link><title>The two cultures: Mashing up Web 2.0 and the Semantic Web☆</title><description>A common perception is that there are two competing visions for the future evolution of the Web: the Semantic Web and Web 2.0. A closer look, though, reveals that the core technologies and concerns of these two approaches are complementary and that each field can and must draw from the other’s strengths. We believe that future Web applications will retain the Web 2.0 focus on community and usability, while drawing on Semantic Web infrastructure to facilitate mashup-like information sharing. However, there ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:52:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vinit/article/2439230</link><title>Using the Semantic Web for linking and reusing data across Web 2.0 communities</title><description>Large volumes of content (bookmarks, reviews, videos, etc.) are currently being created on the “Social Web”, i.e. on Web 2.0 community sites, and this content is being annotated and commented upon. The ability to view an individual's entire contribution to the Social Web would be an interesting and valuable service, particularly important as social networks are often being formed through created content and things that people have in common (“object-centred sociality”). SIOC is a Semantic Web research project that aims to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:53:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rafaellazo/article/825405</link><title>Extracting Social Networks and Contact Information From Email</title><description>We present an end-to-end system that extracts a user's social network and its members' contact information given the user's email inbox. The system identifies unique people in email, finds their Web presence, and automatically fills the fields of a contact address book using conditional random fields---a type of probabilistic model well-suited for such information extraction tasks. By recursively calling itself on new people discovered on the Web, the system builds a social network with... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>