<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:06:13" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:06:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/digitalegrachtengordel/article/10657179</link><title>Patterns of retail location and urban form in Amsterdam in the mid-eighteenth century</title><description>In this article location theory is used to map and analyse the patterns of retail location in Amsterdam in the eighteenth century. In the city centre as well as along the main axes to markets and the city gates the retailing of shopping goods (textiles, consumer durables) was much more prominent than elsewhere in the city. In contrast, shops selling convenience goods (foodstuffs etc.) were scattered all over the city. The correspondence of empirical data and location theory suggests that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:07:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jahaskins84/article/2118947</link><title>1. Introduction: Amsterdam and Beyond</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:08:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jahaskins84/article/2118929</link><title>15. Constitutional Settlements and the Citizen After the Treaty of Amsterdam</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:09:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4267311</link><title>The Parataxis of British Musical Modernism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:10:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7853391</link><title>Hydrodynamic Fluctuations in Fluids and Fluid Mixtures</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:11:40">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14766/article/9517014</link><title>Fifteen years medical information sciences: the Amsterdam curriculum.</title><description>Since its foundation in 1987, the program has undergone several major modifications. From a degree program following medical school it developed into a full-fledged, dedicated 4-year program on medical information sciences training high-school graduates for a master degree. The curriculum has been based from its outset within the University of Amsterdam-Faculty of Medicine. This organizational structure leaves ample opportunity for integration of the informatics-oriented components with the medical and health care-oriented components in the program. Student-centered approaches are heavily employed in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:12:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/4462891</link><title>Insertional mutagenesis in zebrafish: genes for development, genes for disease.</title><description>In order to rapidly identify a substantial fraction of the genes with a unique and essential role in vertebrate development, the laboratory of Nancy Hopkins at MIT has performed a large insertional mutagenesis screen in zebrafish using a pseudotyped retroviral vector as the mutagen. We have recovered mutations in about one-quarter of the embryonic essential genes in this organism, and have identified the mutated genes in nearly all of these (333). As the ease of gene identification allowed us to clone ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:13:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1318868</link><title>Why Bother With Inter-Regionalism? Negotiations for a European Union-Mercosur Agreement</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:14:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jfpsy/article/800564</link><title>Psychodynamic lessons in risk assessment and management</title><description>Risk assessment is notoriously difficult and offers a particular challenge to mental health workers. There are two main conceptual approaches to the consideration of risk assessment and management: the actuarial and the clinical methods. I use case material to examine the clinical, and in particular the psychodynamic, approach in order to illustrate that violent behaviour has meaning. Understanding its meaning and learning from it can substantially reduce the risks of further violent behaviour. Managing risk with the aid of psychodynamic psychotherapy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:15:33">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8777180</link><title>“Letter to the Editor”</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>