<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7060">jobs IBCN</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:16:46" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:16:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelbr11/article/11689406</link><title>The Dropout Crisis: Promising Approaches in Prevention and Recovery</title><description>The number of high school age students who do not complete high school is receiving increased attention as a serious challenge facing the educational system. This is happening for several reasons. New research estimates that about 30 percent of high school students fail to earn a diploma in the standard number of years, a higher figure than state and local education officials typically cite. In many states, barely half of African-Americans and Latinos graduate from high school. The magnitude of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:17:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/814943</link><title>A case study in the globalization of jobs in Ireland</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:19:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4290808</link><title>Youth Movements: Travel, Protest, and Europe in 1968</title><description>doi: 10.1086/ahr.114.2.376 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:20:14">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5316</link><title>Building Community and Reconstructing Citizenship in the Youth and Culture Houses of Post-War France</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:21:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8458294</link><title>Susan B. Whitney. Mobilizing Youth: Communists and Catholics in Interwar France.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:22:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shahlakhan/article/4796485</link><title>Green Jobs Myths</title><description>A rapidly growing literature promises that a massive program of government mandates, subsidies, and forced technological interventions will reward the nation with an economy brimming with green jobs. Not only will these jobs improve the environment, but they will be high paying, interesting, and provide collective rights. This literature is built on mythologies about economics, forecasting, and technology. Myth: Everyone understands what a green job is. Reality: No standard definition of a green job exists. Myth: Creating ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:23:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amandaalders/article/5240495</link><title>Racial-ethnic disparities in health and the labor market: Losing and leaving jobs☆</title><description>This study examines whether employment disruptions have varying health consequences for White and Black or Hispanic workers in the U.S. Since employment disruptions mark major shocks to socioeconomic status (SES), this analysis also speaks to a broader set of questions about how race/ethnicity and SES shape population-level health disparities. Data from 1999, 2001 and 2003 waves of the U.S. Panel Study of Income Dynamics provide no evidence of racial/ethnic variation in the health consequences of involuntary job loss. However, associations between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:24:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gale82/article/8878784</link><title>The complexity of shop-scheduling problems with two or three jobs</title><description>This paper deals with the n/m/J/Cmax problem of optimal makespan scheduling n jobs with fixed routines on m machines. It is shown that the 3/m/J/Cmax problem with identical routines of jobs and the 3/5/J/Cmax problem are NP-hard. The same results are obtained for the 3/m/J/∑Ci problem of minimizing mean flow time of three jobs on m machines. The problem of optimal scheduling of two jobs with any regular criterion is shown to be solved by an O(r3) algorithm if preemptions of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:26:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dbk/article/9951144</link><title>Steve Jobs</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7060-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7060_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:27:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/45033</link><title>KITH AND KIN: Personal Relationships and Cultural Practices, 1830-1980, 20 February 2004, New Brunswick, NJ</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>