<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:28:16" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:28:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/howardjp/article/749652</link><title>The Chicago Manual of Style</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In the 1890s, a proofreader at the University of Chicago Press prepared a single sheet of typographic fundamentals intended as a guide for the University community. That sheet grew into a pamphlet, and the pamphlet grew into a book--the first edition of the &lt;i&gt;Manual of Style&lt;/i&gt;, published in 1906. Now in its fifteenth edition, &lt;i&gt;The Chicago Manual of Style&lt;/i&gt;\--the essential reference for authors, editors, proofreaders, indexers, copywriters, designers, and publishers in any field--is more comprehensive and easier to use than ever ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:29:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/2096082</link><title>A Manual for Writers of Research Papers, Theses, and Dissertations, Seventh Edition: Chicago Style for Students and Researchers (Chicago Guides to Writing, Editing, and Publishing)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Dewey. Bellow. Strauss. Friedman. The University of Chicago has been the home of some of the most important thinkers of the modern age. But perhaps no name has been spoken with more respect than Turabian. The dissertation secretary at Chicago for decades, Kate Turabian literally wrote the book on the successful completion and submission of the student paper. Her &lt;i&gt;Manual for Writers of Research Papers, Theses, and Dissertations&lt;/i&gt;, created from her years of experience with research projects across all fields, has ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:30:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/12823589</link><title>The Chicago Manual of Style, 16th Edition</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:31:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keithhouston/article/10476572</link><title>Footnotes</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:32:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jannon/article/10149300</link><title>Early Chinese Paintings in The Art Institute of Chicago</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:34:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jklugman/article/1642398</link><title>The Plan of Chicago: Daniel Burnham and the Remaking of the American City (Chicago Visions and Revisions)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Arguably the most influential document in the history of urban planning, Daniel Burnham’s 1909 &lt;i&gt;Plan of Chicago&lt;/i&gt;, coauthored by Edward Bennett and produced in collaboration with the Commercial Club of Chicago, proposed many of the city’s most distinctive features. Carl Smith’s fascinating history reveals the &lt;i&gt;Plan&lt;/i&gt;’s central role in shaping the ways people envision the cityscape and urban life itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His concise and accessible narrative begins with a survey of Chicago’s stunning rise from a tiny frontier settlement to the nation’s second-largest ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:35:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keithhouston/article/10607540</link><title>A manual of style : for authors, editors and copywriters.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:36:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/magdaw/article/439113</link><title>The Chicago Guide to Collaborative Ethnography (Chicago Guides to Writing, Editing, and Publishing)</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Collaboration between ethnographers and subjects has long been a product of the close, intimate relationships that define ethnographic research. But increasingly, collaboration is no longer viewed as merely a consequence of fieldwork; instead collaboration now preconditions and shapes research design as well as its dissemination. As a result, ethnographic subjects are shifting from being informants to being consultants. The emergence of collaborative ethnography highlights this relationship between consultant and ethnographer, moving it to center stage as a calculated part not only ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:37:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/2925258</link><title>The Chicago Guide to Writing about Multivariate Analysis (Chicago Guides to Writing, Editing, and Publishing)</title><description>Writing about multivariate analysis is a surprisingly common task. Researchers use these advanced statistical techniques to examine relationships among multiple variables, such as exercise, diet, and heart disease, or to forecast information such as future interest rates or unemployment. Many different people, from social scientists to government agencies to business professionals, depend on the results of multivariate models to inform their decisions. At the same time, many researchers have trouble communicating the purpose and findings of these models. Too often, explanations become bogged down in statistical jargon and technical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:38:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ldcberenicevr/article/2077423</link><title>Chicago In and Around the Loop : Walking Tours of Architecture and History</title><description>Twelve well-mapped walking tours help you discover a city with a long history of being on the forefront of architectural innovation. These tours highlight the works of architectural giants including Frank Lloyd Wright, Dankmar Adler, Louis Sullivan, and others who helped revamp the American skyline. &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br&gt;* Updated to reflect new buildings, owners, functions, and landmark designations; the expansion of McCormick Place, and new information on the Prairie Avenue Historic District &lt;br&gt;* MORE historical facts, background information, anecdotes, architectural details, and ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>