<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:39:42" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:39:47">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13751/article/7532370</link><title>Technology: Software bugs cost big bucks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:40:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/byronf/article/5720115</link><title>A Guide to Merleau-Ponty's Phenomenology of Perception (Marquette Studies in Philosophy)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:41:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/soumitri_varadarajan/article/749652</link><title>The Chicago Manual of Style</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In the 1890s, a proofreader at the University of Chicago Press prepared a single sheet of typographic fundamentals intended as a guide for the University community. That sheet grew into a pamphlet, and the pamphlet grew into a book--the first edition of the &lt;i&gt;Manual of Style&lt;/i&gt;, published in 1906. Now in its fifteenth edition, &lt;i&gt;The Chicago Manual of Style&lt;/i&gt;\--the essential reference for authors, editors, proofreaders, indexers, copywriters, designers, and publishers in any field--is more comprehensive and easier to use than ever ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:43:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/france/article/563005</link><title>A History of the University in Europe (A History of the University in Europe)</title><description>This is the first of four volumes that will comprise A History of the University in Europe, covering the development of the university in Europe (East and West) from its origins to the present day. No other up-to-date, comprehensive history of this type exists: its originality lies in focusing on a number of major themes viewed from a European perspective, and in its interdisciplinary, collaborative and transnational character. Volume I, covering the Middle Ages, places the medieval European ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:44:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zmarty/article/8429198</link><title>Identifying Differences in News Coverage between Cultural/Ethnic Groups</title><description>Large-scale analysis over historical news corpora provides us with unique opportunities to examine sociological issues with respect to local and mass media. In particular, we combine the Lydia named entity recognition system with an name-based ethnicity classification engine to examine issues of ethnic and geocentric sentiment/coverage bias in newspapers. We describe new methods for ethnicity and nationality detection for news entities (people), and build on this to identify interesting temporal, geospatial, and association trends in the coverage with respect to 13 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:45:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keithhouston/article/10476572</link><title>Footnotes</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:46:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ChaTo/article/12217550</link><title>Manufacturing the News</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:48:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MaineC/article/5043997</link><title>Meme-tracking and the dynamics of the news cycle</title><description>Tracking new topics, ideas, and "memes" across the Web has been an issue of considerable interest. Recent work has developed methods for tracking topic shifts over long time scales, as well as abrupt spikes in the appearance of particular named entities. However, these approaches are less well suited to the identification of content that spreads widely and then fades over time scales on the order of days - the time scale at which we perceive news and events. We develop a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:49:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mtkachenko/article/4061692</link><title>Named entity discovery using comparable news articles</title><description>In this paper we describe a way to discover Named Entities by using the distribution of words in news articles. Named Entity recognition is an important task for today's natural language applications, but it still suffers from data sparseness. We used an observation that a Named Entity is likely to appear synchronously in several news articles, whereas a common noun is less likely. Exploiting this characteristic, we successfully obtained rare Named Entities with 90% accuracy just by comparing time series distributions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:50:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brusilovsky/article/939963</link><title>NewsInEssence: summarizing online news topics</title><description>A news delivery and summarization system, acting as a user's agent, gathers and recaps news items based on specifications and interests. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>