<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:51:22" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:51:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/butabaevr/article/10777107</link><title>Unemployment in transition countries : transient or persistent?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:52:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LolaOyebode/article/8421726</link><title>Unemployment causes ill health: The wrong track</title><description>It is not unemployment per se that causes ill health. It can be a very desirable state. There are no diseases specific to unemployment. Contrast this with employment. Unemployment shares with all other socio-environmental situations risk of exposure to common physical social and psychological stressors that predispose to disease. Focus for action and research should be on reducing such stressors and not on provision of full employment. The former is likely to be possible and beneficial. The latter is likely to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:53:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3632581</link><title>Labor market assimilation of immigrants in Spain: employment at the expense of bad job-matches?</title><description>During the last decade, Spain has experienced an unprecedented increase of immigration from three localized areas: Eastern Europe, Latin America, and Africa. Using data from the Labour Force Survey for the period 1996–2006, we study the labour characteristics of recent immigrants, identifying the major differences with the native population at arrival and tracking whether these differences fade away as their years of residence in Spain increase. We allow the returns to human capital and the sensitivity to the business cycle to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:54:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victosp/article/2172787</link><title>3.. Labor Market Institutions and Unemployment: Assessment of the Cross-Country Evidence</title><description>Chapter 3 takes up the question of the robustness of the cross-country evidence for the orthodox claim that labor market institutions explain the pattern of unemployment across the affluent countries. A detailed survey of the most influential cross-country statistical studies finds a wide range of results that are highly sensitive to the nature of the variables, the time period, and the econometric method employed. Simple scatter plots of unemployment against six standard measures of labor market institutions for five-year periods between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:56:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LolaOyebode/article/8404648</link><title>Unemployment as a disease and diseases of the unemployed.</title><description>There is a causal link between unemployment and the deterioration in health status, but there is also an act of selection so that people with health problems have more problems in getting a new job. Unemployed men, especially the young, increase their alcohol consumption as compared with employed referents. Unemployed persons are smokers to a greater extent than employed persons, and smokers have a higher risk of becoming unemployed. Psychological indicators have been studied well in connection with health effects of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:57:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Qkhaliq/article/4431975</link><title>Unemployment and Urban Labour Markets</title><description>Two quite distinct views on how metropolitan labour markets work have co-existed for over three decades. Both claim empirical support and, after a brief period of confrontation, they continue to co-exist today giving quite conflicting signals to policy-makers. According to the first model, the urban labour market consists of a number of spatially defined sub-markets so that local unemployment exists primarily because of deficiencies in highly localised demand for labour. By this argument, unemployment rates remain high in the absence of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:58:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/butabaevr/article/9856788</link><title>A further investigation of unemployment persistence in European transition economies</title><description>This paper analyses the dynamics of the unemployment rate in the eight countries from Central and Eastern Europe which joined the EU in 2004. Unit root tests allowing for nonlinearities and structural changes suggest that the unemployment rate is not stationary in most of the sample countries. Tests allowing for fractional integration, however, reveal that shocks are highly persistent, implying a slow rate of convergence to the natural rate of unemployment. The unemployment rate is least persistent in Hungary and Slovenia, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:59:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pigironjoe/article/944645</link><title>Political and Economic Explanations for Unemployment: A Cross-National and Long-Term Analysis</title><description>This article shows that the widely accepted supply shock and real wage gap explanation of increases in unemployment rates since 1973 has only limited empirical support. The causal factors behind unemployment are best understood by focusing on conflicts of interest in Western democracies, on the distribution of power resources between major interest groups and on strategies of conflict. Given economic constraints, from this perspective unemployment appears as the labour market expression of distributive conflict, alternatives to which are inflation and industrial ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:00:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ruru1958/article/12034074</link><title>Duration of unemployment and suicide in Australia over the period 1985–2006: an ecological investigation by sex and age during rising versus declining national unemployment rates</title><description>Background The relationship between unemployment and suicide may be sensitive to demographic factors, national unemployment rates, and length of time without employment. This study investigated these factors in relation to suicide in Australia for the period 1985–2006, in an ecological study.Methods The outcome variable was annual suicide rate by age group, sex and the eight states and territories over 22 years of observation (total observations=1760). The main predictor variable was the average duration of unemployment in the population, categorised into three time ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:01:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ruru1958/article/11898744</link><title>Long-term unemployment and suicide: a systematic review and meta-analysis.</title><description>There have been a number of reviews on the association+ between unemployment and suicide, but none have investigated how this relationship is influenced by duration of unemployment. A systematic review and meta-analysis was conducted of those studies that assessed duration of unemployment as a risk factor for suicide. Studies considered ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>