<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:16:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:16:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/herythe/article/10616916</link><title>Enlighten Myself with Kindle</title><description>The purpose of this presentation is to share my personal experience using e-books on my Kindle. These e-books are accessible through my Kindle e-reader, Kindle for PC, and Kindle for iPod. Text-to-speech, dictionary, 3G access, MP3, letter size adjustment, and screen rotation are valuable features covered in this presentation. I have experiencing improvement in lots of productivity and learning quality by using these features. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:17:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7324855</link><title>MOZTIF2-mediated destruction of CBP/p300 is blocked by calpain inhibitor 2</title><description>MOZ–TIF2-mediated destruction of CBP/p300 is blocked by calpain inhibitor 2 Leukemia advance online publication, May 20, 2010. doi:10.1038/leu.2010.92 Authors: K B Kindle, H M Collins &amp; D M Heery ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:18:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dandaman/article/2394696</link><title>Homologous Recombination in the Nuclear Genome of Chlamydomonas reinhardtii</title><description>10.1073/pnas.90.19.9199 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:19:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/frackjackson/article/4267119</link><title>Analysis of the Polarization Influence on the Erbium-Doped Fiber Laser Transient Behavior</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:20:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2450180</link><title>Discover Your Child's Learning Style: Children Learn in Unique Ways - Here's the Key to Every Child's Learning Success</title><description>&lt;b&gt;Help Your Child Discover the Joy of Learning&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does your child learn best in the morning, afternoon, or evening? Does his reading comprehension increase or decrease when music is played in the background? Does she prefer to study alone or with others? According to nationally respected educators &lt;b&gt;Mariaemma Willis&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Victoria Kindle Hodson,&lt;/b&gt; our children process information in a multitude of unique ways. What works best for one child is often counterproductive for others. By trying to force all children into the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:21:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zman/article/2523944</link><title>Biochemical indicators of thermal stress in Tilapia aurea (Steindachner)</title><description>Tilapia aurea muscle and liver adenylate nucleotides, the adenylate energy charge (EC), plasma glucose, cortisol and chloride were monitored during acute and chronic temperature stress. Muscle EC is unaffected during acute cold water exposure but decreases significantly when tilapia are exposed to chronic, sublethal, low temperature stress. The decrease in EC is primarily the result of a decrease in ATP concentration. Plasma glucose and cortisol increase when tilapia are exposed to 11-12o C for 60 min, 11 days, and a 5-week ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:22:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6411150</link><title>SUMOylation regulates the nuclear mobility of CREB binding protein and its association with nuclear bodies in live cells</title><description>The lysine acetyltransferase CREB binding protein (CBP) is required for chromatin modification and transcription at many gene promoters. In fixed cells, a large proportion of CBP colocalises to PML or nuclear bodies. Using live cell imaging, we show here that YFP-tagged CBP expressed in HEK293 cells undergoes gradual accumulation in nuclear bodies, some of which are mobile and migrate towards the nuclear envelope. Deletion of a short lysine rich domain that contains the major SUMO acceptor sites of CBP abrogated its ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:23:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8647757</link><title>A semiautomated approach for artefact removal in serial tissue cryosections</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:24:55">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10189760</link><title>Vibrational resonance in biological nonlinear maps</title><description>We investigate vibrational resonance in two different nonlinear maps driven by a biharmonic force: the Bellows and the Rulkov map. These two maps possess dynamical features of particular interest for the study of these phenomena. In both maps, the resonance occurs at the low-frequency of the biharmonic signal as the amplitude of the high-frequency signal is varied. We also consider an array of unidirectionally coupled maps with the forcing signal applied to the first unit. In this case, a signal propagation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:26:00">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8892925</link><title>Cten signals through integrin-linked kinase (ILK) and may promote metastasis in colorectal cancer</title><description>Cten signals through integrin-linked kinase (ILK) and may promote metastasis in colorectal cancer Oncogene advance online publication, February 21, 2011. doi:10.1038/onc.2011.26 Authors: A Albasri, S Al-Ghamdi, W Fadhil, M Aleskandarany, Y-C Liao, D Jackson, D N Lobo, S H Lo, R Kumari, L Durrant, S Watson, K B Kindle &amp; M Ilyas ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>