<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:39:02" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:39:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/enricaki/article/6516938</link><title>Organic Nonvolatile Memory Transistors for Flexible Sensor Arrays</title><description>Using organic transistors with a floating gate embedded in hybrid dielectrics that comprise a 2-nanometer-thick molecular self-assembled monolayer and a 4-nanometer-thick plasma-grown metal oxide, we have realized nonvolatile memory arrays on flexible plastic substrates. The small thickness of the dielectrics allows very small program and erase voltages ([≤]6 volts) to produce a large, nonvolatile, reversible threshold-voltage shift. The transistors endure more than 1000 program and erase cycles, which is within two orders of magnitude of silicon-based floating-gate transistors widely employed in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:40:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suizan/article/167445</link><title>An Organizational Memory Information System using Ontologies</title><description>In the recent years, much has been said about ontologies and their applications in different research fields. The ontological discipline emerged from artificial intelligence as a form of knowledge representation that would minimise the problems of knowledge sharing and reuse between people and between software. Apart from the view that portrays an ontology as a syntactic and semantic standardisation of knowledge structures, other approaches apply this discipline as a means to represent... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:41:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cogniaux/article/7690856</link><title>Key-Study to Execute Code Using Demand Paging and NAND Flash at Smart Card Scale</title><description>Nowadays, the desire to embed more applications in systems as small as Smart Cards or sensors is growing. However, physical limitations of these systems, like very small main memory, and their cost of production make it very difficult to achieve. One solution is to execute code from a secondary memory, cheaper, denser, but slower, as NAND Flash. Solutions based on Demand Paging and using a cache in main memory, began to be proposed and implemented in the domain of mobile phones, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:42:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dmeister/article/3251179</link><title>Flash storage memory</title><description>Can flash memory become the foundation for a new tier in the storage hierarchy? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:43:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/philip-eecs/article/2670364</link><title>Nonvolatile Memory Technologies with Emphasis on Flash: A Comprehensive Guide to Understanding and Using Flash Memory Devices (IEEE Press Series on Microelectronic Systems)</title><description>&lt;b&gt;The authoritative reference guide for nonvolatile memory users&lt;/b&gt; &lt;p&gt; Presented here is an all-inclusive treatment of Flash technology, includingFlash memory chips, Flash embedded in logic, binary cell Flash, and multilevel cell Flash. Comprised of thirteen succinct chapters authored by pioneers in the field, this book begins with a brief tutorial of elementary concepts to orient readers who are less familiar with the subject. Next, it builds upon this foundation to cover all aspects and variations of Flash ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:44:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/YuhuiDeng/article/8585325</link><title>Architectures and optimization methods of flash memory based storage systems</title><description>Flash memory is a non-volatile memory which can be electrically erased and reprogrammed. Its major advantages such as small physical size, no mechanical components, low power consumption, and high performance have made it likely to replace the magnetic disk drives in more and more systems. However, flash memory has four specific features which are different to the magnetic disk drives, and pose challenges to develop practical techniques: (1) Flash memory is erased in blocks, but written in pages. (2) A block ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:45:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ICobraI/article/2757945</link><title>Algorithms and data structures for flash memories</title><description>Flash memory is a type of electrically-erasable programmable read-only memory (EEPROM). Because flash memories are nonvolatile and relatively dense, they are now used to store files and other persistent objects in handheld computers, mobile phones, digital cameras, portable music players, and many other computer systems in which magnetic disks are inappropriate. Flash, like earlier EEPROM devices, suffers from two limitations. First, bits can only be cleared by erasing a large block of memory. Second, each block can only sustain a limited ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:47:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kewms/article/875813</link><title>Non-volatile memory technologies for beyond 2010</title><description>The development of Flash memory technology over the past decade has been one of the driving forces behind the tremendous growth in digital consumer applications, such as digital cameras, handheld music players and mobile phones. NAND Flash has been leading the way from 16Mb in 1994 to 4Gb today. This paper discusses the impact of continuous advances in NAND Flash technology on consumer applications and also reviews technical challenges to the further scaling of NAND and NOR Flash memories, while considering ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:48:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kewms/article/1087677</link><title>Future Outlook of NAND Flash Technology for 40nm Node and Beyond</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:49:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kewms/article/874376</link><title>High work-function metal gate and high-/spl kappa/ dielectrics for charge trap flash memory device applications</title><description>We report the impact of high work-function (/spl Phi//sub M/) metal gate and high-/spl kappa/ dielectrics on memory properties of NAND-type charge trap Flash (CTF) memory devices. In this paper, theoretical and experimental studies show that high /spl Phi//sub M/ gate and high permittivity (high-/spl kappa/) dielectrics play a key role in eliminating electron back tunneling though the blocking dielectric during the erase operation. Techniques to improve erase efficiency of CTF memory devices with a fixed metal gate by employing various ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>