<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7071">buy LP politics yellowjackets</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:50:27" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:50:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/6686/article/6346269</link><title>After Neoliberalism: The Politics of Reregulation in Mexico</title><description>Neoliberal economic reforms, rather than unleashing market forces, can result in new institutions for market governance. By vacating institutionalized policy domains, neoliberal reforms can trigger two-step reregulation processes, as first, political entrepreneurs launch projects to build support coalitions by reregulating markets, and second, societal groups respond to these projects by mobilizing to influence the terms of reregulation. Depending on the strengths and strategies of politicians and societal groups, reregulation processes result in varied institutions for market governance. The article develops this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:51:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/daniel51/article/3936999</link><title>QoS Routing in Communication Networks: Approximation Algorithms Based on the Primal Simplex Method of Linear Programming</title><description>Given a directed network with two integer weights, cost and delay, associated with each link, Quality-of-Service (QoS) routing requires the determination of a minimum cost path from one node to another node such that the delay of the path is bounded by a specified integer value. This problem, also known as the Constrained Shortest Path problem (CSP), admits an Integer Linear Programming (ILP) formulation. Due to the integrality constraints, the problem is NP-hard. So, approximation algorithms have been presented in the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:52:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cobi/article/840931</link><title>The Rational Choice Approach to Politics: A Challenge to Democratic Theory</title><description>In just three decades rational choice theory has emerged as one of the most active, influential, and ambitious subfields in the discipline of political science. Rational choice theory contends that political behavior is best explained through the application of its supposedly "value-neutral" assumptions which posit man as a self-interested, purposeful, maximizing being. Through the logic of methodological individualism, assumptions about human nature are treated as empirical discoveries. My central argument is that by assuming that self-interest is an empirically established component ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:53:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saranshchoudhury/article/10733922</link><title>The Theory of Constraints and the Make-or-Buy Decision: An Update and Review</title><description>The make-or-buy decision has traditionally been made using standard cost accounting methods. In this Journal, Gardiner and Blackstone (1991) made a strong case for incorporating the bottleneck capacity into the decision. However, their method did not guarantee the best solution for the more complicated make-or-buy problem. Additionally, their approach in some cases allowed organizations to forego opportunities for profit improvement. Since the publication of the Gardiner and Blackstone research, spreadsheets with in-built Linear Programming (LP) based optimizers allow for quick “what-if” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:54:56">http://www.citeulike.org/group/7827/article/6209144</link><title>Gender Quotas, Norms, and Politics</title><description>Gender quotas have become an increasingly prominent solution in recent years to the underrepresentation of women in electoral politics. As research on these policies has grown, scholars have primarily sought to explain how and why quotas are adopted and, more recently, why some quota policies are more effective than others in facilitating women&amp;apos;s access to political office. Most studies, however, also consider—often in a less systematic fashion—the normative aspects of quota reform, usually by detailing the various objections leveled against gender ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:56:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zbenjamin/article/5931889</link><title>Review: The Study of Chinese Politics: Toward a Third Generation of Scholarship</title><description>Research on contemporary Chinese politics can be divided into two distinct generations since its initiation in the early 1960s. The first, produced before the Cultural Revolution, was characterized by general description rather than systematic comparison or sophisticated conceptualization. The second generation, which appeared in the late 1960s and early 1970s, assigned greater attention to describing the variation of Chinese politics over space and time, identifying the informal norms and mechanisms by which Chinese politics operates, and developing general theories of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:57:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PaulBHartzog/article/1165706</link><title>Politics Beyond the State: Environmental Activism and World Civic Politics</title><description>Nongovernmental organizations (NGOs) both lobby states and work within and across societies to advance their interests. These latter efforts are generally ignored by students of world politics because they do not directly involve governments. A study of transnational environmental activist groups (TEAGs) such as Greenpeace, Friends of the Earth, and World Wildlife Fund demonstrates that NGO societal efforts indeed shape widespread behavior throughout the world. TEAGs work through transnational social, economic, and cultural networks to shift standards of good conduct, change ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:58:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zbenjamin/article/5931801</link><title>The Modernization of Factionalism in Chinese Politics</title><description>The informal dimension has always been important in Chinese politics, due to a traditional bias against legalism and favoring the sentimentalization of personal qualities. We contend that it remains so still, albeit in altered form. Rather than being oriented solely to personal or in-group security, factionalism in the context of the more secure bureaucratic environment of the reform era has come to embrace policy goals and material interests as well. Thus, informal politics proliferates, and factional fortunes tend to fluctuate according ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:59:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alexupstairs/article/8170988</link><title>Elections and Voting Handbook of Politics</title><description>There are more democracies in the world now than ever before. Elections and voting are the lynchpins of new and established democracies alike. The object of this chapter is to examine the recent developments within studies of elections and voting. This general topic is far too vast for any single chapter or set of authors to survey comprehensively; instead we focus on the developments centered around two of the most central aspects of elections: Who votes and why? Who do those ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7071-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7071_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:00:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chrisgroves/article/9174711</link><title>Eco-politics beyond the paradigm of sustainability: A conceptual framework and research agenda</title><description>This contribution sketches a conceptual framework for the analysis of the post-ecologist era and outlines a research agenda for investigating its politics of unsustainability. The article suggests that this new era and its particular mode of eco-politics necessitate a new environmental sociology. Following a review of some achievements and limitations of the paradigm of sustainability, the concept of post-ecologism is related to existing discourses of the 'end of nature', the 'green backlash' and the 'death of environmentalism'. The shifting terrain of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>