<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7073">buy bausack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:13:10" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:13:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saranshchoudhury/article/10733922</link><title>The Theory of Constraints and the Make-or-Buy Decision: An Update and Review</title><description>The make-or-buy decision has traditionally been made using standard cost accounting methods. In this Journal, Gardiner and Blackstone (1991) made a strong case for incorporating the bottleneck capacity into the decision. However, their method did not guarantee the best solution for the more complicated make-or-buy problem. Additionally, their approach in some cases allowed organizations to forego opportunities for profit improvement. Since the publication of the Gardiner and Blackstone research, spreadsheets with in-built Linear Programming (LP) based optimizers allow for quick “what-if” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:14:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/AntoniaL/article/3106700</link><title>The Right to Buy: Analysis and Evaluation of a Housing Policy (Real Estate Issues)</title><description>An evaluation of the most enduring privatisation of the Thatcher era …_ Written in an accessible style, this is a key reference for students and researchers in housing and planning; geography; and social policy. The book analyses the operation and impact of the right to buy policy (RTB). It includes a critique of the Housing Act and the 2001 Housing (Scotland) Act. The enactment of these changes under a Labour government affirms the continuance of the RTB. The authors take stock of its profound effect on housing policy, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:15:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davide_caldo/article/11610598</link><title>Percutaneous treatment of intervertebral disc herniation.</title><description>Interventional radiology plays a major role in the management of symptomatic intervertebral disc herniations. In the absence of significant pain relief with conservative treatment including oral pain killers and anti-inflammatory drugs, selective image-guided periradicular infiltrations are generally indicated. The precise control of needle positioning allows optimal distribution of steroids along the painful nerve root. After 6 weeks of failure of conservative treatment including periradicular infiltration, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:16:34">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4287398</link><title>Reduction rules for time Petri nets</title><description>Abstract  The goal of net reduction is to increase the effectiveness of Petri-netbased real-time program analysis. Petri-net-based analysis, like all reachabilitybased methods, suffers from the state explosion problem. Petri net reduction is one key method for combating this problem. In this paper, we extend several rules for the reduction of ordinary Petri nets to work with time Petri nets. We introduce a notion of equivalence among time Petri nets, and prove that our reduction rules yield equivalent nets. This notion of equivalence ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:17:52">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3070833</link><title>Analysis of real-time programs with simple time Petri nets</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:18:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pverstra/article/2830843</link><title>Analysis of Real-Time Programs with Simple Time Petri Nets</title><description>We present a first report on our PARTS toolset for the automated static analysis of real-time systems. The PARTS toolset is based upon a timed extension of Petri nets. Our simple time Petri nets or STP nets are specifically aimed at facilitating real-time analysis. Our analysis approach uses the state space of an STP net in order to answer queries about the concurrency and timing behavior of the corresponding system. An attractive feature of STP nets is that they support a variety of techniques ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:20:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/11583936</link><title>Institutions, Capabilities, and Contracts: Make or Buy in the Electric Utility Industry</title><description>This paper integrates transaction cost economics with the resource-based view of the firm and new institutional economics to examine how firms' capabilities and institutional environments influence governance decisions. We demonstrate that the impact of firm capabilities on governance choice varies with the level of transaction costs, which is itself a function of the institutional environment. Based on panel data for 240 investor-owned utility companies in 1990–2007, we find that firms with strong institutional safeguards, prior contracting experience, and inferior firm production ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:21:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/12573236</link><title>How much to make and how much to buy? An analysis of optimal plural sourcing strategies</title><description>While many theories of the firm seek to explain when firms make rather than buy, in practice firms often make and buy the same input—they engage in plural sourcing. We argue that explaining the mix of external procurement and internal sourcing for the same input requires a consideration of complementarities across and constraints within modes of procurement. We create analytical foundations for making empirical predictions about when plural sourcing is likely to be optimal and why the optimal mix of internal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:22:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrjesper/article/3204171</link><title>Automated Testing of Classes</title><description>Programs developed with object technologies have unique features that often make traditional testing methods inadequate. Consider, for instance, the dependence between the state of an object and the behavior of that object: The outcome of a method executed by an object often depends on the state of the object when the method is invoked. It is therefore crucial that techniques for testing of classes exercise class methods when the method's receiver is in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7073-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7073_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:23:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joaoarthurbm/article/2480620</link><title>Automated Testing of Classes</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>