<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:00:31" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:00:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/12089722</link><title>Changing patterns in the clinical characteristics of korean breast cancer from 1996-2010 using an online nationwide breast cancer database.</title><description>Breast cancer is one of the most frequent malignancies in Korean women, and its incidence is increasing at a rapid rate. Since 1996, the Korean Breast Cancer Society has collected nationwide breast cancer data using an online registration program and analyzed the data biennial. The purpose of this study was to evaluate the characteristics of Korean breast cancer and to analyze changes in these characteristics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:00:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/9509337</link><title>Chronological changing patterns of clinical characteristics of Korean breast cancer patients during 10 years (1996-2006) using nationwide breast cancer registration on-line program: biannual update.</title><description>Our results suggest the incidence of breast cancer in Korea will continue to rise. Several characteristics of Korean breast cancer patients seem to follow the patterns of Western countries, but differences are present. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:01:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4085515</link><title>An Inquiry concerning the Source of the Heat Which is Excited by Friction. By Benjamin Count of Rumford, F. R. S. M. R. I. A.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:01:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mycase/article/5269079</link><title>GSTM1, GSTT1 and GSTP1 polymorphisms in the Korean population.</title><description>The isoenzymes of the glutathione s transferase (GST) family play a vital role in phase II of biotransformation of many substances. Using a multiplex polymerase chain reaction and a direct sequencing analysis, the frequencies of GSTM1, GSTT1, and GSTP1 polymorphisms were evaluated in 1,051 Korean male subjects. We found that 53.8% of the individuals had the GSTM1 null genotype and 54.3% had the GSTT 1 null genotype. The genotypic distribution of GSTP1 was Ile105/Ile105 in 68.4%, Ile105/Val105 in 29.1% and Val105/Va105 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:01:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kpal/article/12477061</link><title>An Enquiry concerning the Nature of Heat, and the Mode of Its Communication</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:02:00">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10078347</link><title>Assessment of Risk Factors for Korean Children with Kawasaki Disease</title><description>Kawasaki disease (KD) is the most common cause of acquired heart disease in children. Intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG) is the standard therapy for KD, but more than 10% of KD patients do not respond to IVIG and are at high risk for the development of coronary artery lesions (CALs). To identify clinical and genetic risk factors associated with CAL development and IVIG nonresponsiveness, this study analyzed the clinical data for 478 Korean KD patients. Multivariate logistic regression analysis showed that incomplete KD, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:02:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/7415617</link><title>Triple negative breast cancer in Korea-distinct biology with different impact of prognostic factors on survival.</title><description>We analyzed breast cancer subtypes using Korean Breast Cancer Society Registration Program data to compare clinical features and prognosis for triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC). A cohort of 26,767 breast cancer patients were divided in four groups: luminal A (ER+ and/or PR+, HER2-), luminal B (ER+ and/or PR+ HER2+), HER2+ (ER-, PR-, HER2+), and triple-negative (ER-, PR-, HER2-). Clinicopathologic factors were evaluated. The luminal A (14,437 patients, 53.9%) subtype was the largest in our study. Compared with luminal A subtype, TNBC correlated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:02:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/9448240</link><title>Population-based breast cancer statistics in Korea during 1993-2002: incidence, mortality, and survival.</title><description>In 2002, breast became the most common cancer site in Korean women. Using national breast cancer incidence data during 1993-2002, crude, age-standardized, and age-specific rates for incidence and mortality were calculated. Survival was examined for cases diagnosed during 1993-2002 and followed up to 2004. Observed survival was calculated using the life table method and relative survival using the Ederer II method. Age-standardized incidence rates in female increased from 14.5 in 1993 to 26.2 per 100,000 in 2002. Age-specific incidences showed peaks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:03:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/6617167</link><title>[Guidelines of treatment for non-bleeding peptic ulcer disease]</title><description>Over the past century, since the introduction of non steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAID), antacid, histamine H2-receptor antagonists (H2RA), proton pump inhibitors (PPI), and discovery of Helicobacter pylori infection, the paradigm of peptic ulcer disease has changed with marked decrease in morbidity and mortality. However, peptic ulcer disease still occupies a position as a major health problem with increase of aged population and NSAIDs usage. In daily general practice, the management of peptic ulcer disease is directed according to the presence of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:03:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lullaby/article/3470642</link><title>Pharmacokinetic interaction of flecainide and paroxetine in relation to the CYP2D6*10 allele in healthy Korean subjects.</title><description>AIMS: The objectives were to evaluate the effect of CYP2D6 genetic polymorphism on the pharmacokinetics of flecainide, and also on the extent of drug interaction with paroxetine as a CYP2D6 inhibitor after a single oral administration in healthy subjects. METHODS: An open-label, two-period, single-sequence, cross-over study was performed in 21 healthy Korean male volunteers (seven for CYP2D6*1/*1 or *1/*2, group 1; seven for CYP2D6*1/*10, group 2; seven for CYP2D6*10/*10 or *10/*36, group 3). Subjects were administered 200 mg of flecainide on ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>