<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:02:31" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:02:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misskowalski/article/1531253</link><title>Restricted Play: Synergy and the Limits of Interactivity in The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King Video Game</title><description>Although recent critical studies have begun to acknowledge the aesthetic connections that films and video games share, too often these studies neglect to extend an analysis to consumer culture. As video games now make up an important segment of the film industry's market, this critical engagement is needed to extend the scholarship on video games. Specifically, this essay critically engages the concept of interactivity as an important theoretical construction in the study of video games. Through an analysis of The Lord ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:03:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/y80243/article/1380714</link><title>The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers Visual Companion</title><description>The official, fully authorized companion to the second part of Peter Jackson's award-winning trilogy, The Lord of the Rings.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Two Towers Visual Companion is a full-color guide to the characters, places and landscapes of J.R.R. Tolkien's Middle-earth as depicted in the second film in The Lord of the Rings Trilogy, and features a special introduction by Viggo Mortensen, who plays Aragorn.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Lavishly illustrated with more than 100 full-color photographs, including exclusive images of Gollum, Treebeard and the battle of Helm's Deep, The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:04:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dbirmajer/article/3614500</link><title>On the opposite of the category of rings</title><description>We define a faithful contravariant functor NCSpec from the category of rings to the category of ringed spaces, and show that if R is a commutative ring then NCSpec(R) may be viewed as a completion of Spec(R) in an appropriate sense. We then explain how the spaces NCSpec(R) may be glued, and study quasicoherent sheaves on them. As an example, we compute the category of quasicoherent sheaves on a space constructed from a skew-polynomial ring R by an analogue of the Proj construction. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:05:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/robotact/article/2489182</link><title>The Lord of the Rings</title><description>A Christian can almost be forgiven for not reading the Bible, but there's no salvation for a fantasy fan who hasn't read the gospel of the genre, J.R.R. Tolkien's definitive three-book epic, the Lord of the Rings (encompassing &lt;I&gt;The Fellowship of the Ring&lt;/I&gt;, &lt;I&gt;The Two Towers&lt;/I&gt;, and &lt;I&gt;The Return of the King&lt;/I&gt;), and its charming precursor, &lt;I&gt;The Hobbit&lt;/I&gt;. That many (if not most) fantasy works are in some way derivative of Tolkien is understood, but the influence of the Lord of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:06:52">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3575912</link><title>Lord of the Rings Collection:The Hobbit-The Fellowship of the Ring-The Two Towers-Return of the King-The Silmarillion-Unfinished Tales (Lord of the Rings)</title><description>6 paperbacks-Lord of the Rings Saga ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:08:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2489169</link><title>The Lord of the Rings (Illustrated Edition)</title><description>A Christian can almost be forgiven for not reading the Bible, but there's no salvation for a fantasy fan who hasn't read the gospel of the genre, J.R.R. Tolkien's definitive three-book epic, the Lord of the Rings (encompassing &lt;I&gt;The Fellowship of the Ring&lt;/I&gt;, &lt;I&gt;The Two Towers&lt;/I&gt;, and &lt;I&gt;The Return of the King&lt;/I&gt;), and its charming precursor, &lt;I&gt;The Hobbit&lt;/I&gt;. That many (if not most) fantasy works are in some way derivative of Tolkien is understood, but the influence of the Lord of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:09:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/schmoele/article/5138979</link><title>Modelling and Characterizing the Earth's Gravity Field: From Basic Principles to Current Purposes</title><description>The Earth is a specific body in the Universe. Nowadays, thanks to the high accuracy of the measurements obtained by different techniques of geodesy, its shape, as well as its gravity field, can be described and characterized in a very precise way, with thousands of parameters: the Earth is a spherical body only in a very first approximation! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:10:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kellychristoffersen/article/10743672</link><title>Tonality and Transformation (Oxford Studies in Music Theory)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:11:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3575993</link><title>The Return of the Shadow: The History of The Lord of the Rings, Part One (The History of Middle-Earth, Vol. 6)</title><description>In this sixth volume of The History of Middle-earth the story reaches The Lord of the Rings. In The Return of the Shadow (an abandoned title for the first volume) Christopher Tolkien describes, with full citation of the earliest notes, outline plans, and narrative drafts, the intricate evolution of The Fellowship of the Ring and the gradual emergence of the conceptions that transformed what J.R.R. Tolkien for long believed would be a far shorter book, 'a sequel to The Hobbit'. The enlargement of Bilbo's 'magic ring' into ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7080-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7080_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:12:36">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/437040</link><title>For God and Glory: Lord Nelson and His Way of War</title><description>Taking a highly original, thematic approach to the study of Horatio Lord Nelson, this book analyzes the admiral's unique war-fighting style. Doctrine, tactics, and operational art are part of the analysis, as are Nelson's command and leadership abilities and his attitudes and beliefs. But the book's focus is on how all these elements combined to form the man whose infectious ethos spread through his entire force. It shows that Nelson's creative genius, excitable and intense personality, dramatic visage, and fervor for ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>