<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:08:34" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:08:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rltiller/article/3753911</link><title>Assessing and Managing the Ecological Impacts of Paved Roads</title><description>All phases of road development&amp;from construction and use by vehicles to maintenance&amp;affect physical and chemical soil conditions, water flow, and air and water quality, as well as plants and animals. Roads and traffic can alter wildlife habitat, cause vehicle-related mortality, impede animal migration, and disperse nonnative pest species of plants and animals. Integrating environmental considerations into all phases of transportation is an important, evolving process. The increasing awareness of environmental issues has made road development more complex and controversial. Over the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:09:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jaspervoskuilen/article/1036768</link><title>Modelling and evaluation of road pricing in Paris</title><description>This article describes the impacts of road pricing in Ile-de-France, a region that includes Paris. The morning peak is studied using METROPOLIS: a dynamic network simulator that treats endogenously travellers' mode, departure time and route-choice decisions. Time-independent tolls on selected links, time-varying cordon tolls, and a network-wide toll proportional to travel time are considered. Welfare gains from the link and cordon tolls are relatively small. The comprehensive travel-time-based toll yields much higher benefits. In all cases, benefits to users amount to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:09:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/apwheele/article/1392756</link><title>Measuring the Structure of Road Networks</title><description>Spatial networks display both topologic and geometric variations in their structure. This study investigates the measurement of a road network structure. Existing measures of heterogeneity, connectivity, accessibility, and interconnectivity are reviewed and three supplemental measures are proposed, including measures of entropy, connection patterns, and continuity. The proposed measures were applied to 16 test networks, which were derived from four idealized base networks: 90°, 45°, 30°, and completely connected. The results show that the differentiated structures of road networks can be evaluated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:10:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/flux/article/87030</link><title>Vision for vehicle guidance using two road cues</title><description>An autonomous vehicle must be able to find and maintain visual contact with a negotiable path (a road) in front of it. Presents a strategy for road tracking that uses two road cues in order to maintain better visual contract with a road than could be achieved with either cue alone. Also, using two cues to find the road, it is possible to study the ability of a system to recover when contradictory evidence exists concerning the location of the road ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:11:03">http://www.citeulike.org/group/8123/article/3824646</link><title>Vehicle motion analysis based on a monocular vision system</title><description>This paper presents a comprehensive methodology for on-road vehicle motion analysis using a monocular vision system. Vehicle motion analysis plays an essential role in various intelligent vehicle applications, such as cruise control, vehicle platooning, and collision avoidance. In this paper, it&amp;#x2019;s proposed to improve the accuracy of vehicle motion analysis by breaking the task into two complementary steps: incoming vehicle detection and vehicle motion analysis. In the vehicle detection, a new vehicle which enters the observation field will be identified by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:11:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3623445</link><title>The effect of anesthesia on abdominal muscle resting length and shortening in awake dogs</title><description>Abstract  The objectives of this study were to examine the effects of anesthesia and implantation of sonomicrometer transducers on tonic and phasic expiratory activity of the abdominal muscles. Eight tracheotomized dogs were chronically instrumented with sonomicrometer transducers placed in each of the four abdominal muscles. The dogs were studied in the lateral decubitus position immediately after transducer implantation, while under halothane anesthesia, and then in the awake dogs 2 to 3 days postimplantation, and repeatedly over a 2- to 8-week period. The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:12:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jgaffuri/article/11193008</link><title>Enrichment of topographic road database for the purpose of routing and navigation</title><description>Abstract With growing demand on multi-purpose or multi-modal navigation, the route calculation needs to traverse semantically enriched road networks for different transportation modes. Currently, operational route planning algorithms reveal rather limited performances or their potential for comprehensive applications are constrained by the unavailable or insufficient interoperation among the underlying geo-data that are separately maintained in different spatial databases. To overcome this limitation, a novel approach has been proposed to integrate the routing-relevant information from different data sources, which involves three processes: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:12:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derecognize/article/1182140</link><title>Road Damage Externalities and Road User Charges</title><description>Vehicles on uncongested roads damage the pavement and advance the date at which repairs are necessary. Recent empirical work has identified another potentially more important social cost, for the damage to the pavement raises the operating costs of subsequent vehicles, and these operating costs may be an order of magnitude larger than the road maintenance costs. The paper develops a theory to handle this newly identified externality and establishes a remarkable result. If roads are repaired when they reach a predetermined ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:13:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/simonerfreitas/article/929858</link><title>The Ecological Road-Effect Zone of a Massachusetts (U.S.A.) Suburban Highway</title><description>Ecological flows and biological diversity trace broad patterns across the landscape, whereas transportation planning for human mobility traditionally focuses on a narrow strip close to a road or highway. To help close this gap we examined the "road-effect zone" over which significant ecological effects extend outward from a road. Nine ecological factors-involving wetlands, streams, road salt, exotic plants, moose, deer, amphibians, forest birds, and grassland birds-were measured or estimated near 25 km of a busy four-lane highway west of Boston, Massachusetts. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:13:54">http://www.citeulike.org/group/12735/article/6621824</link><title>Identifying Hazardous Road Locations: Hot Spots versus Hot Zones</title><description>Traffic safety has become top priority for policy makers in most European countries. The first step is to identify hazardous locations. This can be carried out in many different ways, via (Bayesian) statistical models or by incorporating the spatial configuration by means of a local indicator of spatial association. In this paper, the structure of the underlying road network is taken into account by applying Moran’s I to identify hot spots. One step further than the pure identification of hazardous locations ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>