<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:26:24" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:26:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/infantil/article/3889998</link><title>Bone loss during the acute stage following burn injury.</title><description>The aim of this study was to investigate the effect of burn injury on bone metabolism and bone densitometry in the early period. Twenty-one patients with &gt;25% total body surface area (TBSA) burns and 20 healthy controls participated. TBSA burned, ambulation, and functional status were recorded. After 30 days, we measured bone mineral densities of the L1-L4 vertebrae, the left distal forearm, and the left ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:27:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/laidrums/article/6096880</link><title>The Impact of Reading on Second Language Learning</title><description>Five critical differences between first and second language learning were identified and discussed. It was hypothesized that the effect of these differences in formal education could be virtually eliminated by means of a reading program based on the use of an abundance of high-interest illustrated story books. A sample of 380 Class 4 and 5 pupils from eight rural Fijian schools with very few books was selected, and each class was provided with 250 high-interest story books in English. The 16 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:28:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/laidrums/article/10219785</link><title>The influence of decodability in early reading text on reading achievement: a review of the evidence</title><description>The purpose of this review is to synthesize the existing research on decodability as a text characteristic examining how reading decodable text impacts students’ reading performance and growth. The results are organized into two sections based on the research designs of the studies: (1) studies that described student performance when reading texts of varying decodability levels, and (2) studies that compared the reading performance of students after participation in a treatment that manipulated decodable text as an independent variable. Collectively the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:29:51">http://www.citeulike.org/group/214/article/469677</link><title>Theoretical Models and Processes of Reading</title><description>The reading reference of the decade, now in a special hardcover limited edition! Over 80% of the articles are new or revised. The volume includes four sections: Historical Changes in Reading, Processes of Reading and Literacy, Models of Reading and Literacy Processes, and New Paradigms. Introductions to each section provide a brief overview of the articles within, share insights into the rationale for selection of those articles, and provide ideas for guiding discussion and for further reading. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:30:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ajaymalik/article/3889995</link><title>Endocrine changes after burn trauma--a review.</title><description>After burn trauma, a very marked endocrine response occurs. Almost all the known hormones take part in it. Their response influences very much the postburn metabolic changes and participates in the integration of the body's response with the nervous and immune systems. In this review, mainly the changes in various hormone levels are described, as well as the possible role of the acute phase response after burn trauma, and the communications between the endocrine and immune systems, the cells of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:32:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bakakaj/article/2397922</link><title>Burn and scald injuries.</title><description>Burns are one of the most harmful physical and psychological traumas. Infection is the major cause of morbidity and mortality in burns. Infections acquired from hospital or from the patient's own endogenous flora have a significant prevalence after burns. Pseudomonas aeruginosa and Staphylococcus aureus are the most frequent colonizing agents whereas group A beta-haemolytic streptococci are the most virulent bacteria. Anaerobic bacteria and fungi are also prevalent. Viral infection is less frequent. Aggressive resuscitation, nutritional support, thorough surgical excision of infected ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:33:22">http://www.citeulike.org/group/214/article/769981</link><title>Toward an Interactive-Compensatory Model of Individual Differences in the Development of Reading Fluency</title><description>Interactive models of reading appear to provide a more accurate conceptualization of reading performance than do strictly top-down or bottom-up models. When combined with an assumption of compensatory processing (that a deficit in any particular process will result in a greater reliance on other knowledge sources, regardless of their level in the processing hierarchy), interactive models provide a better account of the existing data on the use of orthographic structure and sentence context by good and poor readers. A review of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:34:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/garyfeng/article/14322</link><title>From letter names to word reading: The development of reading in kindergarten</title><description>Full text article (3 pages) available at http://www.reading.org/Library/Retrieve.cfm?D=10.1598/RRQ.39.4.1&amp;F=RRQ-39-4-Ritchey.pdf.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:35:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Mikaela321/article/7609926</link><title>Exploring Individual Differences among Novices Reading in a Specific Domain: The Case of Law</title><description>This study explores the reading strategies used by two groups of readers differentiated in terms of academic performance subsequent to their first year in law school. Strategies were inferred from the verbal reports of readers as they processed a law-related text for the purpose of giving a recitation. Results show that students in the top quartile of their law school class used different strategies than students in the bottom quartile. In addition, recitation scores between the two groups differed. Specifically, readers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:37:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alexstorer/article/4074685</link><title>Development of Neural Systems for Reading</title><description>Abstract Functional and structural neuroimaging studies of adult readers have provided a deeper understanding of the neural basis of reading, yet such findings also elicit new questions about how developing neural systems come to support this learned ability. A developmental cognitive neuroscience approach provides insights into how skilled reading emerges in the developing brain, yet also raises new methodological challenges. This review focuses on functional changes that occur during reading acquisition in cortical regions associated with both the perception of visual ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>