<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7085">Adam rogers music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:38:01" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:38:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hsuance/article/3765935</link><title>The Rest is HistoryMathias Spahlinger and Hans Heinrich Eggebrecht on Utopia in New Music</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:39:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jcampos29/article/2140749</link><title>Swarming and Music</title><description>Music is a pattern of sounds in time. A swarm is a dynamic pattern of individuals in space. The structure of a musical composition is shaped in advance of the performance, but the organization of a swarm is emergent, without pre-planning. What use, therefore, might swarms have in music? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:40:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/triciapadlanwilliams/article/4041916</link><title>Debating Assessment in Music Education</title><description>Music education organizations achieved a huge success in Texas several years ago when legislation declared music as a part of the core curriculum. Similarly, more recent national education legislation like No Child Left Behind has recognized music as a core curricular subject. Since that time, little has been done to assess music students to ensure a set of basic skills and knowledge is being achieved. While national and state music standards exist, these standards, in many cases, are not mandatory and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:41:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alonihill/article/6690548</link><title>The Canadian Music Journal : Special issue : Organs and organ playing in Canada.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:42:22">http://www.citeulike.org/group/17327/article/4146365</link><title>Music Psychology and Music Theory: Problems and Prospects</title><description>Music theorists and music psychologists may benefit from increasing awareness of each others' discipline. However, it is necessary to delimit the common ground shared by the disciplines and, at the same time, to clarify basic differences between the two approaches. Toward this end, this article begins with a schematic history of the psychology of music from the point of view of how it has been influenced by music theory. Following this is a brief characterization of the goals, methods, and theoretical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:43:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vsct103/article/6564814</link><title>Navigating Digital Sheet Music on the Web: Challenges and Opportunities</title><description>Affordable digital sheet music readers, along with the recent proliferation of Web sites hosting digital sheet music, necessitate a more detailed discussion of these valuable resources with a focus on copyright and website functionality in addition to coverage and quality. The phrase digital sheet music represents music digitized from its original paper format and music that is digitally produced in an electronic format. Web sites with digital sheet music content are most commonly hosted by individuals, libraries, professional societies and organizations, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:44:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mdk572/article/421391</link><title>Internet music: An introduction</title><description>This article provides a summary and overview of the key aspects of Internet music, as well as an introduction to the issue of &lt;i&gt;Contemporary Music Review&lt;/i&gt; on the subject. It examines popular conceptions of Internet music and seeks to define the topic by exploring some music that draws inspiration from networking without actually being Internet music itself. This article describes some basic Internet music concepts and attempts to classify it into various types: music that uses the network to connect physical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:45:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Yuhui_ch/article/4760099</link><title>Characteristics of Music Teachers and the Progress of Young Instrumentalists</title><description>This study is an investigation of the role of some key characteristics of teachers in the development of students' musical ability. Interviewing 257 children who differed in the extent of their instrumental mastery, we discovered that the most successful learners regarded their teachers differently from those children who ceased music study. The more successful learners rated their first teacher higher than did other learners on personal dimensions such as friendliness, and rated their current teacher higher than did other learners on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:46:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Juancho31/article/977019</link><title>The biology and evolution of music: A comparative perspective</title><description>Studies of the biology of music (as of language) are highly interdisciplinary and demand the integration of diverse strands of evidence. In this paper, I present a comparative perspective on the biology and evolution of music, stressing the value of comparisons both with human language, and with those animal communication systems traditionally termed “song”. A comparison of the “design features” of music with those of language reveals substantial overlap, along with some important differences. Most of these differences appear to stem ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7085-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7085_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:47:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CarolineLucas/article/4445395</link><title>Music and Urban Geography. By Adam Krims.</title><description>10.1093/ml/gcn113 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>