<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7086">falsifying pictures 21st centurie</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:48:56" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:49:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sobolevnrm/article/12987967</link><title>Exposure science in the 21st century: a vision and a strategy</title><description>From the use of personal products to our consumption of food, water, and air, people are exposed to a wide array of agents each day--many with the potential to affect health. Exposure Science in the 21st Century: A Vision and A Strategy investigates the contact of humans or other organisms with those agents (that is, chemical, physical, and biologic stressors) and their fate in living systems. The concept of exposure science has been instrumental in helping us understand how stressors affect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:50:18">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13847/article/10691591</link><title>A New Biology for the 21st Century</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:51:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kay0702/article/8061217</link><title>Flood! : a novel in pictures</title><description>A semi-autobiographical story in pictures about a city dweller in the last days of the twentieth century, based on events in New York in the late 1980s and early 1990s. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:52:32">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13427/article/7194491</link><title>Physiological responsivity to emotional pictures in schizophrenia.</title><description>Schizophrenic patients are known to experience difficulties in emotional information processing, yet knowledge of their physiological responsivity to emotional stimuli is limited. The purpose of this study was to investigate the physiological reactions of schizophrenic patients to emotional stimuli. We presented pictures selected from the International Affective Picture System (IAPS) to patients and controls, while assessing their subjective evaluations in terms of valence and arousal scores and measuring their responses of heart rate (HR), breathing rate (BR), skin conductance level (SCL) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:53:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mammabear/article/354931</link><title>Pictures for Language Learning (Cambridge Handbooks for Language Teachers)</title><description>A comprehensive resource demonstrating the vital role of visuals in the classroom. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:54:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RachelO/article/9164666</link><title>Phonological Activation of Ignored Pictures: Further Evidence for a Cascade Model of Lexical Access</title><description>Four experiments are reported exploring whether distractor pictures activate their phonological properties in the course of speech production. In Experiment 1, participants were presented with two pictures and were asked to name one while ignoring the other. Distractor pictures were phonologically related, semantically related or unrelated to the target picture. Naming latencies were faster in the phonologically related condition (the phonological facilitation effect--PFE) than in the unrelated condition. No difference between semantically related and unrelated distractors was observed. In Experiment 2, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:55:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/evahara/article/588359</link><title>From emotion perception to emotion experience: emotions evoked by pictures and classical music.</title><description>Most previous neurophysiological studies evoked emotions by presenting visual stimuli. Models of the emotion circuits in the brain have for the most part ignored emotions arising from musical stimuli. To our knowledge, this is the first emotion brain study which examined the influence of visual and musical stimuli on brain processing. Highly arousing pictures of the International Affective Picture System and classical musical excerpts were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:57:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sharilyn/article/9357075</link><title>Predicting memory for pictures from rankings of interestingness, pleasingness, complexity, figure-ground and clarity.</title><description>Pictures used in the test phase of a picture-recognition task were ranked by 10 university students for interestingness, pleasingness, complexity, figure-ground, and clarity. The scale values obtained from these rankings were then correlated with the errors made by other subjects in the test phase of the picture-recognition task. Figure-ground and clarity were found, for the most part, to be reliable predictors of the errors made to both the "old" and "new" subsets of pictures in two experiments. Complexity, while not as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:58:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RachelO/article/7425161</link><title>Words, pictures, and priming: on semantic activation, conscious identification, and the automaticity of information processing.</title><description>We investigated the encoding mechanisms involved in the perceptual recognition of words and pictures. Latencies in naming word and picture targets were analyzed as a function of several characteristics of a preceding prime, including whether it was a word or a picture, its duration of exposure, the interval between the prime and target onset, and whether or not the prime was consciously identified and reported by the subject. Results indicated that a common semantic code is available that can represent the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7086-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7086_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:59:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/caldavis/article/149014</link><title>Selenocysteine: the 21st amino acid.</title><description>Great excitement was elicited in the field of selenium biochemistry in 1986 by the parallel discoveries that the genes encoding the selenoproteins glutathione peroxidase and bacterial formate dehydrogenase each contain an in-frame TGA codon within their coding sequence. We now know that this codon directs the incorporation of selenium, in the form of selenocysteine, into these proteins. Working with the bacterial system has led to a rapid increase in our knowledge of selenocysteine biosynthesis and to the exciting discovery that this ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>