<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7087">Jonathan Kreisberg discography</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:14:13" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:14:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davide_caldo/article/9650575</link><title>Correlation between MR imaging and discography with provocative concordant pain in patients with low back pain.</title><description>disc degeneration grades on MR imaging showedan association with discographic grades. Type IV-V discs on discography, Grade IV-V disc on MR images, the presence of HIZ,and endplate abnormalities might indicate discogenic pain inpatients with chronic low back pain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:14:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davide_caldo/article/9650450</link><title>T1ρ MRI and Discography Pressure as Novel Biomarkers for Disc Degeneration and Low Back Pain.</title><description>ABSTRACT: Study Design: Prospective MRI study of LBP patients requiring discography as part of their routine clinical diagnoses and asymptomatic age-matched volunteers.Objective: To determine whether T1ρ MRI and discography opening pressure are quantitative biomarkers of disc degeneration in LBP patients and in asymptomatic volunteers.Summary of Background Data: Disc degenerative disease (DDD), a common cause of low back pain (LBP), is related to the patient's prognosis and serves as a target for therapeutic interventions. However, there are few quantitative measures in the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:14:51">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5362587</link><title>The prevention of discitis during discography</title><description>Because of the severe complications, discitis represents the most feared complication stemming from discography. Varying needle techniques have been used to prevent discitis, and evidence for the use of intravenous (IV) and/or intradiscal antibiotics is conflicting and often lacking. Consequently, no consensus has been formed for disc infection prevention during discography. The objectives of this review are to summarize and integrate all the available basic science, animal, and clinical evidence regarding prevention of infection from discography and to develop areas of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:15:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/samoday/article/710818</link><title>Lactate homeostasis and lactic acidosis.</title><description>The roles of changes in cellular redox, interorgan lactate flux and balance, and quantitative aspects of lactate metabolism in the pathogenesis of lactic acidosis are discussed. Altered metabolism of pyruvate is central to the development of lactic acidosis and hyperlactatemia. Lactic acidosis occurs as a result of a relative or absolute imbalance in lactate production and utilization. Lactate utilization for oxidative purposes and for the resynthesis of glucose is essential for the maintenance of acid-base balance. Because of its role in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:15:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/1621783</link><title>Clinical problem-solving. Stopping short of certainty.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:15:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/karlheinzschuler/article/9531492</link><title>Discography.</title><description>Discography is a purely diagnostic interventional procedure performed to confirm or refute the hypothesis that a specific lumbar disc is the predominant source of a patient's low back pain. In patients with severe low back pain, unresponsive to conservative care, discography is used when clinical evaluation suggests that the pain is emanating from the intervertebral disc and other sources of pain have been ruled out. The evidence for its use remains controversial. There is variability and subjectivity in discography techniques and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:16:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10331962</link><title>Drug partners for antibiotics</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:16:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10431203</link><title>Turning seaweed into biofuel</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:16:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10558303</link><title>Starving HIV of genome building blocks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7087-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7087_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:16:51">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10652991</link><title>Zinc-finger nucleases hone tumor cell therapy</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>