<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7088">Ezz-thetic</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:01:33" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:01:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/karimda/article/3568162</link><title>Inter-Organisational Collaboration towards Process Integration in the Public Sector. E-Government Collaboration in Egypt</title><description>This paper demonstrates the importance of collaboration between government departments as a backbone for inter-organizational integration between agencies such as ministries. We argue that the challenges related to e-government adoption can be partially attributed to the lack of standard collaboration practices between government agencies. We use the case of the foreign financing decision making process in Egypt as an example of a government process where close collaboration between government agencies such as ministries and the central bank of Egypt is essential. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:02:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2938617</link><title>A Least-Squares Standard Deviation Method to Interpret Gravity Data due to Finite Vertical Cylinders and Sheets</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:03:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8645083</link><title>Origin and evolution of post-collisional volcanism: an example from Neoproterozoic Dokhan volcanics at Gabal Nugara area, Northeastern Desert, Egypt</title><description>Nugara volcanics are one of the northernmost outcrops of the Arabian–Nubian Shield. Two distinct volcanic successions are found in the Nugara basin: (1) old volcanic sequence composed of voluminous medium- to high-K calc-alkaline lavas and minor alkali basalt and (2) young volcanic sequence composed of subordinate tholeiitic mafic lavas. Their eruptions were punctuated by occasional volcaniclastic deposits that generated fall, flow, or reworked suites compositionally identical to the lava flows. These volcanics are a part of a post-subduction and extensional-related magmatic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:04:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/703043</link><title>The Synthesis of Some New Quinazolone Derivatives of Potential Biological Activity</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:05:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8627340</link><title>Capecitabine plus cisplatin treatment in patients with advanced hepatocellular carcinoma</title><description>Objective  Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is the sixth most common cancer in the world and the third leading cause of cancer related death globally. Parentral treatment of Egyptian patients of bilharziasis contributed to the high incidence of viral hepatitis, and subsequently liver cirrhosis and HCC. Capecitabine plus cisplatin protocol was evaluated regarding the efficacy and safety in patients with advanced HCC as first line chemotherapy. Methods  One hundred patients with advanced HCC were randomized to receive either capecitabine (1000 mg/m2) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:06:52">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13978/article/6107928</link><title>Challenges of interorganizational collaboration for information technology adoption: Insights from a governmental financial decision-making process in Egypt</title><description>This article demonstrates the importance of collaboration between government departments as a backbone for interorganizational integration between agencies. It argues that the challenges related to information technology adoption in developing countries can be partially attributed to the lack of standard collaboration practices between government agencies. A case of a foreign financing decision-making process in Egypt was used as an example of a government process in which there was close collaboration between government agencies. The study identified a number of organizational and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:08:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3147763</link><title>Rotavirus fecal antigen retrieval in infantile intussusception</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:09:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/elisabettacarella/article/5894387</link><title>Electrical conductivity of gamma-irradiated V2O5 doped lithium disilicate glasses doped and their glass–ceramics derivatives</title><description>Some physical properties of the lithium disilicate (Li 2 Si 2 O 5 ) glasses doped with different ratios of V 2 O 5 were investigated before and after gamma-rays irradiation. Increasing V 2 O 5 ratio causes remarkable changes in the properties studied. The observed variations in the properties may be correlated with the changes in internal glass network with changes in the chemical composition. Vanadium ions are believed to be present in three possible valence states V ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:10:22">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9504637</link><title>A quadrature tau method for variable coefficients fractional differential equations</title><description>In this article, we develop a direct solution technique for solving multi-order fractional differential equations (FDEs) with variable coefficients using a quadrature shifted Legendre tau (Q-SLT) method. The spatial approximation is based on shifted Legendre polynomials. A new formula expressing explicitly any fractional-order derivatives of shifted Legendre polynomials of any degree in terms of shifted Legendre polynomials themselves is proved. Extension of the tau method for FDEs with variable coefficients is treated using the shifted Legendre Gauss-Lobatto quadrature. Numerical results are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7088-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7088_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:11:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/885516</link><title>The prevalence and characteristics of anaemia at discharge home after intensive care</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>