<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7090">eurovision 2012</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:23:40" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:23:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dullhunk/article/7228984</link><title>How does Europe Make Its Mind Up? Connections, cliques, and compatibility between countries in the Eurovision Song Contest</title><description>We investigate the complex relationships between countries in the Eurovision Song Contest, by recasting past voting data in terms of a dynamical network. Despite the British tendency to feel distant from Europe, our analysis shows that the U.K. is remarkably compatible, or 'in tune', with other European countries. Equally surprising is our finding that some other core countries, most notably France, are significantly 'out of tune' with the rest of Europe. In addition, our analysis enables us to confirm a widely-held belief that there are unofficial cliques of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:24:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/11961525</link><title>Measuring Cultural Dynamics Through the Eurovision Song Contest</title><description>Measuring culture and its dynamics through surveys has important limitations, but the emerging field of computational social science allows us to overcome them by analyzing large-scale datasets. In this article, we study cultural dynamics through the votes in the Eurovision song contest, which are decided by a crowd-based scheme in which viewers vote through mobile phone messages. Taking into account asymmetries and imperfect perception of culture, we measure cultural relations among European countries in terms of cultural affinity. We propose the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:25:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chsticksel/article/12446747</link><title>[FMCAD 2012] proceedings of the 12th Conference on Formal Methods in Computer-Aided Design : (FMCAD 2012) : held in Cambridge, United Kingdom, 22-25 October, at Microsoft's Cambridge research laboratory</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:27:00">http://www.citeulike.org/group/8395/article/4559255</link><title>How does Europe Make Its Mind Up? Connections, cliques, and compatibility between countries in the Eurovision Song Contest</title><description>We investigate the complex relationships between countries in the Eurovision Song Contest, by recasting past voting data from 1992–2003 in terms of a dynamical network. Our analysis shows that the UK is remarkably compatible, or ‘in tune’, with other European countries during the period of study. Equally surprising is our finding that some other core countries, most notably France, are significantly ‘out of tune’ with the rest of Europe during the same period. In addition, our analysis enables us to confirm ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:28:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abellogin/article/9343384</link><title>A study on the impact of crowd-based voting schemes in the 'Eurovision' European contest</title><description>The Eurovision contest has been the reference on european song contests for the past 50 years. Countries in the European Union can shows the rest of the participants their current music tendencies. This phenomena has been studied in domains like physic and social sciences to find correlations between contests and current political and socio-economy trends in EU. The inclusion of web and social technologies some years ago, have caused a disruption in the traditional voting system whereby the audience is encouraged ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:29:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/els2006/article/10441626</link><title>American Geriatrics Society Updated Beers Criteria for Potentially Inappropriate Medication Use in Older Adults</title><description>Potentially inappropriate medications (PIMs) continue to be prescribed and used as first-line treatment for the most vulnerable of older adults, despite evidence of poor outcomes from the use of PIMs in older adults. PIMs now form an integral part of policy and practice and are incorporated into several quality measures. The specific aim of this project was to update the previous Beers Criteria using a comprehensive, systematic review and grading of the evidence on drug-related problems and adverse drug events (ADEs) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:30:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11188869</link><title>Plant Contributed Papers</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:31:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Torsten_Holmer/article/10385796</link><title>Duet 2012: dual eye tracking in CSCW</title><description>Dual eye-tracking (DUET) is a promising methodology to study and support collaborative work. The method consists of simultaneously recording the gaze of two collaborators working on a common task. The main themes addressed in the workshop are eye-tracking methodology (how to translate gaze measures into descriptions of joint action, how to measure and model gaze alignment between collaborators, how to include gaze in multimodal interaction models, how to address task specificity inherent to eye-tracking data), empirical studies involving dual eye tracking ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:32:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fghjorth/article/4568826</link><title>The Eurovision Song Contest. Is voting political or cultural?☆</title><description>We analyze the voting behavior and ratings of judges in a popular song contest held every year in Europe since 1956. The dataset makes it possible to analyze the determinants of success, and gives a rare opportunity to run a direct test of vote trading. Though the votes cast may appear as resulting from such trading, we show that they are rather driven by quality of the participants as well as by linguistic and cultural proximities between singers and voting countries. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7090-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7090_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:33:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fghjorth/article/144907</link><title>Expert Judgment Versus Public Opinion - Evidence from the Eurovision Song Contest</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>