<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:34:51" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:34:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/spinaltap526/article/1240524</link><title>I don't believe in word senses</title><description>Word sense disambiguation assumes word senses. Within the lexicography and linguistics literature, they are known to be very slippery entities. The paper looks at problems with existing accounts of `word sense' and describes the various kinds of ways in which a word's meaning can deviate from its core meaning. An analysis is presented in which word senses are abstractions from clusters of corpus citations, in accordance with current lexicographic practice. The corpus citations, not the word... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:36:01">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5200/article/2811946</link><title>I Still Have It . . . I Just Can't Remember Where I Put It: Confessions of a Fiftysomething</title><description>I bought a new wrinkle cream. If you use it once a day, you look younger in a month. Twice a day, you look younger in two weeks. I ate it. As the years go by, and the decades begin to pile up, people will do just about anything to reverse the signs of aging: LASIK surgery, industrial- strength hair dye, seven consecutive forty-ninth birthday parties. Rita Rudner is no exception. When she turned fifty, she couldn’t even bear to say the word. In _I Still Have It . . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:37:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nbr/article/2183950</link><title>Under the Cherry Blossom Tree: An Old Japanese Tale</title><description>There were eggs in every bird's nest, the air buzzed with honeybees, and cherry trees blossomed all at once. The poor villagers forgot their cares and gathered in the meadow to sing and dance their time away. But their miserly landlord refused to be happy. Mumbling and grumbling, he sat all alone eating a bowl of cherries and glaring at the merry villagers. Then, quite by accident, he swallowed a cherry pit. The pit began to sprout, and soon the landlord ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:38:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amandaf/article/400357</link><title>Coercion : Why We Listen to What "They" Say</title><description>In 1994's &lt;I&gt;Cyberia: Life in the Trenches of Hyperspace&lt;/I&gt;, Douglas Rushkoff extolled the democratic promise of the then-emergent Internet, but the once optimistic author has grown a bit disillusioned with what the Net--and the rest of the world--has become. His exuberantly written, disturbing &lt;I&gt;Coercion&lt;/I&gt; may induce paranoia in readers as it illuminates the countless ways marketing has insinuated itself not just into every aspect of Western culture but into our individual lives. Rushkoff opens with a series of pronouncements: "They say ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:39:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rstamey7/article/6013754</link><title>Help kids with cell phones get the message: Say no to 'sexting'</title><description>10.1542/aapnews.2009308-26d ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:40:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abdonmenebadek/article/8031354</link><title>Dar barah-i qiyam-i hamasahafarinan</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:41:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6970230</link><title>Conservation Psychology: Understanding and Promoting Human Care for Nature, Susan Clayton, Gene Myers. Wiley-Blackwell, Oxford (2009). 251 pp., Price £29.99, Paperback, ISBN: 978-1-4051-9409-9.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:42:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ryang/article/469967</link><title>Theories of adaptation: what they do and don't say.</title><description>Theoretical work on adaptation has lagged behind experimental. But two classes of adaptation model have been partly explored. One is phenotypic and the other DNA sequence based. I briefly consider an example of each--Fisher's geometric model and Gillespie's mutational landscape model, respectively--reviewing recent results. Despite their fundamental differences, these models give rise to several strikingly similar results. I consider possible reasons for this congruence. I also emphasize what predictions do and, as important, do not follow from these models. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:43:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abdonmenebadek/article/8031753</link><title>Khatirat-i Ayat Allah Muhammad Yazdi</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:45:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abdonmenebadek/article/8031866</link><title>Khatirat-i Ayat Allah Mas`udi Khumayni</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>