<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:17:20" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:17:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sschuldt/article/10654432</link><title>Treatment-resistant depression in adolescents: review and updates on clinical management.</title><description>Treatment-resistant depression (TRD) in adolescents is prevalent and impairing. We here review the definition, prevalence, clinical significance, risk factors, and management of TRD in adolescents. Risk factors associated with TRD include characteristics of depression (severity, level of hopelessness, and suicidal ideation), psychiatric and medical comorbidities, environmental factors (family conflict, maternal depression, and history of abuse), and pharmacokinetics and other biomarkers. Management options include review of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:17:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/7208574</link><title>How Much to Copy? Determinants of Effective Imitation Breadth</title><description>It is a common and frequently implicit assumption in the literature on knowledge transfer and organizational learning that imitating practices from high-performing firms has a positive impact on the imitating firm. Although a large body of research has identified obstacles to successful imitation, not much is known about what breadth of imitation is most effective. In this paper, we use a simulation model to explore how context and firm similarity, interdependence among practices, context and firm similarity, and time horizon interact ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:17:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/depression/article/4059453</link><title>Effects of exercise training on older patients with major depression.</title><description>Previous observational and interventional studies have suggested that regular physical exercise may be associated with reduced symptoms of depression. However, the extent to which exercise training may reduce depressive symptoms in older patients with major depressive disorder (MDD) has not been systematically evaluated. To assess the effectiveness of an aerobic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:18:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/depression/article/4501202</link><title>Service use and outcomes among elderly persons with low incomes being treated for depression.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: Older adults with low incomes rarely use mental health care, and untreated depression is a serious problem in this population. This study examined whether a collaborative care model for depression in primary care would increase use of depression treatment and treatment outcomes for low-income elderly adults as well as for higher-income older adults. METHODS: A multisite randomized clinical trial that included 1,801 adults aged 60 years and older who were diagnosed as having depression compared collaborative care for depression with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:18:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/majellaharty/article/3979745</link><title>Gas production during refuse decomposition</title><description>Gas production in sanitary landfills is a subject of much concern because of the potential hazards of CH4 combustion and of groundwater contamination by CO2. This study investigated the pattern of sanitary landfill gas production and the factors which affect it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:19:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jfrantz/article/7176039</link><title>Fluoxetine, Cognitive-Behavioral Therapy, and Their Combination for Adolescents With Depression</title><description>Context  Initial treatment of major depressive disorder in adolescents may include cognitive-behavioral therapy (CBT) or a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI). However, little is known about their relative or combined effectiveness.Objective  To evaluate the effectiveness of 4 treatments among adolescents with major depressive disorder.Design, Setting, and Participants  Randomized controlled trial of a volunteer sample of 439 patients between the ages of 12 to 17 years with a primary Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, Fourth Edition, diagnosis of major depressive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:19:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/msa19/article/7843563</link><title>N&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Fixation by Non-Heterocystous Cyanobacteria</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:19:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/applebyb/article/2851056</link><title>Diagnosing depression in Alzheimer disease with the national institute of mental health provisional criteria.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To compare the rates of depression in Alzheimer Disease (AD) determined using National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) provisional criteria for depression in AD (NIMH-dAD) to those determined using other established depression assessment tools. DESIGN: Descriptive longitudinal cohort study. SETTING: The Alzheimer's Disease Research Centers of California. PARTICIPANTS: A cohort of 101 patients meeting NINDS-ADRDA criteria for possible/probable AD, intentionally selected to increase the frequency of depression at baseline. MEASUREMENTS: Depression was diagnosed at baseline and after 3 months using ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:20:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PaperCollector/article/10519060</link><title>Social isolation in prairie voles induces behaviors relevant to negative affect: toward the development of a rodent model focused on co-occurring depression and anxiety.</title><description>Recent evidence suggests substantial overlap between mood and anxiety disorders, both in clinical presentation and associated features. A theoretical framework to account for this overlap focuses on negative affectivity, defined as the disposition to experience negative emotional states, including fear, sadness, and guilt. This model has been successful in explaining the co-occurrence of depressive and anxiety disorders in humans. As a next step, development of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:20:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kurtgeorgwalther/article/567560</link><title>Gas Turbine Engineering Handbook, Second Edition</title><description>The gas turbine is a power plant that produces a great amount of energy for its size and weight and thus has found increasing service in the past 20 years in the petrochemical industry and utilities throughout the world. The gas turbine's compactness, weight, and multiple fuel applications make it a natural power plant for offshore platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This second edition is not only an updating of technology, which has seen a great leap forward in the 1990s, but also a rewriting of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>