<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:20:48" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:20:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10895484</link><title>Mathematics in Context (MiC). What Works Clearinghouse Intervention Report</title><description>"Mathematics in Context" is a middle school mathematics curriculum for grades 5 through 8. It was developed to align with the 1989 National Council of Teachers of Mathematics (NCTM) Curriculum and Evaluation Standards. It is also based on the Dutch Realistic Mathematics Education approach of engaging students in understanding real-life problems and gradually moving to abstract concepts. Rather than focusing on one mathematical domain at a time, "Mathematics in Context" teaches students to explore the relationships among different domains of mathematics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:21:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/what/article/9079591</link><title>Urban growth, climate change, and freshwater availability</title><description>Nearly 3 billion additional urban dwellers are forecasted by 2050, an unprecedented wave of urban growth. While cities struggle to provide water to these new residents, they will also face equally unprecedented hydrologic changes due to global climate change. Here we use a detailed hydrologic model, demographic projections, and climate change scenarios to estimate per-capita water availability for major cities in the developing world, where urban growth is the fastest. We estimate the amount of water physically available near cities and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:21:48">http://www.citeulike.org/group/3266/article/3440742</link><title>Data pushing: A fly-centric guide to bioinformatics tools.</title><description>Bioinformatics tools can be invaluable resources to Drosophila researchers; however, the sheer number of applications and databases can be overwhelming. We present a broad overview of common bioinformatics tasks and the resources used to do them, with a specific focus on resources for Drosophila. The topics covered include: Genome Databases, Sequence Analysis, Comparative Genomics, Gene Expression Databases and Analysis Tools, Function-Based Data and Analysis, Pathways, Networks and Interactions; and finally, tools to stay current with resources and literature. We also present ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:22:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mahler/article/379582</link><title>Describing, Transforming, and Querying Semistructured Data</title><description>eN FROM Person P, Person C, Person G WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.Child = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN Get the phone numbers of Joe's grandchildren. Against the decomposed relations is even worse: four joins SELECT N.PhoneN FROM Person1 P, ChildOf C, ChildOf G, Phone N WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.SSN = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN AND G.Child = N.SSN Objects Allow Simpler Design Schema: Child: SSN ) No need to decompose in order to eliminate redundancy: the set data type takes ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:22:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dabd/article/7290890</link><title>RESTful Web Services Principles of REST Web Service Design Semantic of HTTP/1.1 Operations SOAP vs. REST Style Assets and Drawbacks Security Public Web Services What is REST? Representational State Transfer</title><description>Representation of resource at URI places client in a state Hyperlinks are transitions between states Services itself should be stateless “The name ‘Representational State Transfer ’ is intended to evoke an image of how a well-designed Web application behaves: a network of web pages (a virtual state-machine), where the user progresses through an application by selecting links (state transitions), resulting in the next page (representing the next state of the application) being transferred to the user and rendered for their use.” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:22:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8031886</link><title>Do You Hear What I Hear: Better Understanding How Forest Management Is Conceptualized and Practiced by Private Forest Landowners</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:22:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dannya222/article/5781811</link><title>Reduction methods applied to non-locally coupled oscillator systems, Chapter 9 from Nonlinear Dynamics and Chaos: Where do we go from here?</title><description>When we try to understand the qualitative dynamics of spatially extendednonlinear systems through mathematical analysis, we require theoretical toolsto reduce the governing dynamical laws to simpler forms. Thus it is natural toask under what general conditions such model reduction can be achieved. Apossible answer is that the reduction is possible when the system involves a fewspecial degrees of freedom whose dynamics is distinctively slower, i.e. whosecharacteristic time scales are far longer than those of the remaining degrees offreedom: then those degrees ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:22:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lmayes/article/9153223</link><title>What happens when things go wrong?</title><description>Summary When a patient is injured or dies during anesthesia care, both the family of the patient and the health care providers suffer. The family needs to know what happened. The family can benefit from personal contact with the involved physicians. Apology to the injured is very important. The health care providers must report adverse events. Systematic review of adverse events can provide improved patient safety. Mechanisms exist to support the health care providers recovering from these potentially devastating experiences, but ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:23:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/headwayireland/article/9022968</link><title>Fitness to fly</title><description>It is estimated that 1 billion people travel by air every year, and this is expected to double in 20 years. For the vast majority, commercial flights are safe and comfortable. All flights, short haul or long haul, impose stresses on passengers. GPs are often asked to advise about or certify patients’ fitness to fly. This article aims to provide guidance to enable doctors to provide informed and evidence-based advice for their patients. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:23:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bangyuzhou/article/4085460</link><title>There are many ways to train a fly.</title><description>A biological understanding of memory remains one of the great quests of neuroscience. For over 30 years the fruit fly Drosophila melanogaster has primarily been viewed as an excellent vehicle to find 'memory genes'. However, the recent advent of sophisticated genetic tools to manipulate neural activity has meant that these genes can now be viewed within the context of functioning neural circuits. A holistic understanding of memory in flies is therefore now a realistic goal. Larvae and adult flies exhibit remarkable ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>