<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:48:26" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:48:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/2226033</link><title>Mutual Entropy</title><description>F10.94&gt; I(X; Y ) = H(X) +H(Y ) H(X;Y ) The mutual entropy I(X; Y ) expresses the amount of information given by image Y on image X. A value of 1:0 would reect perfect agreement and 0:0 complete disagreement between the two images X and Y . Guido Gerig, 21st April 1999 2 reference volume. The second term is the entropy of the part of the test volume into which the reference volume projects. It encourages transformations that project u into complex parts of v. The third term, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:49:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/niahm/article/1699166</link><title>Shut up and calculate</title><description>I advocate an extreme "shut-up-and-calculate" approach to physics, where our external physical reality is assumed to be purely mathematical. This brief essay motivates this "it's all just equations" assumption and discusses its implications. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:50:41">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/168529</link><title>Structural Inertia and Organizational Change</title><description>Theory and research on organization-environment relations from a population ecology perspective have been based on the assumption that inertial pressures on structure are strong. This paper attempts to clarify the meaning of structural inertia and to derive propositions about structural inertia from an explicit evolutionary model. The proposed theory treats high levels of structural inertia as a consequence of a selection process rather than as a precondition for selection. It also considers how the strength of inertial forces varies with age, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:51:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/orange-line/article/5119637</link><title>Subjectivity and the Sphere of Attention</title><description>Human subjectivity is attending activity. This way of speaking may sound dramatic and even strange, but I think it is a clear way of saying what we are and what we do, and I believe it captures the spirit of Gurwitsch’s phenomenology of consciousness, except that it all becomes oriented around a phenomenology of attention. Noting Husserl’s Ideas I (1982), Gurwitsch (1964, 419) writes “Considered as to its specific nature, consciousness is a domain closed in itself, a domain into which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:53:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mj_ovelar/article/11989200</link><title>Polarimetry of extra-solar planets and circumstellar disks with ZIMPOL / SPHERE</title><description>The future SPHERE VLT planet finder instrument includes a high precision polarimeter (ZIMPOL) for the search and characterization of reflected and therefore polarized light from extra-solar planetary systems. We discuss first the expected polarization properties of extra-solar planets and circumstellar disks and the diagnostic potential of polarimetric observations. Then we describe what can be achieved by combining in SPHERE / VLT an 8m telescope, an extreme AO system, coronagraphy, and high precision polarimetry. Performance simulations show that a contrast of 10e-8 should be reachable with this instrument. With this sensitivity ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:54:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shazhalia/article/1579595</link><title>Deliberative democracy, the public sphere and the internet</title><description>The internet could be an efficient political instrument if it were seen as part of a democracy where free and open discourse within a vital public sphere plays a decisive role. The model of deliberative democracy, as developed by Jürgen Habermas and Seyla Benhabib, serves this concept of democracy best. The paper explores first the model of deliberative democracy as a ‘two-track model’ in which representative democracy is backed by the public sphere and a developing civil society. Secondly, it outlines ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:55:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/matthijs/article/3180572</link><title>The evolution of inertia</title><description>This article examines some evolutionary consequences of architectural inertia in organizations. The main theorem holds that selection favors architectural inertia in the sense that the median level of inertia in a closed population of organizations increases over time. The other key theorems hold that the selection intensity favoring architectural inertia increases with the levels of intricacy and structural opacity and decreases with cultural asperity. 10.1093/icc/13.1.213 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:56:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/motchy/article/5328262</link><title>Computing Fourier Transforms and Convolutions on the 2-Sphere</title><description>This paper considers the problem of efficient computation of the spherical harmonic expansion, or Fourier transform, of functions defined on the two dimensional sphere, S2. The resulting algorithms are applied to the efficient computation of convolutions of functions on the sphere. We begin by proving convolution theorems generalizing well known and useful results from the abelian case. These convolution theorems are then used to develop a sampling theorem on the sphere. which reduces the calculation of Fourier transforms and convolutions of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:57:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/4505252</link><title>Gravitation and Inertia</title><description>Einstein's standard and battle-tested geometric theory of gravity--spacetime tells mass how to move and mass tells spacetime how to curve--is expounded in this book by Ignazio Ciufolini and John Wheeler. They give special attention to the theory's observational checks and to two of its consequences: the predicted existence of gravitomagnetism and the origin of inertia (local inertial frames) in Einstein's general relativity: inertia _here_ arises from mass _there_. The authors explain the modern understanding of the link between gravitation and inertia in Einstein's theory, from the origin of inertia ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7094-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7094_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:58:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eyliu/article/47633</link><title>Flux Capacitors and the Origin of Inertia</title><description>The explanation of inertia based on Mach's principle is briefly revisited and an experiment whereby the gravitational origin of inertia can be tested is described. The test consists of detecting a small stationary force with a sensitive force sensor. The force is presumably induced when a periodic transient Mach effect mass fluctuation is driven in high voltage, high energy density capacitors that are subjected to 50 kHz, 1.3 kV amplitude voltage signal, and threaded by an alternating magnetic flux of the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>