<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:59:42" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:59:47">http://www.citeulike.org/group/12850/article/7073933</link><title>MANAGING SCARCITY: CHANGING THE PARADIGM FOR SUSTAINABLE RESOURCE MANAGEMENT</title><description>As Arizona's fastest growing private water and wastewater utility, Global Water Resources (“Global”) is driving the deployment of efficient water resource management to ensure the sustainability of development. The drought plagued Southwest, poised to experience continued rapid growth, does so at the peril of its limited groundwater supplies. Thus, water conservation is imperative in the desert Southwest. Recognizing reclaimed water as the only increasing water supply, and the only true “sustainable” or “renewable” resource, effective management and deployment of reclaimed water ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:00:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Paola_Rattu/article/8405041</link><title>Water, health and the body: the tide, undercurrent and surge of meanings</title><description>Water has meaning for health, illness and wellbeing. Central themes of meaning can be identified consistently throughout history, sometimes easily discernible, while at other times more difficult to identify. These meanings have a substantial social dimension, and reflect physical and bodily interactions with water. This article considers how these aspects of water have caused specific meanings of water to be prioritized by the medical world and the general public throughout history. It focuses on different medical and everyday settings such as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:02:17">http://www.citeulike.org/article/13073717</link><title>Acknowledgement to Reviewers of Water in 2013</title><description>The editors of Water would like to express their sincere gratitude to the following reviewers for assessing manuscripts in 2013. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:03:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/federicastra/article/77963</link><title>Supply Chain Leadership and the High-Performance Business</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:04:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Schopfel/article/12318967</link><title>Line on interlending : selected papers on interlending and document supply</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:05:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/federicastra/article/9474</link><title>Full Circle or Labyrinth? - Weee &amp; Rohs - the Different Approaches of US &amp; Europe, their Effects on the Supply Chain and the International Marketplace</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:06:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wqunit/article/12372911</link><title>Ozwater'10 Australia's national water conference and exhibition</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:07:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wqunit/article/12368811</link><title>Australian environmental water management report 2010</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:08:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lecosepsci/article/11935387</link><title>Online Monitoring Technologies For Drinking Water Systems Security</title><description>More stringent constraints placed nowadays on water companies to provide high quality drinking water, increasing water resources scarcity in many areas of the planet, forcing water companies to work on marginal water bodies for supply, and the threat of hostile actions by political extremists and terrorist groups, that may willingly and deliberately cause contamination of an otherwise safe supply, are recent issues that have spurred demand for more efficient and comprehensive online water monitoring technologies. Traditionally, quality parameters associated with drinking ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:09:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/orenack/article/9829688</link><title>A Water Resources Planning Tool for the Jordan River Basin</title><description>The Jordan River basin is subject to extreme and increasing water scarcity. Management of transboundary water resources in the basin is closely intertwined with political conflicts in the region. We have jointly developed with stakeholders and experts from the riparian countries, a new dynamic consensus database and—supported by hydro-climatological model simulations and participatory scenario exercises in the GLOWA (Global Change and the Hydrological Cycle) Jordan River project—a basin-wide Water Evaluation and Planning (WEAP) tool, which will allow testing of various unilateral ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>