<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7096">touchpad scroll dell latitude</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:11:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:11:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/addone/article/3986337</link><title>Scroll ring performance evaluation</title><description>This study compares a touchpad scroll ring to a mouse scroll wheel and touchpad scroll zone using a Fitts' Law testing methodology. Time, error, and subjective results reveal that the scroll ring offers the most performance advantages over the scroll wheel and scroll zone. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:12:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Lasse/article/8023617</link><title>Rock 'n' Scroll Is Here to Stay</title><description>A novel user input method for digital appliances is introduced using the example of an electronic photo album. Based on tilting and gesturing with the device, the Rock 'n' Scroll input method handles scrolling, selection, and commanding an application without resorting to buttons, touch screens, spoken commands, or other input methods. User experiments with a prototype system showed that users could quickly learn how to operate such devices. The experiments also offered some insight into user expectations. These positive results, combined ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:13:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/susannh/article/4636065</link><title>Changes in applied force to a touchpad during pointing tasks</title><description>We measured the force applied to a touchpad during pointing tasks for large and small targets. A mouse was also used as a baseline condition. Our set-up to measure force included a Plexiglas plate mounted on a high-sensitivity three-axis strain gauge connected to an instrumentation amplifier and a data acquisition computer. The devices were positioned and operated on top of the plate with the selection button removed and actuated by the opposite hand. An experiment used 12 participants performing point-select tasks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:14:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sojyoon/article/9278460</link><title>The retrieval of phonological forms in production: Tests of predictions from a connectionist model*1</title><description>This article reviews a model of retrieval processes in language production that accounts for phonological speech-error data (Dell, 1986, Psychological Review, 93, 283–321). A distinction is drawn between empirical phenomena that are built into the model and phenomena that can be considered predictions from it. Data from experiments creating phonological speech errors are presented as tests of those predictions. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:15:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/9245128</link><title>Exploring the association between anorexia nervosa and geographical latitude.</title><description>The psychosocial and sociocultural features of 'cultures' do not exhaust the factors defining the environment in which we live. Our findings indicate that climatic parameters, such as latitude may be a relevant factor in the occurrence of AN. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:17:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8134625</link><title>Models of Impaired Lexical Access in Speech Production</title><description>Two computational models of lexical access in aphasic speakers are compared. Both are derived from an interactive two-step theory of retrieval based on spreading activation. The weight-decay model (Dell et al., 1997) associates patients with deviant values of two parameters, global connection weight and global decay rate. The new semantic-phonological model characterizes patients by two different parameters, semantic weight and phonological weight. We provide a detailed analysis of the properties of both models and show that the semantic-phonological model is a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:18:16">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2168514</link><title>13. Wisdom in Israel</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:19:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ketangli/article/263486</link><title>A spreading-activation theory of retrieval in sentence production.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:20:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/preeder/article/841255</link><title>Models of Impaired Lexical Access in Speech Production</title><description>Two computational models of lexical access in aphasic speakers are compared. Both are derived from an interactive two-step theory of retrieval based on spreading activation. The weight-decay model (Dell et al., 1997) associates patients with deviant values of two parameters, global connection weight and global decay rate. The new semantic-phonological model characterizes patients by two different parameters, semantic weight and phonological weight. We provide a detailed analysis of the properties of both models and show that the semantic-phonological model is a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7096-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7096_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:21:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/10296627</link><title>Geographical variation and incidence of inflammatory bowel disease among US women</title><description>Objective Geographical variation in the incidence of Crohn's disease (CD) and ulcerative colitis (UC) according to the latitude of residence has been reported in Europe. However, there are no comparable data in the USA. The incidence of CD and UC in relation to latitude was assessed in a geographically diverse population of women enrolled in two large prospective studies in the USA. Design A prospective study was undertaken of women enrolled in the Nurses' Health Study I (NHS) in 1976 and ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>