<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7097">best dum blonds</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:22:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:22:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/3102586</link><title>More Damned Lies and Statistics: How Numbers Confuse Public Issues</title><description>In this sequel to the acclaimed _Damned Lies and Statistics, _which the _Boston Globe _said "deserves a place next to the dictionary on every school, media, and home-office desk," Joel Best continues his straightforward, lively, and humorous account of how statistics are produced, used, and misused by everyone from researchers to journalists. Underlining the importance of critical thinking in all matters numerical, Best illustrates his points with examples of good and bad statistics about such contemporary concerns as school shootings, fatal hospital errors, bullying, teen suicides, deaths at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:23:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dlouzeck/article/606941</link><title>Random Violence : How We Talk about New Crimes and New Victims</title><description>&lt;i&gt;Random Violence&lt;/i&gt; is a deft and thought-provoking exploration of the ways we talk about--and why we worry about--new crimes and new forms of victimization. Focusing on so-called random crimes such as freeway shootings, gang violence, hate crimes, stalking, and wilding, Joel Best shows how new crime problems emerge and how some quickly fade from public attention while others spread and become enduring subjects of concern. Best's original and incisive argument illuminates the fact that while these crimes are in actuality ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:25:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jklugman/article/1542141</link><title>Flavor of the Month: Why Smart People Fall for Fads</title><description>While fads such as hula hoops or streaking are usually dismissed as silly enthusiasms, trends in institutions such as education, business, medicine, science, and criminal justice are often taken seriously, even though their popularity and usefulness is sometimes short-lived. Institutional fads such as open classrooms, quality circles, and multiple personality disorder are constantly making the rounds, promising astonishing new developments--novel ways of teaching reading or arithmetic, better methods of managing businesses, or improved treatments for disease. Some of these trends prove ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:26:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/euclid/article/8361690</link><title>Evidence Examples &amp; Explanations, 6e</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:27:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dayjm/article/2314092</link><title>Advanced Fly Tying: The Proven Methods and Techniques of a Master Professional Fly Tyer--37 Important Patterns</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Master fly tyer A.K. Best shows you how to bring your tying to a higher level. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:28:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4255557</link><title>Spinal cord terminations of the medial wall motor areas in macaque monkeys.</title><description>We used anterograde transport of wheat germ agglutinin-horseradish peroxidase to examine the pattern of spinal termination of efferents from the supplementary motor area (SMA) and the two caudal cingulate motor areas (CMAd and CMAv). Our analysis was limited to cervical segments of the macaque. For comparison, we also examined the pattern of termination of efferents from the primary motor cortex (M1). The SMA, CMAd, CMAv, and M1 all terminate in the ventral horn (lamina IX). Thus, all of these motor areas ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:29:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SinghalLab/article/1303237</link><title>Frontal lobe inputs to the digit representations of the motor areas on the lateral surface of the hemisphere.</title><description>We examined the frontal lobe connections of the digit representations in the primary motor cortex (M1), the dorsal premotor area (PMd), and the ventral premotor area (PMv) of cebus monkeys. All of these digit representations lie on the lateral surface of the hemisphere. We used intracortical stimulation to identify the digit representations physiologically, and then we injected different tracers into two of the three cortical areas. This approach enabled us to compare the inputs to two digit representations in the same ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:30:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SinghalLab/article/1303179</link><title>Motor areas in the frontal lobe of the primate.</title><description>There has been a substantial change in our concepts about the cortical motor areas. It is now clear that the frontal lobe of primates contains at least six premotor areas that project directly to the primary motor cortex (M1). Two premotor areas, the ventral premotor area (PMv) and the dorsal premotor area (PMd), are located on the lateral surface of the hemisphere. Four premotor areas are located on the medial wall of the hemisphere and include the supplementary motor area (SMA) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:32:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wangjenn/article/1377935</link><title>Best friends forever?: High school best friendships and the transition to college</title><description>Abstract The transition from high school to college is an important phase for adolescents in social as well as academic aspects. This study examined the changes that occur in high school best friendships during the first year of college. Results revealed that during the first year in college high school best friendships declined in satisfaction, commitment, rewards, and investments. During this period there was also an increase in costs and alternatives to best friend relationships. Proximity did not influence the friendships; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7097-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7097_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:33:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dayjm/article/2314101</link><title>Dyeing and Bleaching, Second Edition: Natural Fly-Tying Materials</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The second edition of this important book focuses on one of the most crucial aspects of the fly-tyer's art: color control. It is the most important book devoted entirely to the subject-an indispensable and practical handbook by one of America's finest and most respected professional fly tyers.&lt;br&gt;A. K. Best explores the equipment and supplies needed for accurate and safe dyeing and bleaching--most of them commonly available. Then he progresses on such subjects as &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Body Feathers&lt;br&gt;· Bucktails&lt;br&gt;· Deer and Elk Hair&lt;br&gt;· Calf and Squirrel Tails&lt;br&gt;· Furs&lt;br&gt;· Bleaching&lt;br&gt;· Dye ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>