<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:34:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:34:21">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5400788</link><title>On the seminar on qualitative theory of differential equations at Moscow State University</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:35:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/achadol/article/4014742</link><title>Moscow Health Survey 2004 – social surveying under difficult circumstances</title><description>Summary Objectives:  The aim of this paper is to present the Moscow Health Survey 2004, which was designed to examine health inequalities in Moscow. In particular we want to discuss social survey problems, such as non-response, in Moscow and Russia. Methods:  Interviews, covering social and economic circumstances, health and social trust, of a stratified random sample of the greater Moscow population, aged 18+. Reasons for nonresponse were noted down with great care. Odds ratios (ORs) for self-rated health by gender and by six ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:36:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9857011</link><title>Is graphene's future in the hands of the chemist?</title><description>One year after the Nobel Prize in Physics was awarded to Geim and Novoselov for their groundbreaking work on graphene, James Tour asks, “Does graphene now belong to the chemist?” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:37:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/9771759</link><title>Graphene Chemistry: Synthesis and Manipulation</title><description>Monolayer graphene is a two-dimensional material with fascinating electrical and optical properties that has brought great possibilities and challenges to chemists. The possibilities include the many applications in which graphene could be exploited, and the challenges involve optimizing synthetic strategies and manipulating the structure and properties so that graphene can be used in those applications. Here, we cover a portion of the recent progress toward using chemical techniques to render graphene available for incorporation into electronic and optical devices. With top-down ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:38:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yuer/article/1191528</link><title>A Multiresolution Approach For Improving Quality Of Image Denoising Algorithms</title><description>In this paper, we propose a multiresolution framework for improving the quality of several image and audio processing algorithms. The results of algorithms operating at different time-frequency (or space-frequency) resolutions are adaptively combined in order to achieve a variable resolution of a filter bank. Applications of the proposed model to image noise reduction algorithms are demonstrated with examples of non-local means and adaptive PCA algorithms. 1. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:40:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/11055695</link><title>Highly Conductive Graphene Nanoribbons by Longitudinal Splitting of Carbon Nanotubes Using Potassium Vapor</title><description>Here we demonstrate that graphene nanoribbons (GNRs) free of oxidized surfaces can be prepared in large batches and 100% yield by splitting multiwalled carbon nanotubes (MWCNTs) with potassium vapor. If desired, exfoliation is attainable in a subsequent step using chlorosulfonic acid. The low-defect density of these GNRs is indicated by their electrical conductivity, comparable to that of graphene derived from mechanically exfoliated graphite. The possible origins of directionally selective splitting of MWCNTs have been explored using computer modeling, and plausible explanations ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:40:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/4320772</link><title>Longitudinal unzipping of carbon nanotubes to form graphene nanoribbons</title><description>Graphene, or single-layered graphite, with its high crystallinity and interesting semimetal electronic properties, has emerged as an exciting two-dimensional material showing great promise for the fabrication of nanoscale devices1, 2, 3. Thin, elongated strips of graphene that possess straight edges, termed graphene ribbons, gradually transform from semiconductors to semimetals as their width increases4, 5, 6, 7, and represent a particularly versatile variety of graphene. Several lithographic7, 8, chemical9, 10, 11 and synthetic12 procedures are known to produce microscopic samples of graphene ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:41:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dokooh/article/349963</link><title>Cyberguide: a mobile context-aware tour guide</title><description>Future computing environments will free the user from the constraints of the desktop. Applications for a mobile environment should take advantage of contextual information, such as position, to offer greater services to the user. In this paper, we present the Cyberguide project, in which we are building prototypes of a mobile context-aware tour guide. Knowledge of the user's current location, as well as a history of past locations, are used to provide more of the kind of services that we come ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:43:00">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2118/article/4308433</link><title>Context-Aware Mobile Tour Guide</title><description>This paper discusses the requirements for a contextaware mobile tour guide (MTG) and proposes a design for constructing it. With increasing wireless and network connectivity available in the world today, a MTG device will be a powerful hand-held device for adaptive information gathering, query processing, and collaborative work among ad hoc groups of people. By mapping the requirements onto layered functional units and including the user as part of the system design the system complexity is reduced while enhancing the system ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:44:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/235163</link><title>EGFP as your targeted 'hitman'</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>