<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7100">korean bbq san francisco review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:56:53" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:57:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akselkolsen/article/9357450</link><title>Educational and Demographic Profile: San Francisco County</title><description>This profile uniquely presents educational and socioeconomic information for San Francisco County, nearby counties, and the state. It highlights the relationship between various factors that affect the economic well-being of individuals and communities. This information provides a framework for enhanced communication and collaboration between the agencies, at both the state and local level, that have responsibility for education, economic development, workforce training, or social services. The relationship between educational attainment and income is clearly depicted by the maps on pages 4 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:58:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/12722288</link><title>Seroadaptive behaviours among men who have sex with men in San Francisco: the situation in 2008</title><description>Objectives To assess changes in seroadaptive behaviours among men who have sex with men (MSM) in San Francisco over the past 4 years. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:59:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mfrankm111/article/11892350</link><title>Geochemical and isotopic characteristics of lower crustal xenoliths, San Francisco Volcanic Field, Arizona, U.S.A</title><description>A wide variety of xenoliths has been entrained in Miocene-to-Recent alkali olivine and hypersthene-normative basalts in the San Francisco Volcanic Field (SFVF), northern Arizona, U.S.A. Based on petrography, mineralogy, bulk rock chemistry and Sr-Nd isotopic characteristics, SFVF xenoliths can be divided into two major groups: cumulates and granulites. The cumulates are genetically related to the Cenozoic volcanic rocks and represent under- and/or intraplated additions to the crust of the Colorado Plateau. Assemblages are mafic to ultramafic and are dominated by clinopyroxene-orthopyroxene-plagioclase-spinel-amphibole-olivine. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:00:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sierradyer1/article/6102975</link><title>The Million Dollar Backfield: The San Francisco 49ers in the 1950s</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:01:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/12089722</link><title>Changing patterns in the clinical characteristics of korean breast cancer from 1996-2010 using an online nationwide breast cancer database.</title><description>Breast cancer is one of the most frequent malignancies in Korean women, and its incidence is increasing at a rapid rate. Since 1996, the Korean Breast Cancer Society has collected nationwide breast cancer data using an online registration program and analyzed the data biennial. The purpose of this study was to evaluate the characteristics of Korean breast cancer and to analyze changes in these characteristics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:02:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sierradyer1/article/5906645</link><title>Then Steve Said to Jerry: The Best San Francisco 49ers Stories Ever Told (Best Sports Stories Ever Told the Best Sports Stories Ever T) with CD</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:03:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/haziekat/article/2573422</link><title>Gentrification and Grassroots Resistance in San Francisco's Tenderloin</title><description>Since World War II, San Francisco has been transformed by the high-rise postindustrial restructuring of central cities and by corresponding gentrification pressures. In one low-income inner-city district, the Tenderloin, residents organized and fought successful battles against the gentrifying growth regime through the 1980s. Moving beyond being a reactionary antigrowth movement, Tenderloin activists have advanced a proactive, neighborhood-sensitive regime, with a social-production capacity of its own, represented by the neighborhood's nonprofit housing movement. Their example teaches about the neighborhood-responsive progressive forces that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:04:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amoore88/article/505266</link><title>Views from Inside: Memoirs concerning the Yugoslav Breakup and War</title><description>Recent memoirs published in Zagreb, Ljubljana, Sarajevo, and Podgorica offer glimpses into how the principals would like their roles in the events connected with the Yugoslav breakup and war to be remembered. The most indispensable of the ten memoirs under review are those by Janez Drnovsek and Janez Jansa, who have differing perspectives on developments in Slovenia between 1988 and 1991; by Martin Spegelj, who outlines in detail his argument that Croatia should have laid siege to the Yugoslav Army barracks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:06:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/9509337</link><title>Chronological changing patterns of clinical characteristics of Korean breast cancer patients during 10 years (1996-2006) using nationwide breast cancer registration on-line program: biannual update.</title><description>Our results suggest the incidence of breast cancer in Korea will continue to rise. Several characteristics of Korean breast cancer patients seem to follow the patterns of Western countries, but differences are present. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7100-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7100_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:07:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mycase/article/5269079</link><title>GSTM1, GSTT1 and GSTP1 polymorphisms in the Korean population.</title><description>The isoenzymes of the glutathione s transferase (GST) family play a vital role in phase II of biotransformation of many substances. Using a multiplex polymerase chain reaction and a direct sequencing analysis, the frequencies of GSTM1, GSTT1, and GSTP1 polymorphisms were evaluated in 1,051 Korean male subjects. We found that 53.8% of the individuals had the GSTM1 null genotype and 54.3% had the GSTT 1 null genotype. The genotypic distribution of GSTP1 was Ile105/Ile105 in 68.4%, Ile105/Val105 in 29.1% and Val105/Va105 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>