<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7101">innodb versus myisam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:08:12" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:08:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/djmonstermo/article/2954925</link><title>A Comparison of Antiarrhythmic-Drug Therapy with Implantable Defibrillators in Patients Resuscitated from Near-Fatal Ventricular Arrhythmias</title><description>Background Patients who survive life-threatening ventricular arrhythmias are at risk for recurrent arrhythmias. They can be treated with either an implantable cardioverter-defibrillator or antiarrhythmic drugs, but the relative efficacy of these two treatment strategies is unknown. Methods To address this issue, we conducted a randomized comparison of these two treatment strategies in patients who had been resuscitated from near-fatal ventricular fibrillation or who had undergone cardioversion from sustained ventricular tachycardia. Patients with ventricular tachycardia also had either syncope or other ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:09:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/igarmark/article/10062765</link><title>Beclomethasone/formoterol versus budesonide/formoterol combination therapy in asthma.</title><description>The present study was designed to compare the fixed combination of beclomethasone and formoterol in a hydrofluoroalkane Modulite (Chiesi Farmaceutici, Parma, Italy) pressurised metered-dose inhaler (pMDI), with a combination of budesonide and formoterol administered via a Turbuhaler (AstraZeneca, Lund, Sweden) dry powder inhaler (DPI). This was a phase III, multinational, multicentre, double-blind, double-dummy, randomised, two-arm parallel groups, controlled study design. After a 2-week run-in period, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:10:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/valentinarodriguez/article/13131872</link><title>Comparative study of laparoscopic versus open appendicectomy.</title><description>Comparative Study of Laparoscopic (LA) versus Open Appendicectomy (OA) as a Cross sectional hospital based study for evaluation of: Postoperative quality of life Postoperative painAmount of Narcotics/Analgesics usedHospital stayTime to full recovery This underdeveloped residuum of the caecum has no known function and is commonly termed as a 'vestigial' organ, yet diseases of the appendix loom large in surgical practice; and appendicitis continues to be the most common acute abdominal condition that requires immediate surgical treatment. Study to be carried out ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:11:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/livnesca/article/8451652</link><title>Effects of computer versus paper administration of an adult functional writing assessment</title><description>This study investigated the comparability of paper and computer versions of a functional writing assessment administered to adults 16 and older. Three writing tasks were administered in both paper and computer modes to volunteers in the field test of an assessment of adult literacy in 2008. One set of analyses examined mode effects on scoring by comparing scores for adults’ original handwritten responses to scores for their transcribed word-processed versions. Differences in overall or individual criterion scores were either statistically or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:12:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xingxu/article/3812487</link><title>The influence of genetic variation in 30 selected genes on the clinical characteristics of early onset breast cancer.</title><description>INTRODUCTION: Common variants that alter breast cancer risk are being discovered. Here, we determine how these variants influence breast cancer prognosis, risk and tumour characteristics. METHODS: We selected 1,001 women with early onset nonfamilial invasive breast cancer from the Prospective study of Outcomes in Sporadic versus Hereditary breast cancer (POSH) cohort and genotyped 206 single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) across 30 candidate genes. After quality control, 899 cases and 133 SNPs remained. Survival analyses were used to identify SNPs associated with prognosis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:14:02">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10686826</link><title>Progress report on the first sub-Saharan trial of newer versus older antihypertensive drugs in native black patients</title><description>Background: The epidemic surge in hypertension in sub-Saharan Africa is not matched by clinical trials ofantihypertensive agents in Black patients recruited in this area of the world. We mounted theNewer versus Older Antihypertensive agents in African Hypertensive patients (NOAAH) trialto compare, in native African patients, a single-pill combination of newer drugs, notinvolving a diuretic, with a combination of older drugs including a diuretic. Methods: Patients aged 30 to 69 years with uncomplicated hypertension (140 to 179/90 to 109 mmHg)and [less than or equal to]2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:15:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/drhorevitz/article/10798776</link><title>Clinical versus actuarial judgment</title><description>Professionals are frequently consulted to diagnose and predict human behavior; optimal treatment and planning often hinge on the consultant's judgmental accuracy. The consultant may rely on one of two contrasting approaches to decision-making--the clinical and actuarial methods. Research comparing these two approaches shows the actuarial method to be superior. Factors underlying the greater accuracy of actuarial methods, sources of resistance to the scientific findings, and the benefits of increased reliance on actuarial approaches are discussed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:16:15">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/1643762</link><title>The P versus NP Brief</title><description>This paper discusses why P and NP are likely to be different. It analyses the essence of the concepts and points out that P and NP might be diverse by sheer definition. It also speculates that P and NP may be unequal due to natural laws. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:17:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Dorotaz/article/10485051</link><title>Cytology versus HPV testing for cervical cancer screening in the general population</title><description>This is the protocol for a review and there is no abstract. The objectives are as follows: To determine the diagnostic accuracy of HPV testing for detecting histologically confirmed CIN 2 or worse (CIN 2+), including adenocarcinoma in situ, in women participating in primary cervical cancer screening; and how it compares to the accuracy of cytological testing (liquid-based and conventional) at various thresholds. To determine the diagnostic accuracy of the combination of HPV testing and cytological testing and to compare it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7101-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7101_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:18:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Petenko/article/8623212</link><title>Immunostimulation versus immunosuppression after multiple vaccinations: the woes of therapeutic vaccine development.</title><description>Three articles in this issue of Clinical Cancer Research show how multiple vaccinations can lead to immunosuppression. Moreover, two studies in patients show that granulocyte macrophage colony-stimulating factor (GM-CSF) as an adjuvant immunostimulant to different kind of vaccines can lead to adverse outcome in terms of relapse-free and overall survival. Modulation of regulatory T-cell activity may be required to overcome this outcome and may be crucial for the successful development of therapeutic vaccines. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>