<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:19:27" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:19:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/UsmanNMKhan/article/877753</link><title>MAC protocols for wireless sensor networks: a survey</title><description>Wireless sensor networks are appealing to researchers due to their wide range of application potential in areas such as target detection and tracking, environmental monitoring, industrial process monitoring, and tactical systems. However, low sensing ranges result in dense networks and thus it becomes necessary to achieve an efficient medium-access protocol subject to power constraints. Various medium-access control (MAC) protocols with different objectives have been proposed for wireless sensor networks. In this article, we first outline the sensor network properties that are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:20:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andiko/article/4236020</link><title>Z-MAC: a hybrid MAC for wireless sensor networks</title><description>This paper presents the design, implementation and performance evaluation of a hybrid MAC protocol, called Z-MAC, for wireless sensor networks that combines the strengths of TDMA and CSMA while offsetting their weaknesses. Like CSMA, ZMAC achieves high channel utilization and low latency under low contention and like TDMA, achieves high channel utilization under high contention and reduces collision among two-hop neighbors at a low cost. A distinctive feature of Z-MAC is that its performance is robust to synchronization errors, slot assignment ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:21:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andiko/article/604303</link><title>An adaptive energy-efficient MAC protocol for wireless sensor networks</title><description>In this paper we describe T-MAC, a contention-based Medium Access Control protocol for wireless sensor networks. Applications for these networks have some characteristics (low message rate, insensitivity to latency) that can be exploited to reduce energy consumption by introducing an activesleep duty cycle. To handle load variations in time and location T-MAC introduces an adaptive duty cycle in a novel way: by dynamically ending the active part of it. This reduces the amount of energy wasted on idle listening, in which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:22:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andiko/article/994378</link><title>X-MAC: a short preamble MAC protocol for duty-cycled wireless sensor networks</title><description>In this paper we present X-MAC, a low power MAC protocol for wireless sensor networks (WSNs). Standard MAC protocols developed for duty-cycled WSNs such as BMAC, which is the default MAC protocol for TinyOS, employ an extended preamble and preamble sampling. While this "low power listening" approach is simple, asynchronous, and energy-efficient, the long preamble introduces excess latency at each hop, is suboptimal in terms of energy consumption, and suffers from excess energy consumption at nontarget receivers. X-MAC proposes solutions to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:23:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/inki/article/768516</link><title>An energy-efficient MAC protocol for wireless sensor networks</title><description>This paper proposes S-MAC, a medium-access control (MAC) protocol designed for wireless sensor networks. Wireless sensor networks use battery-operated computing and sensing devices; a network of these devices will collaborate for a common application such as environmental monitoring. We expect sensor networks to be deployed in an ad hoc fashion, with individual nodes remaining largely inactive for long periods of time, but then becoming suddenly active when something is detected. These... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:24:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andiko/article/4463513</link><title>RI-MAC: a receiver-initiated asynchronous duty cycle MAC protocol for dynamic traffic loads in wireless sensor networks</title><description>The problem of idle listening is one of the most significant sources of energy consumption in wireless sensor nodes, and many techniques have been proposed based on duty cycling to reduce this cost. In this paper, we present a new asynchronous duty cycle MAC protocol, called Receiver-Initiated MAC ( RI-MAC ), that uses receiver-initiated data transmission in order to efficiently and effectively operate over a wide range of traffic loads. RI-MAC attempts to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:25:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andiko/article/10838491</link><title>WiseMAC: An Ultra Low Power MAC Protocol for Multi-hop Wireless Sensor Networks Algorithmic Aspects of Wireless Sensor Networks</title><description>WiseMAC is a medium access control protocol designed for wireless sensor networks. This protocol is based on non-persistent CSMA and uses the preamble sampling technique to minimize the power consumed when listening to an idle medium. The novelty in this protocol consists in exploiting the knowledge of the sampling schedule of one’s direct neighbors to use a wake-up preamble of minimized size. This scheme allows not only to reduce the transmit and the receive power consumption, but also brings a drastic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:26:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/inki/article/877882</link><title>Comparing energy-saving MAC protocols for wireless sensor networks</title><description>Applications for wireless sensor networks have notably different characteristics and requirements from standard WLAN applications. Low energy consumption is the most important consideration. The low message rate that is typical for sensor network applications and the relaxed latency requirements allow for significant reductions in energy consumption of the radio. In this article we study the energy saved by two MAC protocols optimized for wireless sensor networks, S-MAC and T-MAC, in comparison to standard CSMA/CA, We also report on the effects of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:28:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mortenthansen/article/9702901</link><title>PW-MAC: An energy-efficient predictive-wakeup MAC protocol for wireless sensor networks</title><description>This paper presents PW-MAC (Predictive-Wakeup MAC), a new energy-efficient MAC protocol based on asynchronous duty cycling. In PW-MAC, nodes each wake up to receive at randomized, asynchronous times. PW-MAC minimizes sensor node energy consumption by enabling senders to predict receiver wakeup times; to enable accurate predictions, PW-MAC introduces an on-demand prediction error correction mechanism that effectively addresses timing challenges such as unpredictable hardware and operating system delays and clock drift. PW-MAC also introduces an efficient prediction-based retransmission mechanism to achieve high ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7102-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7102_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:29:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mortenthansen/article/4460618</link><title>Y-MAC: An Energy-Efficient Multi-channel MAC Protocol for Dense Wireless Sensor Networks</title><description>As the use of wireless sensor networks (WSNs) becomes widespread, node density tends to increase. This poses a new challenge for Medium Access Control (MAC) protocol design. Although traditional MAC protocols achieve low-power operation, they use only a single channel which limits their performance. Several multi-channel MAC protocols for WSNs have been recently proposed. One of the key observations is that these protocols are less energy efficient than single-channel MAC protocols under light traffic conditions. In this paper, we propose an ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>