<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:24:03" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:24:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/9814063</link><title>Vitamin D deficiency as a risk factor for cystic fibrosis-related diabetes in the Scandinavian Cystic Fibrosis Nutritional Study.</title><description>AIMS/HYPOTHESIS: Many cystic fibrosis patients are vitamin D-insufficient. Cystic fibrosis-related diabetes is a major complication of cystic fibrosis. The literature suggests that vitamin D might possess certain glucose-lowering properties. We aimed to assess the relationship between vitamin D and cystic fibrosis-related glucose intolerance. METHODS: We enrolled 898 cystic fibrosis patients from Sweden, Norway and Denmark. Vitamin D intake was assessed using a seven-day food record. Serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D (s25OHD) and HbA(1c) were measured, and an OGTT was carried out. Multiple linear ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:24:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bonitaswann/article/9135208</link><title>Nutrition in patients with cystic fibrosis: a European Consensus.</title><description>This document is the result of an European Consensus conference which took place in Artimino, Tuscany, Italy, in March 2001 involving 33 experts on nutrition in patients with cystic fibrosis, organised by the European Cystic Fibrosis Society, and sponsored by Axcan-Scandipharm, Baxter, Dr Falk Pharma, Fresenius, Nutricia, SHS International, Solvay Pharmaceuticals (major sponsor). The purpose of the conference was to develop a consensus document on nutrition in patients with cystic fibrosis based on current evidence. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:24:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/uoltfk3/article/6868270</link><title>Physiological effects of vibration in subjects with cystic fibrosis</title><description>The physiological mechanisms by which vibration and other physiotherapy interventions may clear secretions in subjects with cystic fibrosis are unknown. The main aim of this study was to compare the expiratory flow rates and frequencies of airflow oscillation of vibration to those of Acapella(R), Flutter(R), positive expiratory pressure and percussion. Respiratory flow rates were measured during interventions, the order of which was randomised. The oscillation of the airflow of the interventions was determined by frequency spectral analysis. In 18 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:25:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MAUI/article/36174</link><title>Burkholderia cepacia complex infection in adult patients with cystic fibrosis-is early eradication possible?</title><description>CEPACIA</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:25:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/banner27/article/6359104</link><title>A Controlled Trial of Long-Term Inhaled Hypertonic Saline in Patients with Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Background Inhaled hypertonic saline acutely increases mucociliary clearance and, in short-term trials, improves lung function in people with cystic fibrosis. We tested the safety and efficacy of inhaled hypertonic saline in a long-term trial. Methods In this double-blind, parallel-group trial, 164 patients with stable cystic fibrosis who were at least six years old were randomly assigned to inhale 4 ml of either 7 percent hypertonic saline or 0.9 percent (control) saline twice daily for 48 weeks, with quinine sulfate (0.25 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:25:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7886040</link><title>Treatment of cystic fibrosis associated cutaneous vasculitis with chloroquine</title><description>Vasculitis is a well recognised complication of Cystic Fibrosis. Corticosteroids are the mainstay of treatment but some cases can be resistant and may require additional disease modifying agents. We describe a case of steroid resistant cutaneous vasculitis which was successfully treated with chloroquine in addition to corticosteroids and a subsequent relapse with chloroquine alone. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:25:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nzd1/article/6856664</link><title>Infertility in Females with Cystic Fibrosis is Multifactorial: Evidence from Mouse Models</title><description>Infertility is commonly associated with Cystic Fibrosis (CF). Although infertility in men with CF has been thoroughly investigated, the infertility observed in women with CF has not been well studied. To investigate female infertility associated with CF, we utilized two independently derived mouse models of CF. Both of these models displayed decreased fertility characterized by a reduction in litter number and litter size. Our findings suggest that much of the reduced fertility in these mice originates from decreased fertilization due to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:26:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jmlanderos/article/8820511</link><title>Physiotherapeutic management strategies for the treatment of cystic fibrosis in adults.</title><description>Physiotherapy has long been considered a cornerstone of condition management for people with cystic fibrosis (CF). The presentation of CF has changed over time with an increased life expectancy and increased expectations of people with CF to have a complete lifestyle. In turn, the scope of strategies used in physiotherapy for CF have also changed dramatically over the years, moving away from routine postural drainage ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:26:52">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11630057</link><title>Treatment of lung infection in patients with cystic fibrosis: Current and future strategies</title><description>In patients with cystic fibrosis (CF) lung damage secondary to chronic infection is the main cause of death. Treatment of lung disease to reduce the impact of infection, inflammation and subsequent lung injury is therefore of major importance. Here we discuss the present status of antibiotic therapy for the major pathogens in CF airways, including prophylaxis against infection, eradication of early infection, suppression of chronic infection, and the treatment of infective exacerbations. We outline measures to optimize maintenance treatment for infection ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:27:22">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11706848</link><title>Treatment of lung infection in patients with cystic fibrosis: Current and future strategies</title><description>In patients with cystic fibrosis (CF) lung damage secondary to chronic infection is the main cause of death. Treatment of lung disease to reduce the impact of infection, inflammation and subsequent lung injury is therefore of major importance. Here we discuss the present status of antibiotic therapy for the major pathogens in CF airways, including prophylaxis against infection, eradication of early infection, suppression of chronic infection, and the treatment of infective exacerbations. We outline measures to optimize maintenance treatment for infection ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>