<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:31:07" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:31:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/googya/article/451495</link><title>How Race Is Lived in America: Pulling Together, Pulling Apart</title><description>The Assembly of God Tabernacle in Decatur, Georgia, has succeeded at doing what most institutions in America have failed at--achieving full integration. White parishioners who thought of blacks in the worst terms in the past have now decided that all believers--black and white--are going to the same heaven, so they might as well get used to it here on earth. After a black man hugs an elderly white woman, he says, "Man, 30 or 40 years ago I would have been ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:32:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kslibrarian/article/4602</link><title>Emergent Skills in Higher Education:</title><description>New models and strategies have been on trial for the advantage of emerging information and communication technologies over the last decades. Among these, a particular group of technologies impacts the way time and space constraints are now consider. Additionally, the information and knowledge society requires new skills to both the professional and the learner. In particular, considering a higher education context, the need to deal with change, innovation and evolving models of competition and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:33:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/H-Arrietaumn/article/1469748</link><title>Taking the fossil out of fossil fuel</title><description>In the rolling farm country of central New York state, the cicadas buzz, the barn swallows swoop and the natural gas hisses. Covered from head to toe in a baggy blue safety suit, Jennifer McIntosh, a geochemist from the University of Arizona in Tucson, leans over a rusty wellhead as she extracts a sample. A moment later the hissing stops and a small silver canister, now full of gas, is unfastened and packed away, ready for the lab. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:34:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chvlyl/article/5842862</link><title>How To Choose a Good Scientific Problem</title><description>Choosing good problems is essential for being a good scientist. But what is a good problem, and how do you choose one? The subject is not usually discussed explicitly within our profession. Scientists are expected to be smart enough to figure it out on their own and through the observation of their teachers. This lack of explicit discussion leaves a vacuum that can lead to approaches such as choosing problems that can give results that merit publication in valued journals, resulting ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:35:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/christopherweal/article/6074029</link><title>The New York Times Guide to the Best 1,000 Movies Ever Made, Updated &amp; Revised (Film Critics of the New York Times)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:36:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scis0000001/article/819265</link><title>Http://www.merl.com</title><description>This paper identifies a broad class of nonlinear dimensionality reduced (NLDR) problems where the exact local isometry between an extrinsically curved data manifold M and a low-dimensional parameterization space can be recovered from a finite set of high-dimensional point sampels. The method, Geodesic Nullsapce Analysis (GNA), rests on two results: First, the exact isometric parameterization of a local point clique on M haas an algebraic reduction to arc-length integrations when the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:37:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1334722</link><title>Class Matters</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;The acclaimed &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; series on social class in America—and its implications for the way we live our lives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; We Americans have long thought of ourselves as unburdened by class distinctions. We have no hereditary aristocracy or landed gentry, and even the poorest among us feel that they can become rich through education, hard work, or sheer gumption. And yet social class remains a powerful force in American life. &lt;br&gt; In &lt;i&gt;Class ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:38:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/orm/article/488951</link><title>High Performance Discovery in Time Series: Techniques and Case Studies (Monographs in Computer Science)</title><description>Time-series data—data arriving in time order, or a data stream—can be found in fields such as physics, finance, music, networking, and medical instrumentation. Designing fast, scalable algorithms for analyzing single or multiple time series can lead to scientific discoveries, medical diagnoses, and perhaps profits. High Performance Discovery in Time Series presents rapid-discovery techniques for finding portions of time series with many events (i.e., gamma-ray scatterings) and finding closely related time series (i.e., highly correlated price and return histories, or musical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:39:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Mharrison625/article/8071364</link><title>Learning How to Learn: Implications for Non Traditional Adult Students</title><description>In this article, learning how to learn for non traditional adult students is discussed with a focus on police officers and firefighters. Learning how to learn is particularly relevant for all returning non-traditional adults; however in the era of terrorism it is critical for the public safety officers returning to college after years of absence from the pedagogy classroom to be successful. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:41:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zchen75/article/7822694</link><title>A tale of two obesCities: the role of municipal governance in reducing childhood obesity in New York City and London.</title><description>As rates of childhood obesity and overweight rise around the world, researchers and policy makers seek new ways to reverse these trends. Given the concentration of the world's population, income inequalities, unhealthy diets, and patterns of physical activity in cities, urban areas bear a disproportionate burden of obesity. To address these issues, in 2008, researchers from the City University of New York and London Metropolitan ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>