<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7105">dark knight rises dvd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:42:19" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:42:27">http://www.citeulike.org/group/394/article/349725</link><title>Dark Energy Survey and Camera</title><description>We describe the Dark Energy Survey and Camera. The survey will image 5000 sq. deg. in the southern sky to collect 300 million galaxies, 30,000 galaxy clusters, and 2000 Type Ia supernovae. We expect to derive a value for the dark energy equation of state parameter, w, to a precision of 5% by combining four distinct measurement techniques. We describe the mosaic camera, which will consist of CCDs with enhanced sensitivity in the near infrared. The camera will be mounted at the prime focus of the 4-m Blanco ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:43:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/susannah/article/5429104</link><title>Switching between memory and perception: moving attention or memory retrieval?</title><description>Weber, Burt, and Noll (1986) estimated that the time needed to switch attention between memory and perception was around 300 msec. The first two experiments in the present paper estimated switching time using a variation of their task. Subjects reported aloud lists of six items. The items were read off a computer screen (perception), recited from memory, or reported alternately from the two sources. The data show that the switching-time estimate is influenced by input/output compatibility, response-initiation times, and memory load. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:44:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eme/article/349727</link><title>The Dark Energy Survey</title><description>We describe the Dark Energy Survey (DES), a proposed optical-near infrared survey of 5000 sq. deg of the South Galactic Cap to ~24th magnitude in SDSS griz, that would use a new 3 sq. deg CCD camera to be mounted on the Blanco 4-m telescope at Cerro Telolo Inter-American Observatory (CTIO). The survey data will allow us to measure the dark energy and dark matter densities and the dark energy equation of state through four independent methods: galaxy clusters, weak gravitational lensing tomography, galaxy angular clustering, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:45:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dir289/article/777721</link><title>Are Returns to Investment Lower for the Poor? Human and Physical Capital Interactions in Rural Vietnam</title><description>If the gains from investment depend on knowledge, but households cannot hire skills, then poorly educated households will achieve lower returns than educated ones. If the income-poor are less well educated, then they will also have lower returns to investment. The paper tests this argument for the case of irrigation in Vietnam, a setting where existing irrigation can be treated as exogenous at the household level with appropriate controls for the determinants of facility placement. Strong complementarities between household education and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:47:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arnalte/article/11616285</link><title>Large Synoptic Survey Telescope: Dark Energy Science Collaboration</title><description>This white paper describes the LSST Dark Energy Science Collaboration (DESC), whose goal is the study of dark energy and related topics in fundamental physics with data from the Large Synoptic Survey Telescope (LSST). It provides an overview of dark energy science and describes the current and anticipated state of the field. It makes the case for the DESC by laying out a robust analytical framework for dark energy science that has been defined by its members and the comprehensive three-year work plan they have developed for implementing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:48:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Makris/article/4258923</link><title>DVD, Video and Reaching Audiences: Experiments in Moving-Image Distribution</title><description>The advent of the internet (as a means of marketing and selling) and DVD (as a delivery medium) has revitalized interest in selling/delivering alternative' moving image work direct to the public. The potential these avenues offer for reaching wider audiences are proving particularly attractive in the light of the recent UNESCO Convention on Cultural Diversity. However, similar initiatives were undertaken when VHS took off as a mass delivery medium in the 1980s. This article examines some of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:49:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/markoffkin/article/5780741</link><title>Dynamics of encoding in neuron populations: some general mathematical features.</title><description>The use of a population dynamics approach promises efficient simulation of large assemblages of neurons. Depending on the issues addressed and the degree of realism incorporated in the simulated neurons, a wide range of different population dynamics formulations can be appropriate. Here we present a common mathematical structure that these various formulations share and that implies dynamical behaviors that they have in common. This underlying structure serves as a guide toward efficient means of simulation. As an example, we derive the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:50:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lognormal/article/4254156</link><title>1</title><description>In this paper, we consider the asymptotic behaviour of regression estimators that minimize the residual sum of squares plus a penalty proportional to P jfi j j fl for some fl? 0. These estimators include the Lasso (Tibshirani, 1996) as a special case when fl = 1. Under appropriate conditions, we show that the limiting distributions can have positive probability mass at 0 when the true value of the parameter is 0. We also consider asymptotics for &amp;quot;nearly singular &amp;quot; designs. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:51:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pauljohn32/article/5444128</link><title>The Unions and the Democrats: An Enduring Alliance (ILR Press books)</title><description>Although labor unions have faced a decline in membership in recent decades, they have not necessarily lost their political clout. This timely book illuminates the inner dynamics of labor's relationship to the American political system over the past generation. It examines organized labor from the Johnson administration to the end of Clinton's first term, showing that labor's alliance with the Democratic Party has endured despite changes in the economy and the revival of conservatism. Drawing on extensive interviews with union leaders and lobbyists, Taylor E. Dark provides a historical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7105-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7105_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:52:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/simifilm/article/200809</link><title>The Futurians: The story of the science fiction "family" of the 30's that produced today's top SF writers and editors</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>