<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:05:04" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:05:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/celest1982/article/3123988</link><title>Discovering generalized episodes using minimal occurrences</title><description>Sequences of events are an important special form of data that arises in several contexts, including telecommunications, user interface studies, and epidemiology. We present a general and flexible framework of specifying classes of generalized episodes. These are recurrent combinations of events satisfying certain conditions. The framework can be instantiated to a wide variety of applications by selecting suitable primitive conditions. We present algorithms for discovering frequently occurring episodes and episode rules. The algorithms are based on the use of minimal occurrences ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:06:14">http://www.citeulike.org/group/8946/article/955097</link><title>Comparison of the Grimm 1.108 and 1.109 Portable Aerosol Spectrometer to the TSI 3321 Aerodynamic Particle Sizer for Dry Particles</title><description>This study compared the response of two optical particle counters with that of an aerodynamic particle sizer. The optical particle counters rely on the amount of incident light scattered at 90° by a particle to measure particle number concentration by optical particle size. Two models of optical particle counters from Grimm Technologies were used: the portable aerosol spectrometer (PAS) 1.108 (0.3–20 µm in 15 channels); and the PAS 1.109 (0.2–20 µm in 30 size channels). With a substantially different operating principle ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:07:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4447711</link><title>Asymmetry in siRNA design</title><description>Asymmetry in siRNA design Gene Therapy advance online publication, April 30, 2009. doi:10.1038/gt.2009.45 Author: D Grimm ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:08:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rlang/article/9339387</link><title>What Constitutes an Episode in Episodic Memory?</title><description>The idea of episodic memory implies the existence of a process that segments experience into episodes so that they can be stored in memory. It is therefore surprising that the link between event segmentation and the organization of experiences into episodes in memory has not been addressed. We found that after participants read narratives containing temporal event boundaries at varying locations in the narrative, their long-term associative memory for information across event boundaries was lower than their memory for information within ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:09:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fernandohbc/article/1580486</link><title>Discovery of Frequent Episodes in Event Sequences</title><description>Sequences of events describing the behavior and actions of users or systems can be collected in several domains. An episode is a collection of events that occur relatively close to each other in a given partial order. We consider the problem of discovering frequently occurring episodes in a sequence. Once such episodes are known, one can produce rules for describing or predicting the behavior of the sequence. We give efficient algorithms for the discovery of all frequent episodes from a given class of episodes, and present detailed experimental results. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:10:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9263275</link><title>Entrepreneur – Social Entrepreneur – Policy Entrepreneur</title><description>Social Entrepreneurship erlebt eine Renaissance, weil zunehmend auf Methoden und Interaktionsmodi des Unternehmertums zur Lösung sozialer Probleme zurückgegriffen wird. Der soziale Entrepreneur, angetrieben von einer Mission, befriedigt durch sein Verhalten und unternehmerisches Handeln die Nachfrage nach sozialen Leistungen, erzeugt Wertschöpfung und trägt zum gesamtgesellschaftlichen Wandel bei. Grimm argumentiert, dass der Begriffe des sozialen Entrepreneurs auch in der deutschen Debatte klarer umrissen und von konkurrierenden Begriffen abgegrenzt werden muss und schlägt dafür die Typologisierung in Entrepreneurship, Social Entrepreneur und Policy Entrepreneur vor, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:11:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tg1w/article/2030155</link><title>Ten years of individual-based modelling in ecology: what have we learned and what could we learn in the future?</title><description>Each modeller who builds and analyses an individual-based model learns of course a great deal, but what has ecology as a whole learned from the individual-based models published during the last decade? Answering this question proves extremely difficult as there is no common motivation behind individual-based models. The distinction is introduced between ‘pragmatic’ motivation, which uses the individual-based approach as a tool without any reference to the theoretical issues which have emerged from the classical state variable approach and ‘paradigmatic’ motivation, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:12:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/baisemain/article/9247521</link><title>Die deutsche Lexikographie von den Brüdern Grimm bis Trübner</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:13:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5034718</link><title>Stufen der Rechtsstaatlichkeit: Zur Exportfahigkeit einer westlichen Errungenschaft</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7107-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7107_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:15:07">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1415778</link><title>On Enzensberger</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>