<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:16:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:16:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nicolefirst13/article/2187476</link><title>Urinary tract infections in women: diagnosis and management in primary care</title><description>10.1136/bmj.332.7533.94 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:17:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/helen/article/3503358</link><title>Comparing explanations of fertility decline using event history models with unobserved heterogeneity</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:18:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/erisu/article/972713</link><title>Archetypes: Constraint-based Domain Models for Futureproof Information Systems</title><description>Most information systems today are built using “single-level” methodologies, in which both informational and knowledge concepts are built into one level of object and data models. In domains characterised by complexity, large numbers of concepts, and/or a high rate of definitional change, systems based on such models are expensive to maintain and usually have to be replaced after a few years. However, a two-level methodology is possible, in which systems are built from information models only, and driven at runtime by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:19:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mc1975/article/7691178</link><title>From ab initio onwards</title><description>Roberto Car tells Nature Materials how the Car–Parrinello molecular dynamics method originated and how his research career has evolved since then. You studied engineering. What drove you to this choice? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:21:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Hedwig/article/4433927</link><title>Design by calculation and proof</title><description>Expounds a philosophy of engineering design which is stimulated, guided and checked by mathematical calculations and proofs. The philosophy is illustrated by a familiar example, the design of a hardware circuit for addition of natural numbers in binary representation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:22:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/5293899</link><title>The Seattle longitudinal study: relationship between personality and cognition.</title><description>This article reviews the history, measures and principal findings of the Seattle Longitudinal Study. This study began in 1956 focusing upon age differences and age changes in cognitive abilities. Its sampling frame is a large HMO in the Pacific Northwest. The study has been expanded to investigate various influences on cognitive aging including, cognitive styles, personality traits, life styles, and family environment. Current interest is also in the early detection of risk for dementia. In addition, this article reports original analyses ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:23:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3032987</link><title>Characterizing Social Networks using the Sociometer</title><description>Knowledge of how groups of people interact is important in many disciplines, e.g. organizational behavior, social network analysis, knowledge management and ubiquitous computing. Existing studies of social network interactions have either been restricted to online communities, where unambiguous measurements about how people interact can be obtained, or have been forced to rely on questionnaires, or diaries to get data on face-to-face interactions. Survey-based methods are error prone and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:24:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rmangon/article/6044581</link><title>Low complexity voice recognition in car environment</title><description>A low-complexity voice recognition method in a car environment is proposed. Models of noise in the car environment are adaptable in an easy way. Power computation and memory storage for the proposed method are very low. Some real world tests are conducted and show that the proposed voice recognition method has potential for application to car cellular telephones ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:25:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/apwheele/article/11402350</link><title>NEIGHBORHOOD HOUSING INVESTMENTS AND VIOLENT CRIME IN SEATTLE, 1981–2007*</title><description>Despite significant advances in the study of neighborhoods and crime, criminologists have paid surprisingly less attention to the extralocal forces that shape violence. To address this issue, we draw on an emerging body of work that stresses the role of home mortgage lending—a resource secured via interaction with external actors—in reducing neighborhood violence and extend it by addressing concerns that the lending–violence relationship is spurious and confounded by simultaneity. We explore the longitudinal relationship between residential mortgage lending and violence in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:27:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/movervoorde/article/5117548</link><title>Context-aware smart car: from model to prototype</title><description>Abstract  Smart cars are promising application domain for ubiquitous computing. Context-awareness is the key feature of a smart car for safer and easier driving. Despite many industrial innovations and academic progresses have been made, we find a lack of fully context-aware smart cars. This study presents a general architecture of smart cars from the viewpoint of context-awareness. A hierarchical context model is proposed for description of the complex driving environment. A smart car prototype including software platform and hardware infrastructures is built ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>