<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:28:26" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:28:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/googya/article/451495</link><title>How Race Is Lived in America: Pulling Together, Pulling Apart</title><description>The Assembly of God Tabernacle in Decatur, Georgia, has succeeded at doing what most institutions in America have failed at--achieving full integration. White parishioners who thought of blacks in the worst terms in the past have now decided that all believers--black and white--are going to the same heaven, so they might as well get used to it here on earth. After a black man hugs an elderly white woman, he says, "Man, 30 or 40 years ago I would have been ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:29:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/christopherweal/article/6074029</link><title>The New York Times Guide to the Best 1,000 Movies Ever Made, Updated &amp; Revised (Film Critics of the New York Times)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:30:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/H-Arrietaumn/article/1469748</link><title>Taking the fossil out of fossil fuel</title><description>In the rolling farm country of central New York state, the cicadas buzz, the barn swallows swoop and the natural gas hisses. Covered from head to toe in a baggy blue safety suit, Jennifer McIntosh, a geochemist from the University of Arizona in Tucson, leans over a rusty wellhead as she extracts a sample. A moment later the hissing stops and a small silver canister, now full of gas, is unfastened and packed away, ready for the lab. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:31:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/orm/article/488951</link><title>High Performance Discovery in Time Series: Techniques and Case Studies (Monographs in Computer Science)</title><description>Time-series data—data arriving in time order, or a data stream—can be found in fields such as physics, finance, music, networking, and medical instrumentation. Designing fast, scalable algorithms for analyzing single or multiple time series can lead to scientific discoveries, medical diagnoses, and perhaps profits. High Performance Discovery in Time Series presents rapid-discovery techniques for finding portions of time series with many events (i.e., gamma-ray scatterings) and finding closely related time series (i.e., highly correlated price and return histories, or musical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:33:02">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1334722</link><title>Class Matters</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;The acclaimed &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; series on social class in America—and its implications for the way we live our lives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; We Americans have long thought of ourselves as unburdened by class distinctions. We have no hereditary aristocracy or landed gentry, and even the poorest among us feel that they can become rich through education, hard work, or sheer gumption. And yet social class remains a powerful force in American life. &lt;br&gt; In &lt;i&gt;Class ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:34:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eromsted/article/12595658</link><title>Planning and community appearance : report of the Joint Committee on Design Control of the New York Chapter, American Institute of Architects and the New York Regional Chapter, American Institute of Planners, prepared with the cooperation of the Regional Plan Association</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:35:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zchen75/article/7822694</link><title>A tale of two obesCities: the role of municipal governance in reducing childhood obesity in New York City and London.</title><description>As rates of childhood obesity and overweight rise around the world, researchers and policy makers seek new ways to reverse these trends. Given the concentration of the world's population, income inequalities, unhealthy diets, and patterns of physical activity in cities, urban areas bear a disproportionate burden of obesity. To address these issues, in 2008, researchers from the City University of New York and London Metropolitan ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:36:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/antzil/article/2239873</link><title>Best new product development and management practices in the Korean high-tech industry</title><description>This paper investigates critical factors affecting the likelihood of new product success and effective new product development (NPD) models for Korean high-tech firms. Empirical results suggest that successful projects differ from unsuccessful projects in project environment, skills and resources, project leadership, strategic fit, efficient NPD process, and effective product-positioning strategies. This study confirmed that efficient and effective new product development and management were important determinants of high-tech firms' competitive advantage. Furthermore, the findings of this study raised questions about some commonly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:37:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jamgraham88/article/5868379</link><title>The New York Giants</title><description>"Presents the history, accomplishments and key personalities of the New York Giants football team. Includes timelines, quotes, maps, glossary and websites"--Provided by publisher. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:39:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/blind006/article/10450198</link><title>Mobile@game cultures: The place of urban mobile gaming</title><description>As we look over the last decade, the obvious shifts that can be gleaned are the erosions of once distinct categories such as ‘hardcore’ versus ‘casual’ gamer. Instead, we have witnessed an inversion whereby mobile games, once categorized as ‘casual’, became ‘serious’ and now casual again. With the ubiquity of Global Positioning Systems (GPS) and location aware services along with the transformation of the mobile phone into the multi-mode mobile media, the capacity for mobile location-aware games to teach us new ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>