<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7110">civil engineering jobs pennsylvania</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:40:25" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:40:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Schnoggo/article/9636946</link><title>International Conference on Transportation Engineering 2007 proceedings of the First International Conference, July 22-24, 2007, Southwest Jiaotong University, Chengdu, China</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:41:40">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8422214</link><title>Smart sensing, monitoring, and damage detection for civil infrastructures</title><description>In this paper, recent research and application activities on smart sensing, monitoring, and damage detection for civil infrastructures are briefly introduced. Emphasis is given to the activities in Korea. First, the state of the art in smart sensors technology is reviewed including optical fiber sensors, piezoelectric sensors, and wireless sensors. Then, a brief overview is given to the recent advances in the structural monitoring/damage detection techniques such as ambient vibration-based bridge health evaluation, piezoelectric sensors-based local damage detection, wireless sensor networks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:42:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9146133</link><title>Sustainable development and energy geotechnology — Potential roles for geotechnical engineering</title><description>The world is facing unprecedented challenges related to energy resources, global climate change, material use, and waste generation. Failure to address these challenges will inhibit the growth of the developing world and will negatively impact the standard of living and security of future generations in all nations. The solutions to these challenges will require multidisciplinary research across the social and physical sciences and engineering. Although perhaps not always recognized, geotechnical engineering expertise is critical to the solution of many energy and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:44:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Leadingwestafricanscholar/article/3955101</link><title>Private Security Companies and Civil Wars</title><description>Private security companies (PSCs) have experienced explosive growth since 2001, growth that has been matched only by the consequent explosion in academic attention probing their influence. It is not hard to discover that PSCs and their employees constituted the second-largest member of the US-led Coalition of the Willing during the invasion of Iraq in 2003;1 that this represented a 10-fold increase compared with the first Gulf War in 1991;2 that there are between 15,000 and 50,000 contractors currently operating in Iraq, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:45:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abdullahh/article/3501946</link><title>Building a Better Delivery System: A New Engineering/Health Care Partnership</title><description>In a joint effort between the National Academy of Engineering and the Institute of Medicine, this books attempts to bridge the knowledge/awareness divide separating health care professionals from their potential partners in systems engineering and related disciplines. The goal of this partnership is to transform the U.S. health care sector from an underperforming conglomerate of independent entities (individual practitioners, small group practices, clinics, hospitals, pharmacies, community health centers et. al.) into a high performance "system" in which every participating unit recognizes its dependence and influence on every other unit. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:46:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TaniaEiko/article/12116124</link><title>A framework for recommendation in learning object repositories: An example of application in civil engineering</title><description>Learning Object Repositories (LORs) are an important element in the management, publishing, location and retrieval of instructional resources. In recent times, the task of finding and recommending a list of learning objects that fits the specific user’s needs and requirements is a very active area of research. In this regard, this paper proposes DELPHOS, a framework to assist users in the search for learning objects in repositories and which shows an example of application in engineering. LORs can be used in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:47:32">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16681/article/10686659</link><title>Interplay between phononic bandgaps and piezoelectric microstructures for energy harvesting</title><description>The paper introduces a multifunctional structural design combining superior mechanical wave filtering properties and energy harvesting capabilities. The proposed concept is based on the ability of most periodic structures to forbid elastic waves from propagating within specific frequency ranges known as phononic bandgaps. The bandgap density and the resulting filtering effect are dramatically enhanced through the introduction of a microstructure consisting of stiff inclusions which resonate at specific frequencies and produce significant strain and energy localization. Energy harvesting is achieved as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:48:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9268574</link><title>GEP modeling of oxygen transfer efficiency prediction in aeration cascades</title><description>Artificial intelligence is the area of computer science focusing on creating machines that can engage on behaviors that humans consider intelligent. In the past few years, the applications of artificial intelligence methods have attracted the attention of many investigators. Many artificial intelligence methods have been applied in various areas of civil and environmental engineering. The aim of this study is to develop models to estimate oxygen transfer efficiency in nappe, transition and skimming flow regimes over stepped cascades. For this aim, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:50:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TUchida/article/7234835</link><title>Scope and knowledge gap of ecology and civil engineering —Present situation and future dimensions—</title><description>The majority of published papers in ECE were relating to aquatic ecosystems and written by university and/or institute members. Other fields such as terrestrial or coastal ecosystems should be more focused, and consultant and government employee should be encouraged to submit their case studies. As a philosophy and a target of ECE, interdependence between ecology and civil engineering, holistic view of environment, target for restoration, and ecological health were discussed. At investigation and planning stage, life history trait, habitat condition, disturbance, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7110-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7110_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:51:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asilva/article/1445788</link><title>Supporting and monitoring the creativity of IS personnel during the requirements engineering process</title><description>The early stages of the RE process involve developing understanding of a problem situation, the problem domain, and the requirements for achieving improvements in the problem situation. How requirements engineers work to develop this understanding is poorly understood. The findings from several field studies of the RE process show that the process is creative and opportunistic, involving adaptive and responsive exploration of the problem space. The question of how to support and monitor the... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>