<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:52:13" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:52:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10895484</link><title>Mathematics in Context (MiC). What Works Clearinghouse Intervention Report</title><description>"Mathematics in Context" is a middle school mathematics curriculum for grades 5 through 8. It was developed to align with the 1989 National Council of Teachers of Mathematics (NCTM) Curriculum and Evaluation Standards. It is also based on the Dutch Realistic Mathematics Education approach of engaging students in understanding real-life problems and gradually moving to abstract concepts. Rather than focusing on one mathematical domain at a time, "Mathematics in Context" teaches students to explore the relationships among different domains of mathematics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:53:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dabd/article/7290890</link><title>RESTful Web Services Principles of REST Web Service Design Semantic of HTTP/1.1 Operations SOAP vs. REST Style Assets and Drawbacks Security Public Web Services What is REST? Representational State Transfer</title><description>Representation of resource at URI places client in a state Hyperlinks are transitions between states Services itself should be stateless “The name ‘Representational State Transfer ’ is intended to evoke an image of how a well-designed Web application behaves: a network of web pages (a virtual state-machine), where the user progresses through an application by selecting links (state transitions), resulting in the next page (representing the next state of the application) being transferred to the user and rendered for their use.” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:54:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dullhunk/article/7353866</link><title>Inequities exposed in salary survey</title><description>More than 10,500 industrial and academic scientists worldwide completed Nature's salary and satisfaction survey, published in this issue (see page 1104). Here, five career experts comment on the results of the poll. Differences in benefits, mentoring and contentment could have national and international ramifications, they conclude. Kathleen ChristensenDirector, Workplace, Work Force and Working Families programme, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation*On every continent, in every country, where adequate data exist, Nature finds that, 6–10 years after completing PhDs, women scientists are paid less ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:55:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suzelowe/article/4057193</link><title>Middle School Math. What Works Clearinghouse Topic Report</title><description>The What Works Clearinghouse (WWC) reviewed interventions to promote middle school students' math knowledge and skills. Because there is some variation in how school districts organize middle school, we considered curricula aimed at students in grades 6 through 9, covering one or more of the following content areas: numbers and operations, algebra, geometry, measurement, and data analysis and probability. Only core, comprehensive math curricula were eligible for inclusion in this review. These curricula extend over the course of one semester or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:56:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mahler/article/379582</link><title>Describing, Transforming, and Querying Semistructured Data</title><description>eN FROM Person P, Person C, Person G WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.Child = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN Get the phone numbers of Joe's grandchildren. Against the decomposed relations is even worse: four joins SELECT N.PhoneN FROM Person1 P, ChildOf C, ChildOf G, Phone N WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.SSN = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN AND G.Child = N.SSN Objects Allow Simpler Design Schema: Child: SSN ) No need to decompose in order to eliminate redundancy: the set data type takes ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:57:49">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11234141</link><title>Gastroprotective effect of mummy on induced gastric ulcer in rats</title><description>Mummy was used in traditional medicine as a remedy for inflammation, articular injuries, rheumatism, bone fractures, wounds and back pains. In previous research, the healing effects of mummy on a rabbit’s tibial fracture were studied, and the results supported its efficacy. In consideration of claims and suggestions by traditional medicine about the effectiveness of mummy on wound healing, the present study was aimed at investigating the protective effect of mummy on gastric ulcer induced by ethanol. Young male albino rats (NMRI ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:58:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kikimu/article/105595</link><title>Linked: How Everything Is Connected to Everything Else and What It Means</title><description>How is the human brain like the AIDS epidemic? Ask physicist Albert-László Barabási and he'll explain them both in terms of networks of individual nodes connected via complex but understandable relationships. _Linked: The New Science of Networks_ is his bright, accessible guide to the fundamentals underlying neurology, epidemiology, Internet traffic, and many other fields united by complexity. Barabási's gift for concrete, nonmathematical explanations and penchant for eccentric humor would make the book thoroughly enjoyable even if the content weren't engaging. But the results of Barabási's research into the behavior ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:00:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scholz/article/1887420</link><title>A Loyalty Tax? National Measures of Academic Salary Compression</title><description>This paper presents measures of faculty salary compression for 1993 and 1999 based on national, rather than institutional-level, data. Using a recently developed technique and two national faculty surveys, actual junior to senior salary ratios are derived as well as predicted salary ratios that represent what the salary ratios would be if junior and senior faculty were similarly compensated for their productive traits. The analysis, which considers three alternative definitions of junior faculty and stratifies results by institutional type, produces an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:01:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelliskf/article/4116400</link><title>WWC Quick Review of the Article "Promoting Broad and Stable Improvements in Low-Income Children's Numerical Knowledge Through Playing Number Board Games"</title><description>This review examined a study designed to evaluate whether playing number board games improved numeracy skills of low-income preschoolers. The study included 136 pre-school children from 10 urban Head Start centers: 72 children were randomly selected to play a number board game with a trained experimenter; the remaining 64 children played a different version of the game using colors instead of numbers. Numeracy skills were assessed at the end of a two-week period and again nine weeks later. Study authors reported ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:02:26">http://www.citeulike.org/group/3214/article/6854596</link><title>Why is life so exact?</title><description>This is my attempt to answer Schrödinger's question: "What is Life?". In living cell the local combination of atoms is reproduced with incredible accuracy. In the case of protein biosynthesis the notion of the physical aspect of the process can be qualitatively enriched by taking into account the symmetry of conformational oscillations. This is the key to understand the selectivity in biochemistry. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>