<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7115">pittsburgh steelers news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:27:43" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:27:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kdbrown13720/article/5983557</link><title>Santonio Holmes and the Pittsburgh Steelers : Super Bowl XLIII</title><description>Super Bowl XLIII (43) between the Pittsburgh Steelers and the Arizona Cardinals was coming down to the wire. Could Santonio Holmes and his teammates turn this game around? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:27:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ElisaHo/article/485685</link><title>Devastation and Renewal: An Environmental History of Pittsburgh and Its Region (History of the Urban Environment) (History of the Urban Environment)</title><description>Nineteenth- or early twentieth-century visitors to Pittsburgh were frequently shocked by the ways the industrial environment dominated the natural landscape. Steel mills sprawled across hundreds of acres along the rivers. Land and waterways were crisscrossed by dozens of bridges (some carrying molten iron), miles of railroad track, pipelines, and a net of electrical, telephone, and telegraph wires. Pittsburgh's rivers ran brown from the toxic chemicals, sewage, and refuse that filled them. Coal mines, coke ovens, and their huge piles of debris ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:28:13">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13751/article/7532370</link><title>Technology: Software bugs cost big bucks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:28:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zmarty/article/8429198</link><title>Identifying Differences in News Coverage between Cultural/Ethnic Groups</title><description>Large-scale analysis over historical news corpora provides us with unique opportunities to examine sociological issues with respect to local and mass media. In particular, we combine the Lydia named entity recognition system with an name-based ethnicity classification engine to examine issues of ethnic and geocentric sentiment/coverage bias in newspapers. We describe new methods for ethnicity and nationality detection for news entities (people), and build on this to identify interesting temporal, geospatial, and association trends in the coverage with respect to 13 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:28:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MaineC/article/5043997</link><title>Meme-tracking and the dynamics of the news cycle</title><description>Tracking new topics, ideas, and "memes" across the Web has been an issue of considerable interest. Recent work has developed methods for tracking topic shifts over long time scales, as well as abrupt spikes in the appearance of particular named entities. However, these approaches are less well suited to the identification of content that spreads widely and then fades over time scales on the order of days - the time scale at which we perceive news and events. We develop a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:29:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mtkachenko/article/4061692</link><title>Named entity discovery using comparable news articles</title><description>In this paper we describe a way to discover Named Entities by using the distribution of words in news articles. Named Entity recognition is an important task for today's natural language applications, but it still suffers from data sparseness. We used an observation that a Named Entity is likely to appear synchronously in several news articles, whereas a common noun is less likely. Exploiting this characteristic, we successfully obtained rare Named Entities with 90% accuracy just by comparing time series distributions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:29:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brusilovsky/article/939963</link><title>NewsInEssence: summarizing online news topics</title><description>A news delivery and summarization system, acting as a user's agent, gathers and recaps news items based on specifications and interests. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:29:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/toomash/article/305315</link><title>The Market for News</title><description>We investigate the market for news under two assumptions: that readers hold beliefs which they like to see confirmed, and that newspapers can slant stories toward these beliefs. We show that, on the topics where readers share common beliefs, one should not expect accuracy even from competitive media: competition results in lower prices, but common slanting toward reader biases. On topics where reader beliefs diverge (such as politically divisive issues), however, newspapers segment the market and slant toward extreme positions. Yet ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:30:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/denisparra/article/3063532</link><title>News@hand: A Semantic Web Approach to Recommending News</title><description>We present News@hand, a news recommender system which applies semantic-based technologies to describe and relate news contents and user preferences in order to produce enhanced recommendations. The exploitation of conceptual information describing contents and user profiles, along with the capability of inferring knowledge from the semantic relations defined in the ontologies, enabling different content-based collaborative recommendation models, are the key distinctive aspects of the system. The multi-domain portability, the multi-media source applicability, and addressing of some limitations of current recommender systems ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7115-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7115_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:30:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/y5chen/article/11374102</link><title>NEWS ON NEW DEVICES: Is multi-platform news consumption a reality?</title><description>News organizations worldwide now deliver content through multiple electronic devices such as computers, smartphones, e-readers, and tablets. While multi-platform news delivery is widely prevalent, is multi-platform news ?consumption? a reality? This study examines the extent to which people own, use, and enjoy these electronic devices. Results of a national survey of US Internet users suggested that despite the excitement about newer, more portable devices, not all devices are equally ?newsful.? Most people use only one electronic device for news purposes on ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>