<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7116">pumpkin pie recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:29:56" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:30:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zentrification/article/7172746</link><title>Oil and Tocopherol Content and Composition of Pumpkin Seed Oil in 12 Cultivars</title><description>Twelve pumpkin cultivars (Cucurbita maxima D.), cultivated in Iowa, were studied for their seed oil content, fatty acid composition, and tocopherol content. Oil content ranged from 10.9 to 30.9%. Total unsaturated fatty acid content ranged from 73.1 to 80.5%. The predominant fatty acids present were linoleic, oleic, palmitic, and stearic. Significant differences were observed among the cultivars for stearic, oleic, linoleic, and gadoleic acid content of oil. Low linolenic acid levels were observed (&lt;1%). The tocopherol content of the oils ranged ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:31:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zentrification/article/7172743</link><title>Minerals and antinutrients in fluted pumpkin (Telfairia occidentalis Hook f.)</title><description>Studies were conducted to determine the biochemical composition of fluted pumpkin ( Telfairia occidentalis Hook f. ) at different stages of growth. Analyses were carried out at 12 and 50 weeks after planting on stems, leaves and roots, while seeds were analysed 8 and 32 weeks, respectively, after antethesis. Proximate moisture and carbohydrate content decreased in stems, leaves, roots and seeds with age, while ash, crude fibre and crude fat increased with age in stems, leaves, and roots but not in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:32:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zentrification/article/7172745</link><title>Amino Acid, Mineral and Fatty Acid Content of Pumpkin Seeds ( Cucurbita spp ) and Cyperus esculentus Nuts in the Republic of Niger</title><description>Abstract.  Dried seeds and nuts are widely consumed by indigenous populations of the western Sahel, especially those who inhabit rural areas. In light of the need for quantitative information regarding the content of particular nutrients in these plant foods, we collected dried pumpkin (Cucurbita spp) seeds and nuts of Cyperus esculentus in the Republic of Niger and analyzed them for their content of essential amino acids, minerals and trace elements, and fatty acids.On a dry weight basis, pumpkin seed contained 58.8% protein ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:33:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3680722</link><title>The perfect pumpkin pie</title><description>Mr. Wilkerson, lover of pie, returns as a ghost on Halloween to demand some good pie from Jack and his grandmother. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:34:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aprasad/article/1293054</link><title>Evolution of genome size: a phylogenetic test of the DNA loss hypothesis.</title><description>It has been recently suggested that the C-value paradox, the lack of an obvious association between organismal complexity and genome size, can result simply from biases in insertion and deletion rates--the DNA loss hypothesis. This hypothesis has been heavily criticized, particularly because its evidence, a negative relationship between genome size and DNA loss rate, is based on a highly selective use of the available data. In this study it is show that even the even the most favorable interpretation of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:37:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Kerrybot/article/12172730</link><title>Characterization of the Aroma Signature of Styrian Pumpkin Seed Oil (Cucurbita pepo subsp. pepo var. Styriaca) by Molecular Sensory Science</title><description>Application of the aroma extract dilution analysis on a distillate prepared from an authentic Styrian pumpkin seed oil followed by identification experiments led to the characterization of 47 odor-active compounds in the flavor dilution (FD) factor range of 8?8192 among which 2-acetyl-1-pyrroline (roasty, popcorn-like), 2-propionyl-1-pyrroline (roasty, popcorn-like), 2-methoxy-4-vinylphenol (clove-like), and phenylacetaldehyde (honey-like) showed the highest FD factors. Among the set of key odorants, 2-propionyl-1-pyrroline and another 20 odorants were identified for the first time as constituents of pumpkin seed oil. To ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:38:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fungal/article/6144987</link><title>Antifungal Mechanism of a Novel Antifungal Protein from Pumpkin Rinds against Various Fungal Pathogens</title><description>PMID: 19807165 A novel antifungal protein (Pr-2) was identified from pumpkin rinds using water-soluble extraction, ultrafiltration, cation exchange chromatography, and reverse-phase high-performance liquid chromatography. Matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization time-of-flight mass spectrometry indicated that the protein had a molecular mass of 14865.57 Da. Automated Edman degradation showed that the N-terminal sequence of Pr-2 was QGIGVGDNDGKRGKR−. The Pr-2 protein strongly inhibited in vitro growth of Botrytis cinerea, Colletotrichum coccodes, Fusarium solani, Fusarium oxysporum, and Trichoderma harzianum at 10−20 μM. The results of confocal laser ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:39:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/12657690</link><title>Recipe recommendation using ingredient networks</title><description>The recording and sharing of cooking recipes, a human activity dating back thousands of years, naturally became an early and prominent social use of the web. The resulting online recipe collections are repositories of ingredient combinations and cooking methods whose large-scale and variety yield interesting insights about both the fundamentals of cooking and user preferences. At the level of an individual ingredient we measure whether it tends to be essential or can be dropped or added, and whether its quantity can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:40:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bamberg/article/1177180</link><title>The CMU Pose, Illumination, and Expression (PIE) database</title><description>Between October 2000 and December 2000, we collected a database of over 40,000 facial images of 68 people. Using the CMU (Carnegie Mellon University) 3D Room, we imaged each person across 13 different poses, under 43 different illumination conditions, and with four different expressions. We call this database the CMU Pose, Illumination and Expression (PIE) database. In this paper, we describe the imaging hardware, the collection procedure, the organization of the database, several potential uses of the database, and how to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7116-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7116_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:41:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shtrom/article/12446712</link><title>PIE: A Lightweight Control Scheme To Address the Bufferbloat Problem</title><description>Bufferbloat is a phenomenon where excess buffers in the network cause high latency and jitter. As more and more interactive applications (e.g. voice over IP, real time video streaming and financial transactions) run in the Internet, high latency and jitter degrade application performance. There is a pressing need to design intelligent queue management schemes that can control latency and jitter; and hence provide desirable quality of service to users. We present here a lightweight design, PIE(Proportional Integral controller Enhanced) that can ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>