<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:54:59" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:55:05">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/71362</link><title>On Semantic and Type-Theoretic</title><description>This thesis strives to combine two traditions in theoretical computer science: complexity theory and denotational semantics. The recently proposed setting of game semantics, which provided rst syntax-independent fully abstract models of many programming languages, is used to characterize the polynomial-time computable functions as those de nable by a certain kind of strategies in two-player games. In particular, players must comply with a network protocol that structures the exchange of moves ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:56:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jpb1301/article/10201701</link><title>Patient survey, City Hospital Birmingham, Emergency Department and Urgent Care Centre.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:57:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/seongkilee/article/5661923</link><title>Automated 3-D Reconstruction of Buildings and Visualization of City Models</title><description>This paper describes current research activities at ETH Zurich in automated 3-D reconstruction of buildings and their photo realistic visualization within the context of 3-D city models. Two conceptually different approaches to building reconstruction are presented: TOBAGO and ARUBA. The first approach is semi-automatic and aims at the automatic structuring of manually measured 3-D point clouds to generate (Auto-) CAD models of complete buildings. It is geared towards a reliable and flexible procedure which has a large potential to be useful ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:58:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/y4su0/article/278430</link><title>Time-series analysis of clusters in city size distributions</title><description>Complex systems, such as urban systems, emerge unpredictably without the influence of central control as a result of adaptive behaviour by their component, interacting agents. This paper analyses city size distributions, by decade, from the south-western region of the United States for the years 18901990. It determines if the distributions were clustered and documents changes in the pattern of clusters over time. Clusters were determined utilising a kernel density estimator and cluster analysis. The data were clustered as determined by both ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:59:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelbr11/article/11689406</link><title>The Dropout Crisis: Promising Approaches in Prevention and Recovery</title><description>The number of high school age students who do not complete high school is receiving increased attention as a serious challenge facing the educational system. This is happening for several reasons. New research estimates that about 30 percent of high school students fail to earn a diploma in the standard number of years, a higher figure than state and local education officials typically cite. In many states, barely half of African-Americans and Latinos graduate from high school. The magnitude of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:01:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dglp/article/305955</link><title>`The city' as perverse metaphor</title><description>So ‘city’ is used in very different senses in many discussions, in fact in a multiplicity of different senses. In them ‘city’ stands for a variety of different concepts,7 can be a euphemism for quite varied content, can, in its usage, conceal a whole set of controversial assumptions. Political implications are embedded in many of these usages, strongly in those that are listed below. Other formulations, discussed elsewhere (see Marcuse, 2005), while not as politically loaded, reflect a lack of clarity in what precisely is meant by</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:02:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/814943</link><title>A case study in the globalization of jobs in Ireland</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:03:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joseluismartinez/article/2129924</link><title>1. Marxism and the City?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:04:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joseluismartinez/article/2129918</link><title>7. Remapping the City</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:05:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joseluismartinez/article/5661419</link><title>The 'Right to the City' in the context of shifting mottos of urban social movements</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>