<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:06:57" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:07:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tybert/article/657914</link><title>Mood state effects of chocolate</title><description>Chocolate consumption has long been associated with enjoyment and pleasure. Popular claims confer on chocolate the properties of being a stimulant, relaxant, euphoriant, aphrodisiac, tonic and antidepressant. The last claim stimulated this review. We review chocolate's properties and the principal hypotheses addressing its claimed mood altering propensities. We distinguish between food craving and emotional eating, consider their psycho-physiological underpinnings, and examine the likely ‘positioning’ of any effect of chocolate to each concept. Chocolate can provide its own hedonistic reward ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:08:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tybert/article/7203634</link><title>Dark chocolate: consumption for pleasure or therapy?</title><description>Traditional chocolate is derived from the cocoa bean, which is one of the most concentrated sources of flavanols, a subgroup of the natural antioxidant plant compounds called flavonoids. Accumulating evidence from the past 10 years demonstrates that moderate consumption of chocolate, especially dark chocolate, may exert protective effects against the development of cardiovascular disease. Several mechanisms have been proposed to explain this positive influence, including metabolic, antihypertensive, anti-inflammatory, and anti-thrombotic effects, as well as effects on insulin sensitivity and vascular endothelial ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:09:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12884947</link><title>Chocolate/cocoa and human health: a review.</title><description>Chocolate/cocoa has been known for its good taste and proposed health effects for centuries. Earlier, chocolate used to be criticised for its fat content and its consumption was a sin rather than a remedy, associated with acne, caries, obesity, high blood pressure, coronary artery disease and diabetes. Therefore, many physicians tended to warn patients about the potential health hazards of consuming large amounts of chocolate. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:10:16">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18283/article/12698862</link><title>Quality characteristics of chocolate – Containing some fat replacer</title><description>Chocolate products are the most important products of candy that are popular with a lot, especially children and as a source of energy in addition to its high nutritional value. In chocolate industry, many of ingredients such as cocoa, sugar, cocoa butter, fats, emulsifiers and flavorings play an important role in product quality. This research aims to assess the fatty replacement and its impact on the organoleptic and rheological characteristics of chocolate for the treatment of some problems that arise during ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:11:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/paaoolaa/article/12698919</link><title>Modelling crystal polymorphisms in chocolate processing</title><description>Efforts have been devoted over the last decades towards modelling phase change kinetics of fats in chocolate. The fats in chocolate have a number of polymorphic forms and manufacturers must deliver a product with the right polymorph to the consumer. In this work a model was developed that contains only two polymorphs rather than the six polymorphs that can be identified using Differential Scanning Calorimetry (DSC) and X-Ray Diffraction (XRD). This simplification allowed the phase change kinetics to be estimated from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:12:17">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18283/article/9690816</link><title>Mycobiota of cocoa: From farm to chocolate</title><description>The present work was carried out to study the mycobiota of cocoa beans from farm to chocolate. Four hundred and ninety-four samples were analyzed at various stages of cocoa processing: (i) primary stage at the farm (fermentation, drying, and storage), (ii) secondary stage at processing (testa, nibs, liquor, butter, cake and powder) and (iii) the final chocolate product (dark, milk, white and powdered) collected from retail outlets. Direct plating or dilution plating on Dichloran 18% Glycerol agar were used for cocoa ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:13:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12847395</link><title>Association between chocolate consumption and fatness in European adolescents.</title><description>There is a substantial interest in the potential role of chocolate in the prevention of cardiovascular diseases. It has been recently reported that a higher frequency of chocolate intake is linked to lower body mass index (BMI) in adults. The aim of the present study was to determine if higher chocolate consumption also is associated with lower BMI, as well as other markers of total ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:14:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/paaoolaa/article/12698898</link><title>Influence of phytosterols addition in the rheology and sensory attributes of dark chocolate</title><description>This study evaluated the influence of the application of three types of phytosterols (A- encapsulated pine phytosterol powder; B- oil-based soy phytosterol and C-powder soy phytosterol) in the rheological and sensory properties of dark chocolate. It was observed that the application of phytosterols influenced the rheological properties of the chocolates, mainly the A and C types. On the other hand, the rheological behaviour of the chocolate with B phytosterol was similar to the standard chocolate. In the sensory evaluation, the chocolates ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:15:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/starinetie/article/2163584</link><title>Dark Chocolate Improves Coronary Vasomotion and Reduces Platelet Reactivity</title><description>Background Dark chocolate has potent antioxidant properties. Coronary atherosclerosis is promoted by impaired endothelial function and increased platelet activation. Traditional risk factors, high oxidative stress, and reduced antioxidant defenses play a crucial role in the pathogenesis of atherosclerosis, particularly in transplanted hearts. Thus, flavonoid-rich dark chocolate holds the potential to have a beneficial impact on graft atherosclerosis. Methods and Results We assessed the effect of flavonoid-rich dark chocolate compared with cocoa-free control chocolate on coronary vascular and platelet function in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:16:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/karenkew/article/9987259</link><title>Sensory Analysis of Leading Chocolate Brands in Belgium, the United Kingdom and Poland</title><description>Abstract By taste panel approach the perception of chocolate was measured and analysed. Different types of Belgian, English and Polish solid chocolate bars were evaluated according to organoleptic attributes and package characteristics. Trials in the assessment of the approximate preferences of consumers were undertaken. Methodology applied consisted of discriminatory tests, to check the panelists' ability for sensory recognition, and descriptive tests used for training the assessors, to obtain the panel of experts and also for the assessment of chocolate characteristics. Preferences ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>