<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7120">tortellini pasta salad</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:17:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:17:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tomste/article/9915401</link><title>Salad and satiety. The effect of timing of salad consumption on meal energy intake</title><description>In a previous study, consuming a fixed amount of low-energy-dense salad as a first course reduced meal energy intake. We investigated whether this effect depended on serving salad before rather than with the main course, or on compulsory rather than ad libitum consumption. On five occasions, 46 women consumed ad libitum a main course of pasta, accompanied four times by low-energy-dense salad (300 g; 100 kcal [418 kJ]). At two meals the salad was served 20 min before the pasta (once ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:18:48">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18172/article/7616066</link><title>Rice-based pasta: A comparison between conventional pasta-making and extrusion-cooking</title><description>Good quality gluten-free products continue to be in demand among the celiac community and the production of pasta from non-conventional raw materials is a major technological challenge. In this work, the effects of two different pasta-making processes (conventional and extrusion-cooking) were investigated on parboiled brown and milled rice flours. The two processes differentiated for extrusion temperature (conventional extrusion: 50 °C, max; extrusion-cooking: 115 °C), whereas the drying diagram was the same. Starch modifications induced by each pasta-making process were analyzed by using a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:19:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6372384</link><title>Lithologic and diagenetic attributes of the Sharwayn (Maastrichtian) and Umm Er Radhuma (late Paleocene–Eocene) formations and their significance to the K-T unconformity, Jabal Samhan area, Dhofar, Sultanate of Oman</title><description>Abstract  The boundary separating Maastrichtian Sharwayn Formation from late Paleocene Eocene Umm Er Radhuma (UER) Formation in Dhofar, southern Oman, is characterized by a regionally extensive unconformity. The Jabal Samhan escarpment, north of Marbat-Sadh transect, preserves this unconformable boundary. This paper addresses the lithologic and diagenetic differences of the strata across the boundary and discusses their significance and link to the development of the upper Maastrichtian to lower Paleocene unconformity. The upper part of the Sharwayn Formation is characterized by lower thickly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:20:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/filipmarcinowski/article/9114455</link><title>Giuseppe Pasta (1742-1823): protophysician and pioneer of psychological studies in the medical field.</title><description>Giuseppe Pasta was a pioneer of psychological support in physical disease. Born in Bergamo, Italy, he was a cousin of the physician Andrea Pasta who was a pupil of Giovanni Battista Morgagni. Giuseppe's cultural and clinical resources were the teachings of Francesco Redi's medical school in Tuscany. This paper discusses the courage and philosophical tolerance of disease and the etiquette of the physician. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:22:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emaynard/article/9435097</link><title>GROWTH AND COMPOSITION OF SALAD GREENS AS AFFECTED BY ORGANIC COMPARED TO NITRATE FERTILIZER AND BY ENVIRONMENT IN HIGH TUNNELS*</title><description>Form of fertilizer affects composition of salad greens. This response may vary with growth rate or environment during growth. The interaction of environment and form of fertilizer was examined for salad greens grown as successive plantings in unheated high tunnels. Eight species, including eleven plantings of lettuce and spinach, were grown with either a nitrate-based complete soluble fertilizer in perlite or with an organic fertilizer, namely leaf compost: perlite 1&amp;emsp14;:&amp;emsp14;1&amp;emsp14;v/v amended with cottonseed meal. For each species, relative growth rate and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:23:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tomste/article/9001816</link><title>Prediction and measurement of pasta quality</title><description>Summary In the past several years, pasta and noodle products have become a major growth segment of the cereal foods industry. The popularity of pasta can be attributed to its sensory appeal, versatility, low cost, ease of preparation, strong nutritional image and excellent storage stability as well as to increased consumer interest in ethnic foods. Predominant quality attributes of pasta, as they relate to its appearance, flavour and texture, have been described in this review. Because of their importance to consumer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:24:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vanhau/article/1108323</link><title>Poisson versus Periodic Path Probing (or, Does PASTA Matter?)</title><description>The well-known PASTA (“Poisson Arrivals See Time Averages”) property states that, under very general conditions, the fraction of Poisson arrivals that observe an underlying process in a particular state is equal, asymptotically, to the fraction of time the process spends in that state. When applied to network inference, PASTA implies that a Poisson probing stream provides an unbiased estimate of the desired time average. Our objective is to examine the practical significance of the PASTA property in the context of realistic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:25:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/255395</link><title>The history of the book and publishing in eighteenth-century Italy</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:26:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tomste/article/8230259</link><title>Nutritional and Physicochemical Characteristics of Dietary Fiber Enriched Pasta</title><description>The relationship between pasta texture and physicostructural characteristics was determined in relation to potential starch degradation and subsequent glucose release. Pastas with added soluble and insoluble dietary fiber ingredients were evaluated in relation to biochemical composition, cooking properties, and textural characteristics. Results show that both the type and amount of added fiber influence the overall quality of both raw and cooked pasta. Glucose release may be significantly reduced by the addition of soluble dietary fiber. Keywords: Dietary fiber; nonstarch polysaccharides; starch; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7120-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7120_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:27:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tomste/article/9561299</link><title>Mini Review Pasta brownness: An Assessment</title><description>Pasta colour is an essential factor in assessing pasta quality. It results from a desirable yellow component, an undesirable brown component and, under some drying conditions, a red component. The cause of pasta brownness is complex and its biochemical and technological basis is still a matter of controversy. This paper is a comprehensive review of the literature data in the light of results which have been recently obtained in our laboratory. Pasta brightness (L) is an indicator of the attenuation of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>