<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:28:52" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:29:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mstepien/article/4043229</link><title>Stroke--1989. Recommendations on stroke prevention, diagnosis, and therapy. Report of the WHO Task Force on Stroke and other Cerebrovascular Disorders.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:30:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/4928592</link><title>World Health Organization: Tumours of the Breast and Female Genital Organs (Who/IARC Classification of Tumours) (IARC WHO Classification of Tumours)</title><description>This WHO classification covers the female and male breast, ovaries, fallopian tumours, uterine cervix, uterine corpus, vulva, vagina and inherited tumour syndromes. It includes a comprehensive classification of benign and malignant neoplasms. Targeted readership includes pathologists, gynaecologists, surgeons, oncologists, and basic scientists. Similar to the previous volumes of the series, the book includes numerous colour photographs, magnetic resonance images, CT scans and charts. In addition to its pathology and genetics, each lesion is described with its epidemiology, etiology, clinical features, as well as prognosis and predictive factors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:31:18">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16635/article/5369850</link><title>Prevalence, Severity, and Unmet Need for Treatment of Mental Disorders in the World Health Organization World Mental Health Surveys</title><description>Context Little is known about the extent or severity of untreated mental disorders, especially in less-developed countries. Objective To estimate prevalence, severity, and treatment of Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, Fourth Edition (DSM-IV) mental disorders in 14 countries (6 less developed, 8 developed) in the World Health Organization (WHO) World Mental Health (WMH) Survey Initiative. Design, Setting, and Participants Face-to-face household surveys of 60 463 community adults conducted from 2001-2003 in 14 countries in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:32:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/marceloreis/article/8377749</link><title>Reviewed work(s): An Annotated Bibliography of Sir Richard Francis Burton. by Norman M. Penzer</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:33:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/9179680</link><title>High Speed Downlink Packet Access (HSDPA)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:34:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ce_oenema/article/8194923</link><title>Transparency and e-Voting:</title><description>Electronic voting systems are being introduced, and have been introduced, in many countries for a variety of reasons. The introduction of computers into the electoral process can offer several advantages. Among other things it can speed up the process of calculating results, can help voters avoid accidentally spoiling their vote, and can allow voters with special needs to vote in private. Often, however, little consideration is given to the potential negative effects of electronic voting. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:35:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kalenablaxicanwilliams/article/9025229</link><title>Teacher Education for Cultural Diversity: Enhancing the Capacity of Teacher Education Institutions To Address Diversity Issues.</title><description>This document reports on portions of a study on "Teacher Education for Diversity" in progress since 1990. The overall study includes an ongoing analysis of relevant literature, which has generated a conceptual framework describing the range of existing positions on teacher education for cultural diversity. The study includes the development of three case studies of exemplary programs employing different organizational arrangements and instructional strategies that contravene or compensate for the cultural insularity of teacher education faculty. The specific concern reported in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:37:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chaspir/article/5429611</link><title>Assessment of fracture risk and its application to screening for postmenopausal osteoporosis: Synopsis of a WHO report</title><description>The criteria required for an effective screening strategy for osteoporosis are largely met in Caucasian women. The disease is common and readily diagnosed by the measurement of bone mineral with single- or dual-energy absorptiometry. Such measurements have high specificity but lower sensitivity, so that the value of the technique is greater for those identified as being at higher risk. Against this background there is little evidence that osteoporosis can usefully be tackled by a public health policy to influence risk factors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:38:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/valeriobal/article/8014033</link><title>Contrat de bon usage des m?dicaments et m?decine nucl?aire</title><description>Le contrat de bon usage du médicament est un contrat d’adhésion entre un établissement de santé et l’Agence régionale de santé fixant des objectifs à atteindre en vue de sécuriser le circuit du médicament et de garantir leur bon usage. Ce contrat, établi normalement par chaque établissement depuis 2006, poursuit trois objectifs principaux qui sont d’améliorer et de sécuriser le circuit du médicament, des dispositifs médicaux et des prestations, de favoriser et garantir les pratiques pluridisciplinaires ou en réseau et enfin ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7121-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7121_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:39:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7971791</link><title>M?tastases osseuses tardives d?un ph?ochromocytome</title><description>Le phéochromocytome est une tumeur dérivée du tissu chromaffine, habituellement bénigne (90 % des cas). Nous rapportons l’observation d’un patient de 77 ans opéré d’un phéochromocytome considéré initialement à tort comme « bénin » et présentant des métastases osseuses cinq ans plus tard, diagnostiquées par biopsie. Un traitement associant radiothérapie et interféron permettait de stabiliser les lésions. La possibilité de métastases tardives au cours du phéochromocytome doit être connue. Pheochromocytoma is a usually benign tumor of chromaffin tissue (90 % of cases). We report a 77-year-old ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>