<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7122">horse dog pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:40:02" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:40:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dswan/article/7539591</link><title>PICS: probabilistic inference for ChIP-seq.</title><description>ChIP-seq combines chromatin immunoprecipitation with massively parallel short-read sequencing. While it can profile genome-wide in vivo transcription factor-DNA association with higher sensitivity, specificity, and spatial resolution than ChIP-chip, it poses new challenges for statistical analysis that derive from the complexity of the biological systems characterized and from variability and biases in its sequence data. We propose a method called PICS (Probabilistic Inference for ChIP-seq) for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:41:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/noah977/article/4786119</link><title>Searching for Positive Returns at the Track: A Multinomial Logit Model for Handicapping Horse Races</title><description>This paper investigates fundamental investment strategies to detect and exploit the public's systematic errors in horse race wager markets. A handicapping model is developed and applied to win-betting in the pari-mutuel system. A multinomial logit model of the horse racing process is posited and estimated on a data base of 200 races. A recently developed procedure for exploiting the information content of rank ordered choice sets is employed to obtain more efficient parameter estimates. The variables in this discrete choice probability ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:41:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LaszloKulcsar/article/11282322</link><title>Socio-economic impact of horse production on rural areas: a comparison between Ireland and France Forages and grazing in horse nutrition</title><description>In the European Union, the horse industry is growing and evolving and has various impacts on areas that are still unknown. The horse has an economic and social significance and contributes to the maintenance of landscapes and to the dynamism of rural economies. This paper provides a review of the research that has been conducted on this topic in France and Ireland. In these two countries, the horse industry is growing. In France, the horse industry is represented by almost a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:43:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dchughes/article/2245671</link><title>Molecular analysis using mitochondrial DNA and microsatellites to infer the formation process of Japanese native horse populations.</title><description>To assess the genetic diversity of Japanese native horse populations, we examined seven such populations using mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) and microsatellite analyses. Four reference populations of Mongolian horses and European breeds were employed as other equids. In the mtDNA analysis, the control region (D-loop) of 411 bp was sequenced, and 12 haplotypes with 33 variable sites were identified in the Japanese native horses. The phylogenetic tree constructed by haplogrouping and using worldwide geographic references indicated that the haplotypes of the Japanese ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:44:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LukeDunstan/article/13127570</link><title>The Best Laid Plans of Mice and Men</title><description>An abstract is not available. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:45:17">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7410606</link><title>A Defense of Animal Rights</title><description>Abstract  I argue that animals have rights in the sense of having valid claims, which might turn out to be actual rights as society advances and new scientific-technological developments facilitate finding alternative ways of satisfying our vital interests without using animals. Animals have a right to life, to liberty in the sense of freedom of movement and communication, to subsistence, to relief from suffering, and to security against attacks on their physical existence. Animals’ interest in living, freedom, subsistence, and security are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:46:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LaszloKulcsar/article/11282337</link><title>Territories and grassland exploitation by horses in France Forages and grazing in horse nutrition</title><description>France is the first European country with regard to its agricultural area, and the second after Great Britain, for its permanent grasslands. With nearly a million of horses, this sector is the only French animal production which has been constantly developing for many years. Consequently, equestrian activities occupy a growing part of land in France with a presence in urban as well as agricultural areas or in highly environmental zones. Socio-economic and environmental researches have recently been developed in this country ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:47:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gdmcbain/article/12653058</link><title>PICS 2000: Image Processing, Image Quality, Image Capture, Systems Conference</title><description>IS&amp;T's pictorial imaging conference, focusing particularly on digital photography, is organized into Systems, Image Quality and Image Processing. Systems papers de3scribe performanhce of key subsystems required to capture or print pictures. The quality track brings together papers on the design of good image quality metrics, methods of measuring them and their applicaiton to complete systems. Image processing papers deal with halftoning, algorithms for reducing artifacts that degrade image quality, and some describe use of image processing to deliver features to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:48:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dchughes/article/3420831</link><title>The Legacy of Domestication: Accumulation of Deleterious Mutations in the Dog Genome</title><description>Dogs exhibit more phenotypic variation than any other mammal and are affected by a wide variety of genetic diseases. However, the origin and genetic basis of this variation is still poorly understood. We examined the effect of domestication on the dog genome by comparison with its wild ancestor, the gray wolf. We compared variation in dog and wolf genes using whole-genome single nucleotide polymorphism (SNP) data. The dN/dS ratio (omega) was around 50% greater for SNPs found in dogs than in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7122-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7122_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:49:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardcj/article/405867</link><title>Characterization of candidate genes for neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis in dog.</title><description>The neuronal ceroid lipofuscinoses (NCL) are a heterogenous group of monogenic autosomal recessive inherited progressive neurodegenerative diseases characterized by brain and retinal atrophy and the intracellular accumulation of autofluorescent lysosomal storage bodies resembling lipofuscin in neurons and other cells. Until today, eight forms of NCL have been classified in humans by clinical criteria, which result from mutations in at least six different genes (TPP1, CLN2, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>