<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:51:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:51:14">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13341/article/9274012</link><title>Promoting bike-and-ride: The Dutch experience</title><description>The number of policy initiatives to promote the use of bike-and-ride, or the combined use of bicycle and public transport for one trip, has grown considerably over the past decade as part of the search for more sustainable transport solutions. This paper discusses the experiences with, and impacts of, such initiatives in the Netherlands. The Dutch measures to promote bicycle use in access trips have been generally successful. A country-wide program to upgrade regular and secure bicycle parking at train stations ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:52:15">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5383114</link><title>Politics and the People in Revolutionary Russia: A Provincial History</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:53:28">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6827180</link><title>Political Marginalization, Climate Change, and Conflict in African Sahel States</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:54:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8713516</link><title>Seeing the Forest for the Trees: Does Physical Geography Affect a State's Conflict Risk?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:55:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/6rheology/article/6748988</link><title>Electrohydrodynamic lubrication with thin double layers</title><description>Sliding of one charged body past another in an electrolyte solution induces a streaming potential in the fluid between the surfaces which in turn generates an electrokinetic force on the bodies. In this paper, we extend our previous lubrication analysis for bodies bearing thin double layers from two-dimensional to three-dimensional flows and to squeezing as well as sliding motion. A general differential equation for the streaming potential is derived which is analogous to Reynolds' equation for pressure. When the double layer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:56:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/qwermish/article/3041600</link><title>Making Cycling Irresistible: Lessons from The Netherlands, Denmark and Germany</title><description>This article shows how the Netherlands, Denmark and Germany have made bicycling a safe, convenient and practical way to get around their cities. The analysis relies on national aggregate data as well as case studies of large and small cities in each country. The key to achieving high levels of cycling appears to be the provision of separate cycling facilities along heavily travelled roads and at intersections, combined with traffic calming of most residential neighbourhoods. Extensive cycling rights of way in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:58:05">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9936605</link><title>The search for safety: The effects of conflict, poverty and ecological influences on migration in the developing world</title><description>This article discusses how conflict patterns affect the volume, direction and types of migration within the developing world. Conflict impact and poverty are the two primary drivers directly shaping migrations within poor and high-risk environments. Indirect drivers of migration include livelihood fragility, ecological and political instabilities. Conflicts overwhelmingly occur in states where much of the population is dependent upon the environment/natural resources for their livelihoods. There is little reliable evidence to suggest a link between civil conflict and climate change, however, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:59:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8458424</link><title>Vladislav Zubok, Zhivago's Children: The Last Russian Intelligentsia.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:00:25">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10284651</link><title>Rock and Roll in the Rocket City: The West, Identity, and Ideology in Soviet Dniepropetrovsk, 1960–1985 . By Sergei I. Zhuk . Washington, DC: Woodrow Wilson Center Press; Baltimore: Johns Hopkins University Press, 2010. Pp. xx+440. $65.00.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:01:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11826169</link><title>Captives of Revolution: The Socialist Revolutionaries and the Bolshevik Dictatorship, 1918–1923 . By Scott B. Smith . Pitt Series in Russian and East European Studies. Edited by Jonathan Harris. Pittsburgh: University of Pittsburgh Press, 2011. Pp. xx+380. $45.00.</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>