<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:13:49" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:13:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eduardoalvarez7/article/168828</link><title>Comparison of overweight and obesity prevalence in school-aged youth from 34 countries and their relationships with physical activity and dietary patterns.</title><description>The purposes of this systematic review were to present and compare recent estimates of the prevalence of overweight and obesity in school-aged youth from 34 countries and to examine associations between overweight and selected dietary and physical activity patterns. Data consisted of a cross-sectional survey of 137 593 youth (10-16 years) from the 34 (primarily European) participating countries of the 2001-2002 Health Behaviour in School-Aged ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:14:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/u12081/article/9847740</link><title>Genetics and Nutrigenomics of Obesity Epidemiology of Obesity in Children and Adolescents</title><description>The prevalence of overweight and obesity is rapidly increasing in westernized countries, both in the general population and in children (see International Obesity Task Force 2009, http://www.iotf.org/ ). The increased availability of palatable, energy dense foods and the reduced requirement for physical exertion during working and domestic life as well as during leisure time contribute to a sustained state of positive energy balance and are, no doubt, critical factors underlying this obesity pandemic. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:15:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tuxiaojie/article/605176</link><title>Publication Manual of the American Psychological Association</title><description>...a new and improved style manual for writers and students in psychology and other behavioral and social sciences... gives writers easy-to-use guidelines on how to prepare manuscripts according to APA style. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:16:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jessicathorpeshaw/article/8859903</link><title>Psychosocial Aspects of Childhood Obesity</title><description>The obesity epidemic is increasing in youths at a startling rate. By 2010, it is projected that approximately 50% of North American children and 30% of children from the European Union will be overweight (Wang and Lobstein 2006). In the United States, obesity in children and adolescents is defined as a body mass index (BMI; weight in kilograms divided by the height squared in meters) at or above the 95th percentile for individuals of the same age and sex as established ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:17:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/3680116</link><title>State Ranks of Incident Cancer Burden due to Overweight and Obesity in the United States, 2003</title><description>Objective: Given links between obesity and cancer, we estimated incident cancer burden due to overweight and obesity at the state level in the United States. Methods and Procedures: Using state rankings by per capita burden of incident cancer cases diagnosed in 2003 that were related to overweight and obesity, we examined the frequency with which states ranked in the highest and lowest quintiles of weight-related burden for cancers of the postmenopausal breast, endometrium, kidney, colon, and prostate. In this study, data from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:18:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wmcleod/article/4634184</link><title>Obesity and Sugar-sweetened Beverages in African-American Preschool Children: A Longitudinal Study</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:19:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lisemaj/article/6631809</link><title>Publication manual of the American Psychological Association.</title><description>From the Publisher: With millions of copies sold, the Publication Manual of the American Psychological Association is the style manual of choice for writers, editors, students, educators, and professionals in psychology, sociology, business, economics, nursing, social work, and justice administration, and other disciplines in which effective communication with words and data is fundamental. In addition to providing clear guidance on grammar, the mechanics of writing, and APA style, the Publication Manual offers an authoritative and easy-to-use reference and citation system ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:20:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/achu/article/2009861</link><title>Reducing obesity and related chronic disease risk in children and youth: a synthesis of evidence with ‘best practice’ recommendations</title><description>Childhood obesity is a global epidemic and rising trends in overweight and obesity are apparent in both developed and developing countries. Available estimates for the period between the 1980s and 1990s show the prevalence of overweight and obesity in children increased by a magnitude of two to five times in developed countries (e.g. from 11% to over 30% in boys in Canada), and up to almost four times in developing countries (e.g. from 4% to 14% in Brazil). The goal of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:21:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sfcheung/article/5318807</link><title>Publication Manual of the American Psychological Association, 6th Edition</title><description>The Publication Manual of the American Psychological Association" is the style manual of choice for writers, editors, students, and educators in the social and behavioral sciences. It provides invaluable guidance on all aspects of the writing process, from the ethics of authorship to the word choice that best reduces bias in language. Well-known for its authoritative and easy-to-use reference and citation system, the Publication Manual also offers guidance on choosing the headings, tables, figures, and tone that will result in strong, simple, and elegant scientific communication. The sixth ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:22:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pbeissner/article/9004030</link><title>Use of the Obesity Surgery Mortality Risk Score to Predict Complications of Laparoscopic Bariatric Surgery</title><description>Background This study aimed to evaluate the role of the Obesity Surgery Mortality Risk Score (OS-MRS) to predict the risk of post-operative adverse events, in addition to death, from any laparoscopic bariatric procedure. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>