<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7126">alicia keys brand new me lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:23:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:23:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NIdawahab/article/650119</link><title>From destination brand to location brand</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:24:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/6345574</link><title>Consumer Innovativeness and the Use of New versus Extended Brand Names for New Products</title><description>Despite the importance of branding to new product success, little research has been conducted on how individual adoption orientation might affect brand name preferences. This paper draws on the diffusion literature to investigate how consumer innovativeness affects consumer response to alternative branding strategies (i.e., new vs. extended brands, for new products). The results of an empirical study found that consumer innovativeness has a greater effect on new product evaluations for new brand names relative to extended brand names. Also, results indicate ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:25:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/claurier/article/8405049</link><title>Combination of Audio and Lyrics Features for Genre Classification in Digital Audio Collections</title><description>In many areas multimedia technology has made its way into mainstream. In the case of digital audio this is manifested in numerous online music stores having turned into profitable businesses. The widespread user adaption of digital audio both on home computers and mobile players show the size of this market. Thus, ways to automatically process and handle the growing size of private and commercial collections become increasingly important; along goes a need to make music interpretable by computers. The most obvious ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:26:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kitenet/article/6604936</link><title>SOME ASPECTS OF THE THEORY OF DICHOTOMOUS KEYS</title><description>The structure of dichotomous keys is discussed, and some general theorems are proved concerning the number and arrangement of the taxa in any given key. The possibility is considered that the various questions in a key may occasionally be answered wrongly, the key then leading to a wrong determination. It is shown that if this possibility exists, then the probability of a right determination is almost always improved by changing the structure of the key to make it as 'short'as possible. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:27:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alisonruth/article/139916</link><title>Brand power revisited: measuring brand equity in cyber-space</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:28:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phlow/article/952883</link><title>Natural language processing of lyrics</title><description>We report experiments on the use of standard natural language processing (NLP) tools for the analysis of music lyrics. A significant amount of music audio has lyrics. Lyrics encode an important part of the semantics of a song, therefore their analysis complements that of acoustic and cultural metadata and is fundamental for the development of complete music information retrieval systems. Moreover, a textual analysis of a song can generate ground truth data that can be used to validate results from purely ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:29:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10804963</link><title>50 Years Ago in CORR: A New Method of Pelvic Fixation William Johnson MD Clin Orthop. 1958;11:194–201</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:30:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mat4saj/article/2650348</link><title>Cubic convolution interpolation for digital image processing</title><description>Cubic convolution interpolation is a new technique for resampling discrete data. It has a number of desirable features which make it useful for image processing. The technique can be performed efficiently on a digital computer. The cubic convolution interpolation function converges uniformly to the function being interpolated as the sampling increment approaches zero. With the appropriate boundary conditions and constraints on the interpolation kernel, it can be shown that the order of accuracy of the cubic convolution method is between that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:31:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10408116</link><title>Organised crime in New Zealand 2010</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7126-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7126_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:32:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kitenet/article/6604951</link><title>Keys and the crisis in taxonomy: extinction or reinvention?</title><description>Dichotomous keys that follow a single pathway of character state choices to an end point have been the primary tools for the identification of unknown organisms for more than two centuries. However, a revolution in computer diagnostics is now under way that may result in the replacement of traditional keys by matrix-based computer interactive keys that have many paths to a correct identification and make ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>