<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:33:33" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:33:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lelly/article/259625</link><title>Edge Cities, European-style: Examples from Paris and the Randstad</title><description>Across the developed world, metropolitan regions have become increasingly polycentric. One of the new centre types emerging in the metropolitan periphery in North America in particular is the Edge City. These are recently formed, large multifunctional concentrations of offices, retail, leisure and housing areas at a considerable distance of the 'historic' central city. This paper discusses the extent to which Edge Cities are a typically North-American phenomenon, or something we might also expect in Europe. A review of American and European ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:34:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pinyoji/article/5202968</link><title>Sustaining creativity in the creative archetype: The case of Austin, Texas</title><description>Recently, the popular literature on creative industries and the urban creative landscape has been largely dominated by the work of one scholar, Richard Florida. The popularity of Richard Florida’s work has led to a zealous implementation of his creative class thesis by many city officials, policymakers, and urban planners. Recent studies have investigated the impact of creative city implementation in previously working class and industrial cities, but given Florida’s popularity and influence, it is also necessary to evaluate the sustainability of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:35:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vesk_02/article/3963914</link><title>Experiences of European Digital Cities</title><description>This paper presents the current developments of Digital Cities in the European Union. Starting from the point of view of local authorities and their specific role in the development of the Information Society, three applications clusters are proposed: i) Economic development or regeneration; ii) Social cohesion and quality of life; and iii) better management of the city administration and its infrastructures. The paper also reviews the limits of current pilot projects and gives an outline of the enabling technologies in use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:36:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PaperCollector/article/5489087</link><title>Modulation of perceived contrast by a moving surround.</title><description>The apparent contrast of a center pattern depends on the contrast of its surround. To examine the suprathreshold perception of moving patterns, we measured the perceived contrast of a moving grating while the direction and speed of the surround patterns varied. Subjects matched the apparent contrast of a center patch embedded in surround patches to that of a patch with no surround pattern. Temporal frequency, Michelson contrast and movement direction of both center and surround patterns varied systematically. We found that: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:37:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/long/article/820372</link><title>Reevaluating Alliance Reliability: Specific Threats, Specific Promises</title><description>Previously reported empirical evidence suggests that when conflict arises, military alliances are not reliable; state leaders should only expect their alliance partners to join them in war about 25% of the time. Yet, theoretical arguments explaining the choices of leaders to form cooperative agreements are at odds with such empirical evidence. This puzzling gap between theory and evidence motivates a reconsideration of previous measures of alliance reliability. Many alliance treaties include specific language regarding the circumstances under which the alliance comes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:38:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ggGrace14/article/6627098</link><title>On the relationship between software dependencies and coordination: field studies and tool support</title><description>As software systems provide more, and more distributed, real-time services to our society, it is possible to witness their growing complexity. One way to manage this complexity is to decompose software systems into smaller parts, called modules. The predictable consequence of dividing a system into modules is that these modules need to be put back together in some coordinated way, so that the software system can provide services. A dependency between software modules is said to exist when one module relies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:39:58">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18652/article/13052007</link><title>Domain Specific Memory Management in a Modern Web Browser</title><description>Since their inception, the usage pattern of web browsers has changed substantially. Rather than sequentially navigating static web sites, modern web browsers often manage a large number of simultaneous tabs displaying dynamic web content, each of which might be running a substantial amount of client-side JavaScript code. This environment introduced a new degree of parallelism that was not fully embraced by the underlying JavaScript virtual machine architecture. We propose a novel abstraction for multiple disjoint JavaScript heaps, which we call compartments. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:41:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kresala/article/455224</link><title>Uncertain Family Trajectories: Interactional Consequences of Cancer Diagnosis, Treatment, and Prognosis</title><description>Analysis of a corpus of family phone calls reveals how family members routinely address uncertain issues when attempting to understand cancer diagnosis, treatment, and prognosis. A large collection of moments are overviewed and organized into three prominent social activities: biomedical reportings about anonymous medical staff; references to doctors in anticipation of explanations; and assessing the care provided by doctors and medical staff. Specific attention is drawn to how reportings include lay depictions about lack of knowledge, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:42:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/long/article/883829</link><title>Applying a Two-Step Strategy to the Analysis of Cross-National Public Opinion Data</title><description>In recent years, large sets of national surveys with shared content have increasingly been used for cross-national opinion research. But scholars have not yet settled on the most flexible and efficient models for utilizing such data. We present a two-step strategy for such analysis that takes advantage of the fact that in such datasets each “cluster” (i.e., country sample) is large enough to sustain separate analysis of its internal variances and covariances. We illustrate the method by examining a puzzle of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:43:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vesk_02/article/6609871</link><title>The making of knowledge cities: Melbourne’s knowledge-based urban development experience</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>