<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:44:34" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:44:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stanislavhivanov/article/12054395</link><title>Attitudes and Willingness to Donate towards Heritage Restoration: An Exploratory Study about Bulgarian Socialist Monuments</title><description>In this exploratory study, an attempt was made to clarify the role of the visitors’ perception of the socialist era in relation to their 1) perception of socialist monuments’ maintenance level, 2) willingness to visit socialist monuments, 3) willingness to present socialist monuments for tourism purposes, 4) willingness to pay towards a visit to a socialist-era monument, and 5) willingness to donate towards socialist era sites’ restoration. Based on a quantitative study with 236 Bulgarians at Buzludzha peak, the findings suggest ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:45:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/expressivelyme/article/7379904</link><title>Environmental benefits from reusing clothes</title><description>Abstract Background, aim, and scope  Clothes are often discarded when much of their potential lifetime is left. Many charitable organizations therefore collect used clothing and resell it as second-hand clothes for example in Eastern Europe or Africa. In this connection, the question arises whether reusing clothes actually results in a decrease of the environmental burden of the life cycle of clothing. The environmental burden of clothing has been studied in several studies. However, most of these studies focus solely on the energy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:46:32">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2208/article/7004355</link><title>Effects of mutations and growth conditions on lipid synthesis in Neurospora crassa.</title><description>A morphological mutant (col-2) of Neurospora, which is partially deficient in glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase (G-6-PD) activity and has lower levels of reduced nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide phosphate (NADPH), accumulated three-fold more triglycerides during log-phase growth than the wild-type strain. Increased lipid deposition was not found in other strains that included slow-growing morphological mutants, NADPH-deficient strains, G-6-PD-deficient mutants, wild-type revertants from col-2, and a cel, col-2 double mutant. The cel, col-2 strain was supplemented with an exogenous source of fatty acids because it cannot ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:47:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2208/article/7004327</link><title>Altered fatty acid distribution in mutants of Neurospora crassa.</title><description>Morphological mutants of Neurospora with decreased levels of reduced nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide phosphate (NADPH) and reduced nicotinamide ad enine dinucleotide (NADH) contained only 20% as much of a polyunsaturated fatty acid (linolenic acid) as the wild type in both the phospholipid and neutral lipid fractions. There was an excellent correlation between linolenic acid levels and morphological appearance as a function of total NADPH content, but no correlation with NADH content. The linolenic acid deficiency was balanced by a relative increase in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:48:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/medic0747/article/571879</link><title>Conformational analysis and clustering of short and medium size loops connecting regular secondary structures: a database for modeling and prediction.</title><description>Loops are regions of nonrepetitive conformation connecting regular secondary structures. We identified 2,024 loops of one to eight residues in length, with acceptable main-chain bond lengths and peptide bond angles, from a database of 223 protein and protein-domain structures. Each loop is characterized by its sequence, main-chain conformation, and relative disposition of its bounding secondary structures as described by the separation between the tips of their axes and the angle between them. Loops, grouped according to their length and type of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:49:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/luquej/article/5822505</link><title>Using lay health advisors to promote breast and cervical cancer screening among Latinas: a review.</title><description>CONTEXT: Breast and cervical cancer (BCC) represent leading causes of morbidity and mortality among Latinas. The use of lay health advisors (LHAs) represents a promising approach for health promotion among underserved and minority populations. OBJECTIVE: This study reviews the evidence regarding the effectiveness of LHA-based interventions to promote BCC screening among Latinas. METHODS: A search was conducted using the PubMed online electronic database. The search included studies published through August 2008. Study abstracts were reviewed to select intervention studies that met ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:50:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8214710</link><title>Advanced age increases chromosome structural abnormalities in human spermatozoa</title><description>Advanced age increases chromosome structural abnormalities in human spermatozoa European Journal of Human Genetics advance online publication, November 3, 2010. doi:10.1038/ejhg.2010.166 Authors: Cristina Templado, Anna Donate, Jesús Giraldo, Mercè Bosch &amp; Anna Estop ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:51:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8384929</link><title>Telomeres in cancer and ageing.</title><description>Telomeres protect the chromosome ends from unscheduled DNA repair and degradation. Telomeres are heterochromatic domains composed of repetitive DNA (TTAGGG repeats) bound to an array of specialized proteins. The length of telomere repeats and the integrity of telomere-binding proteins are both important for telomere protection. Furthermore, telomere length and integrity are regulated by a number of epigenetic modifications, thus pointing to higher order control of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:52:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rrbarb/article/7053695</link><title>The effect of organizational culture on knowledge management practices and innovation</title><description>In this paper we analyze the relationships between certain knowledge management (KM) practices, organizational culture, and the technological results of companies. In the last few years, KM literature has highlighted the important role of cultural values on the way KM processes are developed and applied in organizations. From this viewpoint, and focusing on a set of knowledge storage and transfer practices, we try to empirically analyze the existence of a multiplier effect of the knowledge-centered organizational culture on the relationship between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:53:28">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8626864</link><title>Evaluation of delivery conditions for cutaneous plasmid electrotransfer using a multielectrode array</title><description>Evaluation of delivery conditions for cutaneous plasmid electrotransfer using a multielectrode array Gene Therapy advance online publication, December 23, 2010. doi:10.1038/gt.2010.171 Authors: B Ferraro, L C Heller, Y L Cruz, S Guo, A Donate &amp; R Heller ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>