<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:54:30" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:54:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aprilwwiliams/article/44983</link><title>Stories of Home and Affordable Housing</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:55:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eponton/article/6338165</link><title>Pandemic Economics: Financial Survival for Home Care Agencies in a Bird Flu Outbreak</title><description>Flu pandemics have occurred regularly throughout recorded history. Preparation now will determine which home care agencies survive the next flu pandemic financially. This article discusses six cost areas that will affect the home care agency bottom line. These areas include supplies, staff shortages, reimbursement issues, vaccine and antiviral medication, unusual costs associated with a pandemic, and planning. Many suggestions for financial survival are offered. Major suggestions include financial planning in advance of a pandemic, stockpiling six essential supplies to last at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:56:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ShakeeraDMyers/article/6875232</link><title>Family expenditures for clothing : Five regions, by... Economics division, bureau of home economics...</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:57:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10168240</link><title>Writings of Charles S. Peirce: A Chronological Edition, Volume 6, 1886-1890</title><description>Volume 6 of this landmark edition contains 66 writings mainly from the unsettled period in Peirce's life just after he moved from New York to Milford, Pennsylvania, followed shortly afterward by the death of his mother. The writings in this volume reveal Peirce's powerful mind probing into diverse issues, looking for an underlying unity, but, perhaps, also looking for direction. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:58:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/candyapple/article/487433</link><title>Under the Kitchen Surface: Domestic Products and Conflicting Constructions of Home</title><description>This paper examines how the product world around domestic cleanliness plays with the dual construction of the home as safe and dangerous. By participating in this construction, cleaning products engage with a salient concern in domestic life—how to achieve and maintain a safe domestic environment. We have investigated the discursive commentary on domestic cleanliness and safety in one domestic advice manual: Good Housekeeping magazine, over the period 1951-2001. This investigation has also provided insights into the discursive character of cleaning products. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:59:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eponton/article/3097215</link><title>Primary Care in the Home: The Time is Now!</title><description>The Visiting Nurse Association of Greater Philadelphia is the first home health agency to provide primary health care in the home. A team of advanced practice nurses working with a physician provides much-needed medical care in patients' homes. Medicare B and other payors are reimbursing the organization for these services. This collaborative primary health care model integrates multiple health services and provides them to patients. This article describes the conception and implementation of this unique health service delivery model. 10.1177/108482230001200302 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:59:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eponton/article/3410331</link><title>Old Age, New Technology, and Future Innovations in Disease Management and Home Health Care</title><description>The nation's nearly 80 million baby boomers are about to enter their peak years of chronic disease and are set to become an unprecedented driver of health care costs. New technology, however, promises to enable a transformation in the delivery of care, putting patients at the center of care systems that engage and empower them and their families, directly connecting patients to care-givers, and personalizing services in response to patients' unique needs, preferences, and values. Such care systems also offer the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:00:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chgold/article/3410329</link><title>Home Care Primary Nurse Case Management Model</title><description>A typical home care nurse is rarely taught a special structured method to do case management. During an orientation, nurses are told they are primary case managers and are oriented to all of the tasks for which they are responsible. However, there is no structured case management method taught. Nurses are typically told that they will develop their own style after observing others. This article describes an organized method of managing patients and their needs with three outcome objectives: to understand ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:01:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/v100567/article/9925972</link><title>Smart home architecture based on event-driven DPWS</title><description>With the advances of electronic information technology and computer network, especially the embedded technology, smart home is no more just a vision but being practical. The interoperability of heterogeneous devices and flexibility of devices’ usage are two key problems that challenge the implementation of smart home. To deal with these two issues, this paper proposes an event-driven service oriented architecture using device profile for web services (DPWS). DPWS inherits the advantages of the traditional web services in achieving interoperability without dependence ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:02:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5285558</link><title>Is it all bad? Rewards and challenges of mothering children with hidden disabilities</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>