<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7130">l1 versus l2 regularization</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:03:36" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:03:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pprett/article/120508</link><title>Regularization and variable selection via the elastic net</title><description>Summary.  We propose the elastic net, a new regularization and variable selection method. Real world data and a simulation study show that the elastic net often outperforms the lasso, while enjoying a similar sparsity of representation. In addition, the elastic net encourages a grouping effect, where strongly correlated predictors tend to be in or out of the model together. The elastic net is particularly useful when the number of predictors (p) is much bigger than the number of observations (n). By ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:04:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jessopher/article/402207</link><title>Feature selection, L1 vs. L2 regularization, and rotational invariance</title><description>We consider supervised learning in the presence of very many irrelevant features, and study two different regularization methods for preventing overfitting. Focusing on logistic regression, we show that using L1 regularization of the parameters, the sample complexity (i.e., the number of training examples required to learn "well,") grows only logarithmically in the number of irrelevant features. This logarithmic rate matches the best known bounds for feature selection, and indicates that L1 regularized logistic regression can be effective even if there are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:05:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thebaglady608/article/2230841</link><title>L1 interaction domains of papillomavirus l2 necessary for viral genome encapsidation.</title><description>BPHE-1 cells, which harbor 50 to 200 viral episomes, encapsidate viral genome and generate infectious bovine papillomavirus type 1 (BPV1) upon coexpression of capsid proteins L1 and L2 of BPV1, but not coexpression of BPV1 L1 and human papillomavirus type 16 (HPV16) L2. BPV1 L2 bound in vitro via its C-terminal 85 residues to purified L1 capsomers, but not with intact L1 virus-like particles in vitro. However, when the efficiency of BPV1 L1 coimmunoprecipitation with a series of BPV1 L2 deletion ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:06:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rickl/article/5492616</link><title>L1 use during L2 writing: An empirical study of a complex phenomenon</title><description>This study examined writers’ use of their first language (L1) while writing in their second language (L2). Twenty students each wrote four short argumentative essays in their L1 (Dutch) and four in their L2 (English) under think-aloud conditions. We analysed whether L1 use varied between writers and tasks, and whether it was related to general writing proficiency, L2 proficiency, and L2 text quality. The analysis focused on the occurrence of a number of conceptual activities, including Generating ideas, Planning, and Metacomments. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:06:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thebaglady608/article/2230838</link><title>The papillomavirus minor capsid protein, L2, induces localization of the major capsid protein, L1, and the viral transcription/replication protein, E2, to PML oncogenic domains.</title><description>We have used immunofluorescent staining and confocal microscopy to examine the subcellular localization of structural and nonstructural bovine papillomavirus (BPV) proteins in cultured cells that produce infectious virions. When expressed separately, L1, the major capsid protein, showed a diffuse nuclear distribution while L2, the minor capsid protein, was found to localize to punctate nuclear regions identified as promonocytic leukemia protein (PML) oncogenic domains (PODs). Coexpression of L1 and L2 induced a relocation of L1 into the PODs, leading to the colocalization ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:07:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pprett/article/6926437</link><title>An efficient projection for &lt;i&gt;l&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sub&gt;1&lt;/sub&gt;, &lt;sub&gt;&amp;infin;&lt;/sub&gt; regularization</title><description>In recent years the l1, ∞ norm has been proposed for joint regularization. In essence, this type of regularization aims at extending the l1 framework for learning sparse models to a setting where the goal is to learn a set of jointly sparse models. In this paper we derive a simple and effective projected gradient method for optimization of l1, ∞ regularized problems. The main challenge in developing such a method resides on being able to compute efficient projections to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:08:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/billhao/article/10008011</link><title>Articles in child L2 English: When L1 and L2 acquisition meet at the interface</title><description>In this study, the authors investigate the acquisition of the article system of English as a phenomenon at the interface between morphosyntax and semantics. L1 acquisition studies have found that children make mistakes in article use until they are at least four years old or possibly older. Also, adult L2 acquisition studies have reported that learners of English often have consistent difficulty in the use of articles until very late stages of acquisition. This study sought to understand whether child L2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:09:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/imad/article/5182417</link><title>Tracing the culture behind writing: Rhetorical patterns and bidirectional transfer in L1 and L2 essays of Turkish writers in relation to educational context</title><description>The study examines whether writers from shared cultural backgrounds display common writing patterns in their texts and whether these patterns differ while writing in L1 versus L2. The study explored the presence and bidirectional transfer of rhetorical patterns in eighteen Turkish participants’ writing in relation to previous writing instructional context defined as “small culture.” Participants were first given a survey about their writing instruction history. Then, each participant wrote two argumentative essays in Turkish and English. These texts were analyzed and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:10:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/senioritis/article/1217853</link><title>The use of paraphrase in summary writing: A comparison of L1 and L2 writers</title><description>Paraphrasing is considered by many to be an important skill for academic writing, and some have argued that the teaching of paraphrasing might help students avoid copying from source texts. Few studies, however, have investigated the ways in which both L1 and L2 academic writers already use paraphrasing as a textual borrowing strategy when completing their academic assignments. To expand our understanding of university students' paraphrasing strategies, the present study analyzed L1 (n = 79) and L2 (n = 74) writers' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7130-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7130_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:11:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hltlab/article/975626</link><title>Who's in control? Proficiency and L1 influence on L2 processing.</title><description>We report three reaction time (RT)/event-related brain potential (ERP) semantic priming lexical decision experiments that explore the following in relation to L1 activation during L2 processing: (1) the role of L2 proficiency, (2) the role of sentence context, and (3) the locus of L1 activations (orthographic vs. semantic). All experiments used German (L1) homonyms translated into English (L2) to form prime-target pairs (pine-jaw for Kiefer) to test whether the L1 caused interference in an all-L2 experiment. Both RTs and ERPs were ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>