<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:12:01" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:12:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/felipeogo/article/5836064</link><title>Making Computer Games and Design Thinking: A Review of Current Software and Strategies</title><description>This article provides an overview of computer software and instructional strategies intended to engage young people in making computer games, to achieve a variety of educational goals. It briefly describes the most popular of such programs and compares their key features, including the kinds of games that can be created with the software, the types of communities and resources that are associated with each program, claims made for learning outcomes resulting from use of the software, and the results of empirical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:13:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tchisky/article/10163180</link><title>Acknowledgment to Referees</title><description>Games has received help from many individuals since its inaugural issue in 2009. We are especially grateful to the following 146 referees for their great support of Games during the past two years. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:14:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/13073836</link><title>Acknowledgement to Reviewers of Games in 2013</title><description>The editors of Games would like to express their sincere gratitude to the following reviewers for assessing manuscripts in 2013. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:15:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12042838</link><title>Acknowledgment to Referees</title><description>Games has received help from many individuals since its inaugural issue in 2009. We are especially grateful to the following 146 referees for their great support of Games during the past two years. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:16:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/seawidget/article/423548</link><title>Developing Online Games: An Insider's Guide</title><description>&lt;P&gt;A soup-to-nuts overview of just what it takes to successfully design, develop and manage an online game. Learn from the top two online game developers through the real-world successes and mistakes not known to others. There are Case studies from 10+ industry leaders, including Raph Koster, J. Baron, R. Bartle, D. Schubert, A. Macris, and more! Covers all types of online games: Retail Hybrids, Persistent Worlds, and console games. &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Developing Online Games provides insight into designing, developing and managing online games ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:17:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sspela/article/2285586</link><title>Playing and Making Games for Learning: Instructionist and Constructionist Perspectives for Game Studies</title><description>This article presents an overview of what we know about two perspectives, coined instructionist and constructionist, to games for learning. The instructionists, accustomed to thinking in terms of making instructional educational materials, turn naturally to the concept of designing instructional games. Far fewer people have sought to turn the tables: by making games for learning instead of playing games for learning. Rather than embedding "lessons" directly in games, constructionists have focused their efforts on providing students with greater opportunities to construct ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:18:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/felipekenjinakano/article/7153592</link><title>Live Action Role-Playing Games</title><description>Live action role-playing games share a range of characteristics with massively multi-player online games (MMOGs). Because these games have existed for more than 20 years, players of these games have a substantial amount of experience in handling issues pertinent to MMOGs. Survey and review of live action role-playing games, whose participant count can be in the thousands, reveal that features such as size, theme, game master-to-player ratio, and others interact to form complex systems that require several different groups of control ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:19:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yannleroux/article/3823170</link><title>Alien Games: Do Girls Prefer Games Designed by Girls?</title><description>This 3-year study used a mixed-method design beginning with content analysis of games envisioned by 5th and 8th graders, followed by a survey of students in the same age range reacting to video promos representing these games. Results show that the designer's gender influences the design outcome of games and that girls expected that they would find the girl-designed games significantly more fun to play than the boy-designed games, whereas boys imagined that the boy-designed games would be significantly more fun ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:20:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/carolined314/article/7946380</link><title>On the Research Value of Large Games</title><description>Coordination game theory is quite important to a number of literatures but has had very few direct empirical tests because that would require experimental participation by large numbers of people. Large games however can produce natural experiments: situations that through no intent of the designer offer controlled variations on a phenomenon of theoretical interest. Unlike any other social science research technology, such games provide for both sufficient participation numbers and careful control of experimental conditions, making them like Petri dishes for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:21:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jasmithoffice/article/1863248</link><title>Migration and the Origins of the English Atlantic World (Harvard Historical Studies)</title><description>&lt;p&gt; England's seventeenth-century colonial empire in North America and the Caribbean was created by migration. The quickening pace of this essential migration is captured in the London port register of 1635, the largest extant port register for any single year in the colonial period and unique in its record of migration to America and to the European continent. Alison Games analyzes the 7,500 people who traveled from London in that year, recreating individual careers, exploring colonial societies at a time of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>