<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:22:11" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:22:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rturner45/article/6823185</link><title>Patient satisfaction with point-of-care testing in general practice.</title><description>The results from this trial support patient satisfaction and acceptability of point-of-care testing in a general practice setting. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:23:08">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4948760</link><title>Inpatient suicide in a general hospital</title><description>This study aimed to compare the characteristics of psychiatric and nonpsychiatric suicidal inpatients in one general hospital and examine the predictors of completed suicide in the patients with suicidal acts during hospitalization. One hundred ten study subjects were identified by the adverse event reports of suicidal acts during hospitalization from 1995 to 2004. Demographic data and clinical information were collected by chart reviews. Psychiatric inpatients with suicidal acts were mainly younger females with psychiatric diagnoses and previous suicide attempts. Nonpsychiatric suicidal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:24:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/khernandez/article/10297544</link><title>Grade Retention in Massachusetts Public Schools: 2004-05</title><description>This report is the third retention report published by the Massachusetts Department of Education (MADOE) to provide districts and the public general information on student retention in Massachusetts. Retention is defined as repeating a grade--students are retained when they are required to repeat the grade in which they were enrolled in the previous year. For the 2004-05 school year, retained students were reported to be enrolled in the same grade as they were in during the 2003-04 school year. In this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:24:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11694851</link><title>Gender-specific predictors of risky alcohol use among general hospital inpatients</title><description>To investigate sociodemographic-, living situation- and substance-related variables as predictors of current risky alcohol use for both female and male general hospital inpatients. The sample of 6050 female and 8282 male general hospital inpatients was recruited in 2002–2004. Using the Alcohol Use Disorder Identification Test-Consumption, they were assigned to four drinking groups: abstinent, moderate use, slightly increased use and notably increased use. Gender-specific predictors of group affiliation were determined using multivariate multinomial logistic regressions. In both genders, younger age, rural living ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:25:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11755227</link><title>Gender-specific predictors of risky alcohol use among general hospital inpatients</title><description>To investigate sociodemographic-, living situation- and substance-related variables as predictors of current risky alcohol use for both female and male general hospital inpatients. The sample of 6050 female and 8282 male general hospital inpatients was recruited in 2002–2004. Using the Alcohol Use Disorder Identification Test-Consumption, they were assigned to four drinking groups: abstinent, moderate use, slightly increased use and notably increased use. Gender-specific predictors of group affiliation were determined using multivariate multinomial logistic regressions. In both genders, younger age, rural living ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:26:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8181158</link><title>General hospital admission as an opportunity for smoking-cessation strategies: a clinical trial in Brazil</title><description>To compare the results of 6-month follow-ups for hospitalized patients who were divided into two groups of low- and high-intensity treatments for smoking cessation and compared to the results of standard hospital treatment. A total of 2414 patients were screened. Two hundred thirty-seven current smokers were randomly assigned to high-intensity intervention (HII; 30-min motivational interview plus seven routine telephone calls after hospital discharge) or to low-intensity intervention (LII; 15-min counseling about the benefits of quitting) and 80 comprised the usual care ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:27:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/peterpath/article/9853557</link><title>Case records of the Massachusetts General Hospital: Case 29-2011: A 66-year-old woman with cardiac and renal failure.</title><description>Presentation of Case Dr. Jason E. Faris (Medicine): A 66-year-old woman was admitted to this hospital because of cardiac and renal failure. The patient had been well until approximately 6 months earlier, when dyspnea on exertion and leg edema developed. A diagnosis of congestive heart failure was made at another facility. Two months before this evaluation, dyspnea worsened. The patient was admitted to the other hospital. An electrocardiogram (ECG) showed T-wave inversions in leads I and aVL. The serum level of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:28:17">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8740769</link><title>High prevalence and prescription of benzodiazepines for elderly: data from psychiatric consultation to patients from an emergency room of a general hospital</title><description>The aim of this study is to compare the use and prescription of psychotropic drugs, with emphasis on benzodiazepines, in elderly and non-elderly patients who are assisted at the emergency room by a psychiatric consultation of a university teaching hospital. This is a cross-sectional study. We analyzed all records of psychiatric consultation in an emergency room of a general hospital from March 2009 until March 2010. Sociodemographic and clinical variables were compared between the group of elderly and non-elderly in two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:29:26">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6180284</link><title>Motivation to change risky drinking and motivation to seek help for alcohol risk drinking among general hospital inpatients with problem drinking and alcohol-related diseases</title><description>The objective of this study was to analyze motivation to change drinking behavior and motivation to seek help in general hospital inpatients with problem drinking and alcohol-related diseases. The sample consisted of 294 general hospital inpatients aged 18–64 years. Inpatients with alcohol-attributable disease were classified according to its alcohol-attributable fraction (AAF; AAF=1, AAF&lt;1 and AAF=0). Baseline differences in alcohol-related variables, demographics and motivation between the AAF groups were analyzed. Furthermore, differences in motivation to change, in motivation to seek help and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7132-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7132_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:30:35">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9177475</link><title>Quality of psychiatric care in the general hospital: referrer perceptions of an inpatient liaison psychiatry service</title><description>To explore the experience of senior staff on acute medical wards using an established inpatient liaison psychiatry service and obtain their views on clinically relevant performance measures. Semistructured face-to-face interviews with consultants and senior nurses were taped, transcribed and analyzed manually using the framework method of analysis. Twenty-five referrers were interviewed. Four key themes were identified — benefits of the liaison service, potential areas of improvement, indices of service performance such as speed and quality of response and expanded substance misuse ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>