<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:30:59" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:31:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hmoffet/article/12104898</link><title>Effects of yoga on functional capacity and well being.</title><description>Yoga has proven beneficial effects on various health domains including musculoskeletal conditions, cardiopulmonary conditions through the practice of asana and pranayamas as well as on mental health, as it is known to enhance the body-and mind coordination. There is paucity of data on the effect of yoga on functional capacity in literature using 6 min walk test. The present study aims to look at the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:31:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/morgengold/article/10018483</link><title>Exploring the therapeutic effects of yoga and its ability to increase quality of life.</title><description>The objective of this study is to assess the findings of selected articles regarding the therapeutic effects of yoga and to provide a comprehensive review of the benefits of regular yoga practice. As participation rates in mind-body fitness programs such as yoga continue to increase, it is important for health care professionals to be informed about the nature of yoga and the evidence of its ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:31:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hmoffet/article/9971912</link><title>Effect of an integrated approach of yoga therapy on quality of life in osteoarthritis of the knee joint: A randomized control study.</title><description>An integrated approach of yoga therapy is better than therapeutic exercises as an adjunct to transcutaneous electrical stimulation and ultrasound treatment in improving knee disability and quality of life in patients with OA knees. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:32:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hmoffet/article/11058275</link><title>A comparative study of the effects of yoga and swimming on pulmonary functions in sedentary subjects.</title><description>The modality of exercise that is most beneficial and easy to perform has become a topic of research. Yogic exercises are being widely studied; however, postulated benefits of yogic exercises over other exercises must be scientifically explored. Prospective randomized comparative studies involving yoga and other endurance exercises are conspicuous by their absence. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:32:28">http://www.citeulike.org/group/740/article/757131</link><title>Ashtanga Yoga: The Practice Manual: An Illustrated Guide to Personal Practice</title><description>This is the most user-friendly yoga book available! It contins the entire Primary and Intermediate series of Ashtanga Yoga with three options for every asana. It is spiral bound to easily remain open while practicing. It contains over 650 photos with clear instructions and commentary. It is a great book for all levels of practitioners to enjoy and teachers will find it to be an invaluable tool for teaching their students. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:32:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sssmith/article/6777710</link><title>Prescribing Yoga.</title><description>More than 15.8 million people in the United States now practice some form of yoga, and nearly half of current practitioners stated they began yoga practice as a means of improving overall health. More broadly understood in a modern context, yoga is a set of principles and practices designed to promote health and well-being through the integration of body, breath, and mind. This article outlines the history of yoga and describes several forms, including asana-based yoga, which is becoming popular in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nathanen/article/3731656</link><title>The History of the History of Software</title><description>Just as the fields of software and hardware development have evolved, the field of software history has likewise matured. At first, the history of software was exclusively focused on technology. Later, there were historical explorations of the software industry and professions. Today the emphasis is on applications and the societal changes resulting from software. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hmoffet/article/5632132</link><title>Yoga in cardiac health (a review).</title><description>This review studies the efficacy of yoga in the primary and secondary prevention of ischaemic heart disease and post-myocardial infarction patient rehabilitation. Yoga is an unconventional form of physical exercise that has been practised over a long period of time in the Indian sub-continent. It has gained immense popularity as a form of recreational activity all over the world. Its possible contributions to healthy living have been studied and many interesting revelations have been made. Benefits of yoga in the modification ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wujastyk/article/117724</link><title>The Yoga of Siddha Boganathar</title><description>ISBN 1895383196. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:34:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hmoffet/article/11058271</link><title>Comparative study of conventional therapy and additional yogasanas for knee rehabilitation after total knee arthroplasty.</title><description>Amongst various modalities of post operative rehabilitation in a total knee replacement (TKR) surgery, this study focuses on evaluating the effect of additional yoga therapy on functional outcome of TKR patients. A comparative study was done to compare the effects of conventional physiotherapy and additional yoga asanas, on 56 patients ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>