<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:43:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:43:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dima10000/article/6611406</link><title>DNA zip codes control an ancient mechanism for gene targeting to the nuclear periphery</title><description>Many genes in Saccharomyces cerevisiae are recruited to the nuclear periphery after transcriptional activation. We have identified two gene recruitment sequences (GRS I and II) from the promoter of the INO1 gene that target the gene to the nuclear periphery. These GRSs function as DNA zip codes and are sufficient to target a nucleoplasmic locus to the nuclear periphery. Targeting requires components of the nuclear pore complex (NPC) and a GRS is sufficient to confer a physical interaction with the NPC. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:44:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tasabeehsala/article/12121822</link><title>Telomerase does not counteract telomere shortening but protects mitochondrial function under oxidative stress.</title><description>Telomerase is a ribonucleoprotein that counteracts telomere shortening and can immortalise human cells. There is also evidence for a telomere-independent survival function of telomerase. However, its mechanism is not understood. We show here that TERT, the catalytic subunit of human telomerase, protects human fibroblasts against oxidative stress. While TERT maintains telomere length under standard conditions, telomeres under increased stress shorten as fast as in cells ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:45:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lcrowell82/article/3471354</link><title>Affective Economies</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:46:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ghannah/article/5087106</link><title>Assassination and Preventive Killing</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:47:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lcrowell82/article/2492690</link><title>The Happiness Turn</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:48:00">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9774707</link><title>The Ahmed Versus Baerveldt Study</title><description>To report the design, baseline patient characteristics, and intraoperative complications of the Ahmed Versus Baerveldt (AVB) Study. Multicenter, randomized, clinical trial. Patients were recruited from 7 international clinical sites and treated by 10 surgeons between 2005 and 2009. Inclusion criteria required that patients be at least 18 years of age and have uncontrolled glaucoma refractory to medicinal, laser, and surgical therapy. Eligible patients were randomized to undergo implantation of an Ahmed-FP7 valve (New World Medical, Inc., Rancho Cucamonga, CA) or a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:49:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nicolasvasilache/article/1432748</link><title>Tiling Imperfectly-nested Loop Nests</title><description>Tiling is one of the more important transformations for enhancing locality of reference in programs. Tiling of perfectly-nested loop nests (which are loop nests in which all assignment statements are contained in the innermost loop) is well understood. In practice, most loop nests are imperfectly-nested, so existing compilers heuristically try to find a sequence of transformations that convert such loop nests into perfectly-nested ones but not always succeed. In this paper, we propose a novel... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:50:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3141370</link><title>A catalogue of cryptognathid mites (Acari: Prostigmata, Cryptognathidae) with the descriptions of a new species of Favognathus Luxton and a newly discovered male of F. amygdalus Dogan and Ayyildiz from Turkey</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:51:14">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10011850</link><title>SIU Scholar: Dr. Ahmed Muhammed</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7135-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7135_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:52:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shabbir0ahmed/article/5372736</link><title>Approximating the stability region for binary mixed-integer programs</title><description>The stability region of a solution is the polyhedral set of objective coefficients for which the solution is optimal. It provides valuable information for sensitivity analysis and re-optimization. An exact description of it may require an exponential number of inequalities. We develop polyhedral inner and outer approximations of linear size. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>