<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:53:42" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:53:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joekilner/article/638247</link><title>Fly Through View Video</title><description>Recently there has been great deal of interest in making system that enables an audience to view sports event from any arbitrary viewpoint. The rapid development of networks and computers will soon make it possible to provide a form of real-time video that allows the viewer to select any desired view of the action. This paper introduces a novel method for generating an arbitrary view of a scene in a soccer match. This allows the viewers to observe the action in a soccer game from a favorite... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:54:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jiho0205/article/2959146</link><title>The Priority/Confidence Model as a Framework for Soccer Agents</title><description>We propose the Priority/Confidence model as a reasoning model for agents. Decisions are made according to a confidence measure which is based on the importance of actions (priority) and the satisfaction of a priori preconditions. We implemented the Priority/Confidence model for a robotic soccer domain, namely the RoboCup. Our team, AIACS, has demonstrated the feasibility of this model by beating the world champion of 1997, AT-Humboldt in training matches and reaching a 9th place in the RoboCup’98 tournament. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:56:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/smcc/article/1659259</link><title>Critical Events or Critical Conditions: The 1999 Women’s World Cup and the Women’s United Soccer Association</title><description>In the wake of the 1999 Women’s World Cup final, a women’s professional league was formed, and play commenced with much fanfare in 2001. Attendance for the tournament had been stellar, and the final between China and the United States garnered a phenomenal television rating. It was with much optimism that the WUSA (Women’s United Soccer Association) was launched. However, despite a strong first season, attendance and television ratings declined, and the league folded after three years of play. This essay ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:57:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fheintz/article/5632913</link><title>Real-Time Spatio-Temporal Analysis of Dynamic Scenes in 3D Soccer Simulation</title><description>We propose a framework for spatio-temporal real-time analysis of dynamic scenes. It is designed to improve the grounding situation of autonomous agents in (simulated) physical domains. We introduce a knowledge processing pipeline ranging from relevance-driven compilation of a qualitative scene description to a knowledge-based detection of complex event and action sequences, conceived as a spatio-temporal pattern matching problem. A methodology for the formalization of motion patterns and their inner composition is introduced and applied to capture human expertise about domain-specific motion ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:58:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sigoldberg1/article/6581114</link><title>Understanding Quaternions and the Dirac Belt Trick</title><description>The Dirac belt trick is often employed in physics classrooms to show that a $2π$ rotation is not topologically equivalent to the absence of rotation whereas a $4π$ rotation is, mirroring a key property of quaternions and their isomorphic cousins, spinors. The belt trick can leave the student wondering if a real understanding of quaternions and spinors has been achieved, or if the trick is just an amusing analogy. The goal of this paper is to demystify the belt trick and to show that it implies an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:59:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guzzettg/article/3749659</link><title>You have the right to remain violent: power and resistance in the club</title><description>This study examines the aggressive commodification and corporatisation strategies experienced by a Macedonian-based club in the north-western suburbs of Melbourne. The administrative acquisition of the club by a quasi-corporate consortium colloquially referred to as the Silver Lining emphasized an abated model of its cultural heritage in favour of a newly fashioned corporate identity. Further evidence obtained via fieldwork observations and interviews documents the evolution of the power relationship between the clubs supporters and its administrators over a five-year period. We draw ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:01:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/paullamphear/article/3025241</link><title>GENDER EGALITARIANISM IN COED SPORT: A Case Study of American Soccer</title><description>This article uses an ethnographic and case-study approach to examine aspects of egalitarianism between men and women in an American coed soccer league. We describe the formal adjustments of the league, the informal arrangements made by participants, and the conceptualization of the game by both male and female players. Our findings indicate that even in a highly egalitarian form, coed soccer remains dominated by males both on the pitch and in concept. Our results challenge the thesis of `American exceptionalism' about ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:02:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/1904004</link><title>Action bias among elite soccer goalkeepers: The case of penalty kicks</title><description>In soccer penalty kicks, goalkeepers choose their action before they can clearly observe the kick direction. An analysis of 286 penalty kicks in top leagues and championships worldwide shows that given the probability distribution of kick direction, the optimal strategy for goalkeepers is to stay in the goal’s center. Goalkeepers, however, almost always jump right or left. We propose the following explanation for this behavior: because the norm is to jump, norm theory (Kahneman, D., &amp; Miller, D. T. (1986). Norm ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:03:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fxdm/article/8663965</link><title>Soccer and the art of deception</title><description>Time was when footballers (soccer players, to Americans) prided themselves on playing tough. They took their knocks and played on without complaint. But these days it’s common to see a player fake a collision with an opponent and writhe on the ground in hopes of getting a free kick. Such “dives” are “very frustrating to watch,” says Christopher Rose of James Madison University in Harrisonburg, Virginia, and goals have been scored and games won on wrongly awarded free kicks. To Gwendolyn David, Robbie Wilson, and Daniel Ortiz-Barrientos, however, the deceptive practice provided a unique research ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:04:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/neilh/article/1164974</link><title>Why are small and large numbers enumerated differently? A limited-capacity preattentive stage in vision.</title><description>"Subitizing," the process of enumeration when there are fewer than 4 items, is rapid (40-100 ms/item), effortless, and accurate. "Counting," the process of enumeration when there are more than 4 items, is slow (250-350 ms/item), effortful, and error-prone. Why is there a difference in the way the small and large numbers of items are enumerated? A theory of enumeration is proposed that emerges from a general theory of vision, yet explains the numeric abilities of preverbal infants, children, and adults. We ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>