<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:06:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:06:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/YolandaHeath/article/6694839</link><title>O's big book of happiness : the best of O, the Oprah magazine : wisdom, wit, advice, interviews, and inspiration</title><description>"You can't buy happiness, so why not grow your own? All you need is a piece of fertile ground (your beautiful mind) plus some hardy seeds of wisdom, creativity, and plain good sense. In this inspiring new collection from the pages of O, The Oprah Magazine, more than 75 warm, wise, and insightful contributors write about beating the blues, dropping the weight, kissing fear goodbye, making your dreams real, and putting your best face forward (with a little help from the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:07:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/3466763</link><title>Hyperthermic biology and cancer therapies: a hypothesis for the "Lance Armstrong effect".</title><description>THERE IS PERHAPS NO MORE IMPORTANT QUESTION IN cancer research than to understand the molecular basis of how the majority of patients with testicular cancer can be treated so effectively. For instance, how could Lance Armstrong, who was diagnosed with very advanced metastatic testicular cancer, be treated so successfully that he could subsequently win multiple grueling Tours de France? Although such therapeutic success is now common for many patients with this type of advanced testicular cancer, this type of outcome is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:08:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/treeves/article/5094540</link><title>The Oprah Phenomenon</title><description>Her image is iconic: Oprah Winfrey has built an empire on her ability to connect with and inspire her audience. No longer just a name, "Oprah" has become a brand representing the talk show host's unique style of self- actualizing individualism. The cultural and economic power wielded by Winfrey merits critical evaluation. The contributors to The Oprah Phenomenon examine the origins of her public image and its substantial influence on politics, entertainment, and popular opinion. Contributors address praise from her many supporters and weigh criticisms from her detractors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:09:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6711117</link><title>Target volume definition for three-dimensional conformal radiation therapy of lung cancer.</title><description>Three-dimensional conformal radiation therapy (3DCRT) is a mode of high precision radiotherapy which has the potential to improve the therapeutic ratio of radiation therapy for locally advanced non-small cell lung cancer. The preliminary clinical experience with 3DCRT has been promising and justifies further endeavour to refine its clinical application and ultimately test its role in randomized trials. There are several steps to be taken before 3DCRT evolves into an effective single modality for the treatment of lung cancer and before it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:10:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6711086</link><title>The impact of three-dimensional radiation on the treatment of non-small cell lung cancer.</title><description>PURPOSE: Non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) patients with locally advanced unresectable disease have a grim prognosis. Radiotherapeutic strategies are necessary to improve the permanent eradication of thoracic disease. The poor results achieved with conventional external beam radiation therapy reflect in part, the inadequacy of such therapy in achieving its primary objective of achieving local control. The impact of three-dimensional conformal radiation therapy (3-DCRT) on local disease eradication and its potential role in improving survival is assessed. DESIGN: This review addresses aspects ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:11:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/7194538</link><title>Analysis of dose distribution in the 'Rind'--a volume outside the PTV--in 3-dimensional conformal radiation therapy of non-small cell lung cancer.</title><description>BACKGROUND AND PURPOSE: Appropriate planning target volume (PTV) definition is critical for local disease eradication in the treatment of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC). When margins are added to the gross tumour volume (GTV) in the standard way, the PTV formed may be too large to facilitate dose escalation due to normal tissue tolerance. To increase the feasibility of dose escalation with 3-dimensional conformal radiotherapy (3DCRT), this study examines an alternative method for the formation of the PTV in NSCLC. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:12:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/5373240</link><title>Factors influencing conformity index in radiotherapy for non-small cell lung cancer.</title><description>The radiotherapy conformity index (CI) is a useful tool to quantitatively assess the quality of radiotherapy treatment plans, and represents the relationship between isodose distributions and target volume. A conformity index of unity implies high planning target volume (PTV) coverage and minimal unnecessary irradiation of surrounding tissues. We performed this analysis to describe the CI for lung cancer 3-dimensional conformal radiotherapy (3DCRT) and to identify clinical and technical determinants of CI, as it is not known which factors are associated with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:13:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6711048</link><title>Dose escalation of chart in non-small cell lung cancer: is three-dimensional conformal radiation therapy really necessary?</title><description>PURPOSE: To evaluate, preclinically, the potential for dose escalation of continuous, hyperfractionated, accelerated radiation therapy (CHART) for non small-cell lung cancer (NSCLC), we examined the strategy of omission of elective nodal irradiation with and without the application of three-dimensional conformal radiation technology (3DCRT). METHODS AND MATERIALS: 2D, conventional therapy plans were designed according to the specifications of CHART for 18 patients with NSCLC (Stages Ib, IIb, IIIa, and IIIb). Further plans were generated with the omission of elective nodal irradiation (ENI) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:14:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6711829</link><title>Accelerated radiation therapy, seven fractions per week, for advanced head and neck cancer--a feasibility study.</title><description>AIM: The feasibility and improved efficacy of six conventional fractions per week has previously been proven in a Danish randomized trial. We tested the tolerance and efficacy of seven conventional fractions per week using a concomitant boost technique. METHODS: From September 1996 to May 1998, 20 patients with squamous cancer of the head and neck were treated with radiation alone. The site of disease was oropharynx in 35%, larynx in 30%, oral cavity 20%, and hypopharynx in 15%. All patients had ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7138-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7138_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:15:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6710997</link><title>New chemotherapy combinations with docetaxel in the treatment of patients with non-small cell lung cancer.</title><description>The modest antitumor activity and clinical benefit of conventional platinum-containing multidrug regimens in locally advanced and metastatic non-small cell lung cancer have provided the impetus for the development of novel combinations. The promising single-agent activity of docetaxel makes it an obvious candidate for incorporation into active programs. The Irish Clinical Oncology Research Group is conducting a phase I-II evaluation of a three-drug combination of docetaxel, ifosfamide, and cisplatin with lenograstim support in patients with stages III-IV non-small cell lung cancer. Preliminary ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>