<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:10" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jasmithoffice/article/2035800</link><title>The Cambridge History of the Bible</title><description>Volume 3 covers the effects of the Bible on the history of the West between the Reformation and the publication of the New English Bible. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MonicaBerti/article/4108409</link><title>Review: [Frammenti della Commedia Greca e del Mimo nella Sicilia e nella Magna Grecia]</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ncory79/article/6705563</link><title>The Disease Burden Associated With Overweight and Obesity</title><description>Context  Overweight and obesity are increasing dramatically in the United States and most likely contribute substantially to the burden of chronic health conditions.Objective  To describe the relationship between weight status and prevalence of health conditions by severity of overweight and obesity in the US population.Design and Setting  Nationally representative cross-sectional survey using data from the Third National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES III), which was conducted in 2 phases from 1988 to 1994.Participants  A total of 16,884 adults, 25 years ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keithhouston/article/9254474</link><title>Abbreviations</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9407969</link><title>Cherry-Picking Sartorial Identities in Cherry-Blossom Land: Uniforms and Uniformity in Japan</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:44">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8379954</link><title>ARTS D'ISLAM: CHEFS-D'OEUVRES DE LA COLLECTION KHALILI BY J M ROGERS ET AL.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:16">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8379934</link><title>THE MOURNERS: TOMB SCULPTURES FROM THE COURT OF BURGUNDY BY SOPHIE JUGIE</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/468012</link><title>Newcountries in Europe - Research, development and innovation strategies vs bibliometric data</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lmichan/article/10226997</link><title>Alone or together: examples from history research</title><description>Individualistic nature of research in the humanities is a common fact, as well as the notion that boundaries in humanities are poorly defined. Using citation analysis we have to take into account differences in citation practices not only between humanities and sciences but also within narrower fields of humanities. In the current study we observe differences between publication behaviour of historians and archaeologists, examine some aspects of citation practices in those fields, and show their effect on visibility. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/5324492</link><title>Looking for Class: Days and Nights at Oxford and Cambridge</title><description>An irresistible, entertaining peek into the privileged realm of Wordsworth and Wodehouse, Chelsea Clinton and Hugh Grant, Looking for Class offers a hilarious account of one man’s year at Oxford and Cambridge -- the garden parties and formal balls, the high-minded debates and drinking Olympics. From rowing in an exclusive regatta to learning lessons in love from a Rhodes Scholar, Bruce Feiler’s enlightening, eye-popping adventure will forever change your view of the British upper class, a world romanticized but rarely seen. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>