<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:50" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sutterlibrarian/article/265777</link><title>Teratogenic hearing loss.</title><description>Congenital hearing loss continues to be a devastating and disabling affliction in our society. In an effort to promote early recognition and treatment of hearing impairment in children, the Joint Committee on Infant Hearing has established a series of risk factors that place a newborn or infant at risk for hearing loss. These factors have been selected based on either genetic evidence of inherited familial hearing loss, acquired hearing loss from either known or unknown causative agents, or multifactorial inheritance that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/walke2mj/article/6211801</link><title>Phonemic restoration by hearing-impaired listeners with mild to moderate sensorineural hearing loss</title><description>The auditory system is capable of perceptually restoring inaudible portions of speech. This restoration may be compromised as a result of hearing impairment, particularly if it is combined with advanced age, because of degradations in the bottom-up and top-down processes. To test this hypothesis, phonemic restoration was quantitatively measured with hearing-impaired listeners of varying ages and degrees of hearing impairment, as well as with a normal hearing control group. The results showed that the restoration benefit was negatively correlated with both ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sutterlibrarian/article/265776</link><title>Teratogenic hearing loss: a clinical perspective.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: The Joint Committee on Infant Hearing recently published a series of indicators that place a neonate at risk for hearing loss. Included among these risk factors are environmental teratogens capable of negatively impacting the developing auditory system. This article serves to revisit and update potential environmental teratogens. The characteristic clinical presentation with audiometric, electrophysiologic, and temporal bone findings as well as available treatment options are discussed. DATA SOURCES: A Medline search encompassing the latter half of this century was undertaken ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/VesnaCMK/article/10851937</link><title>Sensorineural hearing loss in postmeningitic children.</title><description>To establish the proportion of children who develop sensorineural hearing loss after bacterial meningitis and to correlate such loss with patient factors. Retrospective case review. McMaster University Children's Hospital, a tertiary referral center. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kgss1/article/6796632</link><title>Protective effects of N-acetylcysteine on noise-induced hearing loss in guinea pigs.</title><description>Increasing evidence suggests the involvement of oxidative stress in noise-induced hearing loss. The present study analysed, in an animal experimental model, the time course of the pathogenic mechanisms of noise-induced cochlear damage and the efficacy of the antioxidant drug N-acetylcysteine in reducing noise ototoxicity. Animals were divided into two groups, exposed to noise one treated with N-acetylcysteine for 3 days and one (the control group) with saline. Acoustic trauma was induced by a continuous pure tone of 6 kHz, at 120 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hb124/article/5664984</link><title>Bilateral progressive hearing loss and vestibular dysfunction with inner ear antibodies</title><description>Autoimmune inner ear disease (AIED) is a clinical syndrome of uncertain etiology. We present the neuro-otological findings of 2 cases of bilateral hearing loss, dizziness and the antibody profiles of the inner ears. Case 1 had bilateral progressive hearing loss, vestibular dysfunction and abnormal eye movement as the disease progressed. She had inner ear antibodies against 42 and 58 kDa protein antigency on Western blot immune assay, and responded to glycocorticosteroid but not to immunosuppressant treatment. Intratympanic steroid injection temporally eliminated her ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/roc/article/11053708</link><title>From Stethoscopes to Headphones: An Acoustic Spatialization of Subjectivity</title><description>ABSTRACT Working from a phenomenological position, the author investigates ?in-head? acoustic localization in the context of the historical development of modern listening. Starting from the development of the stethoscope in the early 19th century, he traces novel techniques for generating space within the body and extrapolates from them into contemporary uses of headphones in sound art. The first half of the essay explores the history, techniques and technology of ?in-head? acoustics; the second half presents three sound artists who creatively generate ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:44:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/walke2mj/article/6525988</link><title>Young People: Taking Few Precautions Against Hearing Loss in Discotheques</title><description>This study evaluated adolescents' music-listening risk and protective behaviors in discotheques. While frequently standing close to the loudspeakers, taking few breaks, and hardly using hearing-protection devices, many are at risk of developing permanent hearing loss. Assessing visiting mode may be a first and quick screener to identify adolescents at risk. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:44:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keiichi/article/813189</link><title>Effects of hearing loss and spectral shaping on identification and neural response patterns of stop-consonant stimuli</title><description>In order to determine the effects of hearing loss and spectral shaping on a dynamic spectral speech cue, behavioral identification and neural response patterns of stop-consonant stimuli varying along the /b-d-g/ place-of-articulation continuum were measured from 11 young adults (mean age=27 years) and 10 older adults (mean age=55.2 years) with normal hearing, and compared to those from 10 older adults (mean age=61.3 years) with mild-to-moderate hearing impairment. Psychometric functions and N1-P2 cortical evoked responses were obtained using consonant-vowel (CV) stimuli with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:45:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ucbpdku/article/9600918</link><title>The quantitative relation between sensory cell loss and hearing thresholds</title><description>On the basis of experimental data obtained from 420 noise-exposed animals (chinchilla), the amount of sensory cell loss has been quantitatively related to the amount of permanent threshold shift at eight audiometric test frequencies between 0.125 and 16 kHz. The noise exposures, which varied extensively in spectrum, intensity and duration, produced permanent threshold shifts that ranged from 0 to 70 dB across a broad range of test frequencies. These data show: (1) consistent outer hair cell losses with less than 5 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>