<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7145">why do cats purr</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:45:50" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/HEIRS/article/3438141</link><title>Protein kinase C contributes to abnormal capsaicin responses in DRG neurons from cats with feline interstitial cystitis.</title><description>Interstitial cystitis (IC) is a painful disorder which affects urinary bladder function in cats and humans. We have used patch clamp techniques to examine the possibility that the properties of primary afferent neurons are changed in feline interstitial cystitis (FIC). We measured transient receptor potential vanilloid receptor 1 (TRPV1) responses to capsaicin (CAPS) in dorsal root ganglion (DRG) neurons (L4-S3) from normal cats and cats with FIC. We show that FIC neurons are increased in size and exhibit CAPS responses which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/7329172</link><title>From the Editors Why Aren't Business Schools More Global and What Can Management Educators Do About It?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:27">http://www.citeulike.org/group/7555/article/1297506</link><title>Time Series Prediction Competition: The CATS Benchmark</title><description>This paper presents the CATS Benchmark and the results of the competition organised during the IJCNN'04 conference in Budapest. Twenty-four papers and predictions have been submitted and seventeen have been selected. The goal of the competition was the prediction of 100 missing values divided into five groups of twenty consecutive values. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:48:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dullhunk/article/8239288</link><title>How Cats Lap: Water Uptake by Felis catus</title><description>Animals have developed a range of drinking strategies depending on physiological and environmental constraints. Vertebrates with incomplete cheeks use their tongue to drink; the most common example is the lapping of cats and dogs. We show that the domestic cat (Felis catus) laps by a subtle mechanism based on water adhesion to the dorsal side of the tongue. A combined experimental and theoretical analysis reveals that Felis catus exploits fluid inertia to defeat gravity and pull liquid into the mouth. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:48:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11442995</link><title>Self-Enhancement and Cardiovascular Reactivity: Limitations of the Hemodynamic Profile-Compensation Deficit (HP-CD) Model of Blood Pressure Regulation</title><description>We examined the consistency of results obtained when examining the relationship between self-enhancement and cardiovascular reactivity via analysing raw cardiovascular data and compared this with the Hemodynamic Profile-Compensation Deficit (HP-CD) model of blood pressure regulation (James, Gregg, Matyas, Hughes, &amp; Howard, 2012) method. A sample of 112 male participants underwent a computer-based task three times in three weeks. Our results indicate that significant results for self-enhancement and hemodynamic cardiovascular reactivity found using raw cardiovascular data were non-significant when HP-CD model was ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:49:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/4688825</link><title>Why learning from failure isn’t easy (and what to do about it): Innovation trauma at Sun Microsystems☆</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/provero/article/7325161</link><title>Observation learning in cats.</title><description>In two experiments cats acquired a stimulus-controlled approach or avoidance response by observational or conventional shaping procedures. Observer cats acquired the avoidance response (hurdle jumping in response to a buzzer stimulus) significantly faster and made fewer errors than cats that were conventionally trained. Observer cats acquired the approach response (lever pressing for food in response to a light stimulus) with significantly fewer errors than cats that were conventionally trained. In some cases, observer cats committed one or no errors while reaching ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dhooper/article/989012</link><title>Iatrogenic hyperadrenocorticism in 12 cats.</title><description>Iatrogenic hyperadrenocorticism is an extremely rare condition in cats. Twelve cats with a medical history of progressive skin lesions and long-term treatment with corticosteroids were retrospectively studied. Noncutaneous signs in the cats were variable and included anorexia, lethargy, polydipsia, polyuria, and atrophy of the thigh muscles. Laboratory abnormalities included leukocytosis, elevated alanine aminotransferase levels, and hyperglycemia. Transient diabetes mellitus was a secondary complication in four cats, and transient hypothyroidism was suspected in four cats. The mean time for regression of signs ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:51:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/misonneh/article/10345714</link><title>Part 3: Pharmacogenetic variability in phase II anticancer drug metabolism.</title><description>Equivalent drug doses may lead to wide interpatient variability in drug response to anticancer therapy. Known determinants that may affect the pharmacological response to a drug are, among others, nongenetic factors, including age, gender, use of comedication, and liver and renal function. Nonetheless, these covariates do not explain all the observed interpatient variability. Differences in genetic constitution among patients have been identified to be important ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7145-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7145_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:51:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7406933</link><title>The impact of task controllability on perceived control and cardiovascular processes</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>