<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:19:47" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:19:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akshayk/article/2972987</link><title>Pig Latin: A Not-so-foreign Language for Data Processing</title><description>There is a growing need for ad-hoc analysis of extremely large data sets, especially at internet companies where innovation critically depends on being able to analyze terabytes of data collected every day. Parallel database products, e.g., Teradata, offer a solution, but are usually prohibitively expensive at this scale. Besides, many of the people who analyze this data are entrenched procedural programmers, who find the declarative, SQL style to be unnatural. The success of the more procedural map-reduce programming model, and its ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/camershon/article/11053525</link><title>Policy Gatekeepers in Latin American Legislatures</title><description>Legislators who control the congressional agenda have a significant advantage over the membership at large. Policy gatekeepers can restrict change to outcomes they prefer over the status quo and can use this prerogative to keep a legislative party or coalition unified. This article examines agenda-setting rules in 26 Latin American chambers, shows why the institutional structure is theoretically relevant, and reveals some implications for policymaking with evidence from Argentina, Chile, and Mexico. Majority leaders in the Argentine and Chilean lower chambers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ycnanzeravla/article/9943041</link><title>A description of rare and important Medina imprints in the University of New Mexico Library</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:31:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emerson/article/4311341</link><title>Active help systems</title><description>Good on-line help systems are of crucial importance for the computer systems of the future. An increased functionality (required by the many different tasks which a user wants to do) will lead to an increased complexity. Empirical investigations have shown that on the average only 40% of the functionality of complex computer systems are used. Passive help systems (which require that the user requests help explicitly from the system) are of little use if the user does not know the existence ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:32:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/y1234/article/12534123</link><title>Pig Meat and Carcass Quality</title><description>This chapter contains sections titled: * Introduction * Marketing * Consumption patterns * Quality assurance * Pig meat quality * Meat from entire male pigs * Shape and meatiness * Carcass quality and grading standards * Carcass yield: killing-out percentage (ko%) * Choice of carcass weight and carcass fatness * Problems of variation * Manipulation of carcass quality by control of feeding * Manipulation of slaughter pig value by control of the production process ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:35:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/oliverchoihk/article/10155320</link><title>Brazil, a review of agricultural policies.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:39:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tuiqiao/article/5345397</link><title>Latin American Studies in the People's Republic of China</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:39:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/13074352</link><title>China Matters: China’s Economic Impact in Latin America</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:40:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nlarkin/article/11487086</link><title>The Age of Insecurity: Violence and Social Disorder in the New Latin America</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/paolaaguilar/article/11572168</link><title>The Rise and Decline of Economic Structuralism in Latin America: New Dimensions</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>