<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/balathandayutham/article/7804704</link><title>Customer Satisfaction Surveys and Barometers</title><description>Customer satisfaction research methodologies may be divided, according to their content and objectives, into qualitative and quantitative research (Dutka, 1995). The main aim of qualitative research is to obtain detailed information and additional explanations on customersâ attitude and opinions. This justifies the exploratory nature of qualitative research. The main characteristics of qualitative research include the following (Taylor and Bogdan, 1975) Open-ended (probing) questions are used, and thus customer responses are not given in a predefined format. The number of respondents ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:49:21">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1461783</link><title>Risk Sharing, the Cost of Equity and the Optimal Capital Structure of the Regulated Firm</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:50:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rsr2001/article/345903</link><title>Stones from bowel disease.</title><description>Kidney stones are increased in patients with bowel disease, particularly those who have had resection of part of their gastrointestinal tract. These stones are usually CaOx, but there is a marked increase in the tendency to form uric acid stones, as well, particularly in patients with colon resection. These patients all share a tendency to chronic volume contraction due to loss of water and salt in diarrheal stool, which leads to decreased urine volumes. They also have decreased absorption, and therefore ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:53:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/224262</link><title>EDITORIAL</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:53:45">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7606614</link><title>The parity of the number of quasigroups</title><description>Let I ( n ) be the number of isomorphism classes of quasigroups of order n . Despite prior enumerations showing that I ( n ) is odd for 1≤ n ≤11 , we find that I (12) is even. We also give a method for finding the parity of I ( n ) , which we use to show that I ( n ) is odd for n 13,14,15,16,17,19,21 . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:57:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rahernan/article/6048330</link><title>TOURIST SATISFACTION AND DISSATISFACTION</title><description>Satisfaction surveys usually include evaluations of different destination attributes on an ordinal scale. On such a scale, the mid-point of which is indifference, the tourist can express his/her satisfaction or dissatisfaction with each attribute. In this study it is suggested that some of the tourists’ negative or unsatisfactory experiences need to be defined within a specific context of evaluation. An analysis is made of the differences and the complementary nature of the concepts and measurements of satisfaction and dissatisfaction during the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:33">http://www.citeulike.org/article/58935</link><title>Plutarque: Oeuvres morales. Tome XV, 2e partie. Traite 72: Sur les notions communes, contre les stoiciens</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:02:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/10869685</link><title>Age, exercise, and coding performance.</title><description>We investigated the effects of exercise on the coding performance of young and older subjects. Hypotheses were tested that exercise either facilitates spatial localization or reduces susceptibility to distraction in older subjects. In a balanced design, we administered Digit Symbol and Symbol Digit coding tasks to exercisers and nonexercisers at two age levels under conditions of low or high within-task interference. The findings showed higher ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:05:00">http://www.citeulike.org/group/318/article/497353</link><title>Kidney stones</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7154-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7154_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:06:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NIlz/article/13053348</link><title>Patient satisfaction: Implications and predictors of success.</title><description>Patient satisfaction is an individual's cognitive evaluation of, and emotional reaction to, his or her health-care experience. This concept is increasing in importance as survey data are being used by health-care facilities for self-assessment, accreditation requirements, and compensation formulas. High patient satisfaction is associated with increased market share, financial gains, decreased malpractice claims, and improved reimbursement rates. Modifiable factors that contribute to satisfaction include physician-patient ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>