<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:48">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10888/article/12556280</link><title>The Initial State of Students Taking an Introductory Physics MOOC</title><description>As part of a larger research project into massively open online courses (MOOCs), we have investigated student background, as well as student participation in a physics MOOC with a laboratory component. Students completed a demographic survey and the Force and Motion Conceptual Evaluation at the beginning of the course. While the course is still actively running, we have tracked student participation over the first five weeks of the eleven-week course. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:08">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10888/article/12723846</link><title>Participation And performance In 8.02x Electricity And Magnetism: The First Physics MOOC From MITx</title><description>Massive Open Online Courses are an exciting new avenue for instruction and research, yet they are full of unknowns. In the Spring of 2013, MITx released its first introductory physics MOOC through the edX platform, generating a total enrollment of 43,000 students from around the world. We describe the population of participants in terms of their age, gender, level of education, and country of origin, highlighting both the diversity of 8.02x enrollees as well as gender gap and retention. Using three midterm exams and the final as waypoints, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:14:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/voiklis/article/10240057</link><title>Children's understanding of mind: Constructivist but theory-like</title><description>Although in general agreement with Carpendale &amp; Lewis&amp;apos;s (C&amp;L&amp;apos;s) claims, I argue that (1) gradual development is better supported by within-task eye gaze/verbal comparisons; (2) gradual development and social construction do not contradict the theory-theory view; (3) there is good evidence for an early developing self-other distinction; and (4) the languageâfalse belief link could be mediated by parental talk. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:19:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/richpb7/article/13124572</link><title>Do Professors Matter?: Using an a/B Test to Evaluate the Impact of Instructor Involvement on MOOC Student Outcomes</title><description>This research investigates the impact professors, and other instructional staff, have on student content knowledge acquisition in a physical science MOOC offered through the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. An A/B test was used to randomly assign MOOC participants in either a control group (with no instructional interaction) or an intervention group (in which the professor and teaching assistants responded to comments in the discussion and complied summary weekly feedback statements) to identify the differences in learning outcomes, participation rates, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:20:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dullhunk/article/1835579</link><title>Education, Education, Education: The Best Bits of Ted Wragg</title><description>&lt;P&gt;When New Labour came into office in the UK 1997, its commitment to "Education, Education, Education" captured the imagination of the public. This collection of articles from 1998 to the present day exposes the real state of education during this period, when educational policy has never been far from the headlines. &lt;br&gt;No one escapes Ted's sharp-shooting wit: from the blamers and shamers who try to turn teacher-bashing into a national pastime to the pale policy wonks in the Department of Education, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:23:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MaineC/article/732895</link><title>Accurate Methods for the Statistics of Surprise and Coincidence</title><description>Much work has been done on the statistical analysis of text. In some cases reported in the literature, inappropriate statistical methods have been used, and statistical significance of results have not been addressed. In particular, asymptotic normality assumptions have often been used unjustifiably, leading to flawed results.This assumption of normal distribution limits the ability to analyze rare events. Unfortunately rare events do make up a large fraction of real text.However, more applicable methods based on likelihood ratio tests are available that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:25:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dasokalee/article/10957750</link><title>A Pedagogy of Abundance or a Pedagogy to Support Human Beings? Participant Support on Massive Open Online Courses</title><description>This paper examines how emergent technologies could influence the design of learning environments. It will pay particular attention to the roles of educators and learners in creating networked learning experiences on massive open online courses (MOOCs). The research shows that it is possible to move from a pedagogy of abundance to a pedagogy that supports human beings in their learning through the active creation of resources and learning places by both learners and course facilitators. This pedagogy is based on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/c-jguo/article/10957744</link><title>Using mLearning and MOOCs to Understand Chaos, Emergence, and Complexity in Education</title><description>In this paper, we look at how the massive open online course (MOOC) format developed by connectivist researchers and enthusiasts can help analyze the complexity, emergence, and chaos at work in the field of education today. We do this through the prism of a MobiMOOC, a six-week course focusing on mLearning that ran from April to May 2011. MobiMOOC embraced the core MOOC components of self-organization, connectedness, openness, complexity, and the resulting chaos, and, as such, serves as an interesting paradigm ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:32:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11921288</link><title>By Ted Bastin - Combinatorial Physics</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7155-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7155_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:35:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dasokalee/article/10957754</link><title>The Technological Dimension of a Massive Open Online Course: The Case of the CCK08 Course Tools</title><description>In 2008, a new term emerged in the already crowded e-learning landscape: MOOC, or massive open online course. Lifelong learners can now use various tools to build and manage their own learning networks, and MOOCs may provide opportunities to test such networks. This paper focuses on the technological aspects of one MOOC, the Connectivism and Connective Knowledge (CCK08) course, in order to investigate lifelong learners? attitudes towards learning network technologies. The research framework is represented by three perspectives: (a) lifelong learning ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>