<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:07" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/12657690</link><title>Recipe recommendation using ingredient networks</title><description>The recording and sharing of cooking recipes, a human activity dating back thousands of years, naturally became an early and prominent social use of the web. The resulting online recipe collections are repositories of ingredient combinations and cooking methods whose large-scale and variety yield interesting insights about both the fundamentals of cooking and user preferences. At the level of an individual ingredient we measure whether it tends to be essential or can be dropped or added, and whether its quantity can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thenose/article/4134539</link><title>Complications of microdebrider-assisted powered intracapsular tonsillectomy and adenoidectomy.</title><description>OBJECTIVES: To study complications of powered intracapsular tonsillectomy and adenoidectomy (PITA) in pediatric patients with obstructive sleep apnea (OSA). STUDY DESIGN: Retrospective chart review and long-term follow-up in office or by telephone interview. METHODS: We studied 278 patients who underwent PITA between September 2000 and October 2002. Outcome measures were postoperative bleeding, velopharyngeal insufficiency, need for hospital readmission, tonsil regrowth, and return of snoring or sleep apnea symptoms. RESULTS: All 278 children treated by PITA had immediate resolution of symptoms of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:22:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thenose/article/2999178</link><title>Efficacy of powered intracapsular tonsillectomy and adenoidectomy.</title><description>OBJECTIVES/HYPOTHESIS: We sought to determine the effectiveness of powered intracapsular tonsillectomy and adenoidectomy (PITA) in the treatment of children with moderately severe obstructive sleep apnea and to measure changes in quality of life that occur with such treatment. STUDY DESIGN: Prospective, nonrandomized clinical trial in an academic pediatric otolaryngology practice. METHODS: Convenience sample of children ages 3 to 12 years diagnosed with obstructive sleep apnea of moderate severity, defined as an apnea-hypopnea index (AHI) between 5 and 20 on polysomnography. Children ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lucybuykx/article/10238448</link><title>A personalized recipe advice system to promote healthful choices</title><description>We present a prototype of a personalized recipe advice system, which facilitates its users to make health-aware meal choices based on past selections. To stimulate the adoption of a healthier lifestyle, a goal setting mechanism is applied in combination with personalized recipe suggestions. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:29:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Kovanen/article/10040385</link><title>Recipe recommendation using ingredient networks</title><description>The recording and sharing of cooking recipes, a human activity dating back thousands of years, naturally became an early and prominent social use of the web. The resulting online recipe collections are repositories of ingredient combinations and cooking methods whose large-scale and variety yield interesting insights about both the fundamentals of cooking and user preferences. At the level of an individual ingredient we measure whether it tends to be essential or can be dropped or added, and whether its quantity can be modified. We also construct two types ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:31:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lucybuykx/article/11862352</link><title>The Recipe, the Prescription and the Experiment</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:34:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/7108094</link><title>Intelligent food planning: personalized recipe recommendation</title><description>As the obesity epidemic takes hold across the world many medical professionals are referring users to online systems aimed at educating and persuading users to alter their lifestyle. The challenge for many of these systems is to increase initial adoption and sustain participation for sufficient time to have real impact on the life of its users. In this work we present some preliminary investigation into the design of a recipe recommender, aimed at educating and sustaining user participation, which makes tailored ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:35:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/6330857</link><title>Finding replaceable materials in cooking recipe texts considering characteristic cooking actions</title><description>The number of cooking recipe texts published on the Web is increasing in recent years. However, in general, cooking recipe texts have little flexibility. So, it is not always easy to retrieve cooking recipe texts that satisfy users' various demands. Therefore, it is necessary to create and offer recipes that suit the user's requirements. In this paper, we propose a method for finding replaceable materials considering characteristic cooking actions from a large amount of cooking recipe texts. The proposed method finds ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:37:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/8853465</link><title>Deriving a recipe similarity measure for recommending healthful meals</title><description>A recipe recommender system may stimulate healthful and varied eating, when the presented recipes fit the lifestyle of the user. As consumers face the barrier to change their eating and cooking behavior, we aim for a strategy to provide more healthful variations to routine recipes. In this paper, a similarity measure for recipes is derived by taking a user-centered approach. Such a measure can be used to recommend healthier alternatives to commonly selected meals, which are perceived to be similar. Recipes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7166-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7166_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:40:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrkn/article/10238447</link><title>Content-boosted matrix factorization for recommender systems: experiments with recipe recommendation</title><description>The Netflix prize has rejuvenated a widespread interest in the matrix factorization approach for collaborative filtering. We describe a simple algorithm for incorporating content information directly into this approach. We present experimental evidence using recipe data to show that this not only improves recommendation accuracy but also provides useful insights about the contents themselves that are otherwise unavailable. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>