<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:02" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/10962613</link><title>Friction in aluminium extrusion—part 2: A review of friction models for aluminium extrusion</title><description>This paper presents a review of recent development of the friction models for aluminium extrusion processes. The friction models used in aluminium extrusion can be classified as three categories: classic friction models, empirical friction models and physically based friction models. A comparative study of the friction models for the bearing channel of hot aluminium extrusion dies was conducted and in the current testing conditions, full sticking friction appeared to represent the interfacial contact between the hot aluminium and the die the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/6481245</link><title>Modelling of contact and friction in aluminium extrusion</title><description>A physical model capable of predicting the friction and sticking/slipping lengths in the bearing channel during unlubricated aluminium extrusion processes is presented. The model takes into account the pressure build up in the extrusion direction in relation with the bearing – extrudate friction and how it will be influenced by die geometry such as die angle and bearing length. The results show that a high friction coefficient in the bearing will increase the sticking length and shorten the slipping length. The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:46:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/10962614</link><title>Friction in aluminium extrusion—Part 1: A review of friction testing techniques for aluminium extrusion</title><description>In the aluminium extrusion process, the friction at the workpiece/tooling interface is a highly complex phenomenon, affected by local temperature, relative velocity, contact pressure, geometry and tooling surface roughness, etc. Despite of this understanding, general rules for the selection of friction testing techniques have not been established yet. This paper summarises the recent development of the friction testing techniques for aluminium extrusion processes and detailed comparisons of these techniques are presented. Of the existing friction testing techniques, the combination of extrusion ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/10040541</link><title>Friction conditions in the bearing area of an aluminium extrusion process</title><description>In aluminium extrusion processes, friction inside the bearing channel is important for controlling the surface quality of the extrusion products. The contact materials show a large hardness difference, one being hot aluminium, and the other being hardened tool steel. Further, the contact pressure is high, which means that contact at the bearing–aluminium interface is fully plastic. A load dependent fully plastic friction model has been developed for such fully plastic contact conditions. This roughness based contact model is applied on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:49:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/8404507</link><title>Optimisation of flow balance and isothermal extrusion of aluminium using finite-element simulations</title><description>There is significant demand to reduce variations in the shape and mechanical properties of the aluminium extrusion process to meet tighter tolerance requirements. To reduce variations, the flow and temperature evolution in the container and die must be controlled. To study how the process parameters influence the temperature evolution and the material flow, the effects of ram speed, initial temperature distribution in the billet and container cooling rate have been studied. This work is divided into three parts which examine the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:53:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/5376487</link><title>Experimental and finite element simulations of cold pressure welding of aluminium by divergent extrusion</title><description>In the present investigation, the aptness of the divergent extrusion process in simulating cold pressure welding (CPW) is further documented and explored. As a starting point, the situation existing both prior to and after cold bonding is adequately reproduced using finite element (FE) modelling. Combined extrusion and joining experiments are then carried out to unravel the conditions under which cold bonding takes place in commercial purity aluminium. Based on three-point bend testing and fracture surface investigations in the scanning electron microscope ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:57:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/10472072</link><title>Identification of a friction model for the bearing channel of hot aluminium extrusion dies by using ball-on-disc tests</title><description>A physically-based friction model is developed based on the ball-on-disc test results. The model is verified by using double action extrusion tests. Good agreements between the FE predictions and experiments have been obtained, in terms of the extrudate length and steady-state extrusion load, indicating that ball-on-disc test is an effect way of characterizing the friction for the bearing channel of hot extrusion dies. The nature of friction in the bearing channel can be summarized as a pressure dependant process: formation of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/7244819</link><title>The role of creep and fatigue in determining the high-temperature behaviour of AISI H11 tempered steel for aluminium extrusion dies</title><description>The present study was aimed to analyze the effect of loading cycles on the behaviour of the AISI H11 tool steel commonly used for aluminium extrusion dies working at high temperatures and under high, cyclic stresses. A technological test method in which the specimen geometry resembled the mandrel of a hollow extrusion die was developed. Finite element analyses were performed to aid in determining specimen geometry and dimensions as well as the levels of stress to be applied to the specimen ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:02:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/10930307</link><title>Performance of gas nitrided and AlTiN coated AISI H13 hot work tool steel in aluminium extrusion</title><description>The performances of nitrided and AlTiN coated AISI H13 hot work tool steel samples were investigated under conditions similar to those encountered in aluminium extrusion. The compound layer on the surface of the gas nitrided tool steel is entirely removed during sliding contact with aluminium after a sliding length of 3900 m, under a contact load of 60 N exposing the underlying diffusion zone to the aluminium counterface. Aluminium is known to have a strong tendency to adhere to steel and forms an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7167-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7167_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/numponormmahayotsanun/article/11087137</link><title>Sliding wear of CrN, AlCrN and AlTiN coated AISI H13 hot work tool steels in aluminium extrusion</title><description>The frictional forces arising from sliding contact with aluminium produce considerable shear stresses on the CrN coating that degrade its integrity and its adhesion to the substrate tool steel. The CrN coating suffers the most extensive wear damage. There is a net improvement in the sliding wear performance of the AlCrN coating owing to a multilayered structure and a much higher hardness. However, AlTiN outperforms both CrN and AlCrN in sliding contact against aluminium owing to its exceptionally high chemical resistance ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>