<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:16" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/benoitvalley/article/11657859</link><title>Relation of elastic properties of rocks to fabric</title><description>Variation of linear compressibility in ten rocks was compared with preferred orientation of mica, calcite, or quartz. Actual variation, measured at a confining pressure of 3 kb, was in close agreement with the variation calculated from preferred orientation, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:15:39">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1428/article/763789</link><title>Bayesian estimation of uncertainty in runoff prediction and the value of data: An application of the GLUE approach</title><description>This paper addresses the problem of evaluating the predictive uncertainty of TOPMODEL using the Bayesian Generalized Likelihood Uncertainty Estimation (GLUE) methodology in an application to the small Ringelbach research catchment in the Vosges, France. The wide range of parameter sets giving acceptable simulations is demonstrated, and uncertainty bands are presented based ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:16:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chunjean/article/4062201</link><title>The fabric of society: a proposal to investigate the emotional and sensory experience of wearing denim clothing</title><description>This paper introduces a project that intends to utilise research methods derived from experience within Art and Design, to investigate the sensory and emotional experience of wearing denim clothing in public. The researcher will provide an explanation of context and identify the range of research methods under consideration. The project is based on the premise that as a 21st century mass-produced product, denim typifies the processes inherent within design and commercial culture. Although culturally complex, its current ubiquity and 'ordinariness' make ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:21:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andreozzi/article/3069957</link><title>Experiences with the GLUE information schema in the LCG/EGEE production grid</title><description>A common information schema for the description of Grid resources and services is an essential requirement for interoperating Grid infrastructures, and its implementation interacts with every Grid component. In this context, the GLUE information schema was originally defined in 2002 as a joint project between the European DataGrid and DataTAG projects and the US iVDGL. The schema has major components to describe Computing and Storage Elements, and also generic Service and Site information. It has been used extensively in the LCG/EGEE ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:25:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jjacob/article/4826747</link><title>Analysis of Aqueous Glue Coating Proteins on the Silk Fibers of the Cob Weaver, Latrodectus hesperus†</title><description>Elucidation of the molecular composition and physical properties of spider glue is necessary to understand its function in the mechanics of the web and prey capture. Previous reports have indicated that components of the adhesive coating contain inorganic molecules, phosphorylated glycoproteins, lipids, and organic low-molecular mass (LMM) compounds. Using a proteomic strategy, we have investigated the viscid, aqueous components that coat different silk fiber types from the black widow spider, Latrodectus hesperus. After in-solution tryptic digestion of the aqueous protein material ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:26:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10433302</link><title>Comparative efficacy of anti-manic drugs in acute mania</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:28:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stargazers/article/1289006</link><title>The Lucifer Principle: A Scientific Expedition into the Forces of History</title><description>Now in a revised tenth-anniversary edition, The Lucifer Principle is a revolutionary work that explores the intricate relationships among genetics, human behavior, and culture to argue that evil is woven into our biological fabric. Intensely controversial and polarizing upon its initial publication, The Lucifer Principle is a sweeping narrative that challenges some of our most popular scientific assumptions. Drawing on evidence ranging from studies of the most primitive organisms to those on ants, apes, and humankind, Howard Bloom argues that nature ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:30:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lorenzana/article/10065253</link><title>Is There Glue in Cuprate Superconductors?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:34:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/googleuboy/article/11412790</link><title>Improving the mechanical properties of natural fibre fabric reinforced epoxy composites by alkali treatment</title><description>In this article, three bio-composites, i.e. flax, linen and bamboo fabric reinforced epoxy resin, were manufactured using a vacuum bagging technique. The influence of alkali treatment (with 5 wt% NaOH solution for 30 min) on tensile properties of flax, linen and bamboo single-strand yarns, surface morphology and mechanical properties (with respect to tensile and flexural properties) of the composites were investigated. It was found that the failure mechanism of single-strand fibres under tension consists of fibre breakage and slippage simultaneously. The alkali treatment ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:35:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7035621</link><title>New Prospects for the Drug Treatment of Generalized Anxiety Disorder A Systematic Review</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>