<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:45:23" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:45:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CYNTHIA231/article/9899870</link><title>Retrospective study of rehabilitation outcomes following spinal cord injury due to tumour</title><description>Retrospective study of rehabilitation outcomes following spinal cord injury due to tumour Spinal Cord advance online publication, October 11, 2011. doi:10.1038/sc.2011.103 Authors: M Tan &amp; P W New ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:45:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CYNTHIA231/article/10461583</link><title>Early acute management in adults with spinal cord injury: a clinical practice guideline for health-care professionals.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:45:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CYNTHIA231/article/9119815</link><title>Recovery following ischemic myelopathies and traumatic spinal cord lesions</title><description>Recovery following ischemic myelopathies and traumatic spinal cord lesions Spinal Cord advance online publication, April 5, 2011. doi:10.1038/sc.2011.31 Authors: G Scivoletto, L Laurenza, A Mammone, C Foti &amp; M Molinari ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:46:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maestrianeurouam/article/8825150</link><title>Effects of exercise training and inspiratory muscle training in spinal cord injury: a systematic review.</title><description>There are insufficient data to strongly support the use of exercise training or IMT for improved respiratory function in people with SCI. There is some evidence of efficacy of both regimens; however, the evidence is not of the best possible quality. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:46:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/minshady/article/4945048</link><title>Validity and responsiveness of the spinal cord index of function: an instrument on activity level</title><description>Validity and responsiveness of the spinal cord index of function: an instrument on activity level Spinal Cord advance online publication, June 16, 2009. doi:10.1038/sc.2009.57 Authors: C Johansson, P Bodin &amp; M Kreuter ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:46:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/minshady/article/4945046</link><title>Assessment of the sympathetic level of lesion in patients with spinal cord injury</title><description>Assessment of the sympathetic level of lesion in patients with spinal cord injury Spinal Cord advance online publication, June 23, 2009. doi:10.1038/sc.2009.61 Authors: C Putz, C H Fürstenberg, M Akbar, H J Gerner, B Wiedenhöfer &amp; R Rupp ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:47:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/minshady/article/4945044</link><title>A multi-centre study of the community needs of people with spinal cord injuries: the first 18 months</title><description>A multi-centre study of the community needs of people with spinal cord injuries: the first 18 months Spinal Cord advance online publication, June 16, 2009. doi:10.1038/sc.2009.65 Authors: P Kennedy, O Sherlock, M McClelland, D Short, J Royle &amp; C Wilson ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:47:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/minshady/article/4945047</link><title>Comparison of computed tomographic and magnetic resonance imaging in fracture healing after spinal injury</title><description>Comparison of computed tomographic and magnetic resonance imaging in fracture healing after spinal injury Spinal Cord advance online publication, June 16, 2009. doi:10.1038/sc.2009.59 Authors: R Warwick, J M Willatt, B Singhal, J Borremans &amp; T Meagher ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:47:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CYNTHIA231/article/9402414</link><title>The development of evidence-informed physical activity guidelines for adults with spinal cord injury</title><description>The development of evidence-informed physical activity guidelines for adults with spinal cord injury Spinal Cord advance online publication, June 7, 2011. doi:10.1038/sc.2011.63 Authors: K A Martin Ginis, A L Hicks, A E Latimer, D E R Warburton, C Bourne, D S Ditor, D L Goodwin, K C Hayes, N McCartney, A McIlraith, P Pomerleau, K Smith, J A Stone &amp; D L Wolfe ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:47:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CYNTHIA231/article/510631</link><title>The inter rater reliability of the original and of the modified Ashworth scale for the assessment of spasticity in patients with spinal cord injury.</title><description>Thirty patients with spinal cord injury (SCI) were randomly selected to participate in this study which evaluated the inter rater reliability of the original and of the modified Ashworth scale for the assessment of spasticity in the lower limbs. A doctor and a physiotherapist rated the muscle tone of hip adductors, hip extensors, hip flexors and ankle plantarflexors according to the original and to the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>