<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:08:32" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:08:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TEAM/article/3008952</link><title>The TEAM trial : Safety and efficacy of endovascular treatment of unruptured intracranial aneurysms in the prevention of aneurysmal hemorrhages: A randomized comparison with indefinite deferral of treatment in 2002 patients followed for 10 years</title><description>The management of patients with unruptured aneurysms remains controversial. Patients with unruptured aneurysms may suffer intracranial haemorrhage, but the incidence of this event is still debated; endovascular treatment may prevent rupture, but involves immediate risks. Hence, the balance of risks and benefits of endovascular treatment is uncertain. Here, we report the design of the TEAM trial, the first international, randomized, controlled trial comparing conservative management with endovascular treatment. Primary endpoint is mortality and morbidity (modified Rankin Score 3) from intracranial haemorrhage ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:10:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/els2006/article/13142186</link><title>Position Statement on Interdisciplinary Team Training in Geriatrics: An Essential Component of Quality Health Care for Older Adults</title><description>Interdisciplinary team training (IDT) is an important component of ensuring quality geriatric care delivery, which can be complex and time intensive, requiring coordination of many medical, psychosocial, and therapeutic interventions and professionals. The Partnership for Health in Aging (PHA), a loose coalition of more than 30 organizations representing healthcare professionals who care for older adults supported by the American Geriatrics Society, identified IDT training in geriatrics as a priority area in addressing the geriatrics workforce shortage described in the 2008 Institute ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:11:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jamesoliver/article/9178369</link><title>Adult congenital heart disease.</title><description>For a decade now, it has been recognized that optimal management of adult congenital heart disease (ACHD) requires a skilled multidisciplinary team. The size and complexity of the population of adults with congenital heart disease (CHD) are increasing. This article reviews the general considerations for giving an anesthetic to an adult with CHD for cardiac or noncardiac surgery and provides further elaboration for a variety of complex patient types. Lastly, the advantages of an organized multidisciplinary approach to patients with ACHD ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:13:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/syuusui/article/1230850</link><title>Underwater auditory localization by a swimming harbor seal (Phoca vitulina)</title><description>The underwater sound localization acuity of a swimming harbor seal (Phoca vitulina) was measured in the horizontal plane at 13 different positions. The stimulus was either a double sound (two 6-kHz pure tones lasting 0.5  s separated by an interval of 0.2  s) or a single continuous sound of 1.2  s. Testing was conducted in a 10-m-diam underwater half circle arena with hidden loudspeakers installed at the exterior perimeter. The animal was trained to swim along the diameter of the half circle and to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:14:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4082173</link><title>Scaling of body weight and fat content in fungus-gardening ant queens: does this explain why leaf-cutting ants found claustrally?</title><description>Abstract  Offspring traits are among the most important life history traits, yet we lack an adequate understanding of their role in social insect life history evolution. Colony founding in the fungus-gardening ants (Tribe Attini) is different from most other ant species because the queens forage during the founding phase. Queens of the most derived genus, Atta, are the only attines that exhibit the more typical claustral founding, where the queens seal themselves in a below-ground chamber and produce their first generation of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:18:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/syuusui/article/1283202</link><title>Mortality of harbor seal pups at different sites in the inland waters of Washington</title><description>We examined the mortality rates and causes of death of harbor seal (Phoca vitulina) pups in three regions of the inland waters of Washington (USA) in 1984. One hundred eight pups were collected during 239 searches of the shoreline areas near harbor seal haulout sites or through public reports. Minimum neonatal (up to 1 mo after birth) mortality rates at these regions ranged from 12% to 26% of the pups born. Neonatal mortality was highest in the Strait of Juan de ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:19:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/syuusui/article/1413687</link><title>Hematology and serum chemistry comparisons between free-ranging and rehabilitated harbor seal (Phoca vitulina richardsi) pups</title><description>The objectives of this study were to compare the hematology and serum chemistry values between free-ranging and stranded harbor seal (Phoca vitulina richardsi) pups and to ascertain how blood values of stranded pups changed during the rehabilitation process. Coincident with these comparisons, reference values were obtained for free-ranging pups. Stranded harbor seal pups (n = 28) recovered from areas between Pebble Beach and Moss Landing, California (USA) were admitted to The Marine Mammal Center, Sausalito, from March to May 1995, 1996, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:24:00">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14459/article/8446933</link><title>Tools for evaluating team performance in simulation-based training.</title><description>Teamwork training constitutes one of the core approaches for moving healthcare systems toward increased levels of quality and safety, and simulation provides a powerful method of delivering this training, especially for face-paced and dynamic specialty areas such as Emergency Medicine. Team performance measurement and evaluation plays an integral role in ensuring that simulation-based training for teams (SBTT) is systematic and effective. However, this component of SBTT systems is overlooked frequently. This article addresses this gap by providing a review and practical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:28:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/syuusui/article/1447513</link><title>A case of cleft palate in a Kuril seal (Phoca vitulina stejnegeri), from Hokkaido, Japan</title><description>A male pup Kuril seal (Phoca vitulina stejnegeri) from Hokkaido, Japan, was observed with a unilateral and total cleft of the primary palate. Complications included a supernumerary tooth, hypoplasia and asymmetry of the face, and deformation of the eyeball and external auditory meatus. An accompanying pneumonia may have resulted from water flowing into the respiratory system due to imperfect closure of the nostril by the cleft. No other abnormalities were found. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:32:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/BridgetM/article/5898950</link><title>Barriers and facilitators of multidisciplinary team working: a review.</title><description>Professionals from many different organisations can be involved in the care of a child, especially a child with special/complex needs. A literature review was undertaken to explore some of the barriers and facilitators of joint working with the aim of informing local practices. Different models of joint working and the barriers and facilitators to effective multidisciplinary team working were identified. Four of the most prominent themes for effective working were: co-location; key workers; appreciation for other agencies; communication and information sharing. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>