<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:07:15" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:07:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dayap/article/12255516</link><title>Weather cycles</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:10:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/castillo_grc/article/3358962</link><title>Weather Radar Technology Beyond NEXRAD</title><description>Report from the Committee on Weather Radar Technology and the National Research Council. Softcover. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nurban/article/10904035</link><title>Weather, Climate, and Worldviews: The Sources and Consequences of Public Perceptions of Changes in Local Weather Patterns*</title><description>Abstract This paper analyzes the changes Americans perceive to be taking place in their local weather and tests a series of hypotheses about why they hold these perceptions. Using data from annual nationwide surveys of the American public taken from 2008 to 2011, coupled with geographically specific measures of temperature and precipitation changes over that same period, the authors evaluate the relationship between perceptions of weather changes and actual changes in local weather. In addition, the survey data include measures of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:17:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nurban/article/264039</link><title>Diversity in Interpretations of Probability: Implications for Weather Forecasting</title><description>Over the last years, probability weather forecasts have become increasingly popular due in part to the development of ensemble forecast systems. Despite its widespread use in atmospheric sciences, probability forecasting remains a subtle and ambiguous way of representing the uncertainty related to a future meteorological situation. There are several schools of thought regarding the interpretation of probabilities, none of them without flaws, internal contradictions, or paradoxes. Usually, researchers tend to have personal views that are mostly based on intuition and follow ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:17:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nurban/article/12117647</link><title>Blowin’ in the Wind: Short-Term Weather and Belief in Anthropogenic Climate Change</title><description>Abstract A series of polls provides new tests for how weather influences public beliefs about climate change. Statewide data from 5000 random-sample telephone interviews conducted on 99 days over 2.5 yr (2010?12) are merged with temperature and precipitation indicators derived from U.S. Historical Climatology Network (USHCN) station records. The surveys carry a question designed around scientific consensus statements that climate change is happening now, caused mainly by human activities. Alternatively, respondents can state that climate change is not happening, or that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:21:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nurban/article/6591709</link><title>Bayesian Approach to Decision Making Using Ensemble Weather Forecasts</title><description>The economic value of ensemble-based weather or climate forecasts is generally assessed by taking the ensembles at “face value.” That is, the forecast probability is estimated as the relative frequency of occurrence of an event among a limited number of ensemble members. Despite the economic value of probability forecasts being based on the concept of decision making under uncertainty, in effect, the decision maker is assumed to ignore the uncertainty in estimating this probability. Nevertheless, many users are certainly aware of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:22:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akleeman/article/3360711</link><title>Probabilistic quantitative precipitation forecasting using Bayesian model averaging. Monthly Weather Review 135</title><description>and useful comments, and for providing data. They are also grateful to Patrick Tewson for implementing the UW Ensemble BMA website. This research was supported by the DoD Multidisciplinary University Research Initiative (MURI) program administered by the Office of Naval Research under Grant N00014-01-10745. Bayesian model averaging (BMA) is a statistical way of postprocessing forecast ensembles to create predictive probability density functions (PDFs) for weather quantities. It represents the predictive PDF as a weighted average of PDFs centered on the individual ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:26:43">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2208/article/7004355</link><title>Effects of mutations and growth conditions on lipid synthesis in Neurospora crassa.</title><description>A morphological mutant (col-2) of Neurospora, which is partially deficient in glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase (G-6-PD) activity and has lower levels of reduced nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide phosphate (NADPH), accumulated three-fold more triglycerides during log-phase growth than the wild-type strain. Increased lipid deposition was not found in other strains that included slow-growing morphological mutants, NADPH-deficient strains, G-6-PD-deficient mutants, wild-type revertants from col-2, and a cel, col-2 double mutant. The cel, col-2 strain was supplemented with an exogenous source of fatty acids because it cannot ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:29:51">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2208/article/7004327</link><title>Altered fatty acid distribution in mutants of Neurospora crassa.</title><description>Morphological mutants of Neurospora with decreased levels of reduced nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide phosphate (NADPH) and reduced nicotinamide ad enine dinucleotide (NADH) contained only 20% as much of a polyunsaturated fatty acid (linolenic acid) as the wild type in both the phospholipid and neutral lipid fractions. There was an excellent correlation between linolenic acid levels and morphological appearance as a function of total NADPH content, but no correlation with NADH content. The linolenic acid deficiency was balanced by a relative increase in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:30:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scis0000001/article/1296642</link><title>A Simulated Network of Weather Stations - A Laboratory for the Course Dkom</title><description>This article describes the simulation of a network of weather-stations, which all can poll another station to get its weather-status or can send a message to an arbitrary weather-station. The services that are offered on the several OSI-layers are shown, as well as the internal function of each layer. I will also present some quantitative results and a very brief overview over possible correctness proof strategies. Contents 1 The System There are up to 15 Countries, which will build a network... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>