<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:48" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zhihui42/article/2016454</link><title>Blink-Perturbed Saccades in Monkey. I. Behavioral Analysis</title><description>Goossens, H.H.L.M. and A. J. Van Opstal. Blink-Perturbed Saccades in Monkey. I. Behavioral Analysis. J. Neurophysiol. 83: 3411-3429, 2000. Saccadic eye movements are thought to be influenced by blinking through premotor interactions, but it is still unclear how. The present paper describes the properties of blink-associated eye movements and quantifies the effect of reflex blinks on the latencies, metrics, and kinematics of saccades in the monkey. In particular, it is examined to what extent the saccadic system accounts for blink-related perturbations ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:55:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PaperCollector/article/7833036</link><title>Blink detection robust to various facial poses</title><description>Applications based on eye-blink detection have increased, as a result of which it is essential for eye-blink detection to be robust and non-intrusive irrespective of the changes in the user's facial pose. However, most previous studies on camera-based blink detection have the disadvantage that their performances were affected by the facial pose. They also focused on blink detection using only frontal facial images. To overcome these disadvantages, we developed a new method for blink detection, which maintains its accuracy despite changes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:57:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zhihui42/article/2016486</link><title>Time on task and blink effects on saccade duration</title><description>Changes in saccade duration, saccade amplitude and slope of the regression line relating amplitude and duration were assessed during a 2 hour air traffic control simulating task. Mean duration significantly increased as a function of time on task (TOT). Saccade amplitude decreased during the beginning part of the two hour period, increased in the middle and decreased in the final part of task performance. Differences in saccade duration were also assessed for saccades occurring during and independent of eye blinks. When ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:00:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/almostc/article/938256</link><title>Abnormal classical eye-blink conditioning in autism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:02:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/WillWelby/article/8185772</link><title>Blink and Wink Detection for Mouse Pointer Control</title><description>A Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) system that is designed for individuals with severe disabilities to simulate control of a traditional computer mouse is introduced. The camera-based system monitors a user’s eyes and allows the user to simulate clicking the mouse using voluntary blinks and winks. For users who can control head movements and can wink with one eye while keeping their other eye visibly open, the system allows complete use of a typical mouse, including moving the pointer, left and right clicking, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:06:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/WillWelby/article/8185371</link><title>Just Blink Your Eyes: A Head-Free Gaze Tracking System</title><description>We propose a head-free, easy-setup gaze tracking system designed for a gaze-based Human-Computer Interaction. Our system enables the user to interact with the computer soon after catching the user's eye blinks. The user can move his/her head freely since the system keeps tracking the user's eye. In addition, our system only needs a 10 second calibration procedure at the very first time of use. An eye tracking method based on our unique eye blink detection and a sophisticated gaze estimation method ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:08:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PaperCollector/article/11857198</link><title>Blink-related momentary activation of the default mode network while viewing videos</title><description>It remains unknown why we generate spontaneous eyeblinks every few seconds, more often than necessary for ocular lubrication. Because eyeblinks tend to occur at implicit breakpoints while viewing videos, we hypothesized that eyeblinks are actively involved in the release of attention. We show that while viewing videos, cortical activity momentarily decreases in the dorsal attention network after blink onset but increases in the default-mode network implicated in internal processing. In contrast, physical blackouts of the video do not elicit such reciprocal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:11:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/filipmarcinowski/article/8897979</link><title>Observations on the blink reflex.</title><description>The blink reflex and its equivalent glabella tap reflex are behavioural motor responses normally found in neonates and in the physiological startle reflex. Historically, it was described by Overend in 1896 and soon afterwards by McCarthy and by Bekhterev who disputed its origins. Kugelberg in 1952 recorded the early-latency R1 and the late-latency R2 electromyographic responses from orbicularis oculi and considered the blink reflex to be 'a true skin reflex'. The mechanisms and clinical diagnostic value are discussed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:15:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ybysk/article/9608583</link><title>Characterizing the Spontaneous Blink Generator: An Animal Model</title><description>Although spontaneous blinking is one of the most frequent human movements, little is known about its neural basis. We developed a rat model of spontaneous blinking to identify and better characterize the spontaneous blink generator. We monitored spontaneous blinking for 55 min periods in normal conditions and after the induction of mild dry eye or dopaminergic drug challenges. The normal spontaneous blink rate was 5.3 ± 0.3 blinks/min. Dry eye or 1 mg/kg apomorphine significantly increased and 0.1 mg/kg haloperidol significantly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7180_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:18:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fcummins/article/7262958</link><title>Maturation of blink reflex in children.</title><description>The blink reflex was examined in 57 subjects aged from neonate to adult in the alert state. The ipsilateral late response (R2) was elicited in all subjects and considered most suitable to evaluate maturational changes of the blink reflex. In a few subjects older than 3 years and of adults, the ipsilateral early response (R1) was difficult to observe. The contralateral late response (R2') could not be obtained in 32% of neonates and infants. From the observation about developmental change of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>