<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:03:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:03:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chloewallace/article/7223673</link><title>What Is a Political Constitution?</title><description>The question--what is a political constitution?--might seem, at first blush, fairly innocuous. At one level, the idea of a political constitution seems fairly well settled, at least insofar as most political constitutionalists subscribe to a similar set of commitments, arguments and assumptions. At a second, more reflective level, however, there remains some doubt whether a political constitution purports to be a descriptive or normative account of a real world constitution, such as Britain's. By exploring the idea of a political constitution ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:07:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/buggle/article/1668406</link><title>International Conference on Shape Medeling and Applications: Proceedings : Genova, Italy May 7-11, 2001</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:11:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/goonsqad/article/3935113</link><title>Rational Rhetoric in Politics: The Debate Over Ratifying the U.S. Constitution</title><description>During the debate over ratifying the U.S. Constitution, both the Federalists and the Anti-Federalists offered inconsistent arguments. They violated principles of transitivity (e.g., statements such as "A furthers B" and "B furthers C" coexist with the statement "A hinders C"). Using cognitive mapping to extract the network of causal assertions offered during the debate, and transaction resource theory to identify game-theoretic structures in these maps, including coordination, bargaining, and social dilemma games, we find that violations of transitivity have only two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:14:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kranakis/article/7366717</link><title>Max Mara and the origins of Italian ready-to-wear</title><description>This article charts the establishment and expansion of the ready-to-wear Max Mara label before the birth of the Max Mara group in 1967. Until recently, little consideration has been given to the evolution of Italian fashion, and few histories of dress or Italian culture even mention its presence before the 1970s. Still fewer acknowledge the crucial emergence of fashionable ready-to-wear in Italy in the 1960s, in which Max Mara played a key role, and which anticipated the international success of Italian ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:14:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nilsma/article/6037685</link><title>Application of electric and electromagnetic methods to the definition of the Campi Flegrei caldera (Italy)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:18:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/iamisha/article/7679967</link><title>Development Policies for Southern Italy</title><description>I. Southern Italy as an underdeveloped economy, 517.--II. A model of regional development, 528.--III. The pattern of regional growth, 533.-- IV. Implication for development policy, 539. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:20:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/iamisha/article/6431038</link><title>The nature of regional unemployment in Italy</title><description>Taking as a starting point the evidence of growing disparities for most of the 1984-2007 period, this article investigates the nature of regional unemployment in Italy. In particular, we assess whether the Italian regional unemployment rates contain a unit root and are, thus, subject to pure hysteresis, considering as alternative hypotheses both a linear and a non-linear stationary process. For that purpose, we employ three recently developed panel unit-root tests, taking account of structural breaks, cross-section dependence and non-linearities. Contrary to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:22:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Horduna/article/5128063</link><title>Foreword: System Effects and the Constitution</title><description>A system effect arises when the properties of an aggregate differ from the properties of its members, taken one by one. The failure to recognize system effects leads to fallacies of division and composition, in which the analyst mistakenly assumes that what is true of the aggregate must also be true of the members, or that what is true of the members must also be true of the aggregate. Examples are (1) the fallacious assumption that if the overall ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:22:55">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2131273</link><title>The Argument for the Secret Constitution</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:24:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/8146339</link><title>Matter, Antimatter and Dark Matter: Proceedings of the Second International Workshop Trento, Italy 29-30 October 2001</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>