<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7194">hobcaw barony</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:31:00" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7194-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7194_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:31:01">http://www.citeulike.org/article/875973</link><title>Britons in the Barony of Gilsland, Cumbria</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7194-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7194_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:34:22">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5493731</link><title>The Barony and the Churches of Late Nineteenth Century Glasgow</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7194-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7194_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:38:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7384963</link><title>South Carolina Shipyards: Labour, Logistics, Lumber and Ladies</title><description>Abstract  Southern shipyards, like Hobcaw and Mars Bluff, were established at locations chosen primarily for convenient access to transportation networks, building materials, clientele and labour. The historical record reveals a home front role played by local plantation owners and slaves as shipyard labour. Women served as project fundraisers, shipyard dilettantes, shipwright’s wives and possibly slave mistresses with a paucity of material culture to confirm their presence in the archaeological record. Archaeological investigations on land and underwater yield evidence of artefacts associated with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7194-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7194_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:40:26">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9885344</link><title>Time-of-flight system for the multipurpose detector (MPD)</title><description>A conceptual design for a multipurpose detector (MPD) [1] is proposed for the study of hot and dense barony matter in collisions of heavy ions over the atomic mass range A = 1–197 at center-of-mass energies of up to 11 GeV (for Au 79+ ). The MPD experiment is scheduled to be performed at a future JINR accelerator complex facility for heavy ions, the Nuclotron-based Ion Collider Facility (NICA), which is designed to reach the required parameters with an average luminosity ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>