<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:37:31" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:37:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/erikcmic/article/6368254</link><title>Echoes across the diaphragm</title><description>The echoes appearing above the diaphragm in liver sector scans are attributed to acoustic scattering structures in the liver, the ultrasound being reflected back to the transducer by the air-backed diaphragm, which acts as a sound mirror. The hypothesis is evidenced by observations of pathology in the upper portion of the liver and by investigations in vitro . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:41:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Sergey_CMU/article/10120805</link><title>Contraceptive use and abortion among women of reproductive age in st. Petersburg, Russia.</title><description>Although the characteristics associated with contraceptive use among Russian women have been studied, no large-scale research has been conducted on women's use of different contraceptive methods and abortion. A random sample of 1,147 women aged 18-44 completed questionnaires at local women's clinics in St. Petersburg in 2003-2004. Chi-square tests were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:43:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/blafon/article/12324687</link><title>Sonographic evaluation of the diaphragm in critically ill patients. Technique and clinical applications</title><description>The use of ultrasonography has become increasingly popular in the everyday management of critically ill patients. It has been demonstrated to be a safe and handy bedside tool that allows rapid hemodynamic assessment and visualization of the thoracic, abdominal and major vessels structures. More recently, M-mode ultrasonography has been used in the assessment of diaphragm kinetics. Ultrasounds provide a simple, non-invasive method of quantifying diaphragmatic movement in a variety of normal and pathological conditions. Ultrasonography can assess the characteristics of diaphragmatic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:44:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/10349229</link><title>Early age at first intercourse and subsequent gaps in contraceptive use.</title><description>Abstract Background: Sexual debut before age 15 years has been associated with increased sexual risk behaviors among teens, but little is known about its effects beyond adolescence. This study examines the relationship between the age at first intercourse and subsequent contraceptive gaps. Methods: We identified 3538 sexually active, fertile women participants from the 2006-2008 National Survey of Family Growth. Women were ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/georgekoenig/article/6840681</link><title>Diagnosis of blunt traumatic ruptured diaphragm: is it still a difficult problem?</title><description>BACKGROUND: Blunt traumatic rupture of the diaphragm (BTRD) is uncommon. The diagnosis can be easily overlooked, and radiological findings misinterpreted. In a 15-year experience at the two major trauma hospitals in Brisbane reported in 1991, 85 patients with BTRD were treated, and the diagnosis not always made expeditiously. With the introduction of mandatory Early Management of Severe Trauma course training in the 90s and newer diagnostic tools, it might be expected that BTRD would be a less problematic diagnosis. The aim ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:52:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/10433696</link><title>Injectable and Oral Contraceptive Use and Cancers of the Breast, Cervix, Ovary, and Endometrium in Black South African Women: Case–Control Study</title><description>Oral contraceptives are known to influence the risk of cancers of the female reproductive system. Evidence regarding the relationship between injectable contraceptives and these cancers is limited, especially in black South Africans, among whom injectable contraceptives are used more commonly than oral contraceptives. We analysed data from a South African hospital-based caseâcontrol study of black females aged 18â79 y, comparing self-reported contraceptive use in patients with breast (n = 1,664), cervical (n = 2,182), ovarian (n = 182), and endometrial (n ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:55:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/els2006/article/10442572</link><title>Dysfunction of the diaphragm.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:55:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/9808652</link><title>Oral contraceptive use and reproductive factors and risk of ovarian cancer in the European Prospective Investigation into Cancer and Nutrition</title><description>Oral contraceptive use and reproductive factors and risk of ovarian cancer in the European Prospective Investigation into Cancer and Nutrition British Journal of Cancer advance online publication, September 13, 2011. doi:10.1038/bjc.2011.371 Authors: K K Tsilidis, N E Allen, T J Key, L Dossus, A Lukanova, K Bakken, E Lund, A Fournier, K Overvad, L Hansen, A Tjønneland, V Fedirko, S Rinaldi, I Romieu, F Clavel-Chapelon, P Engel, R Kaaks, M Schütze, A Steffen, C Bamia, A ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:58:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/erikcmic/article/6368153</link><title>A novel respiratory detection method based on automated analysis of ultrasound diaphragm video.</title><description>This paper proposes a novel respiratory detection method based on diaphragm motion measurements using a 2D ultrasound unit. The proposed method extracts a respiratory signal from an automated analysis of the internal diaphragm motion during breathing. The respiratory signal may be used for gating. Ultrasound studies of diaphragm breathing motion were performed on four volunteers. The ultrasound video stream was captured and transferred to a personal computer and decomposed into individual image frames. After straightforward image analysis, region of interest selection, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:59:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/10156379</link><title>The NICHD Women's Contraceptive and Reproductive Experiences Study: methods and operational results.</title><description>This paper presents methods and operational results of a population-based case-control study examining the effects of oral contraceptive use on breast cancer risk among white and black women aged 35-64 years in five U.S. locations. Cases were women newly diagnosed with breast cancer during July 1994 through April 1998. Controls ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>