<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7205">turkey leftover recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:44:37" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:44:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/afinara/article/1678719</link><title>Liberal thought and democracy in turkey</title><description>Turkish Republican history has witnessed the subsequent formation of liberal circles and/or political parties. The circles and/or political parties concerned were either immediately dissolved due to their opposition to Republican principles or they came to terms with these principles, either by force or consent. This had de-liberalising effects on liberal identity. In the 1990s, an intellectual circle was formed and it adopted neo-liberalism as its basic frame of reference. The circle seems to promise a break with Republican encroachment on liberal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:48:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lizaball/article/1101112</link><title>Working with neglected children and their families</title><description>Child neglect has proved a particularly difficult area for social work to address. In the first pan of the paper a number of reasons for this are discussed. We go on to suggest that chronic child neglect characteristically involves the breakdown or absence of a relationship of care. Therefore, the social work response needs to include a focus on the relationship difficulties between parent and child which manifest as either an unwillingness or inability on the pan of the primary carer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:50:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/clin12/article/10105331</link><title>Flavor Components and Factors Associated with the Development of Off-Flavors in Cooked Turkey Rolls</title><description>The influence of storage and roll position on the development of warmed-over flavors in cooked turkey rolls was investigated. Following cooking the rolls were refrigerated for 0, 2 and 4 days and analyzed by headspace gas chromatography/mass spectrometry, TBA numbers, flavor profile analysis, and sensory category scaling. TBA numbers increased significantly by 52 and 165% after 4 days in the interior and exterior portions of the rolls, respectively, and were correlated with flavor deteriorations. Thirty-two compounds were identified, 30 of which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:51:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/georgmodzelewski/article/11465222</link><title>Communications and Networking Android Recipes</title><description>The key to many successful mobile applications is their ability to connect and interact with remote data sources. Web services and APIs are abundant in today’s world, allowing an application to interact with just about any service, from weather forecasts to personal financial information. Bringing this data into the palm of a user’s hand and making it accessible from anywhere is one of the greatest powers of the mobile platform. Android builds on the Web foundations that Google is known for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:54:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/druvus/article/6389367</link><title>Re-emergence of tularemia in Turkey.</title><description>Four tularemia epidemics were reported from three different regions of Turkey between 1936 and 1953. After a long interval, a new tularemia epidemic was reported from the area around Bursa in the northwestern part of Turkey in 1988. Following this first epidemic in Bursa, small epidemics occurred in areas around Bursa between 1988 and 2002. Other tularemia epidemics in different regions of Turkey were reported ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:57:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/meryemtanarhte/article/6654561</link><title>Trend analysis of streamflow in Turkey</title><description>This paper presents trends computed for the 31-year period of monthly streamflows obtained from 26 basins over Turkey. Four non-parametric trend tests (the Sen's T, the Spearman's Rho, the Mann-Kendall, and the Seasonal Kendall which are known as appropriate tools in detecting linear trends of a hydrological time series) are adapted in this study. Moreover, the Van Belle and Hughes’ basin wide trend test is included in the analysis for the same purpose. Homogeneity of trends in monthly streamflows is also ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:58:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dayjm/article/13130904</link><title>Prevalence of parvoviruses in commercial turkey flocks.</title><description>Turkey parvovirus belongs to the family Parvoviridae, subfamily Parvovirinae, Genus parvovirus. Since the initial report on turkey parvovirus in the United States appeared in 1983, there had been no further reports of parvovirus in turkeys until 2008. The aims of our study were to determine the prevalence of parvovirus in commercial turkey flocks using PCR; to determine their genetic relationship to previous strains identified in North America and Europe; and to test samples for enteric viruses by transmission electron microscopy (TEM). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pesmit/article/6015842</link><title>The Black Family Reunion Cookbook: Recipes and Food Memories</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:06:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jnicolai/article/4373087</link><title>British American Tobacco's failure in Turkey</title><description>Background and objectivesTransnational tobacco companies (TTCs) considered Turkey an important, potential investment market because of its high consumption rates and domestic commitment to tobacco. This paper outlines how British American Tobacco (BAT) attempted to establish a joint venture with the government monopoly TEKEL, while waiting for privatisation and a private tender. MethodsAnalysis of tobacco industry documents from the Guildford Depository and online tobacco document sources. ResultsBAT failed to establish a market share in Turkey until 2000 despite repeated attempts ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7205-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7205_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:09:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ddahlem/article/1386464</link><title>Numerical Recipes 3rd Edition: The Art of Scientific Computing</title><description>Co-authored by four leading scientists from academia and industry, Numerical Recipes Third Edition starts with basic mathematics and computer science and proceeds to complete, working routines. Widely recognized as the most comprehensive, accessible and practical basis for scientific computing, this new edition incorporates more than 400 Numerical Recipes routines, many of them new or upgraded. The executable C++ code, now printed in color for easy reading, adopts an object-oriented style particularly suited to scientific applications. The whole book is presented in ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>