<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7209">crab dip appetizer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:38:17" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:38:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tingying/article/787592</link><title>Caffeine reduces the initial dip in the visual BOLD response at 3 T.</title><description>Localized changes in oxygen consumption related to increased neural activity can result in a small and transient "initial dip" of the blood oxygenation level-dependent (BOLD) signal used in functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI). The initial dip has been of great interest to the fMRI community because it may provide a more accurate and localized measure of neural activity than the conventional BOLD signal increase. Although potentially useful as a technique for human brain mapping, the initial dip is not always detected ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:39:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Thanh77/article/7730050</link><title>The 1997 event in the Crab pulsar revisited</title><description>A complex event observed in the radio pulses from the Crab pulsar in 1997 included echoes, a dispersive delay, and large changes in intensity. It is shown that these phenomena were due to refraction at the edge of a plasma cloud in the outer region of the Crab Nebula. Several similar events have been observed, although in less detail. It is suggested that the plasma cloud is in the form of filaments with diameter around 3 x 10^11m and electron density of order 10^4 cm-3 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:39:44">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2062082</link><title>Gendered-Caste Violations and the Cultural Politics of Voice in Rural Orissa, India</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:41:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lguariguata/article/9201975</link><title>Atlantic Diabetes in Pregnancy (DIP): the prevalence and outcomes of gestational diabetes mellitus using new diagnostic criteria.</title><description>AIMS/HYPOTHESIS: New diagnostic criteria for gestational diabetes mellitus (GDM) have recently been published. We wished to evaluate what impact these new criteria would have on GDM prevalence and outcomes in a predominantly European population. METHODS: The Atlantic Diabetes In Pregnancy (DIP) programme performed screening for GDM in 5,500 women with an oral glucose tolerance test at 24-28 weeks. GDM was defined according to the new International Association of Diabetes and Pregnancy Study Groups (IADPSG) criteria and compared with previous WHO criteria; maternal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:44:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mhmh/article/8898834</link><title>The Crab Nebula: An Astrophysical Chimera</title><description>The Crab Nebula, henceforth the Crab, the remnant of the historical supernova of 1054 AD, has long been of intense interest. The pulsar at the center of the Crab has a spin-down luminosity ∼105 times that of the Sun. The outer nebula holds several solar masses of material ejected by the explosion. Between the two lies the trapped pulsar wind, visible as synchrotron radiation at radio wavelengths through X-ray wavelengths. Recent observations with the Hubble Space Telescope, the Chandra X-ray Observatory, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:46:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bigbossman/article/226627</link><title>DIP: the database of interacting proteins.</title><description>The Database of Interacting Proteins (DIP; http://dip.doe-mbi.ucla.edu) is a database that documents experimentally determined protein-protein interactions. This database is intended to provide the scientific community with a comprehensive and integrated tool for browsing and efficiently extracting information about protein interactions and interaction networks in biological processes. Beyond cataloging details of protein-protein interactions, the DIP is useful for understanding protein function and protein-protein relationships, studying the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-07"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/cme/article/5891665</link><title>Pulse variation of the optical emission of Crab pulsar</title><description>The stability of the optical pulse of the Crab pulsar is analyzed based on the 1 $μ$s resolution observations with the Russian 6-meter and William Hershel telescopes equipped with different photon-counting detectors. The search for the variations of the pulse shape along with its arrival time stability is performed. Upper limits on the possible short time scale free precession of the pulsar are placed. The evidence of pulse time of arrival (TOA) variations on 1.5-2 hours time scale is presented, along with evidence of small light curve (shape ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:53:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aarchiba/article/3338398</link><title>Detection of pulsed gamma-ays above 25 GeV from the Crab pulsar</title><description>One fundamental unanswered question about pulsars concerns the mechanism of their pulsed electromagnetic radiation. Measuring the high end region of a pulsar's spectrum would shed light on this question, but has challenged ground- based experiments for three decades. By developing a new type of electronic trigger, we could lower the threshold of the MAGIC Cherenkov telescope to 25 GeV, a major breakthrough for this kind of instrument. We detected pulsed gamma-ays from the Crab above 25 GeV, revealing a relatively high energy cut-off in the phase-averaged spectrum. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:54:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cme/article/8137623</link><title>Fermi Large Area Telescope Observations of the Crab Pulsar and Nebula</title><description>We report on gamma-ray observations of the Crab Pulsar and Nebula using 8 months of survey data with the Fermi Large Area Telescope (LAT). The high quality light curve obtained using the ephemeris provided by the Nancay and Jodrell Bank radio telescopes shows two main peaks stable in phase with energy. The first gamma-ray peak leads the radio main pulse by (281 ± 12 ± 21) mus, giving new constraints on the production site of non-thermal emission in pulsar magnetospheres. The improved sensitivity and the unprecedented statistics afforded ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7209-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7209_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:58:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/byy/article/1121740</link><title>Floral dip: a simplified method forAgrobacterium-mediated transformation ofArabidopsis thaliana</title><description>TheAgrobacteriumvacuum infiltration method has made it possible to transformArabidopsis thalianawithout plant tissue culture or regeneration. In the present study, this method was evaluated and a substantially modified transformation method was developed. The labor-intensive vacuum infiltration process was eliminated in favor of simple dipping of developing floral tissues into a solution containingAgrobacterium tumefaciens, 5% sucrose and 500 microliters per litre of surfactant Silwet L-77. Sucrose and surfactant were critical to the success of the floral dip method. Plants inoculated when numerous immature ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>