<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:27:15" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:27:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/baharehs1/article/5645981</link><title>Merkel Cell Carcinoma: Recent Progress and Current Priorities on Etiology, Pathogenesis, and Clinical Management</title><description>PurposeTo expedite improved understanding, diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of Merkel cell carcinoma (MCC), a rare malignancy of cutaneous neuroendocrine cells that has a 28% 2-year mortality rate. MethodsThis article summarizes a workshop that discussed the state-of-the-art research and priorities for research on MCC and on a new human polyomavirus (ie, MCPyV) recently discovered in 80% of MCC tumors. ResultsNormal Merkel cells are widely distributed in the epidermis near the end of nerve axons and may function as mechanoreceptors or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:29:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nodawo/article/1260224</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin.</title><description>LEARNING OBJECTIVES: After studying this article, the participant should be able to: 1. Identify the subtypes of squamous cell carcinoma of the skin. 2. Identify factors that affect recurrence and/or metastasis. 3. Develop a surgical management plan for treating high-risk squamous cell carcinoma of the skin.In treating squamous cell carcinoma of the skin, a key concept in proper management is understanding why certain tumors are more prone to both recurrence and metastasis. When developing a surgical management plan, an understanding of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:34:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mishibas/article/11838274</link><title>Treatment of Unresectable and Metastatic Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>Cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) is an already common disorder with a rapidly increasing incidence. Treatment of early disease depends primarily on surgery or destructive techniques. In contrast to the frequency of early SCC, unresectable or metastatic SCC is relatively rare, but potentially life-threatening without clearly proven treatment options. Few rigorous studies of the treatment of advanced SCC have been undertaken. In the past, various agents have been explored in a limited fashion, including chemotherapy (cisplatin, fluoropyrimidines, bleomycin, doxorubicin), 13-cis-retinoic acid, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/7476538</link><title>Genus β human papillomaviruses and incidence of basal cell and squamous cell carcinomas of skin: population based case-control study</title><description>AbstractObjective To investigate the association between genus β human papillomaviruses and the incidence of non-melanocytic skin cancer in the general population.Design Population based case-control study.Setting New Hampshire, USA.Participants 2366 skin cancer cases and controls from the general population aged 25 to 74 years (663 squamous cell carcinoma, 898 basal cell carcinoma, 805 controls), with plasma samples tested for L1 antibodies to 16 genus β human papillomaviruses by multiplex serology.Main outcome measures Odds ratios for squamous cell carcinoma and basal cell carcinoma ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:39:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/moltech/article/9392337</link><title>The MET receptor tyrosine kinase is a potential novel therapeutic target for head and neck squamous cell carcinoma.</title><description>Recurrent/metastatic head and neck cancer remains a devastating disease with insufficient treatment options. We investigated the MET receptor tyrosine kinase as a novel target for the treatment of head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC). MET/phosphorylated MET and HGF expression was analyzed in 121 tissues (HNSCC/normal) by immunohistochemistry, and in 20 HNSCC cell lines by immunoblotting. The effects of MET inhibition using small interfering RNA/two small-molecule inhibitors (SU11274/PF-2341066) on signaling, migration, viability, and angiogenesis were determined. The complete MET gene was ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:40:51">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1954/article/6796745</link><title>Computed tomographic features of oral squamous cell carcinoma in cats: 18 cases (2002-2008).</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To describe the computed tomographic features of oral squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) in cats and identify imaging characteristics associated with survival time. DESIGN: Retrospective case series. ANIMALS: 18 cats with a diagnosis of oral SCC. PROCEDURES: Information on history; clinical, laboratory, and diagnostic imaging findings; treatment; and survival time was obtained from medical records of 18 cats with oral SCC. Computed tomography (CT) studies were examined to identify features associated with oral SCC. The association of CT features with survival ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:42:32">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1954/article/2245260</link><title>Evaluation of strontium Sr 90 for the treatment of superficial squamous cell carcinoma of the nasal planum in cats: 49 cases (1990-2006).</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To determine progression-free and overall survival times of cats with squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) of the nasal planum following treatment with a single fraction of strontium Sr 90 ((90)Sr). DESIGN: Retrospective case series. ANIMALS: 49 cats with SCC of the nasal planum. PROCEDURES: Information including FIV infection status, diagnosis of SCC vs SCC in situ (ie, evidence that the tumor did or did not penetrate the epidermal basement membrane, respectively), (90)Sr dose and number of probe applications, treatment-related response and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:43:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jm356/article/6799414</link><title>Translocation (12;14) and other chromosome abnormalities in squamous cell carcinoma of the tongue</title><description>Abstract  Tongue squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) has an increasing incidence, a high morbidity rate, and a 50% 5-year survival rate. The prognosis of tongue SCC is poor compared to SCC originating at other sites in the oral cavity, because they represent different biological subentities. Cytogenetic studies of head and neck SCC showed more losses than gains of various chromosomes or chromosomal segments. Among the frequent alterations there are losses of −4, −10, −13, −14, −18, −19, −21, −22, gains of +7, +8, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:46:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NaliniChilkov/article/3937024</link><title>Glutathione, ascorbic acid and antioxidant enzymes in the tumor tissue and blood of patients with oral squamous cell carcinoma.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Oral squamous cell carcinoma is one of the most common cancers in the world. Reactive oxygen species are postulated to be involved in neoplastic transformation. The antioxidant defence system limits cell injury induced by reactive oxygen species. Oxidative stress occurs when there is an imbalance between the production of reactive oxygen species and a cell's oxidant capacity or when there is a decrease in this capacity. This stress may cause mutagenesis, cytotoxicity and changes in gene expression that initiate or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:47:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/serioussyrian/article/3126171</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma with clear cells: how often is there evidence of tricholemmal differentiation?</title><description>Clear-cell carcinoma of the skin was described by Kuo in 1980 as a cutaneous tumor composed of clear cells that lacked cytoplasmic glycogen or evidence of tricholemmal keratinization. Tricholemmal carcinoma (TC) is conventionally considered to be a neoplasm derived from adnexal keratinocytes with glycogenated clear cells and evidence of outer root sheath or tricholemmal differentiation. The existence of TC has been questioned as it has been argued that without clear immunohistochemical evidence of outer root sheath differentiation, TC cannot be distinguished ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>