<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:49:06" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:49:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SaraLo/article/4313966</link><title>Detection of salmonella in finishing pigs on farm and at slaughter in piedmont, Italy.</title><description>Salmonella is one of the most common causes of human gastroenteritis often associated with pork consumption. The aims of this cross-sectional study were to collect preliminary data on the presence of Salmonella enterica in pigs in Piedmont (Italy), through sampling on farm and at slaughter and to gather pilot data on serotypes and phagetypes present in the sampled area and distribution of anti-microbial resistance among isolated strains. Salmonella was detected through culture and identified with Salmonella spp. and Salmonella Typhimurium PCR; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:53:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vshahrez/article/8958157</link><title>TLR signaling is required for Salmonella typhimurium virulence.</title><description>Toll-like receptors (TLRs) contribute to host resistance to microbial pathogens and can drive the evolution of virulence mechanisms. We have examined the relationship between host resistance and pathogen virulence using mice with a functional allele of the nramp-1 gene and lacking combinations of TLRs. Mice deficient in both TLR2 and TLR4 were highly susceptible to the intracellular bacterial pathogen Salmonella typhimurium, consistent with reduced innate ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:58:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aktiha/article/8448292</link><title>Chronic and acute infection of the gall bladder by Salmonella Typhi: understanding the carrier state</title><description>Despite major treatment and prevention efforts, millions of new typhoid infections occur worldwide each year. For a subset of infected individuals, Salmonella enterica subsp. enterica serovar Typhi colonizes the gall bladder and remains there long after symptoms subside, serving as a reservoir for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:59:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arashomidi/article/12825227</link><title>Antimicrobial drug resistance in Salmonella: problems and perspectives in food- and water-borne infections</title><description>Strains of Salmonella spp. with resistance to antimicrobial drugs are now widespread in both developed and developing countries. In developed countries it is now increasingly accepted that for the most part such strains are zoonotic in origin and acquire their resistance in the food-animal host before onward transmission to humans through the food chain. Of particular importance since the early 1990s has been a multiresistant strain of Salmonella typhimurium definitive phage type (DT) 104, displaying resistance to up to six commonly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:01:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/druvus/article/7339549</link><title>Genome-wide identification of novel genomic islands that contribute to Salmonella virulence in mouse systemic infection.</title><description>Salmonella pathogenicity islands are inserted into the genome by horizontal gene transfer and are required for expression of full virulence. Here, we performed tRNA scanning of the genome of Salmonella enterica serovar Typhimurium and compared it with that of nonpathogenic Escherichia coli in order to identify genomic islands that contribute to Salmonella virulence. Using deletion analysis, we identified four genomic islands that are required for virulence in the mouse infection model. One of the newly identified pathogenicity islands was the pheV-tRNA-located ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:04:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arashomidi/article/1400014</link><title>Comparison of Salmonella enterica serotype Infantis isolates from a veterinary teaching hospital</title><description>Aims:  To compare Salmonella enterica serotype Infantis isolates obtained from patients or the environment of a veterinary teaching hospital over a period of 9 years following a nosocomial outbreak to determine whether isolates were epidemiologically related or represented unrelated introductions into the hospital environment. Methods and Results:  Fifty-six S. Infantis isolates were compared based on their phenotypic (antimicrobial drug [AMD] susceptibility pattern) and genotypic (pulsed-field gel electrophoresis [PFGE] pattern and presence of integrons) characteristics. Epidemiologically unrelated S. Infantis isolates clustered separately from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:06:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cdallett/article/1031705</link><title>The secreted effector protein of Salmonella dublin, SopA, is translocated into eukaryotic cells and influences the induction of enteritis.</title><description>Salmonella-induced enteritis is associated with the induction of an acute intestinal inflammatory response and net fluid secretion into the lumen of infected mucosa. Proteins secreted by the Inv/Spa type III secretion system of Salmonella play a key role in the induction of these responses. We have demonstrated recently that the Inv/Spa-secreted SopB and SopD effector proteins are translocated into eukaryotic cells via a Sip-dependent pathway and act in concert to mediate inflammation and fluid secretion in infected ileal mucosa. Mutations of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/druvus/article/6186553</link><title>Genomic and phenotypic variation in epidemic-spanning Salmonella enterica serovar Enteritidis isolates</title><description>BACKGROUND:Salmonella enterica serovar Enteritidis (S. Enteritidis) has caused major epidemics of gastrointestinal infection in many different countries. In this study we investigate genome divergence and pathogenic potential in S. Enteritidis isolated before, during and after an epidemic in Uruguay.RESULTS:266 S. Enteritidis isolates were genotyped using RAPD-PCR and a selection were subjected to PFGE analysis. From these, 29 isolates spanning different periods, genetic profiles and sources of isolation were assayed for their ability to infect human epithelial cells and subjected to comparative ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:09:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/konrad_foerstner/article/9723382</link><title>Experimental annotation of post-translational features and translated coding regions in the pathogen Salmonella Typhimurium</title><description>BACKGROUND:Complete and accurate genome annotation is crucial for comprehensive and systematic studies of biological systems. However, determining protein-coding genes for most new genomes is almost completely performed by inference using computational predictions with significant documented error rates (&gt; 15%). Furthermore, gene prediction programs provide no information on biologically important post-translational processing events critical for protein function. RESULTS:We experimentally annotated the bacterial pathogen Salmonella Typhimurium 14028, using "shotgun" proteomics to accurately uncover the translational landscape and post-translational features. The data provide protein-level ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:12:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cdallett/article/1031695</link><title>SipA, SopA, SopB, SopD, and SopE2 Contribute to Salmonella enterica Serotype Typhimurium Invasion of Epithelial Cells</title><description>The centisome 63 type III secretion system (T3SS-1) encoded by Salmonella pathogenicity island 1 (SPI1) mediates invasion of epithelial cells by Salmonella enterica serotype Typhimurium. Characterization of mutants lacking individual genes has revealed that T3SS-1 secreted proteins (effectors) SopE2 and SopB are required for invasion while the SipA protein accelerates entry into cells. Here we have revisited the question of which T3SS-1 effectors contribute to the invasion of epithelial cells by complementing a strain lacking all of the effector genes that ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>