<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7217">who was lincolns vice president</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:16:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:16:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mstepien/article/4043229</link><title>Stroke--1989. Recommendations on stroke prevention, diagnosis, and therapy. Report of the WHO Task Force on Stroke and other Cerebrovascular Disorders.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:19:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/danielwaweru/article/7804572</link><title>“How Do I Live in This Strange Place?”</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:23:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Entunombre/article/2110529</link><title>3. Degrees of Virtue and Vice</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:24:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Entunombre/article/2110528</link><title>4. Varieties of Virtue and Vice</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:27:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rodrigupo/article/8120533</link><title>Communicating Risk to Consumers in Domestic and Internationally Traded Products</title><description>Today, in the twenty first century, the food supply chain is increasingly global in nature and relies on a complex system involving farmers, growers, ingredients suppliers, food processors, food distributors, food importers, and food retailers in many different regions of the world. To achieve safety of food from farm to fork, and to reduce the frequency, impact and severity of foodborne illness outbreaks, there have to be effective working partnerships and cooperation throughout the entire food chain. However, the delivery of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:27:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chaspir/article/5429611</link><title>Assessment of fracture risk and its application to screening for postmenopausal osteoporosis: Synopsis of a WHO report</title><description>The criteria required for an effective screening strategy for osteoporosis are largely met in Caucasian women. The disease is common and readily diagnosed by the measurement of bone mineral with single- or dual-energy absorptiometry. Such measurements have high specificity but lower sensitivity, so that the value of the technique is greater for those identified as being at higher risk. Against this background there is little evidence that osteoporosis can usefully be tackled by a public health policy to influence risk factors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:31:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tamakat/article/5037933</link><title>Introducing Bakhtin</title><description>The Russian critic and theorist Mikhail Bakhtin is once again in favor, his influence spreading across many discourses including literature, film, cultural and gender studies. This book provides the most comprehensive introduction to Bakhtin’s central concepts and terms. Sue Vice illustrates what is meant by such ideas as carnival, the grotesque body, dialogism and heteroglossia. These concepts are then placed in a contemporary context by drawing out the implications of Bakhtin’s writings, for current issues such as feminism and sexuality. Vice’s examples are always practically based on specific texts ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:32:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/smcc/article/4129166</link><title>The Final Report of the President's Commission on Olympic Sports, 1975-1977. Vol I &amp; II</title><description>White softcovers published Jan. 1977. Vol I Executive Summary and Major Conclusions and Recommendations; Vol II Findings of Fact and Supporting Material ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:33:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/4928592</link><title>World Health Organization: Tumours of the Breast and Female Genital Organs (Who/IARC Classification of Tumours) (IARC WHO Classification of Tumours)</title><description>This WHO classification covers the female and male breast, ovaries, fallopian tumours, uterine cervix, uterine corpus, vulva, vagina and inherited tumour syndromes. It includes a comprehensive classification of benign and malignant neoplasms. Targeted readership includes pathologists, gynaecologists, surgeons, oncologists, and basic scientists. Similar to the previous volumes of the series, the book includes numerous colour photographs, magnetic resonance images, CT scans and charts. In addition to its pathology and genetics, each lesion is described with its epidemiology, etiology, clinical features, as well as prognosis and predictive factors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7217-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7217_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:35:49">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6850287</link><title>President’s Column</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>