<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:37:11" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:37:16">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3683444</link><title>The Immigration Act of 1965</title><description>For more than forty years, the national-origins quota system dominatedmiddle dotUnited States immigration policy. It was not until Congress overrode President Truman's veto of the Immigration Act of 1952 that concerted effort to eliminate the quota system began, with the work of President Truman's Commission on Immigration and Naturalization. President Kennedy, long an active supporter of this effort, forwarded his legislative recommendations for immigration reform to Congress on July 23, 1963. The heart of President Kennedy's bill lay in its provisions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:38:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/naskapi/article/3771407</link><title>Astronomy and astrology in the medieval Islamic world</title><description>Not Available ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:39:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/H-Arrietaumn/article/6240133</link><title>Gangs and public policy: Constructing and deconstructing gang databases</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:42:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/9998767</link><title>The Perfection of Wisdom in Eight Thousand Lines &amp; Its Verse Summary</title><description>After the Torah, the Koran and the Gospels, the Indian literature of "The Perfection of Wisdom" has had the greatest impact on the religious consciousness of mankind. Its composition extended for over seven hundred years, and here we offer the reader the first two works which were composed in South India between 100 B.C. and A.D. 100. These documents are not only indispensable to those who wish to undersand the mentality of the East, they still carry a potent spiritual message; and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:43:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4849718</link><title>Customer experience management: Industry trends An interview with Bob Kennedy of Tealeaf Technologies</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:44:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10163840</link><title>Conversations with Edward Said</title><description>In these conversations with Tariq Ali, recorded in Edward Said's Riverside Drive apartment in New York in June 1994, about a decade before he finally lost his battle with cancer, Said brings his considerable intellect and deep personal engagement to bear on some of the most troubling and volatile issues of our time as he ranges back over his own dislocated existence, his initiation into politics, his involvement with the Palestine cause, his approach to the study of culture and his ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:47:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10083055</link><title>The Edward Said Reader</title><description>Edward Said, the renowned literary and cultural critic and passionately engaged intellectual, is one of our era's most formidable, provocative, and important thinkers. For more than three decades his books, which include Culture and Imperialism, Peace and Its Discontents, and the seminal study Orientalism, have influenced not only our worldview but the very terms of public discourse. The Edward Said Reader includes key sections from all of Said's books, from the groundbreaking 1966 study of Joseph Conrad to his new memoir, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:48:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kahenry/article/9387008</link><title>Topology of the C-Terminal Tail of HIV-1 gp41: Differential Exposure of the Kennedy Epitope on Cell and Viral Membranes</title><description>The C-terminal tail (CTT) of the HIV-1 gp41 envelope (Env) protein is increasingly recognized as an important determinant of Env structure and functional properties, including fusogenicity and antigenicity. While the CTT has been commonly referred to as the “intracytoplasmic domain” based on the assumption of an exclusive localization inside the membrane lipid bilayer, early antigenicity studies and recent biochemical analyses have produced a credible case for surface exposure of specific CTT sequences, including the classical “Kennedy epitope” (KE) of gp41, leading ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:51:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10163855</link><title>Culture and Resistance: Conversations with Edward W. Said</title><description>In his latest book of interviews, Edward W. Said discusses the centrality of popular resistance to his understanding of culture, history, and social change. He reveals his latest thoughts on the war on terrorism, the war in Afghanistan, and the Israeli-Palestinian conflict, and lays out a compelling vision for a secular, democratic future in the Middle East—and globally. Edward W. Said, a renowned cultural and literary critic, was born in Jerusalem, Palestine, and was educated there, in Egypt, and in the United ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:55:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mbiophys/article/6893193</link><title>Intracellular sites of lipid synthesis and the biogenesis of mitochondria</title><description>Experimental data are presented on the intracellular localization in rat liver of three enzymes which are involved in the biosynthesis of phosphatidylethanolamine and diphosphatidylglycerol. These enzymes are phosphatidylserine decarboxylase, CDP-diglyceride-l-[agr]-glycerophosphate phosphatidyl transferase, and phosphatidylethanolamine-l-serine phosphatidyl transferase. It was found that the first two enzymes are primarily mitochondrial while the latter enzyme is primarily microsomal. The intracellular sites for the biosynthesis of phosphatidylcholine, phosphatidylethanolamine, and diphosphatidylglycerol are discussed, and the implications of their sites of biosynthesis on the assembly processes involved in ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>