<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:58:23" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:58:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3819474</link><title>AMS INSIGHT—Absorbable Metal Stent Implantation for Treatment of Below-the-Knee Critical Limb Ischemia: 6-Month Analysis</title><description>Abstract  Endoluminal treatment of infrapopliteal artery lesions is a matter of controversy. Bioabsorbable stents are discussed as a means to combine mechanical prevention of vessel recoil with the advantages of long-term perspectives. The possibility of not having a permanent metallic implant could permit the occurrence of positive remodeling with lumen enlargement to compensate for the development of new lesions. The present study was designed to investigate the safety of absorbable metal stents (AMSs) in the infrapopliteal arteries based on 1- and 6-month ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:59:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tharris/article/3311111</link><title>Responses to oxygen in the daf-2 and daf-12 mutants</title><description>Oxygen has been postulated to play a role in the aging processes (S. Honda et al., 48 B57 `93), although it is not yet known how oxygen is involved. The mutants of daf-2 (C. Kenyon et al., Nature 366 461 `93) and daf-2;daf-12 (P. L. Larsen &amp; D. L. Riddle WBG 13 40 `94) are known to have a longer lifespan than that of the wild type. We hypothesize that the daf-2 and daf-12 genes would be involved in the regulational ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:00:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/voiklis/article/8461653</link><title>Gaining Insight Into the “Aha” Experience</title><description>The literature on insight lists four main characteristics of this experience: (a) suddenness (the experience is surprising and immediate), ease (the solution is processed without difficulty), positive affect (insights are gratifying), and the feeling of being right (after an insight, problem solvers judge the solution as being true and have confidence in this judgment). Although this phenomenology is well known, no theory has explained why insight feels the way it does. We propose a fluency account of insight: Positive affect and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:01:44">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1696/article/933838</link><title>Sleep inspires insight.</title><description>Insight denotes a mental restructuring that leads to a sudden gain of explicit knowledge allowing qualitatively changed behaviour. Anecdotal reports on scientific discovery suggest that pivotal insights can be gained through sleep. Sleep consolidates recent memories and, concomitantly, could allow insight by changing their representational structure. Here we show a facilitating role of sleep in a process of insight. Subjects performed a cognitive task requiring the learning of stimulus-response sequences, in which they improved gradually by increasing response speed across task ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:05:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3610040</link><title>On Some Twistor Spaces Over 4ℂℙ2</title><description>We show that for any positive integer t there exist on 4CP2, the connected sum of four complex projective planes, twistor spaces whose algebraic dimensions are two. Here, t appears as the order of the normal bundle of C in S, where S is a real smooth half-anti-canonical divisor on the twistor space and C is a real smooth anti-canonical divisor on S. This completely answers the problem posed by Campana and Kreussler. Our proof is based on the method developed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:05:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tharris/article/3319450</link><title>Effects of the gene disruption of SOD on stress resistance, development and lifespan in Caenorhabditis elegans</title><description>Insulin/IGF-I signaling controls stress resistance and development as well as aging in C. elegans. We found that the expression of sod-3, one of two Mn superoxide dismutase (SOD) isoform genes (sod-2 and sod-3), was much higher in insulin/IGF-I receptor (DAF-2) mutants (1) and phosphatidyl inositol 3 kinase (AGE-1) mutants (2) than in N2. To elucidate the function of MnSODs in the control by insulin/IGF-I signaling, the effects of MnSOD gene deletions in the background of daf-2 mutants on stress resistance, lifespan ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/johncumbers/article/717638</link><title>The daf-2 gene network for longevity regulates oxidative stress resistance and Mn-superoxide dismutase gene expression in Caenorhabditis elegans</title><description>Longevity is regulated by the daf-2 gene network in Caenorhabditis elegans. Mutations in the daf-2 gene, which encodes a member of the insulin receptor family, confer the life extension (Age) phenotype and the constitutive dauer (a growth-arrested larval form specialized for dispersal) formation phenotype. The Age phenotype is mutually potentiated by two life extension mutations in the daf-2 gene and the clk-1 gene, a homologue of yeast CAT5/COQ7 known to regulate ubiquinone biosynthesis. In this study, we demonstrated that the daf-2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jandira1/article/10140625</link><title>Are there specific neuropsychological deficits underlying poor insight in first episode psychosis?</title><description>Insight in psychosis is a multi-dimensional phenomenon, and has been hypothesised to have some sort of neuropsychological basis. It is unclear to what extent specific neuropsychological abilities are able to predict insight beyond the effect of generalised cognitive ability. We aimed to test this association, alongside the relationship of insight with illness duration and diagnosis, in a sample of first episode psychosis patients. 110 first episode psychosis patients were recruited and a comprehensive assessment was administered, including insight, symptoms, diagnosis and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:10:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/908/article/687668</link><title>An insight-based methodology for evaluating bioinformatics visualizations</title><description>High-throughput experiments, such as gene expression microarrays in the life sciences, result in very large data sets. In response, a wide variety of visualization tools have been created to facilitate data analysis. A primary purpose of these tools is to provide biologically relevant insight into the data. Typically, visualizations are evaluated in controlled studies that measure user performance on predetermined tasks or using heuristics and expert reviews. To evaluate and rank bioinformatics visualizations based on real-world data analysis scenarios, we developed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:14:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/oori/article/1065514</link><title>Precursors of insight in event-related brain potentials.</title><description>Event-related potentials (ERPs) were investigated to find precursors of insightful behavior. Participants had to process successive pairs in strings of digits to obtain a final response in each trial. Within the sequence of five responses required in each trial, the last two responses mirrored the two preceding ones. This hidden regularity, allowing for shortcutting each trial from five to two responses, was discovered by 6 out of 26 participants. Both groups, solvers and nonsolvers, implicitly learned the regularity, reflected by faster ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>