<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7221">what is mittelschmerz</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:30:02" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:30:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10895484</link><title>Mathematics in Context (MiC). What Works Clearinghouse Intervention Report</title><description>"Mathematics in Context" is a middle school mathematics curriculum for grades 5 through 8. It was developed to align with the 1989 National Council of Teachers of Mathematics (NCTM) Curriculum and Evaluation Standards. It is also based on the Dutch Realistic Mathematics Education approach of engaging students in understanding real-life problems and gradually moving to abstract concepts. Rather than focusing on one mathematical domain at a time, "Mathematics in Context" teaches students to explore the relationships among different domains of mathematics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:31:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dabd/article/7290890</link><title>RESTful Web Services Principles of REST Web Service Design Semantic of HTTP/1.1 Operations SOAP vs. REST Style Assets and Drawbacks Security Public Web Services What is REST? Representational State Transfer</title><description>Representation of resource at URI places client in a state Hyperlinks are transitions between states Services itself should be stateless “The name ‘Representational State Transfer ’ is intended to evoke an image of how a well-designed Web application behaves: a network of web pages (a virtual state-machine), where the user progresses through an application by selecting links (state transitions), resulting in the next page (representing the next state of the application) being transferred to the user and rendered for their use.” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:34:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suzelowe/article/4057193</link><title>Middle School Math. What Works Clearinghouse Topic Report</title><description>The What Works Clearinghouse (WWC) reviewed interventions to promote middle school students' math knowledge and skills. Because there is some variation in how school districts organize middle school, we considered curricula aimed at students in grades 6 through 9, covering one or more of the following content areas: numbers and operations, algebra, geometry, measurement, and data analysis and probability. Only core, comprehensive math curricula were eligible for inclusion in this review. These curricula extend over the course of one semester or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:36:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mahler/article/379582</link><title>Describing, Transforming, and Querying Semistructured Data</title><description>eN FROM Person P, Person C, Person G WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.Child = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN Get the phone numbers of Joe's grandchildren. Against the decomposed relations is even worse: four joins SELECT N.PhoneN FROM Person1 P, ChildOf C, ChildOf G, Phone N WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.SSN = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN AND G.Child = N.SSN Objects Allow Simpler Design Schema: Child: SSN ) No need to decompose in order to eliminate redundancy: the set data type takes ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:37:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelliskf/article/4116400</link><title>WWC Quick Review of the Article "Promoting Broad and Stable Improvements in Low-Income Children's Numerical Knowledge Through Playing Number Board Games"</title><description>This review examined a study designed to evaluate whether playing number board games improved numeracy skills of low-income preschoolers. The study included 136 pre-school children from 10 urban Head Start centers: 72 children were randomly selected to play a number board game with a trained experimenter; the remaining 64 children played a different version of the game using colors instead of numbers. Numeracy skills were assessed at the end of a two-week period and again nine weeks later. Study authors reported ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:39:25">http://www.citeulike.org/group/3214/article/6854596</link><title>Why is life so exact?</title><description>This is my attempt to answer Schrödinger's question: "What is Life?". In living cell the local combination of atoms is reproduced with incredible accuracy. In the case of protein biosynthesis the notion of the physical aspect of the process can be qualitatively enriched by taking into account the symmetry of conformational oscillations. This is the key to understand the selectivity in biochemistry. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:41:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/12446600</link><title>What Are Microfoundations?</title><description>In the extant organizational, management, and strategy literatures there are now frequent calls for microfoundations. However, there is little consensus on what microfoundations are and what they are not. In this paper we first (briefly) review the history of the microfoundations discussion and then discuss what microfoundations are and are not. We highlight four misconceptions or “half-truths” about microfoundations: (1) that microfoundations are psychology, human resources, or micro-organizational behavior, (2) that borrowed concepts constitute microfoundations, (3) that microfoundations lead to an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:44:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1375585</link><title>Factors influencing organizations to improve data quality in their information systems</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:46:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/9999605</link><title>Computational Modeling for What-Is, What-Might-Be, and What-Should-Be Studies—And Triangulation</title><description>In this essay, we examine what-is, what-might-be, and what-should-be computational models where the purpose is to explore new concepts, ideas, boundaries, and limitations going beyond what we know at the moment. Computational models complement well with other approaches: ethnographies, field studies, human subject lab studies, and surveys in novel triangulations. Triangulation of two or more complementary approaches permits us to broaden and deepen our understanding and insights. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7221-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7221_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:47:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/3741290</link><title>What Theory is Not</title><description>This essay describes differences between papers that contain some theory rather than no theory. There is little agreement about what constitutes strong versus weak theory in the social sciences, but there is more consensus that references, data, variables, diagrams, and hypotheses are not theory. Despite this consensus, however, authors routinely use these five elements in lieu of theory. We explain how each of these five elements can be confused with theory and how to avoid such confusion. By making this consensus ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>