<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7222">route 666</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:51:34" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:51:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aschramm/article/7835179</link><title>Route choice of cyclists in Zurich</title><description>This paper presents the first route choice model for bicyclists estimated from a large sample of GPS observations and overcomes the limitations inherent in the generally employed stated preference approach. It employs an improved mode detection algorithm for GPS post-processing to determine trips made by bicycle, which are map matched to an enriched street network. The alternatives are generated as a random sample from an exhaustive, but constrained search. Accounting for the similarity between the alternatives with the path-size factor the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:54:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aschramm/article/297012</link><title>An empirical basis for route choice in cycling</title><description>We used data from international cycle stage races to examine a rule for cyclists that is similar to Naismith's rule. Naismith's rule is used by walkers to estimate travel times for routes involving climb (i.e. the vertical distance component of a route). The rule is also used in route choice decision-making to compare differing, competing routes. We developed such a rule for use in cycling events, and also considered an extension of the climb-distance rule to take account of the effect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:55:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aschramm/article/4364807</link><title>An analysis of bicycle route choice preferences in Texas, US</title><description>In the US, the rise in motorized vehicle travel has contributed to serious societal, environmental, economic, and public health problems. These problems have increased the interest in encouraging non-motorized modes of travel (walking and bicycling). The current study contributes toward this objective by identifying and evaluating the importance of attributes influencing bicyclists’ route choice preferences. Specifically, the paper examines a comprehensive set of attributes that influence bicycle route choice, including: (1) bicyclists’ characteristics, (2) on-street parking, (3) bicycle facility type and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:56:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aschramm/article/9038982</link><title>Modeling Stated and Revealed Route Choice: Consideration of Consistency, Diversion, and Attitudinal Variables</title><description>Data from Global Positioning System (GPS) route data collection and a survey conducted after data collection obtain both stated and revealed route choice preferences from respondents in Lexington, Kentucky. A subset of the GPS data was analyzed to reveal how much their chosen routes differ from minimum-time routes. The post-GPS data collection survey includes attitudinal data, travel habits, route descriptors, and demographic data as stated by respondents, who identified preferred and nonpreferred peak and off-peak routes between the University of Kentucky ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:59:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aschramm/article/9246827</link><title>GIS or GPS? A Comparison of Two Methods For Assessing Route Taken During Active Transport</title><description>Current methods of assessing routes taken during active transport rely on subjective recall of trip length and barriers encountered enroute or the utilization of objective measures (Geographic Information Systems –[GIS]) that may not represent actual travel patterns. This study examined the utility of Global Positioning Systems (GPS) to measure actual routes taken compared with GIS-estimated travel distance and barriers encountered. Comparisons between GPS and GIS routes were performed for 59 of 75 children who wore a GPS during the journey to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:00:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pkgw/article/11370245</link><title>The Arecibo Detection of the Coolest Radio-flaring Brown Dwarf</title><description>Radio detection provides unique means to measure and study magnetic fields of the coolest brown dwarfs. Previous radio surveys have observed quiescent and flaring emission from brown dwarfs down to spectral type L3.5, but only upper limits have been established for even cooler objects. We report the detection of sporadic, circularly polarized flares from the T6.5 dwarf, 2MASS J1047+21, with the Arecibo radio telescope at 4.75 GHz. This is by far the coolest brown dwarf yet detected at radio frequencies. The fact ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:03:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/porfitek/article/9314838</link><title>Personalized tourist route generation</title><description>When tourists are at a destination, they typically search for information in the Local Tourist Organizations. There, the staff determines the profile of the tourists and their restrictions. Combining this information with their up-to-date knowledge about the local attractions and public transportation, they suggest a personalized route for the tourist agenda. Finally, they fine tune up this route to better fit tourists' needs. We present an intelligent routing system to fulfil the same task. We divide this process in three steps: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:06:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pkgw/article/12407659</link><title>The 5 GHz Arecibo Search for Radio Flares from Ultracool Dwarfs</title><description>We present the results of a 4.75 GHz survey of 33 brown dwarfs and one young exoplanetary system for flaring radio emission, conducted with the 305-m Arecibo radio telescope. The goal of this program was to detect and characterize the magnetic fields of objects cooler than spectral type L3.5, the coolest brown dwarf detected prior to our survey. We have also attempted to detect flaring radio emission from the HR 8799 planetary system, guided by theoretical work indicating that hot, massive exoplanets may have strong magnetic fields capable ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:08:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yctai/article/1250508</link><title>Pigeons combine compass and landmark guidance in familiar route navigation.</title><description>How do birds orient over familiar terrain? In the best studied avian species, the homing pigeon (Columba livia), two apparently independent primary mechanisms are currently debated: either memorized visual landmarks provide homeward guidance directly, or birds rely on a compass to home from familiar locations. Using miniature Global Positioning System tracking technology and clock-shift procedures, we set sun-compass and landmark information in conflict, showing that experienced birds can accurately complete their memorized routes by using landmarks alone. Nevertheless, we also find ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7222-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7222_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:11:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/FriendlyThing/article/3107096</link><title>Route 66 Remembered</title><description>Now available in paperback!!This incredible collection of historical photographs captures the reverence of all the attractions and towns of the Mother Road, Route 66. Noted author Michael Witzel spent years traveling Route 66 collecting mementos of life and folklore that make up the most famous road in America. His unmatched photography takes readers back to the attractions and towns as they were and offers a captivating view of them today. Here it is, the American highway past and present in Motorbooks' beautiful 10 x 10 format, the classic ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>