<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:54:36" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:54:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ritarovai/article/8366504</link><title>Curriculum Standards for Social Studies: Expectations of Excellence (Bulletin (National Council for the Social Studies))</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:55:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ChristianRauh/article/10242779</link><title>Interventions and negotiation in the Council of Ministers of the European Union</title><description>Making interventions during negotiations within the Council of Ministers is the primary way in which member states make their policy positions known to one another and attempt to influence negotiations. In spite of this, relatively little scholarly attention has been paid to the factors that influence a member state’s decision to intervene. This paper seeks to address this gap in our understanding by analysing a new data set that specifies which member states are intervening and at what level of negotiation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:57:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pcconway/article/7680645</link><title>World social science report 2010: knowledge divides</title><description>Social science from Western countries continues to have the greatest global influence, but the field is expanding rapidly in Asia and Latin America, particularly in China and Brazil. In sub-Saharan Africa, social scientists from South Africa, Nigeria and Kenya produce 75% of academic publications. In South Asia, barring some centres of excellence in India, social sciences as a whole have low priority. These are a few of the findings from World Social Science Report, 2010: Knowledge divides. Produced by the International ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:59:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scouserontour/article/7425851</link><title>Resuscitation guidelines 2005.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:01:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jpb1301/article/9020931</link><title>Advanced life support.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:05:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mommagot4/article/5846360</link><title>Project WILD K-12 Curriculum and Activity Guide</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:05:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maispace/article/9735846</link><title>User fees : RCO workshop proceedings</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alonihill/article/6690548</link><title>The Canadian Music Journal : Special issue : Organs and organ playing in Canada.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ChristianRauh/article/3495839</link><title>Party politics in the European Council</title><description>This article explores the extent to which the growing party politicization of the EU extends to the European Council. We advance the argument that three central factors shape the extent to which party politics influences European Council outcomes: the salience of an issue along the left?right dimension, the partisan composition of the European Council, and the cohesion and mobilization of transnational parties. We explore the influence of these factors empirically through an inventory of élite interview evidence as well as two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7230-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7230_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:12:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maispace/article/9735869</link><title>Achieving a balance : public and private sector roles in the development of a 3Rs infrastructure : discussion paper</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>