<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7234">347 ford engines</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:52:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:52:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/seabay/article/463026</link><title>Search in Peer-to-Peer File-Sharing System:</title><description>Peer-to-peer information systems have gained prominence of late with applications such as file sharing systems and grid computing. However, the information retrieval component of these systems is still limited because traditional techniques for searching and ranking are not directly applicable. This work compares search in peer-to-peer information systems to that in metasearch engines, and describes how they are unique. Many works describing advances in peer-to-peer information retrieval are... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:53:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/HugoDeBacker/article/3143570</link><title>Statistical reconstruction of daily total ozone over Europe 1950 to 2004</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:55:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9231538</link><title>A novel compression strategy for air hybrid engines</title><description>A novel compression strategy for air hybrid engines is proposed utilizing two storage tanks which increases the efficiency of regenerative braking of air hybrid vehicles significantly by increasing the stored air mass and, consequently, the storing pressure in the tank. The second law definition for efficiency is suggested and employed to evaluate the regenerative system capability in storing the kinetic energy of a decelerating vehicle. The maximum energy storing capacity of conventional and proposed compression methods are derived and the advantage ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:57:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/muli/article/6518401</link><title>Microkernels meet recursive virtual machines</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brianb/article/4199097</link><title>Comparative Proteomic Profiling of Membrane Proteins in Rat Cerebellum, Spinal Cord, and Sciatic Nerve.</title><description>Proteomics is an increasingly powerful technology that can provide in-depth insights into entire proteomes and their variation upon disease. Large scale proteomics today enables identification and measurement of changes of thousands of proteins from minute amount of tissues. Here we provide a proteomic profile of three distinct parts of the murine nerve system: cerebellum, spinal cord, and sciatic nerve. We focus on membrane proteins as the key regulators of neural transmission and memory. Rat tissues were homogenized and extracted to remove ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:01:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vvijay03/article/8271944</link><title>Efficient System-Enforced Deterministic Parallelism</title><description>Deterministic execution offers many benefits for debugging, fault tolerance, and security. Running parallel programs deterministically is usually difficult and costly, however - especially if we desire system-enforced determinism, ensuring precise repeatability of arbitrarily buggy or malicious software. Determinator is a novel operating system that enforces determinism on both multithreaded and multi-process computations. Determinator's kernel provides only single-threaded, "shared-nothing" address spaces interacting via deterministic synchronization. An untrusted user-level runtime uses distributed computing techniques to emulate familiar abstractions such as Unix processes, file ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:01:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4501631</link><title>Independence Day</title><description>A visionary account of American life--and the long-awaited sequel to one of the most celebrated novels of the past decade--_Independence Day_ reveals a man and our country with unflinching comedy and the specter of hope and even permanence, all of which Richard Ford evokes with keen intelligence, perfect emotional pitch, and a voice invested with absolute authority. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:02:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sangman/article/12248338</link><title>Coal vs. Charcoal-fueled Diesel Engines: A Review</title><description>Abstract Coal-fired diesel engines utilizing coal-water slurries have been intensively investigated by previous researchers. Specialized coal-water slurries injection equipment was developed to handle the slurries, and hard materials were used to handle the abrasion due to coal ash. Charcoal-based water slurries are shown to result in dramatically reduced engine abrasion problems compared to coal. An economic comparison of charcoal-based water slurries to #2 diesel fuel for fueling diesel engines shows promise for the charcoal-based water sluries diesel fuel. In addition, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:05:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5664758</link><title>What is recovery? Revisiting the Betty Ford Institute Consensus Panel Definition</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7234-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7234_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:07:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/770607</link><title>Modern Theologians: An Introduction to Christian Theology since 1918 (The Great Theologians)</title><description>The Modern Theologians provides a comprehensive and accessible overview of the main Christian theologies of the twentieth and twenty-first centuries. Each chapter is written by a leading theologian and gives a clear picture of a particular movement, topic or individual. Together these provide an unparalleled picture of the development of modern theology.The third edition includes:- new and updated treatments of topics covered in earlier editions;- a new section on six classic theologians of the twentieth century;- expanded treatment of the natural ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>