<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7235">silicone roof coatings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:08:51" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:08:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kdesmond/article/11035792</link><title>Pull-off behavior of epoxy bonded to silicone duplex coatings</title><description>Flat-head studs, 7.2 mm diameter, were epoxied to 0.1–0.9 mm thick silicone layers attached to a rigid substrate. Pull-off tests were performed at nominally 1.5 N/s to establish critical pull-off forces and detachment modes at the epoxy–silicone interface. Most tests were performed on a two-layer coating consisting of a silicone top coat and a stiffer silicone bond coat. A few tests were performed with a single layer of transparent silicone on a glass substrate, which allowed video analysis of the interface during pull-off. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:10:09">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5230410</link><title>A study of the effect of different iron oxide pigment grades on properties of an industrial latex coating</title><description>Abstract  Two red iron oxide pigments with similar properties but prepared by different chemical processes were obtained for evaluation. One process provided a pigment described as rhombohedral in shape; the other was described as spheroidal. The pigments were incorporated into an industrial latex coating formulation at the same pigment volume concentration. Properties of the liquid formulations, wet applied films, dried films, and free films were measured. Representative tests run were viscosity, gloss, adhesion, and prohesion. Differences in the degree of coalescence, accelerated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:11:59">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5272/article/2997521</link><title>Self-healing coatings for steel</title><description>The efficacy of a "self-healing" corrosion protection coating system for use on steel enclosures for outdoor equipment has been investigated using urea formaldehyde microcapsules (50-150 [mu]m in diameter) containing several types of film forming compounds (healants) and corrosion inhibitors mixed into commercially available coatings systems. Five different types of inhibitors/film formers were tested, and three different techniques for application of the coatings with microcapsules were evaluated. Laboratory tests showed that when the coating system was damaged by abrasion, the microcapsules released the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:15:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arcticwoman/article/1220965</link><title>Spiritual Marketplace: Baby Boomers and the Remaking of American Religion.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In large chain bookstores the "religion" section is gone and in its place is an expanding number of topics including angels, Sufism, journey, recovery, meditation, magic, inspiration, Judaica, astrology, gurus, Bible, prophesy, evangelicalism, Mary, Buddhism, Catholicism, and esoterica. As Wade Clark Roof notes, such changes over the last two decades reflect a shift away from religion as traditionally understood to more diverse and creative approaches. But what does this splintering of the religious perspective say about Americans? Have we become more ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:15:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Alina_Lyagusha/article/12384870</link><title>Silicone-containing polymer matrices as protective coatings</title><description>The paper addresses the technologically important problem of porous building materials protection, e.g. sandstone, limestone, marble against soiling. Protective coatings applied to the surface of porous building material should be characterized by very efficient water vapour permeability and self-cleaning properties. The objective of this work was to examine the properties of silicone-containing polymer matrices as coating materials. Fluoropolymers, polyolefins and acrylic resins were applied as organic components of the polymer matrix. The surface properties of protective coatings obtained from silicone-containing polymer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:16:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pintaude/article/7349636</link><title>An approach to elucidate the different response of PVD coatings in different tribological tests</title><description>In this paper, the different performances of duplex (i.e. with a prior plasma nitriding treatment) and non-duplex PVD coatings in micro-abrasive wear tests and impact tests are discussed, taking into account some key properties, such as nanohardness ( H ), elastic modulus ( E ) and the H / E ratio. The nanohardness and elastic modulus of the coatings were determined by nanoindentation and were characterised by means of several analytical methods, such as glow discharge optical emission spectroscopy (GDOES), X-ray ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:18:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5403222</link><title>A Separate Peace? The Soviet Union and the Making of British Strategy in the Wake of 'Barbarossa', June-September 1941</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:20:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3174446</link><title>Sacrifice for Stalin: The Cost and Value of the Arctic Convoys Reassessed</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:23:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7857157</link><title>Why David Sometimes Wins: Leadership, Organization, and Strategy in the California Farm Worker Movement</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7235-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7235_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:26:55">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6467155</link><title>Reloadable antimicrobial coatings based on amphiphilic silicone networks</title><description>Summaries  Amphiphilic networks composed of polydimethylsiloxane (PDMS), poly(2-hydroxyethylacrylate) (PHEA), and poly(acrylic acid) (PAA) have been prepared as thin covalently surface-attached coatings via a protecting group strategy. Atomic force microscopy (AFM) images revealed that both the hydrophobic PDMS phase as well as the hydrophilic PHEA and PAA phase, respectively, are present at the surface and show nanophase separation. The coatings were loaded with Rhodamine B (RB) as a model compound for release experiments. The dye is quickly released from the pure PHEA-I-PDMS coatings ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>