<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:52:15" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:52:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/simdoc/article/7134965</link><title>Transforming healthcare: a safety imperative.</title><description>Ten years ago, the Institute of Medicine reported alarming data on the scope and impact of medical errors in the US and called for national efforts to address this problem. While efforts to improve patient safety have proliferated during the past decade, progress toward improvement has been frustratingly slow. Some of this lack of progress may be attributable to the persistence of a medical ethos, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:52:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asilva/article/550524</link><title>Safety design: Towards a new philosophy</title><description>Thinking on safety integration right from design stage is of some interest in research terms. How can we increase the overall efficiency of a working system, whilst reducing risks at source and consequently costs? Can future operation of a working system be anticipated? What can be anticipated? Can we help designers to respond to statutory requirements by experience feedback and by structuring our knowledge of working system operational performance?Based on a "user-focused" design approach, this paper is structured in two sections. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:53:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/miwismith/article/12827522</link><title>Patient safety in primary care</title><description>http://www.bcpsqc.ca/pdf/Primary_Care_2010_english_FINAL.PDF</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:53:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tomfrench/article/433261</link><title>The challenge of change for strategies on health and safety at work in the 21st century</title><description>In the year of IOSH's 60th anniversary, this paper discusses some of the features of the current landscape of health and safety in Britain. It focuses especially on the nature of change and its consequences. The consequences of the structure of change in the organisation of work, employment relationships and the labour market are therefore central to its concerns, but so are the implications for the health and safety policy and practice of wider political, regulatory and economic reforms in this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:53:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/larisch/article/224006</link><title>Measuring occupational safety: from safety culture to safety orientation?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:54:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/planetiaetopia/article/9541831</link><title>Core competencies for patient safety research: a cornerstone for global capacity strengthening.</title><description>Reducing patient harm worldwide will require long-term sustained efforts to build capacity to enable practical research that addresses local problems and improves patient safety. The first edition of Competencies for Patient Safety Researchers is proposed by WHO Patient Safety as a foundation for strengthening research capacity by guiding the development of training programmes for researchers in the area of patient safety, particularly in developing and transitional countries, where such research is urgently needed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:54:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asilva/article/1604643</link><title>Formal socio-technical barrier modelling for safety-critical interactive systems design</title><description>This paper presents a three step approach to improve safety in the field of interactive systems. The approach combines, within a single framework, previous work in the field of barrier analysis and modelling, with model based design of interactive systems. The approach first uses the Safety Modelling Language to specify safety barriers which could achieve risk reduction if implemented. The detailed mechanism by which these barriers behave is designed in the subsequent stage, using a Petri nets-based formal description technique called ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:54:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asilva/article/1700224</link><title>State/event fault trees—A safety analysis model for software-controlled systems</title><description>Safety models for software-controlled systems should be intuitive, compositional and have the expressive power to model both software and hardware behaviour. Moreover, they should provide quantitative results for failure or hazard probabilities. Fault trees are an accepted and intuitive model for safety analysis, but they are incapable of expressing state dependencies or temporal order of events. We propose to combine fault trees with an explicit State/Event semantics, using a graphical notation that is similar to Statecharts. Our new model, named State/Event ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:55:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dwponder/article/9730991</link><title>Vegetation control for safety : a guide for local highway and street maintenance personnel.</title><description>Vegetation, if not controlled, can present a safety hazard for several reasons. Trees close to the road can present a fixed object hazard. Tall grass, weeds brush and tree limbs obscure or limit a driver's view of the road ahead, traffic control devices, approaching vehicles, wildlife and livestock, and pedestrians and bicycles. The purpose of this guide is to help local road agency maintenance workers identify locations where vegetation control is needed to improve traffic and pedestrian safety, to provide guidance ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7239-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7239_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:55:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/BridgetM/article/4184935</link><title>Towards an International Classification for Patient Safety: the conceptual framework</title><description>Global advances in patient safety have been hampered by the lack of a uniform classification of patient safety concepts. This is a significant barrier to developing strategies to reduce risk, performing evidence-based research and evaluating existing healthcare policies relevant to patient safety. Since 2005, the World Health Organization's World Alliance for Patient Safety has undertaken the Project to Develop an International Classification for Patient Safety (ICPS) to devise a classification which transforms patient safety information collected from disparate systems into a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>