<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:36" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sengelken/article/5208323</link><title>H ∞ loop-shaping</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:50">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14812/article/9611523</link><title>Learning and memory: Flies know their way</title><description>Flies use visual cues to guide their navigation and require neurons in the ellipsoid body to do so. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sengelken/article/7677140</link><title>RECOVER: A Benchmark for Integrated Fault Tolerant Flight Control Evaluation</title><description>Fault tolerant flight control (FTFC), or intelligent self-adaptive control, enables improved survivability and recovery from adverse flight conditions induced by faults, damage and associated upsets. This can be achieved by âintelligentâ utilisation of the control authority of the remaining control effectors in all axes consisting of the control surfaces and engines or a combination of both. In this technique, control strategies are applied to restore vehicle stability, manoeuvrability and conventional piloting techniques for continued safe operation and a survivable landing of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12099395</link><title>Consensus guidelines for validation of virtual reality surgical simulators.</title><description>The Work Group for Evaluation and Implementation of Simulators and Skills Training Programmes is a newly formed sub-group of the European Association of Endoscopic Surgeons (EAES). This work group undertook a review of validation evidence for surgical simulators and the resulting consensus is presented in this article. Using clinical guidelines criteria, the evidence for validation for six different simulators was rated and subsequently translated to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hannibal_07/article/1361300</link><title>Simulation of Computer Architectures: Simulators, Benchmarks, Methodologies, and Recommendations</title><description>Simulators have become an integral part of the computer architecture research and design process. Since they have the advantages of cost, time, and flexibility, architects use them to guide design space exploration and to quantify the efficacy of an enhancement. However, long simulation times and poor accuracy limit their effectiveness. To reduce the simulation time, architects have proposed several techniques that increase the simulation speed or throughput. To increase the accuracy, architects try to minimize the amount of error in their ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-06"><link>http://www.citeulike.org/user/c3r/article/6805910</link><title>Run-Time Interoperability Between Neuronal Network Simulators Based on the MUSIC Framework</title><description>MUSIC is a standard API allowing large scale neuron simulators to exchange data within a parallel computer during runtime. A pilot implementation of this API has been released as open source. We provide experiences from the implementation of MUSIC interfaces for two neuronal network simulators of different kinds, NEST and MOOSE. A multi-simulation of a cortico-striatal network model involving both simulators is performed, demonstrating how MUSIC can promote inter-operability between models written for different simulators and how these can be re-used ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7911315</link><title>Phylogenetic Comparative Methods Strengthen Evidence for Reduced Genetic Diversity among Endangered Tetrapods</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/schehbaz/article/9567119</link><title>A Performance Comparison of Recent Network Simulators</title><description>A widespread methodology for performance analysis in the field of communication systems engineering is network simulation. While ns-2 has established itself as virtually the standard network simulation tool, other network simulators have gained more and more attention during the last years. In this paper, we briefly survey new developments in the field of network simulation and conduct a performance comparison study by implementing an identical simulation set-up in five simulators, namely ns-2, OMNet++, ns-3, SimPy and JiST/SWANS. Our results reveal large ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zivganor/article/12602520</link><title>Visual system: Mapping motion detection.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:04:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/anamanzano/article/12803050</link><title>Simulating Work: Can Simulators Help Develop a Workforce?</title><description>The aviation model of simulator training emphasises realistic physical conditions and practice of emergency responses. Its apparent success has led to the adoption of simulators in other industries such as rail. Relatively light levels of use of the simulators in that industry indicate that simulators may not fit well in all industries, no matter how similar their operations may seem. This leads us to ask what needs to be simulated in workplace development settings and whether better-targeted simulation might expand the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>