<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:33:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:33:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/672/article/406779</link><title>Population-based study of event-rate, incidence, case fatality, and mortality for all acute vascular events in all arterial territories (Oxford Vascular Study).</title><description>Acute coronary, cerebrovascular, and peripheral vascular events have common underlying arterial pathology, risk factors, and preventive treatments, but they are rarely studied concurrently. In the Oxford Vascular Study, we determined the comparative epidemiology of different acute vascular syndromes, their current burdens, and the potential effect of the ageing population on future rates. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:36:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akylbeksydykov/article/10025905</link><title>High-Altitude Pulmonary Edema Textbook of Pulmonary Vascular Disease</title><description>High-altitude pulmonary edema (HAPE) is an uncommon form of pulmonary edema that occurs in healthy individuals within a few days of arrival at altitudes above 2,500–3,000 m. The crucial pathophysiology is an excessive hypoxia-mediated rise in pulmonary vascular resistance (PVR) or hypoxic pulmonary vasoconstriction (HPV) leading to increased microvascular hydrostatic pressures despite normal left atrial pressure. The resultant hydrostatic stress can cause both dynamic changes in the permeability of the alveolar capillary barrier and mechanical damage leading to leakage of large ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:40:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/5402387</link><title>Arteriovenous hemodialysis access: the Society for Vascular Surgery practice guidelines.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:44:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jorn79/article/1907637</link><title>Tissue-engineered vascular grafts composed of marine collagen and PLGA fibers using pulsatile perfusion bioreactors.</title><description>Novel tubular scaffolds of marine source collagen and PLGA fibers were fabricated by freeze drying and electrospinning processes for vascular grafts. The hybrid scaffolds, composed of a porous collagen matrix and a fibrous PLGA layer, had an average pore size of 150+/-50 microm. The electrospun fibrous PLGA layer on the surface of a porous tubular collagen scaffold improved the mechanical strength of the collagen scaffolds in both the dry and wet states. Smooth muscle cells (SMCs)- and endothelial cells (ECs)-cultured collagen/PLGA ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:44:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/iskanbasal/article/903663</link><title>Elevated Lipoprotein(a)--A Genetic Risk Factor for Premature Vascular Disease in People With and Without Standard Risk Factors: A Review</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:48:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alweber/article/4441813</link><title>Oxidative Stress and Vascular Disease</title><description>Growing evidence indicates that chronic and acute overproduction of reactive oxygen species (ROS) under pathophysiologic conditions is integral in the development of cardiovascular diseases (CVD). These ROS can be released from nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide (phosphate) oxidase, xanthine oxidase, lipoxygenase, mitochondria, or the uncoupling of nitric oxide synthase in vascular cells. ROS mediate various signaling pathways that underlie vascular inflammation in atherogenesis: from the initiation of fatty streak development through lesion progress to ultimate plaque rupture. Various animal models of oxidative stress ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:51:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mabetsch/article/5304091</link><title>Definition and evaluation of transient ischemic attack: a scientific statement for healthcare professionals from the American Heart Association/American Stroke Association Stroke Council; Council on Cardiovascular Surgery and Anesthesia; Council on Cardiovascular Radiology and Intervention; Council on Cardiovascular Nursing; and the Interdisciplinary Council on Peripheral Vascular Disease. The American Academy of Neurology affirms the value of this statement as an educational tool for neurologists.</title><description>This scientific statement is intended for use by physicians and allied health personnel caring for patients with transient ischemic attacks. Formal evidence review included a structured literature search of Medline from 1990 to June 2007 and data synthesis employing evidence tables, meta-analyses, and pooled analysis of individual patient-level data. The review supported endorsement of the following, tissue-based definition of transient ischemic attack (TIA): a transient episode of neurological dysfunction caused by focal brain, spinal cord, or retinal ischemia, without acute infarction. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:53:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wagrob/article/8652830</link><title>American society of echocardiography report. Clinical application of noninvasive vascular ultrasound in cardiovascular risk stratification: a report from the American Society of Echocardiography and the Society for Vascular Medicine and Biology.</title><description>Noninvasive measures of atherosclerosis have emerged as adjuncts to standard cardiovascular disease (CVD) risk factors in an attempt to refine risk stratification and the need for more aggressive preventive strategies. Two such approaches, carotid artery imaging and brachial artery reactivity testing (BART), are ultrasound based. Numerous carotid artery imaging protocols have been used, and methodologic aspects are described in detail in this review. The panel recommends that protocols: (1) use end-diastolic (minimum dimension) images for intimal-medial thickness (IMT) measurements; (2) provide ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:55:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gustavmalangu/article/137753</link><title>Tuberculosis bacteriology-priorities and indications in high prevalence countries: position of the technical staff of the Tuberculosis Division of the International Union Against Tuberculosis and Lung Disease Counterpoint</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:56:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mutya8/article/10775163</link><title>Diagnosing coeliac disease</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>