<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:20:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:20:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/baisemain/article/9305738</link><title>Swahili</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:21:14">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11158995</link><title>Recycled dishes form telescope network</title><description>Africa refits redundant satellite dishes for radio astronomy. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:23:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11335748</link><title>Finding Meaning in Ancient Swahili Spatial Practices</title><description>The development of the Swahili world involved new ways of organizing and conceiving of space. Archaeology and historical linguistics are both crucial in charting the trajectory of changing spatial practice during the late first and early second millennium ad , yet their respective datasets have been correlated only in specific and restricted ways. In this paper, we take the first steps toward working between archaeological and historical linguistic data to understand the changing contexts and meanings of Swahili spatial practice. We ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:24:08">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10376589</link><title>Archaeology at the micro-scale: micromorphology and phytoliths at a Swahili stonetown</title><description>Geoarchaeological and archaeobotanical techniques are increasingly applied to the study of urban and domestic space. However, they are seldom performed as part of an integrative approach, where the soil and botanical micro-records are used together. This paper presents the preliminary results of ongoing research at Songo Mnara in Tanzania that combines customised intra-site soil macro- and micromorphological analyses, chemical analysis and the study of phytoliths. The research is part of a multidisciplinary project on the use of urban space in Swahili ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:26:26">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2718/article/2919080</link><title>Performing the Nation: Swahili Music and Cultural Politics in Tanzania</title><description>Since its founding in 1964, the United Republic of Tanzania has used music, dance, and other cultural productions as ways of imagining and legitimizing the new nation. Focusing on the politics surrounding Swahili musical performance, Kelly Askew demonstrates the crucial role of popular culture in Tanzania's colonial and postcolonial history. As Askew shows, the genres of _ngoma_ (traditional dance), _dansi_ (urban jazz), and _taarab_ (sung Swahili poetry) have played prominent parts in official articulations of "Tanzanian National Culture" over the years. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:29:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9856714</link><title>The message in the navel: (ir)realis and negation in Swahili</title><description>It is argued that the encoding of conceptual categories such as ‘realis’ should be investigated by analyzing the meanings of linguistic signs rather than by focusing on a priori message-categories that may not be expressed by specific linguistic forms. Applying this method to the expression of ‘realis’ in Swahili reveals a complex relationship between tense-aspect-modality, negation, and realis status in which some forms signal information related to irrealis, but no forms explicitly signal the meaning ‘realis’; the two negation markers span ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:33:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aletteschoon/article/8222285</link><title>A mobile phone: mobility, materiality and everyday Swahili trading practices</title><description>This article engages with the recent literature on material culture, ‘follow-the-thing geographies’, mobility and mobile communication technologies by linking these theoretical reflections to ethnographic research in East Africa. Using the biography of a specific mobile phone as a window through which to shed light on the spatial and cultural practices in which the object is embedded, it attempts to provide an insight into contemporary trading practices in a Swahili context. Presenting phases in the life course of a particular mobile phone, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:36:58">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10164249</link><title>Ceramics and the Early Swahili: Deconstructing the Early Tana Tradition</title><description>Archaeological understandings of the Iron Age societies that developed on the East African coast and its hinterland have been transformed by exploration of locally produced ceramics. During the late first millennium, c. AD 600–900, sites across eastern Africa are characterized by ceramics known as early Tana Tradition or Triangular-Incised Ware, containing necked jars with incised decoration and a series of other jar and bowl forms in varying quantities. The recognition of this pan-regional tradition of pottery, known from an ever-growing number ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:40:41">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10408221</link><title>Characteristics of Swahili–English bilingual agrammatic spontaneous speech and the consequences for understanding agrammatic aphasia</title><description>Most studies on spontaneous speech of individuals with agrammatism have focused almost exclusively on monolingual individuals. There is hardly any previous research on bilinguals, especially of structurally different languages; and none on characterization of agrammatism in Swahili. The current study identifies the features of Swahili agrammatic narrative and spontaneous speech, and compares the use of verb inflections for tense and time reference in English and Swahili in six bilingual agrammatic speakers and 12 non-brain-damaged speakers matched on age, native language and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7258-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7258_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:43:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5352739</link><title>Size vis-à-vis frequency: minimality and maximality constraints in Swahili</title><description>The article focuses on the role of frequency in allomorphy, specifically, on the correlation between lexical frequency and the size of an appropriate allomorph. It is demonstrated that various kinds of apparently irregular morphophonemic processes, as well as many cases of static generalizations, receive a natural and unified explanation, if size and frequency criteria are taken into account. While constraints imposing minimal prosodic structure have been previously recognized in the formal apparatus of phonological theory, a new proposal consists in postulating ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>