<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:44:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:44:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maniruzzaman/article/9455341</link><title>Root nitrogen acquisition and assimilation Root Physiology: from Gene to Function</title><description>Nitrogen (N) is the main mineral element in plant tissues and almost all of this nutrient is acquired from the soil by the roots. Nitrogen is available in many different forms in the soil, but the three most abundant forms are nitrate, ammonium and amino acids. The relative importance of these different soil N pools to a plant is difficult to measure and depends on many different environmental factors. Changes in the available amounts and imbalance in the supply of some ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:47:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ben-villarreal/article/6871872</link><title>Attachment of Listeria monocytogenes to radish tissue is dependent upon temperature and flagellar motility.</title><description>Outbreaks of listeriosis and febrile gastroenteritis have been linked to produce contamination by Listeria monocytogenes. In order to begin to understand the physiology of the organism in a produce habitat, the ability of L. monocytogenes to attach to freshly cut radish tissue was examined. All strains tested had the capacity to attach sufficiently well such that they could not be removed during washing of the radish slices. A screen was developed to identify Tn917-LTV3 mutants that were defective in attachment to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:49:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucioAlencar/article/10257216</link><title>Controls of biomass partitioning between roots and shoots: Atmospheric CO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; enrichment and the acquisition and allocation of carbon and nitrogen in wild radish</title><description>The effects of CO 2 enrichment on plant growth, carbon and nitrogen acquisition and resource allocation were investigated in order to examine several hypotheses about the mechanisms that govern dry matter partitioning between shoots and roots. Wild radish plants ( Raphanus sativus × raphanistrum ) were grown for 25 d under three different atmospheric CO 2 concentrations (200 ppm, 330 ppm and 600 ppm) with a stable hydroponic 150 µmol 1 -1 nitrate supply. Radish biomass accumulation, photosynthetic rate, water use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:49:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ajaymalik/article/4817889</link><title>Beautiful Bones without Hormones: The All-New Natural Diet and Exercise Program to Reduce the Risk of Osteoporosis</title><description>Dr. Leon Root, world-renowned orthopedic surgeon and author of the bestseller _Oh, My Aching Back_, presents a 100% natural, HRT-free diet and exercise program for increasing bone density and reducing the risk of osteoporosis. "Save your bones, save your life." That’s Dr. Root’s motto after thirty-five years in practice. Today, forty-four million Americans suffer from osteoporosis or osteopenia. Having seen scores of people lose their independence and their lives to osteoporosis-related fractures, Dr. Root has become a crusader against this silent killer. Dr. Root’s plan is the first ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:51:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/icq242500260/article/7664729</link><title>Evolution and genetics of root hair stripes in the root epidermis.</title><description>Root hair pattern develops in a number of different ways in angiosperm. Cells in the epidermis of some species undergo asymmetric cell divisions to form a smaller daughter cell from which a hair grows, and a larger cell that forms a non-hair epidermal cell. In other species any cell in the epidermis can form a root hair. Hair cells are arranged in files along the Arabidopsis root, located in the gaps between underlying cortical cell files. Epidermal cells overlying a single ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:53:58">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7401031</link><title>Experimental Test of L- and D-Amino Acid Binding to L- and D-Codons Suggests that Homochirality and Codon Directionality Emerged with the Genetic Code</title><description>L-amino acids bind preferentially to their D-codons, but almost nothing is known about whether D-amino acids correspondingly prefer L-codons, or how codon directionality affects amino acid binding. To investigate these issues, two D-RNA-oligonucleotides having inverse base sequences (D-CGUA and D-AUGC) and their corresponding L-RNA-oligonucleotides (L-CGUA and L-AUGC) were synthesized and their affinity determined for Gly and eleven pairs of L- and D-amino acids. The data support the hypothesis (Root-Bernstein, Bioessays 2007; 29: 689–698) that homochirality and codon directionality emerged as a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:54:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/svuskumar/article/10051494</link><title>From weeds to crops: genetic analysis of root development in cereals</title><description>Root development of Arabidopsis, Zea mays (maize) and Oryza sativa (rice) differs in both overall architecture and the anatomy of individual roots. In maize and rice, the post-embryonic shoot-borne root system becomes the major backbone of the root stock; in Arabidopsis, the embryonic root system formed by a simple primary root and its lateral roots remains dominant. Recently, several specific root mutants and root-specific genes have been identified and characterized in maize and rice. Interestingly, some of these mutants indicate that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:55:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/svuskumar/article/9459215</link><title>An Auxin-Dependent Distal Organizer of Pattern and Polarity in the Arabidopsis Root</title><description>Root formation in plants involves the continuous interpretation of positional cues. Physiological studies have linked root formation to auxins. An auxin response element displays a maximum in the Arabidopsis root and we investigate its developmental significance. Auxin response mutants reduce the maximum or its perception, and interfere with distal root patterning. Polar auxin transport mutants affect its localization and distal pattern. Polar auxin transport inhibitors cause dramatic relocalization of the maximum, and associated changes in pattern and polarity. Auxin application and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:59:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/icq242500260/article/7679187</link><title>Genetic Interactions during Root Hair Morphogenesis in Arabidopsis</title><description>Root hairs are a major site for the uptake of water and nutrients into plants and form an increasingly important model system for studies of development of higher plants and cell biology. We have identified loss-of-function mutations in eight new genes required for hair growth in Arabidopsis: SHAVEN1 (SHV1), SHV2, and SHV3; CENTIPEDE1 (CEN1), CEN2, and CEN3; BRISTLED1 (BST1); and SUPERCENTIPEDE1 (SCN1). We combined mutations in 79 pairs of genes to determine the stages at which these and six previously known ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:02:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Vladislav2904/article/2057167</link><title>Cross-platform approach to create the interactive applications based on ROOT and Qt GUI libraries</title><description>This paper presents the approach and an implementation of the Qt-based low-level graphical plug-in of the ROOT package. In spite of other existing implementations, this work uniquely allows to create applications which can seamlessly use the ROOT GUI classes as well as the Qt Widgets. The current code can be built from a single ROOT-base package and can be assembled for both Unix and Windows OS. No alteration of either user code or core ROOT code is required. An example application ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>