<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:42:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:42:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EricBatard/article/12766498</link><title>A Worldwide Perspective of Nursing Home-Acquired Pneumonia compared to Community-acquired Pneumonia.</title><description>Nursing home-acquired pneumonia (NHAP) is the leading cause of death among long-term care patients and the second most common cause of transfers to acute care facilities. The objective was to characterize the incidences, microbiology, and outcomes for hospitalized patients with community-acquired pneumonia (CAP) and NHAP. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:44:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/8700087</link><title>Vitamin D, innate immunity and outcomes in community acquired pneumonia</title><description>ABSTRACT Background and objective:  Vitamin D regulates the production of the antimicrobial peptides cathelicidin and beta-defensin-2, which play an important role in the innate immune response to infection. We hypothesized that vitamin D deficiency would be associated with lower levels of these peptides and worse outcomes in patients admitted to hospital with community acquired pneumonia. Methods:  Associations between mortality and serum levels of 25-hydroxyvitamin D, cathelicidin and beta-defensin-2 were investigated in a prospective cohort of 112 patients admitted with community acquired ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:47:44">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6233614</link><title>The pneumonia severity index and the CRB-65 in cancer patients with community-acquired pneumonia</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:50:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jufunkystyle/article/3777841</link><title>Mortality in ICU patients with bacterial community-acquired pneumonia: when antibiotics are not enough</title><description>Abstract Background  It remains uncertain why immunocompetent patients with bacterial community-acquired pneumonia (CAP) die, in spite of adequate antibiotics. Methods  This is a secondary analysis of the CAPUCI database which was a prospective observational multicentre study. Two hundred and twelve immunocompetent patients admitted to 33 Spanish ICUs for CAP were analyzed. Comparisons were made for lifestyle risk factors, comorbidities and severity of illness. ICU mortality was the principal outcome variable. Results  Bacteremic CAP (43.3 vs. 21.1%) and empyema (11.5 vs. 2.2%) were more frequent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:52:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/inbetweener/article/1577855</link><title>The Relation Between Hyperglycemia and Outcomes in 2,471 Patients Admitted to the Hospital With Community-Acquired Pneumonia</title><description>10.2337/diacare.28.4.810 â To examine whether hyperglycemia at the time of presentation was associated with outcomes in patients admitted to nonâintensive care settings with community-acquired pneumonia (CAP). â Prospective cohort study of consecutive patients admitted to six hospitals between 15 November 2000 and 14 November 2002. â Of the 2,471 patients in this study (median age 75 years), 279 (11%) had serum glucose at presentation &gt;11 mmol/l: 178 of the 401 patients (44%) with a prior diagnosis of diabetes and 101 of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:55:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/416698</link><title>Swedish guidelines for the management of community-acquired pneumonia in immunocompetent adults</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:58:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wqunit/article/12749038</link><title>Legionnaires' disease - Results of a multicentre Canadian study.</title><description>There has never been a cross-Canada surveillance project to determine the rate of Legionella species as a cause of community-acquired pneumonia requiring hospitalization and to determine whether there are any regional differences in the rates of Legionnaires' disease in Canada. Anecdotally, Legionnaires' disease is thought to be uncommon in Western Canada. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:01:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/697190</link><title>The pneumonia severity index predicts time to clinical stability in patients with community-acquired pneumonia</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:02:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/KGelling/article/12822204</link><title>Vitamin D Status and Community-Acquired Pneumonia: Results from the Third National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey</title><description>To investigate the association between serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D [25(OH)D] level and history of community-acquired pneumonia (CAP). We identified 16,975 individuals (≥17 years) from the third National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES III) with documented 25(OH)D levels. To investigate the association of 25(OH)D with history of CAP in these participants, we developed a multivariable logistic regression model, adjusting for demographic factors (age, sex, race, poverty-to-income ratio, and geographic location), clinical data (body mass index, smoking status, asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:02:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/4886846</link><title>Acid-suppressive medication use and the risk for hospital-acquired pneumonia.</title><description>CONTEXT: The use of acid-suppressive medication has been steadily increasing, particularly in the inpatient setting, despite lack of an accepted indication in the majority of these patients. OBJECTIVE: To examine the association between acid-suppressive medication and hospital-acquired pneumonia. DESIGN, SETTING, AND PATIENTS: Prospective pharmacoepidemiologic cohort study. All patients who were admitted to a large, urban, academic medical center in Boston, Massachusetts, from January 2004 through December 2007; at least 18 years of age; and hospitalized for 3 or more days were ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>