<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:53:21" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:53:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/imarregui/article/6487599</link><title>The Fabulous Ruins of Detroit: Selected Excerpts</title><description>Excerpts are presented from each of three acts of The Fabulous Ruins of Detroit, a play that tells the story of a Black man and a White woman, who grow up in the same neighborhood, survive the 1967 riots/rebellion together, and meet again 40 years later. Ruins is based on the author's autoethnography, oral histories, archival materials, and the imaginative re-creation of actual events. 10.1177/1077800409350703 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:54:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Rootfruit/article/453452</link><title>Interdisciplinary criticism: analysing the experience of &lt;i&gt;riot!&lt;/i&gt; a location-sensitive digital narrative</title><description>This paper reports the findings from quantitative and qualitative studies of Riot!  a location-sensitive interactive play for voices. The paper begins by introducing Riot!; it then explores the growing literature on theories of experience and goes on to report the findings from three empirical studies of the event: a questionnaire-based survey of 563 participants; 30 semi-structured interviews with groups and individuals; and in-depth ethnographic case studies of four participants. It was clear from the survey that most people had enjoyed Riot! However, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:55:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mdebbink/article/494029</link><title>Neighborhood Racial Composition, Neighborhood Poverty, and the Spatial Accessibility of Supermarkets in Metropolitan Detroit</title><description>Objectives. We evaluated the spatial accessibility of large "chain" supermarkets in relation to neighborhood racial composition and poverty. Methods. We used a geographic information system to measure Manhattan block distance to the nearest supermarket for 869 neighborhoods (census tracts) in metropolitan Detroit. We constructed moving average spatial regression models to adjust for spatial autocorrelation and to test for the effect of modification of percentage African American and percentage poor on distance to the nearest supermarket. Results. Distance to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:57:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dwaynecole/article/7110431</link><title>Can communities and academia work together on public health research? Evaluation results from a community-based participatory research partnershipin detroit</title><description>Abstract  This article reports the results of a formative evaluation of the first 4 years of the Detroit Community-Academic Urban Research Center (URC), a community-based participatory research partnership that was founded in 1995 with core funding from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). Several organizations are members of this partnership, including a university, six community-based organizations, a city health department, a health care system, and CDC. The Detroit URC is a strong partnership that has accomplished many of its goals, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:59:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mdebbink/article/1693028</link><title>Unfair treatment, neighborhood effects, and mental health in the Detroit metropolitan area.</title><description>Why do racial differences in many indicators of mental and emotional well-being show inconsistent patterns? We propose that mental and emotional well-being are influenced by aspects of the social context, including experiences of unfair treatment and the concentration of households with incomes below the poverty level, and that differential exposure to these factors influences racial differences in mental well-being. We analyze the reporting of psychological distress and life satisfaction in a multistage area probability sample of 1,139 African American and white ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:02:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/310447</link><title>One or several models for competence descriptions: Does it matter?</title><description>In the late 1980s, job and competence descriptions appeared as a necessity for human resource development (HRD). Afterward, they were used more and more to build or to change training programs. In a country such as France, which promotes life-long learning through the VAP Act (Accreditation of Work Experience), and since January 2002, through a new act concerning VAE (Accreditation of Experiential Learning), will they still have to evolve? In fact, the way we define competencies is necessarily oriented toward ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:06:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5892937</link><title>It’s Raining Dykes (Il pleut des gouines): A Queer and Feminist Comix Zine</title><description>doi: 10.1086/599291 Abstract When i make art, I want people to look at it, smile, and say, “This also happens to me.” Fun, when it is full of criticisms and questioning, is a revolutionary tool. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:09:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mdebbink/article/1693031</link><title>Racial and spatial relations as fundamental determinants of health in Detroit.</title><description>African Americans in the United States have a higher than average risk of morbidity and mortality, despite declining mortality rates for many causes of death for the general population. This article examines race-based residential segregation as a fundamental cause of racial disparities, shaping differences in exposure to, and experiences of, diseases and risk factors. The spatial distribution of racial groups, specifically the residential segregation of African Americans in aging urban areas, contributes to disparities in health by influencing access to economic, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:09:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/imarregui/article/6285302</link><title>Detroit: A tale of two crises</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:12:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/apwheele/article/11598233</link><title>Spatial Patterns in the 2011 London Riots</title><description>Riots broke out in London on 6th August 2011. Many narratives of the riots describe them as having subsequently intensified within and spread across various parts of the city during the following 4 days and nights before finally petering out. This article addresses two important empirical puzzles stemming from the riots. First, we ask whether the riot events did indeed display distinct spatial patterns and, if so, whether these events spread between locations. Second, we discuss how knowledge of the spatial ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>