<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:24:52" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:24:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10895484</link><title>Mathematics in Context (MiC). What Works Clearinghouse Intervention Report</title><description>"Mathematics in Context" is a middle school mathematics curriculum for grades 5 through 8. It was developed to align with the 1989 National Council of Teachers of Mathematics (NCTM) Curriculum and Evaluation Standards. It is also based on the Dutch Realistic Mathematics Education approach of engaging students in understanding real-life problems and gradually moving to abstract concepts. Rather than focusing on one mathematical domain at a time, "Mathematics in Context" teaches students to explore the relationships among different domains of mathematics ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:25:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dabd/article/7290890</link><title>RESTful Web Services Principles of REST Web Service Design Semantic of HTTP/1.1 Operations SOAP vs. REST Style Assets and Drawbacks Security Public Web Services What is REST? Representational State Transfer</title><description>Representation of resource at URI places client in a state Hyperlinks are transitions between states Services itself should be stateless “The name ‘Representational State Transfer ’ is intended to evoke an image of how a well-designed Web application behaves: a network of web pages (a virtual state-machine), where the user progresses through an application by selecting links (state transitions), resulting in the next page (representing the next state of the application) being transferred to the user and rendered for their use.” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:28:43">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14171/article/8118382</link><title>The Frequency of Self-Limiting Behavior in Groups: A Measure and an Explanation</title><description>This study sought to develop a valid and reliable measure of the frequency with which individuals choose to engage in self-limiting behavior in groups, i.e., behavior that reduces the individual's influence on or contribution to the performance of a work group's task. In addition, this study explored under what general conditions managers perceive they are most inclined to engage in self-limiting behavior when they are members of a task group. Based on in-depth interviews of managers and executives, and a relevant ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:30:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suzelowe/article/4057193</link><title>Middle School Math. What Works Clearinghouse Topic Report</title><description>The What Works Clearinghouse (WWC) reviewed interventions to promote middle school students' math knowledge and skills. Because there is some variation in how school districts organize middle school, we considered curricula aimed at students in grades 6 through 9, covering one or more of the following content areas: numbers and operations, algebra, geometry, measurement, and data analysis and probability. Only core, comprehensive math curricula were eligible for inclusion in this review. These curricula extend over the course of one semester or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:32:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mahler/article/379582</link><title>Describing, Transforming, and Querying Semistructured Data</title><description>eN FROM Person P, Person C, Person G WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.Child = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN Get the phone numbers of Joe's grandchildren. Against the decomposed relations is even worse: four joins SELECT N.PhoneN FROM Person1 P, ChildOf C, ChildOf G, Phone N WHERE P.Name = `Joe Public' AND P.SSN = C.SSN AND C.Child = G.SSN AND G.Child = N.SSN Objects Allow Simpler Design Schema: Child: SSN ) No need to decompose in order to eliminate redundancy: the set data type takes ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:33:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cherrie/article/4311368</link><title>Dispositions of junctional feet in muscles of invertebrates</title><description>Summary The structure and disposition of the feet occupying the junctions between sarcoplasmic reticulum (SR) and surface membrane/transverse tubules were studied in muscles from a variety of invertebrates. Feet were imaged by rotary shadowing of isolated junctional SR vesicles and by filtering of micrographs from grazing views of the junction in thin sections. The overall size and shape of invertebrate feet is the same as that of feet in skeletal and cardiac muscle of vertebrates. However, the arrangement of feet in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:35:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rogeriodt/article/8257235</link><title>Ultrasound of the small joints of the hands and feet: current status.</title><description>The aim of this article was to review the current status of ultrasound imaging of patients with rheumatological disorders of the hands and feet. Ultrasound machines with high-resolution surface probes are readily available in most radiology departments and can be used to address important clinical questions posed by the rheumatologist and sports and rehabilitation physician. There is increasing evidence that ultrasound detects synovitis that is silent to clinical examination. Detection and classification of synovitis and the early detection of bone erosions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:37:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mpgrayer/article/3667218</link><title>Material deprivation and leading causes of death by gender: evidence from a nationwide small area study</title><description>STUDY OBJECTIVE[---]To investigate the association between material deprivation and 10 leading causes of death by gender. DESIGN[---]Small area cross sectional ecological study using two dimensions of material deprivation (Index 1 and Index 2) drawn from 1991 census and cause specific mortality data aggregated for 1987-1995. SETTING[---]2218 small areas in Spain. MAIN RESULTS[---]Strong detrimental associations of two deprivation indices were found with top six leading causes of death for men and top seven leading causes of death for women, except breast cancer. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:39:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/paldaily/article/12153529</link><title>Eight ways to stay healthy after cancer: an evidence-based message.</title><description>Since 1999, in conjunction with the internationally known and award-winning Your Disease Risk ( yourdiseaserisk.org ) risk assessment tool, the "Eight Ways to Stay Healthy and Prevent Cancer" message campaign has provided an evidence-based, but user-friendly, approach to cancer prevention. The scientific evidence behind the campaign is robust and while not a complete list, provides a great deal of benefit in the reduction of cancer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7303-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7303_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:40:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelliskf/article/4116400</link><title>WWC Quick Review of the Article "Promoting Broad and Stable Improvements in Low-Income Children's Numerical Knowledge Through Playing Number Board Games"</title><description>This review examined a study designed to evaluate whether playing number board games improved numeracy skills of low-income preschoolers. The study included 136 pre-school children from 10 urban Head Start centers: 72 children were randomly selected to play a number board game with a trained experimenter; the remaining 64 children played a different version of the game using colors instead of numbers. Numeracy skills were assessed at the end of a two-week period and again nine weeks later. Study authors reported ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>