<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:22:08" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:22:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tillgeiger/article/4810607</link><title>Sexing up the Cold War: New Evidence on the MolotovTruman Talks of April 1945</title><description>This article presents and examines new evidence from the Russian archives on the TrumanMolotov talks of April 1945. This new evidence undercuts the conventional story that this was a rough and tough meeting that led to a significant deterioration of SovietAmerican relations. The turn to Cold War came much later, and it was only in that context that the MolotovTruman encounter came to be looked upon as a particularly negative event. That retrospective view fed into postwar memoirs and then into ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:23:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dsogge/article/11861430</link><title>Cold War Social Science</title><description>From World War II to the early 1970s, social science research expanded in dramatic and unprecedented fashion in the United States, which became the world's acknowledged leader in the field. This volume examines how, why, and with what consequences this rapid and yet contested expansion depended on the entanglement of the social sciences with the Cold War. Utilizing the controversial but useful concept of "Cold War Social Science," the contributions gathered here reveal how scholars from established disciplines and new interdisciplinary ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:23:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/martindbrown/article/1079759</link><title>Devices and Desires: On the Uses of Cold War History</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:26:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tillgeiger/article/6743658</link><title>The Costs and Consequences of the Cold War</title><description>After World War II, the consequences of the Soviet Union's victory over the Nazis were rejected, and a global containment of communism was elevated into a doctrine by President Truman. By the Cold War, we spurred the Soviet Union from exhaustion to great-power status, the atomic bomb, and space achievement. Our policies against communism in China had much the same effect there. The Cold War has also frozen the world into its immediate postwar postures and pre vented peace settlements in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:28:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/craigtalbert/article/903536</link><title>Tibet's Cold War: The CIA and the Chushi Gangdrug Resistance, 1956-1974</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This article analyzes the Chushi Gangdrug Tibetan resistance as narrated primarily by Tibetan veterans. The article recounts the origins of the Tibetan resistance forces, their relationship with the U.S. Central Intelligence Agency,&amp;#x00A0;their eventual laying down of arms in 1974, and their legacy in the present-day exile community. Analyses of the Tibetan resistance and the guerrilla war must take account of cultural as well as political and historical factors. The war, pitting a voluntary Tibetan guerrilla movement against the Chinese Communist army, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:30:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shamma/article/3107108</link><title>Brainwashed for War Programmed to Kill: The Military-Industrial-Media Complex Propaganda Behind the Cold War, the Vietnam War &amp; the War on Terrorism</title><description>The Companion to Future Fast Forward. In a continuing effort by the best- selling author of Future Fastforward, the erudite scholar of political intrigue and conspiracy, Matthias Chang, sets for the modi operandi of the Zionist masterminds to brainwash and program the minds of the people to achieve their goal of world domination. Tracing back four decades and more, Brainwashed for War - Programmed to Kill documents the atrocities carried out by the imperialist forces to subjugate the peoples of the world. Replete with documentary evidence, this volume ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:31:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shamma/article/580453</link><title>Winning the Long War : Lessons from the Cold War for Defeating Terrorism and Preserving Freedom</title><description>The war on terrorism, like the Cold War will be a protracted conflict requiring a long-term strategy for victory. In this book experts on homeland security, civil liberties and economics examine current U. S. Policy and map out a strategy. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:33:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/FriendlyThing/article/3107113</link><title>American Science Fiction and the Cold War: Literature and Film</title><description>American science fiction has played a key role in the portrayal of the fears inherent in the Cold War. Working through a series of important texts, David Seed investigates the political inflections put on American narratives in the post-war decades by Cold War cultural circumstances. Nuclear holocaust, Russian invasion, and the perceived rise of totalitarianism in American society are key elements in the author's exploration of science fiction narratives which include _Fahrenheit 451, Invasion of the Body Snatchers_, and _Dr. Strangelove_. The author's approach draws on the significant ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:33:33">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3040839</link><title>Cold War history in Germany</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:05">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3040838</link><title>Cold War history in Italy</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>