<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7320">cayenne pepper plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:03:17" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:03:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/10752973</link><title>The pepper RNA-binding protein CaRBP1 functions in hypersensitive cell death and defense signaling in the cytoplasm.</title><description>The regulation of gene expression via post-transcriptional modification by RNA-binding proteins is crucial for plant disease and innate immunity. Here, we report the identification of the pepper (Capsicum annuum) RNA-binding protein1 gene, CaRBP1, as essential for hypersensitive cell death and defense signaling in the cytoplasm. CaRBP1 contains an RNA recognition motif (RRM) and is rapidly and strongly induced in pepper by avirulent Xanthomonas campestris pv. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:05:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/1389519</link><title>Molecular signals required for type III secretion and translocation of the Xanthomonas campestris AvrBs2 protein to pepper plants.</title><description>Strains of Xanthomonas campestris pv. vesicatoria (Xcv) carrying avrBs2 are specifically recognized by Bs2 pepper plants, resulting in localized cell death and plant resistance. Agrobacterium-mediated transient expression of the Xcv avrBs2 gene in plant cells results in Bs2-dependent cell death, indicating that the AvrBs2 protein alone is sufficient for the activation of disease resistance-mediated cell death in planta. We now provide evidence that AvrBs2 is secreted from Xcv and that secretion is type III (hrp) dependent. N- and C-terminal deletion analysis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:08:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davidchristiansen/article/3918817</link><title>Cayenne — a language with dependent types</title><description>Cayenne is a Haskell-like language. The main difference between Haskell and Cayenne is that Cayenne has dependent types, i.e., the result type of a function may depend on the argument value, and types of record components (which can be types or values) may depend on other components. Cayenne also combines the syntactic categories for value expressions and type expressions; thus reducing the number of language concepts.Having dependent types and combined type and value expressions makes the language very powerful. It is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:09:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/10542346</link><title>Xanthomonas campestris pv. vesicatoria effector AvrBsT induces cell death in pepper, but suppresses defense responses in tomato.</title><description>A type III effector protein, AvrBsT, is secreted into plant cells from Xanthomonas campestris pv. vesicatoria Bv5-4a, which causes bacterial spot disease on pepper (Capsicum annuum) and tomato (Solanum lycopersicum). To define the function and recognition of AvrBsT in the two host plants, avrBsT was introduced into the virulent pepper strain X. campestris pv. vesicatoria Ds1. Expression of AvrBsT in Ds1 rendered the strain avirulent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:11:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/waweruk2001/article/12160038</link><title>Withania somnifera : the Indian ginseng ashwagandha</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:12:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/12231446</link><title>A pepper (Capsicum annuum L.) metacaspase 9 (Camc9) plays a role in pathogen-induced cell death in plants.</title><description>Metacaspases, which belong to the cysteine-type C14 protease family, are most structurally similar to mammalian caspases than any other caspase-like protease in plants. Atmc9 (Arabidopsis thaliana metacaspase 9) has a unique domain structure, and distinct biochemical characteristics, such as Ca(2+) binding, pH, redox status, S-nitrosylation and specific protease inhibitors. However, the biological roles of Atmc9 in plant-pathogen interactions remain largely unknown. In this study, a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:14:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/9294313</link><title>Expression of the Bs2 pepper gene confers resistance to bacterial spot disease in tomato</title><description>The Bs2 resistance gene of pepper specifically recognizes and confers resistance to strains of Xanthomonas campestris pv. vesicatoria that contain the corresponding bacterial avirulence gene, avrBs2. The involvement of avrBs2 in pathogen fitness and its prevalence in many X. campestris pathovars suggests that the Bs2 gene may be durable in the field and provide resistance when introduced into other plant species. Employing a positional cloning strategy, the Bs2 locus was isolated and the gene was identified by coexpression with avrBs2 in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:15:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gonzalez/article/12161531</link><title>Development of gene-based markers for the Bs2 bacterial spot resistance gene for marker-assisted selection in pepper (Capsicum spp.)</title><description>The Bs2 gene of pepper (Capsicum spp.) confers resistance to the most commonly detected races of Xanthomonas campestris pv vesicatora (Xcv). Using information from a published database, we developed gene-based markers for selection of Bs2 in pepper. High polymorphism was detected in exon 3, intron 2 and 3’-UTR of the Bs2 gene. The three regions were sequenced and numerous SNPs and In/Dels were identified between resistant and susceptible inbred lines. Seven SNPs were selected to develop SNP markers using the tetra-primer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:16:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10417000</link><title>Acute myocardial infarction and coronary vasospasm associated with the ingestion of cayenne pepper pills in a 25-year-old male</title><description>Capsaicin, one of the major active components of cayenne pepper pills, is an over-the-counter substance with sympathomimetic activity used commonly by young individuals for weight loss. Here we report the case of a previously healthy young male who developed severe chest pain after using cayenne pepper pills for slimming and sustained an extensive inferior myocardial infarction. Electrocardiography combined with a bedside transthoracic echocardiogram confirmed the diagnosis of acute myocardial infarction. The patient denied using illicit substances, and he had no risk ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7320-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7320_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:19:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maniruzzaman/article/10424439</link><title>Mineral cost of carnivory in aquatic carnivorous plants</title><description>Tissue N, P, K, Ca, and Mg content was estimated in traps and photosynthetic and carnivorous shoots in five aquatic carnivorous plant species from an outdoor culture: Aldrovanda vesiculosa, Utricularia vulgaris, U. reflexa, U. intermedia, and U. stygia, for the determination of the mineral cost of carnivory. In three species with monomorphic shoots (A. vesiculosa, U. vulgaris, U. reflexa), tissue P and K content in traps was significantly higher than that in their photosynthetic shoots, whereas N content was about the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>