<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:02:41" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:02:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shengj/article/9238908</link><title>Arctic oscillation response to the 1991 Pinatubo eruption in the SKYHI general circulation model with a realistic quasi-biennial oscillation</title><description>Stratospheric aerosol clouds from large tropical volcanic eruptions can be expected to alter the atmospheric radiative balance for a period of up to several years. Observations following several previous major eruptions suggest that one effect of the radiative perturbations is to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:05:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eumelus/article/11581887</link><title>Excess mortality in Europe following a future Laki-style Icelandic eruption</title><description>Historical records show that the A.D. 1783–1784 Laki eruption in Iceland caused severe environmental stress and posed a health hazard far beyond the borders of Iceland. Given the reasonable likelihood of such an event recurring, it is important to assess the scale on which a future eruption could impact society. We quantify the potential health effects caused by an increase in air pollution during a future Laki-style eruption using a global aerosol model together with concentration-response functions derived from current epidemiological studies. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:05:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shengj/article/9238810</link><title>Climate/chemistry effects of the Pinatubo volcanic eruption simulated by the UIUC stratosphere/troposphere GCM with interactive photochemistry</title><description>The influence of the sulfate aerosol formed following the massive Pinatubo volcanic eruption in June 1991 on the chemical composition, temperature, and dynamics of the atmosphere has been investigated with the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign (UIUC) stratosphere–troposphere General Circulation Model ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:08:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/carueda/article/332748</link><title>Automated volcanic eruption detection using MODIS</title><description>The moderate resolution imaging spectroradiometer (MODIS) flown on-board NASA's first earth observing system (EOS) platform, Terra, offers complete global data coverage every 1-2 days at spatial resolutions of 250, 500, and 1000 m. Its ability to detect emitted radiation in the short (4 [mu]m)- and long (12 [mu]m)-wave infrared regions of the electromagnetic spectrum, combined with the excellent geolocation of the image pixels (~200 m), makes it an ideal source of data for automatically detecting and monitoring high-temperature volcanic thermal anomalies. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:09:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ahrager/article/2289298</link><title>Volcanic eruptions and climate</title><description>Volcanic eruptions are an important natural cause of climate change on many timescales. A new capability to predict the climatic response to a large tropical eruption for the succeeding 2 years will prove valuable to society. In addition, to detect and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:10:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jbrenn19/article/6039075</link><title>Environmental impact of the 73ka Toba super-eruption in South Asia</title><description>The cooling effects of historic volcanic eruptions on world climate are well known but the impacts of even bigger prehistoric eruptions are still shrouded in mystery. The eruption of Toba volcano in northern Sumatra some 73,000 years ago was the largest explosive eruption of the past two million years, with a Volcanic Explosivity Index of magnitude 8, but its impact on climate has been controversial. In order to resolve this issue, we have analysed pollen from a marine core in the Bay ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:12:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ehunt10/article/10526503</link><title>The ∼73 ka Toba super-eruption and its impact: History of a debate</title><description>Toba volcano in northern Sumatra is located at the intersection of two major tectonic lineaments in one of the most seismically active regions in the world, and its caldera is considered the largest Quaternary caldera on earth. The most recent Toba explosive eruption at ∼73 ka was an order of magnitude larger than that of Tambora in 1815, and has a Volcanic Explosivity Index of 8. The exceptional magnitude of this super-eruption and the widespread distribution of the Younger Toba Tuff (YTT) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:13:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/laharrin/article/9610081</link><title>Brief communication: Dental development timing in captive Pan paniscus with comparisons to Pan troglodytes</title><description>Abstract Dental eruption provides markers of growth and is one component of a chimpanzee's physical development. Dental markers help characterize transitions between life stages, e.g., infant to juvenile. Most of what we know about the timing of development in chimpanzees derives from Pan troglodytes. Much less is known about the sister species, Pan paniscus, with few in captivity and a restricted wild range in central Africa. Here we report on the dental eruption timing for female captive P. paniscus (n = ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:16:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ehunt10/article/11617926</link><title>Impact of an extremely large magnitude volcanic eruption on the global climate and carbon cycle estimated from ensemble Earth System Model simulations</title><description>The response of the global climate-carbon cycle system to an extremely large Northern Hemisphere mid latitude volcanic eruption is investigated using ensemble integrations with the comprehensive Earth System Model MPI-ESM. The model includes dynamical compartments of the atmosphere and ocean and interactive modules of the terrestrial biosphere as well as ocean biogeochemistry. The MPI-ESM was forced with anomalies of aerosol optical depth and effective radius of aerosol particles corresponding to a super eruption of the Yellowstone volcanic system. The model experiment ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:17:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Tdivoux/article/11231482</link><title>An empirical scaling of shear-induced outgassing during magma ascent: Intermittent magma ascent causes effective outgassing</title><description>Outgassing, which changes the distribution of volcanic gases in magmas, is one of the most important processes to determine the eruption styles. Shear deformation of ascending bubbly magmas at the vicinity of the volcanic conduit wall has been considered as an efficient mechanism of outgassing. On the other hand, seismological observations of volcanic eruptions reveal the gas bursting associated with long-period (LP) earthquakes and tremors, suggesting the existence of a large void space in the conduit. However both, the quantitative features ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>