<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:36:37" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:36:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/djmonstermo/article/3334365</link><title>Treatment of acne vulgaris.</title><description>CONTEXT: Management of acne vulgaris by nondermatologists is increasing. Current understanding of the different presentations of acne allows for individualized treatments and improved outcomes. OBJECTIVE: To review the best evidence available for individualized treatment of acne. DATA SOURCES: Search of MEDLINE, EMBASE, and the Cochrane database to search for all English-language articles on acne treatment from 1966 to 2004. STUDY SELECTION: Well-designed randomized controlled trials, meta-analyses, and other systematic reviews are the focus of this article. DATA EXTRACTION: Acne literature is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:38:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Hrandfield/article/12394551</link><title>Acne vulgaris.</title><description>What are the clinical characteristics of acne?A spectrum of lesions may be present, including non-inflammatory open and closed comedones (blackheads and whiteheads, respectively) and inflammatory papules, pustules, nodules, and cysts. Lesions may be present on the face, neck, chest, or back—areas with the greatest density of pilosebaceous units.12 Comedone formation is intrinsic to the diagnosis of acne vulgaris—when not clinically apparent, consider alternative diagnoses. Diseases that mimic acne include rosacea, folliculitis, angiofibromas, perioral dermatitis, and keratosis pilaris.5 13 14 The patient’s ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:39:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/11269809</link><title>Acne vulgaris.</title><description>Acne vulgaris affects over 80% of teenagers, and persists beyond the age of 25 years in 3% of men and 12% of women. Typical lesions of acne include comedones, inflammatory papules, and pustules. Nodules and cysts occur in more severe acne and can cause scarring and psychological distress. METHODS AND OUTCOMES: We conducted a systematic review and aimed to answer the following clinical question: What ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:41:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/11269795</link><title>Treatment of acne scarring.</title><description>Post-acne scarring remains a common entity despite advances in the treatment of acne. This represents limitations in our quality of therapy and a failure of public education. The level of severe scarring remains as much an ongoing challenge to prevent as well as manage. This review will concentrate on the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:42:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/11269766</link><title>Acne vulgaris: pathogenesis, treatment, and needs assessment.</title><description>Acne vulgaris is a common skin condition with substantial cutaneous and psychologic disease burden. Studies suggest that the emotional impact of acne is comparable to that experienced by patients with systemic diseases, like diabetes and epilepsy. In conjunction with the considerable personal burden experienced by patients with acne, acne vulgaris also accounts for substantial societal and health care burden. The pathogenesis and existing treatment strategies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:44:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/beapen/article/12305108</link><title>What is the role of antimicrobial peptides (AMP) in acne vulgaris?</title><description>Acne vulgaris is the most common disorder of the pilosebaceous unit leading to inflamed skin characterized by the formation of comedones, papules, pustules and scarring. There is increasing evidence that the abundance of Propionibacterium acnes (P. acnes) in the inflamed acne lesions triggers inflammation. Therefore, in addition to treatment with retinoids, the use of antimicrobial agents has been established as a treatment option for acne. This indicates that antimicrobial mechanisms to control the growth of P. acnes may have an important ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:46:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/12899099</link><title>Diagnosis and treatment of acne.</title><description>Acne is a chronic inflammatory skin disease that is the most common skin disorder in the United States. Therapy targets the four factors responsible for lesion formation: increased sebum production, hyperkeratinization, colonization by Propionibacterium acnes, and the resultant inflammatory reaction. Treatment goals include scar prevention, reduction of psychological morbidity, and resolution of lesions. Grading acne based on lesion type and severity can help guide treatment. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:47:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/11269751</link><title>Guidance on the diagnosis and clinical management of acne.</title><description>This article discusses the effects of acne (sometimes referred to as acne vulgaris), how to diagnose it confidently and how to distinguish it from rosacea, and the options available for treatment, especially in primary care. We also suggest when referral to dermatology should be considered, and try to anticipate some frequently asked questions. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:47:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maniruzzaman/article/10802015</link><title>Strength of winter leaf redness as an indicator of stress vulnerable individuals in Pistacia lentiscus</title><description>Leaf anthocyanins are believed to afford protection against photoinhibition, yet the dependence of protection on actual anthocyanin concentrations has not been investigated. To that aim, non-invasive optical methods (spectral reflectance and chlorophyll fluorescence) were used to assess the levels of anthocyanins and chlorophylls as well as photosystem II photochemical efficiency in hundreds of leaves from the mastic tree (Pistacia lentiscus), which displays in the field a continuum of leaf tints during winter from fully green to fully red. Contrary to expectations ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:50:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/11027355</link><title>Acne vulgaris.</title><description>Acne is a chronic inflammatory disease of the pilosebaceous unit resulting from androgen-induced increased sebum production, altered keratinisation, inflammation, and bacterial colonisation of hair follicles on the face, neck, chest, and back by Propionibacterium acnes. Although early colonisation with P acnes and family history might have important roles in the disease, exactly what triggers acne and how treatment affects the course of the disease remain ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>