<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7344">pampered chef</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:23:07" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:23:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/humnut/article/10831430</link><title>Long-term impact of a chef on school lunch consumption: findings from a 2-year pilot study in Boston middle schools.</title><description>School cafeterias can play an important role in providing healthy meals. Although schools participating in the National School Lunch Program are required to meet minimum program standards, advocates recommend that innovations be sought to enhance menu dietary quality. This study evaluated the Chef Initiative, a 2-year pilot study in two Boston middle schools, designed to increase the availability and consumption of healthier school foods. Between ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:24:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lucybuykx/article/6369421</link><title>The interactive chef: a task-sensitive assistant</title><description>In this paper, we describe the Interactive Chef (IChef), an intelligent system that attempts to emulate a human cooking assistant. The user navigates through a recipe using voice, while IChef reads aloud each step. IChef is designed to be aware of the present context and exploit this knowledge by answering questions about ingredients or techniques posed by the user in natural spoken language. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:27:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10630756</link><title>Cancer and non-cancer brain and eye effects of chronic low-dose ionizing radiation exposure</title><description>According to a fundamental law of radiobiology ("Law of Bergonie and Tribondeau", 1906), the brain is a paradigm of a highly differentiated organ with low mitotic activity, and is thus radio-resistant to stochastic effects of radiation. This assumption has been challenged by recent evidence discussed in the present review. The brain is among the most critical dose-limiting organs in radio-therapy, mainly due to the development of cognitive dysfunction following white matter disruption, since radio-sensitive oligodendrocyte precursor stem cells have mitotic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:28:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ajaymalik/article/9531407</link><title>Cell biology. Autophagy's top chef.</title><description>http://stke.sciencemag.org/cgi/content/summary/sci;332/6036/1392</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:29:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6518357</link><title>Is it art or science? Chef's competencies for success</title><description>One of the most challenging professions in the hospitality industry, comprised of both scientific mastery and artistic innovation, is the Chef. It is imperative that these positions are occupied by individuals who possess the appropriate set of skills allowing them to perform with equal success in both culinary, as well as managerial competence. Thus, this research sets out to investigate, from “the Chef's” perspective, competencies required for a successful career in the field as well as the level to which these ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:31:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/6865374</link><title>An Individual Business Model in the Making: a Chef’s Quest for Creative Freedom</title><description>This article extends the study of business models by exploring a type rarely considered – the individual business model – and investigates the set of activities, organizing, and strategic resources individuals employ to create and capture value while pursuing their interests and motivations. Insights are drawn from an in-depth longitudinal inductive case study to examine the triggers, mechanisms and changes in the evolving individual business model developed by chef and gastronomic innovator Ferran Adrià. His quest for creative freedom is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:32:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lucybuykx/article/9478509</link><title>su-chef: Adaptive coordination of intelligent home environments</title><description>Traditional recipes are the static products of an empirical, off-line procedure, and contain implicit environmental assumptions, as they are devised based on the exact ingredients and household devices that were available in the environment where they were created. When the parameters of the environment in which a dish is being cooked do not match those of the one in which the corresponding recipe was prepared, frustration is imminent. We present our work on dynamic service composition to facilitate adaptive coordination of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:33:15">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12042385</link><title>Assessing Organ Doses from Paediatric CT Scans&amp;amp;#8212;A Novel Approach for an Epidemiology Study (the EPI-CT Study)</title><description>The increasing worldwide use of paediatric computed tomography (CT) has led to increasing concerns regarding the subsequent effects of exposure to radiation. In response to this concern, the international EPI-CT project was developed to study the risk of cancer in a large multi-country cohort. In radiation epidemiology, accurate estimates of organ-specific doses are essential. In EPI-CT, data collection is split into two time periods&amp;#8212;before and after introduction of the Picture Archiving Communication System (PACS) introduced in the 1990s. Prior to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:36:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kleintoma/article/911185</link><title>Reducing simulation models for scheduling manufacturing facilities</title><description>Within the framework of the application of their industrial management system, companies compile a Master Production Schedule (MPS). However, once the MPS is released, daily events may require it to be brought into question. The use of reduced models within the framework of flow dynamic simulation enables quick decision-making while maximizing the use of resources and minimizing risk. The article shows the advantage of model reduction and how we arrive at it. Afterwards we develop an analysis of the influence of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7344-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7344_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:40:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cucurbituril/article/11450647</link><title>Coumarin-Based Chemosensors for Zinc(II):  Toward the Determination of the Design Algorithm for CHEF-Type and Ratiometric Probes</title><description>The synthesis of a series of coumarin-based chemosensor assemblies for zinc is detailed, using established and novel synthetic pathways. Variations of the nature of the chelating unit (DPA or cyclen), position of the attachment point of the chelating unit (3- or 4-position), and nature of the 7-substituent (?OH, ?OAc, or ?NR2) on the coumarin play a crucial role in whether, and to what extent, a CHEF-type or ratiometric response of the chemosensor is observed. Solvent effects are also discussed. The chemosensors ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>