<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:30:54" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:31:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rouven/article/5457968</link><title>Public papers of the Presidents of the United States, George Bush : 1989-</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:32:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rouven/article/5457905</link><title>Public papers of the Presidents of the United States, William J. Clinton.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:32:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rouven/article/5457985</link><title>Public papers of the Presidents of the United States, George Bush : 1989 (in two books).</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:35:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bcoverson/article/6662161</link><title>Space cooperation : memorandum of understanding between the United States of America and Brazil, signed at Washington December 5, 1996.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:37:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SashaStrother/article/6872206</link><title>The Performance Rights In Sound Recordings Act of 1995 : hearing before the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate, One Hundred Fourth Congress, first session, on S. 227 ... March 9, 1995.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:39:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SashaStrother/article/6872160</link><title>The Performance Rights Act and parity among music delivery platforms : hearing before the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate, One Hundred Eleventh Congress, first session, August 4, 2009.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:40:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nilsma/article/10018866</link><title>Program NetMoment; Simultaneous Calculation of Moment, Source Corner Frequency, and Site Specific t* from Network Recordings</title><description>The purpose of computer program NetMoment (Appendix I) is to utilize fundamental knowledge of earthquake sources, propagation attenuation, and site response in a simultaneous inversion of network data to determine the moment and source corner frequency of earthquakes, and site specific t*. The source parameters are especially difficult to determine for small earthquakes. A fundamental problem in determining the source corner frequencies of small earthquakes is that site response can result in spectral corner frequencies in the range that may be ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:42:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/A_Khalil/article/10783410</link><title>A Critical Review of the State-of-the-Art in Autonomous Land Vehicle Systems and Technology</title><description>This report describes the current state-of-the-art in Autonomous Land Vehicle (ALV) systems and technology. Five functional technology areas are identified and addressed. For each a brief, subjective, preface is first provided which envisions the necessary technology for the deployment of an operational ALV system. Subsequently, a detailed literature review is provided to support and elaborate these views. It is further established how these five technology areas fit together as a functioning whole. The essential conclusion of this report is that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:44:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/shaharshlomi/article/12185131</link><title>Fault tree handbook</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:46:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/robert/article/8407044</link><title>Food safety: Controls can be strengthened to reduce the risk of disease linked to unsafe animal feed : report to the Honorable Richard J. Durbin, United States Senate</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>