<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:55:01" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:55:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cutelilthing831/article/8026059</link><title>Transforming Work: Protestantism and the Piers Plowman Tradition</title><description>The figure of the plowman achieved a certain popularity in mid-sixteenth-century England with the publication of William Langland's medieval poem, Piers Plowman, and in a number of treatises written in imitation of it such as I playne Piers which cannot flatter. This post-Reformation plowman has long been read as an uncomplicated spokesman for an anticlerical Protestantism. This article argues, in contrast, that these plowmen are evidence of a continuing interest in a medieval Catholic symbolic imagination centered on work-as physical labor ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:57:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/realaphex/article/4544563</link><title>A Proof for the Queuing Formula: L= λ W</title><description>In a queuing process, let 1/λ be the mean time between the arrivals of two consecutive units, L be the mean number of units in the system, and W be the mean time spent by a unit in the system. It is shown that, if the three means are finite and the corresponding stochastic processes strictly stationary, and, if the arrival process is metrically transitive with nonzero mean, then L=λ W. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:58:30">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/1319952</link><title>Little Theories</title><description>In the "little theories" version of the axiomatic method, different portions of mathematics are developed in various different formal axiomatic theories. Axiomatic theories may be related by inclusion or by theory interpretation. We argue that the little theories approach is a desirable way to formalize mathematics, and we describe how imps, an Interactive Mathematical Proof System, supports it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:00:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/terning/article/7285448</link><title>The Bestest Little Higgs</title><description>While little Higgs models provide an interesting way to address the hierarchy problem, concrete models in the literature typically face two major obstacles. First, the mechanism for generating a Higgs quartic coupling often leads to large violations of custodial symmetry. Second, there is a tension between precision electroweak observables in the gauge sector and fine-tuning in the top sector. In this work, we present a new little Higgs model which solves both of these problems. The model is based on an SO(6)xSO(6)/SO(6) coset space which has custodial symmetry ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:02:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Zephyrus/article/7537188</link><title>Cancer models, genomic instability and somatic cellular Darwinian evolution.</title><description>The biology of cancer is critically reviewed and evidence adduced that its development can be modelled as a somatic cellular Darwinian evolutionary process. The evidence for involvement of genomic instability (GI) is also reviewed. A variety of quasi-mechanistic models of carcinogenesis are reviewed, all based on this somatic Darwinian evolutionary hypothesis; in particular, the multi-stage model of Armitage and Doll (Br. J. Cancer 1954:8;1-12), the two-mutation model of Moolgavkar, Venzon, and Knudson (MVK) (Math. Biosci. 1979:47;55-77), the generalized MVK model of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:03:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/terning/article/770972</link><title>Little M-theory</title><description>Using the language of theory space, i.e. moose models, we develop a unified framework for studying composite Higgs models at the LHC. This framework--denoted little M-theory--is conveniently described by a theoretically consistent three-site moose diagram which implements minimal flavor and isospin violation. By taking different limits of the couplings, one can interpolate between simple group-like and minimal moose-like models with and without T-parity. In this way, little M-theory reveals a large model space for composite Higgs theories. We argue that this framework is suitable as a starting point for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:06:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/terning/article/3749783</link><title>A Quirky Little Higgs Model</title><description>We consider an extra dimensional model where the quadratically divergent top loop contribution to the Higgs mass is cancelled by an uncolored heavy "top quirk" charged under a different SU(3) gauge group. The cancellation is enforced by bulk gauge symmetries. Thus we have an unusual type of little Higgs model which has some quirky signatures. The top partner in this model could be identified at the Large Hadron Collider due to macroscopic strings that connect quirk and anti-quirks. The model can undergo radiative electroweak symmetry breaking and is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:06:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/terning/article/4024021</link><title>SUSY without the Little Hierarchy</title><description>We propose a simple gauge extension of the minimal supersymmetric standard model (MSSM), where the fine tuning in the Higgs mass parameters is highly reduced. The Higgs boson is insensitive to high energies because of supersymmetry and also because it is a pseudo-Goldstone boson of a global symmetry (referred to as double protection or super-little Higgs mechanism). A large shift in the Higgs quartic self coupling is obtained via a non-decoupling D-term coming from an extra gauge group, resulting in a Higgs that can be as heavy as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:07:58">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3615247</link><title>The Role of Regret in Informed Consent</title><description>Abstract  Informed consent to medical procedures tends to be construed in terms of principle-based ethics and one or other form of expected utility theory. These constructions leave problems created by imperfect communication; subjective distress and other emotions; imperfect knowledge and incomplete understanding; complexity, and previous experience or the lack of it. There is evidence that people giving consent to therapy or to research participation act intuitively and assess consequences holistically, being influenced more by the magnitude of outcomes than their probability. People ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:08:48">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4686322</link><title>Heterogeneity of variation of relative risk by age at exposure in the Japanese atomic bomb survivors</title><description>Abstract  General reductions in cancer relative risk with increasing age at exposure are observed in the Japanese atomic bomb survivors and in other groups. However, there has been little evidence of heterogeneity in such trends by cancer type within the Japanese cohort, nor for cancer-type variations in other factors (sex, attained age) that modify relative risk. A recent report on the Japanese atomic bomb survivors published by Preston et al. in 2007 suggests that solid cancer relative risk exhibits a U-shaped relationship ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>