<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:09:59" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:10:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wamserma/article/8247785</link><title>Hardware Trojans in Wireless Cryptographic ICs</title><description>Editor's note:This article studies the problem of hardware Trojans in wireless cryptographic ICs. The objective is to design Trojans to leak secret information through the wireless channel. The authors investigate challenges related to detection for such Trojans and propose using statistical analysis of the side-channel signals to help detect them.—Mohammad Tehranipoor, University of Connecticut ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:11:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jannon/article/2842271</link><title>Our Time Base Is Real</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:12:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wamserma/article/8247767</link><title>A Survey of Hardware Trojan Taxonomy and Detection</title><description>Editor's note:Today's integrated circuits are vulnerable to hardware Trojans, which are malicious alterations to the circuit, either during design or fabrication. This article presents a classification of hardware Trojans and a survey of published techniques for Trojan detection.—Krish Chakrabarty, Editor in Chief ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:13:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Torsten_Holmer/article/2352830</link><title>Cognition and the Theory of Learning by Doing</title><description>The standard model of utility maximization assumes that individuals make complete contingent plans before making a decision. This paper shows that when the environment is sufficiently complex the optimal rule entails learning by doing rather than contingent planning. An implication of this result is that spill-overs from learning by doing are less than perfect, a hypothesis central to many models of learning by doing, such as Rosen (1972). It is shown that one can derive learning curves that can be fitted ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:14:26">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3584837</link><title>The dynamics of inclined Neptune Trojans</title><description>Abstract  We investigated the stable area for fictive Trojan asteroids around Neptune’s Lagrangean equilibrium points with respect to their semimajor axis and inclination. To get a first impression of the stability region we derived a symplectic mapping for the circular and the elliptic planar restricted three body problem. The dynamical model for the numerical integrations was the outer Solar system with the Sun and the planets Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus and Neptune. To understand the dynamics of the region around L 4 and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6854269</link><title>Where are the Uranus Trojans?</title><description>Abstract  The area of stable motion for fictitious Trojan asteroids around Uranus’ equilateral equilibrium points is investigated with respect to the inclination of the asteroid’s orbit to determine the size of the regions and their shape. For this task we used the results of extensive numerical integrations of orbits for a grid of initial conditions around the points L 4 and L 5, and analyzed the stability of the individual orbits. Our basic dynamical model was the Outer Solar System (Jupiter, Saturn, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:18:01">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7177039</link><title>A Peculiar Family of Jupiter Trojans: the Eurybates</title><description>The Eurybates family is a compact core inside the Menelaus clan, located in the L 4 swarm of Jupiter Trojans. Fornasier et al. (2007) found that this family exhibits a peculiar abundance of spectrally flat objects, similar to Chiron-like Centaurs and C-type main belt asteroids. On the basis of the visible spectra available in literature, Eurybates family’s members seemed to be good candidates for having on their surfaces water/water ice or aqueous altered materials. To improve our knowledge of the surface ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:19:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4243634</link><title>GOGS: USC GamePipe Online Game Server</title><description>Massively multiplayer online games (MMO) are at the height of interest and growing in popularity in the commercial video game market. New development studios are vying for the position of top MMO, both in the number of users and market value. Recently, interest in online games has entered the realm of educational practitioners and researchers. It was as researchers, as well as game developers and designers in mind, that the USC GamePipe Laboratory has developed its initial version of the academic, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:21:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Jiwei/article/7938400</link><title>The Size Distribution of the Neptune Trojans and the Missing Intermediate Sized Planetesimals</title><description>We present an ultra-deep survey for Neptune Trojans using the Subaru 8.2-m and Magellan 6.5-m telescopes. The survey reached a 50% detection efficiency in the R-band at 25.7 magnitudes and covered 49 square degrees of sky. This depth corresponds to Neptune Trojans that are about 16 km in radius (assuming an albedo of 0.05). A paucity of smaller Neptune Trojans (radii &lt; 45 km) compared to larger ones was found. The brightest Neptune Trojans appear to follow a steep power-law slope (q = 5+-1) similar to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:22:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9769546</link><title>Trojans’ Odyssey: Unveiling the early history of the Solar System</title><description>In our present understanding of the Solar System, small bodies (asteroids, Jupiter Trojans, comets and TNOs) are the most direct remnants of the original building blocks that formed the planets. Jupiter Trojan and Hilda asteroids are small primitive bodies located beyond the ‘snow line’, around respectively the L 4 and L 5 Lagrange points of Jupiter at ∼5.2 AU (Trojans) and in the 2:3 mean-motion resonance with Jupiter near 3.9 AU (Hildas). They are at the crux of several outstanding and ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>