<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:23:49" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:23:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/JaGutta/article/6074795</link><title>Kobe Bryant</title><description>Highlights signature moves and greatest moments from Kobe Bryant's career. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:25:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4406145</link><title>John Bryant takes a closer look at some of this month's Original Articles</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:26:20">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4267224</link><title>John Bryant takes a closer look at some of this month's Original Articles</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:27:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4177714</link><title>John Bryant takes a closer look at some of this month's Original Articles</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:28:10">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6200784</link><title>John Bryant takes a closer look at some of this month's Original Articles</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:28:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cordon85/article/8270022</link><title>Water-proton-spin-lattice-relaxation dispersion of paramagnetic protein solutions.</title><description>The paramagnetic contributions to water-proton-spin-lattice relaxation rate constants in protein systems spin-labeled with nitroxide radicals were re-examined. As noted by others, the strength of the dipolar coupling between water protons and the protein-bound nitroxide radical often appears to be larger than physically reasonable when the relaxation is assumed to be controlled by 3-dimensional diffusive processes in the vicinity of the spin label. We examine the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:29:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kroncb00/article/8003043</link><title>Water and backbone dynamics in a hydrated protein.</title><description>Rotational immobilization of proteins permits characterization of the internal peptide and water molecule dynamics by magnetic relaxation dispersion spectroscopy. Using different experimental approaches, we have extended measurements of the magnetic field dependence of the proton-spin-lattice-relaxation rate by one decade from 0.01 to 300 MHz for (1)H and showed that the underlying dynamics driving the protein (1)H spin-lattice relaxation is preserved over 4.5 decades in frequency. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:31:41">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8936717</link><title>The Routledge Companion to Creativity Edited by T. Rickards, M.A. Runco and S. Moger</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:32:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/JaGutta/article/6074789</link><title>Kobe Bryant</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:33:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Garth_9145/article/4304984</link><title>Autoinhibition by an internal nuclear localization signal revealed by the crystal structure of mammalian importin alpha.</title><description>Importin alpha is the nuclear import receptor that recognizes classical monopartite and bipartite nuclear localization signals (NLSs). The structure of mouse importin alpha has been determined at 2.5 A resolution. The structure shows a large C-terminal domain containing armadillo repeats, and a less structured N-terminal importin beta-binding domain containing an internal NLS bound to the NLS-binding site. The structure explains the regulatory switch between the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>