<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:35:05" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:35:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5488732</link><title>Light therapy for seasonal and nonseasonal depression: efficacy, protocol, safety, and side effects.</title><description>Bright light therapy for seasonal affective disorder (SAD) has been investigated and applied for over 20 years. Physicians and clinicians are increasingly confident that bright light therapy is a potent, specifically active, nonpharmaceutical treatment modality. Indeed, the domain of light treatment is moving beyond SAD, to nonseasonal depression (unipolar and bipolar), seasonal flare-ups of bulimia nervosa, circadian sleep phase disorders, and more. Light therapy is simple to deliver to outpatients and inpatients alike, although the optimum dosing of light and treatment ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:36:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5295599</link><title>Light therapy for non-seasonal depression.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Efficacy of light therapy for non-seasonal depression has been studied without any consensus on its efficacy. OBJECTIVES: To evaluate clinical effects of bright light therapy in comparison to the inactive placebo treatment for non-seasonal depression. SEARCH STRATEGY: We searched the Depression Anxiety &amp; Neurosis Controlled Trials register (CCDANCTR January 2003), comprising the results of searches of Cochrane Central Register of Controlled Trials (CENTRAL), MEDLINE (1966 -), EMBASE (1980 -), CINAHL (1982 -), LILACS (1982 -), National Research Register, PsycINFO/PsycLIT (1974 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:38:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5295677</link><title>Efficacy of light therapy in nonseasonal depression: a systematic review.</title><description>BACKGROUND: The efficacy of bright light therapy is well established for winter depression but its status in depression without seasonal pattern is unclear. METHODS: We systematically evaluated available data on the efficacy of light therapy in nonseasonal depression. RESULTS: We identified 62 reports among which 15 met our predefined selection criteria. The available data show evidence for the efficacy of light therapy as an adjuvant treatment to antidepressants. Trials that evaluated light therapy alone (without antidepressants) in nonseasonal depression yielded inconsistent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:39:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/7942867</link><title>Early combination antibiotic therapy yields improved survival compared with monotherapy in septic shock: a propensity-matched analysis.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Septic shock represents the major cause of infection-associated mortality in the intensive care unit. The possibility that combination antibiotic therapy of bacterial septic shock improves outcome is controversial. Current guidelines do not recommend combination therapy except for the express purpose of broadening coverage when resistant pathogens are a concern. OBJECTIVE: To evaluate the therapeutic benefit of early combination therapy comprising at least two antibiotics of different mechanisms with in vitro activity for the isolated pathogen in patients with bacterial septic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:42:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/simonjudge/article/5341325</link><title>Communicative Competence for Individuals Who Use AAC: From Research to Effective Practice (Augmentative and Alternative Communication Series)</title><description>Pennsylvania State Univ., Univ. Park. Text presents in-depth research andtheory and covers four skill areas important to the development ofcommunicative competence. Discusses linguistic, operational, social, andstrategic competence. Also covers intervention strategies for those who useAAC. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:43:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Kyaita/article/6996026</link><title>Causes of Death in HIV-1—Infected Patients Treated with Antiretroviral Therapy, 1996–2006: Collaborative Analysis of 13 HIV Cohort Studies</title><description>Background. We examined specific causes of mortality in human immunodeficiency virus type 1 (HIV-1)—infected patients who initiated antiretroviral therapy (ART) in Europe and North America from 1996 through 2006, and we quantified associations of prognostic factors with cause-specific mortality.Methods. We retrospectively classified all deaths among 39,272 patients enrolled in 13 HIV-1 cohorts (154,667 person years of follow-up) into the categories specified in the Cause of Death (CoDe) project protocol.Results. In 1597 (85%) of 1876 deaths, a definitive cause of death could ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:44:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ajdee/article/12104167</link><title>Strengthening and optimal movements for painful shoulders (STOMPS) in chronic spinal cord injury: a randomized controlled trial.</title><description>Shoulder pain is a common problem after spinal cord injury (SCI), with negative effects on daily activities and quality of life (QOL). The purpose of this study was to determine the effect of an exercise program and instruction to optimize performance of upper-extremity tasks on shoulder pain in people with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:46:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5080916</link><title>An Open Trial of Morning Light Therapy for Treatment of Antepartum Depression</title><description>OBJECTIVE: About 5% of pregnant women meet criteria for major depression. No pharmacotherapy is specifically approved for antepartum depression; novel treatment approaches may be welcome. The authors explored the use of morning bright light therapy for antepartum depression. METHOD: An open trial of bright light therapy in an A-B-A design was conducted for 3-5 weeks in 16 pregnant patients with major depression. The Hamilton Depression Rating Scale, Seasonal Affective Disorders Version, was administered to assess changes in mood. A follow-up questionnaire ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:48:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5295698</link><title>The efficacy of light therapy in the treatment of mood disorders: a review and meta-analysis of the evidence.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: The purpose of this study was to assess the evidence base for the efficacy of light therapy in treating mood disorders. METHOD: The authors systematically searched PubMed (January 1975 to July 2003) to identify randomized, controlled trials of light therapy for mood disorders that fulfilled predefined criteria. These articles were abstracted, and data were synthesized by disease and intervention category. RESULTS: Only 13% of the studies met the inclusion criteria. Meta-analyses revealed that a significant reduction in depression symptom severity ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:49:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cwtjoa/article/5081028</link><title>Randomized clinical trial of bright light therapy for antepartum depression: preliminary findings.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Bright light therapy was shown to be a promising treatment for depression during pregnancy in a recent open-label study. In an extension of this work, we report findings from a double-blind placebo-controlled pilot study. METHOD: Ten pregnant women with DSM-IV major depressive disorder were randomly assigned from April 2000 to January 2002 to a 5-week clinical trial with either a 7000 lux (active) or 500 lux (placebo) light box. At the end of the randomized controlled trial, subjects had the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>