<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:53:27" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:53:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SFIRES/article/721828</link><title>Virtue ethics and healthcare accreditation: the end of whistleblowing? : An article from: Global Virtue Ethics Review</title><description>This digital document is an article from Global Virtue Ethics Review, published by Southern Public Administration Education Foundation, Inc. on July 1, 2001. The length of the article is 7310 words. The page length shown above is based on a typical 300-word page. The article is delivered in HTML format and is available in your Amazon.com Digital Locker immediately after purchase. You can view it with any web browser.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Citation Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Virtue ethics and healthcare accreditation: the end of whistleblowing?&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author:&lt;/strong&gt; Peter L. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:54:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ghpirie/article/11767217</link><title>Elite Exoticism: Sea-rail Cruise Tourism to South Africa, 1926–1939</title><description>Abstract South Africa's railway and harbours operator (SAR&amp;H) was the arch promoter of overseas tourism to South Africa for thirty years after Union in 1910. To its package tours for independent inbound tourists, the SAR&amp;H added exclusive port-to-port rail trips across South Africa by partnering with overseas cruise ship operators. Whereas the European market was a mainstay, the more distant North American market only became accessible in relation to lengthy round-the-world cruises. Between 1926 and 1939 approximately fifty long-distance luxury trains ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:56:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davideiacono/article/7459374</link><title>Sick-sad dreams: Burne-Jones and Pre-Raphaelite Medievalism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:58:34">http://www.citeulike.org/article/778050</link><title>Warning when using a Foley catheter for post-nasal space packing fill the balloon with water rather than saline</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:01:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4740704</link><title>Re: Childhood epistaxis is unlikely to be caused by nose picking</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:02:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6649335</link><title>DRAWING ATTENTION: SELECTED WORKS ON PAPER FROM RENAISSANCE TO MODERNISM BY KATHARINE A LOCHNAN</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:03:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8379942</link><title>INTO THE FRAME: THE FOUR LOVES OF FORD MADOX BROWN BY ANGELA THIRLWELL, FREDERIC, LORD LEIGHTON: 18301896 PAINTER AND SCULPTOR OF THE VICTORIAN AGE BY CHRISTOPHER NEWALL ET AL. AND JAMES TISSOT: THE LIFE OF CHRIST BY JUDITH DOLKART (ED.)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:05:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ly3/article/411355</link><title>How language relates to belief, desire, and emotion understanding</title><description>Two experiments examined syntax and semantics as correlates of theory-of-mind (ToM). In Experiment 1 children’s language was examined at 3 years of age in relation to ToM at 3, 3.5, 4, and 5.5 years. Semantics predicted unique variance in later belief understanding but not desire understanding. Syntax did not explain unique variance in belief or desire. In Experiment 2 two measures of syntax and a measure of semantics were used with 65 3-5-year-olds. The syntax measures tested children’s understanding of word ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:06:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3044247</link><title>THE AGE OF ENCHANTMENT: BEARDSLEY, DULAC AND THEIR CONTEMPORARIES BY RODNEY ENGEN AND FACING THE LATE VICTORIANS: PORTRAITS OF WRITERS AND ARTISTS FROM THE MARK SAMUELS LASNER COLLECTION BY MARGARET D STETZ</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:07:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2751377</link><title>Pictures of Millais</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>