<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7409">rihanna chris brown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:08:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:08:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cp/article/3615218</link><title>The inhibition of mitochondrial cytochrome oxidase by the gases carbon monoxide, nitric oxide, hydrogen cyanide and hydrogen sulfide: chemical mechanism and physiological significance</title><description>Abstract  The four gases, nitric oxide (NO), carbon monoxide (CO), hydrogen sulfide (H2S) and hydrogen cyanide (HCN) all readily inhibit oxygen consumption by mitochondrial cytochrome oxidase. This inhibition is responsible for much of their toxicity when they are applied externally to the body. However, recently these gases have all been implicated, to greater or lesser extents, in normal cellular signalling events. In this review we analyse the chemistry of this inhibition, comparing and contrasting mechanism and discussing physiological consequences. The inhibition by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:09:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/japepper/article/6658450</link><title>Orbital Migration and the Brown Dwarf Desert</title><description>The orbital elements of extreme mass ratio binaries will be modified by interactions with surrounding circumstellar disks. For brown dwarf companions to Solar-type stars the resulting orbital migration is sufficient to drive short period systems to merger, creating a brown dwarf desert at small separations. We highlight the similarities and the differences between the migration of brown dwarfs and massive extrasolar planets, and discuss how observations can test a migration model for the brown dwarf desert. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:10:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maper102/article/1934328</link><title>The Da Vinci Code</title><description>With &lt;I&gt;The Da Vinci Code,&lt;/I&gt; Dan Brown masterfully concocts an intelligent and lucid thriller that marries the gusto of an international murder mystery with a collection of fascinating esoteria culled from 2,000 years of Western history. &lt;p&gt; A murder in the silent after-hour halls of the Louvre museum reveals a sinister plot to uncover a secret that has been protected by a clandestine society since the days of Christ. The victim is a high-ranking agent of this ancient society who, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:11:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/seudonimo_falso/article/788828</link><title>Cloud detection for CHRIS/Proba hyperspectral images</title><description>(published online Nov. 1, 2005) Accurate and automatic detection of clouds in satellite scenes is a key issue for a wide range of remote sensing applications. With no accurate cloud masking, undetected clouds are one of the most significant source of error in both sea and land cover biophysical parameter retrieval. Sensors with spectral channels beyond 1 um have demonstrated good capabilities to perform cloud masking. This spectral range can not be exploited by recently developed hyperspectral sensors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:13:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/seudonimo_falso/article/788826</link><title>Compact high-resolution imaging spectrometer (CHRIS) design and performance</title><description>This paper describes a Compact High Resolution Imaging Spectrometer (CHRIS) developed at Sira. The imaging spectrometer is flying on PROBA, a small agile satellite, which was launch in 2001. This paper provides details of the instrument design and performance. The main purpose of the instrument is to provide images of land areas, particularly the measurement of the Bi-directional Reflectance Distribution Function (BRDF) properties for selected targets on the Earth surface using multi-angle observations. The platform provides pointing in both ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:13:50">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2835324</link><title>Humanitarian Intervention: Ideas in Action By Thomas G. Weiss</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:14:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2115477</link><title>European International Relations and the 800-Pound Gorilla</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:15:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1245297</link><title>Situating Critical Realism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:16:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1012654</link><title>Some thoughts about improvising</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7409-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7409_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:17:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3615522</link><title>Sex differences in the career development of urban African American adolescents</title><description>Without Abstract ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>