<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:44:51" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:44:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6477932</link><title>The world of wound care loses an inspirational leader! A special editorial in memory of Donalyn Hyland, RN (19512009)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:46:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6828200</link><title>2010 and the International Wound Journal</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:47:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6828199</link><title>The emergence of a clinical specialty in wound care</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:48:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9317223</link><title>Congratulations to Cardiff University for its 20 Years of Excellence in Wound Care Research and Practice</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:49:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/derchao/article/3392508</link><title>The Red Queen in Organizational Evolution</title><description>We propose that competitive success and failure evolve through an ecology of organizational learning. An organization facing competition is likely to engage in a search for ways to improve performance. When successful, this search results in learning that is likely to increase the organization's competitive strength, which in turn triggers learning in its rivals-consequently making them stronger competitors and so again triggering learning in the first organization. We elaborate the conditions under which this self-reinforcing process, known in evolutionary theory as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:49:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hectorianus1977/article/6938294</link><title>Chaotic Red Queen coevolution in three-species food chains.</title><description>Coevolution between two antagonistic species follows the so-called 'Red Queen dynamics' when reciprocal selection results in an endless series of adaptation by one species and counteradaptation by the other. Red Queen dynamics are 'genetically driven' when selective sweeps involving new beneficial mutations result in perpetual oscillations of the coevolving traits on the slow evolutionary time scale. Mathematical models have shown that a prey and a predator can coevolve along a genetically driven Red Queen cycle. We found that embedding the prey-predator ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:50:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/macaulus/article/264281</link><title>Volunteering as Red Queen Mechanism for Cooperation in Public Goods Games</title><description>The evolution of cooperation among nonrelated individuals is one of the fundamental problems in biology and social sciences. Reciprocal altruism fails to provide a solution if interactions are not repeated often enough or groups are too large. Punishment and reward can be very effective but require that defectors can be traced and identified. Here we present a simple but effective mechanism operating under full anonymity. Optional participation can foil exploiters and overcome the social dilemma. In voluntary public goods interactions, cooperators ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:51:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/1877385</link><title>Where Do We Fall When We Fall in Love?</title><description>Where do we fall when we fall in love? Evolutionary psychologists have a ready description: they tell us that we fall into a pool of natural amphetamines in our brains. These hormonal processes make us feel exhilarated, speeded up. For psychoanalysts, however, the question is much more difficult to answer. &lt;P&gt;What are the differences between narcissistic love and affectionate love? What are the contrasts between sexual instinctual relations and ego relations? Are all human beings ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:53:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/digitalish/article/29029</link><title>`Du hast jar keene Ahnung': African American English dubbed into German</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:54:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Marvin/article/1417342</link><title>Sociolinguistic Horizons: Language and Sexuality</title><description>In this essay, I examine the current state of research on the connections between language and sexuality and argue that the time has arrived for such research to adopt a more vigorous use of the scientific method, which will allow for testing the predictions made by the various theoretical interventions that have been proposed since the 1990s. I begin by outlining the major theoretical debate within the field, namely, the question of the place of social identity within a theory of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>