<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:37:22" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:37:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tulaydemir/article/549822</link><title>The third manifesto</title><description>We present a manifesto for the future direction of data and database management systems. The manifesto con- sists of a series of prescriptions, proscriptions, and "very strong suggestions." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:38:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/1286080</link><title>Solitons: Differential Equations, Symmetries and Infinite Dimensional Algebras</title><description>This book investigates the high degree of symmetry that lies hidden in integrable systems. To that end, differential equations arising from classical mechanics, such as the KdV equation and the KP equations, are used here by the authors to introduce the notion of an infinite dimensional transformation group acting on spaces of integrable systems. Chapters discuss the work of M. Sato on the algebraic structure of completely integrable systems, together with developments of these ideas in the work of M. Kashiwara. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:38:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bah-la/article/3955253</link><title>SQL and Relational Theory: How to Write Accurate SQL Code</title><description>Understanding SQL's underlying theory is the best way to guarantee that your SQL code is correct and your database schema is robust and maintainable. On the other hand, if you're not well versed in the theory, you can fall into several traps. In _SQL and Relational Theory_, author C.J. Date demonstrates how you can apply relational theory directly to your use of SQL. With numerous examples and clear explanations of the reasoning behind them, you'll learn how to deal with common SQL dilemmas, such as: * ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:39:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ansobol/article/710780</link><title>On obtaining classical mechanics from quantum mechanics</title><description>Constructing a classical mechanical system associated with a given quantum mechanical one, entails construction of a classical phase space and a corresponding Hamiltonian function from the available quantum structures and a notion of coarser observations. The Hilbert space of any quantum mechanical system naturally has the structure of an infinite dimensional symplectic manifold (`quantum phase space'). There is also a systematic, quotienting procedure which imparts a bundle structure to the quantum phase space and extracts a classical phase space as the base space. This works straight forwardly when the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:40:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hkimura/article/4533399</link><title>An Introduction to Database Systems</title><description>From the Publisher: For over 25 years, C. J. Date's An Introduction to Database Systems has been the authoritative resource for readers interested in gaining insight into and understanding of the principles of database systems. This revision continues to provide a solid grounding in the foundations of database technology and to provide some ideas as to how the field is likely to develop in the future.. "Readers of this book will gain a strong working knowledge of the overall structure, concepts, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:42:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/robby/article/236573</link><title>Database in Depth: Relational Theory for Practitioners</title><description>This book sheds light on the principles behind the relational model, which is fundamental to all database-backed applications--and, consequently, most of the work that goes on in the computing world today. &lt;i&gt;Database in Depth: The Relational Model for Practitioners&lt;/i&gt; goes beyond the hype and gets to the heart of how relational databases actually work.&lt;p&gt;Ideal for experienced database developers and designers, this concise guide gives you a clear view of the technology--a view that's not influenced by any vendor or product. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:44:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tjessel/article/5761055</link><title>Prepublication data sharing</title><description>Rapid release of prepublication data has served the field of genomics well. Attendees at a workshop in Toronto recommend extending the practice to other biological data sets ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:46:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eabait/article/5139205</link><title>What Not How: The Business Rules Approach to Application Development</title><description>"What I think Date has done is nothing less than to lay out the foundational concepts for the next generation of business logic servers based on predicate logic. Such a breakthrough should revolutionize application development in our industry -- and take business rules to their fullest expression." --Ronald G. Ross, Principal, Business Rule Solutions, LLC Executive Editor, DataToKnowledge Newsletter The way we build computer applications is about to change dramatically, thanks to a new development technology known as business rules. The key idea behind the technology is that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:47:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/irenas/article/139102</link><title>An Introduction to Database Systems (Introduction to Database Systems, 7th ed)</title><description>The newest edition of the classic &lt;I&gt;An Introduction to Database Systems&lt;/I&gt; incorporates the latest developments in relational databases, including semantic modeling, decision support, and temporal modeling. There's better information on distributed databases, security, and the mathematics of relational databases too. With the same strong coverage of fundamental theory that made its predecessors stand out, this book ranks as the definitive textbook for those studying database systems.&lt;p&gt; This is an extraordinarily academic book. In his preface, C.J. Date goes so far as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:48:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scis0000001/article/887094</link><title>Infinite iterated function systems</title><description>: We examine iterated function systems consisting of a countably infinite number of contracting mappings (IIFS). We state results analogous to the well-known case of finitely many mappings (IFS). Moreover, we show that IIFS can be approximated by appropriately chosen IFS both in terms of Hausdorff distance and of Hausdorff dimension. Comparing the descriptive power of IFS and IIFS as mechanisms defining closed and bounded sets, we show that IIFS are strictly more powerful than IFS. On the... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>