<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7421">story magic flute</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:42:32" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:42:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lshao/article/10216062</link><title>Recent Results from the MAGIC Telescopes</title><description>MAGIC (Major Atmospheric Gamma-ray Imaging Cherenkov Telescope) is a system of two 17 meters Cherenkov telescopes, sensitive to very high energy (VHE; $&gt; 10^11$ eV) gamma radiation above an energy threshold of 50 GeV. The first telescope was built in 2004 and operated for five years in stand-alone mode. A second MAGIC telescope (MAGIC-II), at a distance of 85 meters from the first one, started taking data in July 2009. Together they integrate the MAGIC stereoscopic system. Stereoscopic observations have improved the MAGIC sensitivity and its performance in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:43:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/klepser/article/2951991</link><title>VHE Gamma-Ray Observation of the Crab Nebula and its Pulsar with the MAGIC telescope</title><description>We report about very high energy (VHE) gamma-ray observations of the Crab Nebula with the MAGIC telescope. The gamma-ray flux from the nebula was measured between 60 GeV and 9 TeV. The energy spectrum can be described with a curved power law dF/dE=f0 (E/300 GeV)^(a+b*log10(E/300 GeV)) with a flux normalization f0 of(6.0+-0.2)*10^-10 1/(cm^2 s TeV), a=-2.31+-0.06 and b=-0.26+-0.07. The position of the IC-peak is determined at (77+-47) GeV. Within the observation time and the experimental resolution of the telescope, the gamma-ray emission is steady and pointlike. The emission's ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:44:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hypotyposis/article/4154363</link><title>The Meanings of Magic</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:45:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bbaugh/article/9835675</link><title>Mapping the extended TeV source HESS J1857+026 down to Fermi-LAT energies with the MAGIC telescopes</title><description>HESS J1857+026 is an extended TeV gamma-ray source discovered by H.E.S.S. very close to the Galactic plane. Located in the vicinity of the pulsar PSR J1856+0245, the source represents a pulsar wind nebula (PWN) candidate. In Fermi-LAT data, 7 photons above 100GeV were associated to it as VHE J1857+0252 by Neronov and Semikoz (2010), while in the previous MeV-GeV catalogs no associated source was reported yet. MAGIC was upgraded to a stereoscopic Cherenkov telescope system in 2009, which substantially improved its performance with respect to extended objects. We ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:45:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bbaugh/article/9923061</link><title>Measurement of the cosmic electron plus positron spectrum with the MAGIC telescopes</title><description>Cosmic electrons with energies in the TeV range lose their energy rapidly through synchrotron radiation and inverse Compton processes, resulting in a relatively short lifetime (~ 10^5 years). They are only visible from comparatively nearby sources (&lt;1 kpc). Unexpected features in their spectrum at a few hundreds GeV, as measured by several experiments (ATIC, Fermi and H.E.S.S. among others), might be caused by local sources such as pulsars or by dark matter annihilation/decay. In order to investigate these possibilities, new measurements in the TeV energy region are needed. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:47:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rlineros/article/9846326</link><title>Segue 1: the best dark matter candidate dwarf galaxy surveyed by MAGIC</title><description>Despite the interest in Dark Matter (DM) searches is currently more focused on underground experiments, a signature of DM annihilation/decay in gamma-rays from space would constitute a smoking gun for its identification. In this contribution, we start with a brief review of the efforts of the ground-based MAGIC Cherenkov telescopes system to detect DM signatures from dwarf satellite galaxies orbiting the Milky Way halo. We then present the recent survey of Segue 1, considered by many as possibly the most DM dominated satellite galaxy known in our galaxy. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:48:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jannon/article/6600796</link><title>Sound and Motion in Goethe's "Magic Flute"</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:49:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/giacomo/article/8526315</link><title>A Virtually Real Flute</title><description>Since the first keyboard-controlled digital synthesizers became available, several new synthesis interfaces have been developed (e.g., Mathews 1991a, 1991b; Cook 1992; De Laubier 1998). As most of these digital instruments differ considerably from traditional instruments, musicians must learn new techniques to play them (Kronland-Martinet, Voinier, and Guillemain 1997). Here, we propose overcoming this difficulty by designing a digital flute using a traditional instrument form factor to control a synthesis model. The digital flute was assumed to extend the technical scope of the traditional flute, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:50:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bbaugh/article/9971548</link><title>Exploring the very high energy gamma-ray emission (E &gt; 100 GeV) of the hard spectrum Fermi sources 1FGL J2001.1+4351 and B3-2247+381 with MAGIC</title><description>MAGIC, a stereoscopic cherenkov telescope array, sensitive to gamma-rays between 50 GeV and several tens of TeV, is ideally suited to observe promising Fermi LAT sources with a hard γ-ray spectrum. Here we discuss the discovery of very high energy gamma-ray (VHE, E &gt; 100 GeV) emission from the Fermi LAT sources 1FGL J2001.1+4351 and B3-2247+381 with MAGIC. 1FGL J2001.1+4351, recently identified as MG4 J200112+4352 (Bassani et al. 2010), is most likely a high peaked BL Lacertae object. The red shift of this source is still unknown, though ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7421-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7421_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:52:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bbaugh/article/9905018</link><title>MAGIC measurement of the Crab Nebula spectrum over three decades in energy</title><description>The Crab Pulsar Wind Nebula is the best studied source of $γ$-ray astrophysics. The contribution of the various soft radiation fields to the Inverse Compton component of its high energy emission, the strenght of the internal magnetic field and the maximum energies reached by primary electrons are however still matter of study. The MAGIC stereoscopic system recorded almost 50 hours of Crab Nebula data in the last two years, between October 2009 and April 2011. Analysis of this data sample using the latest improvements in the MAGIC stereo ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>