<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:08:26" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:08:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ggolosov/article/9588355</link><title>New Russian political parties and transition to democracy : the case of Western Siberia</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:09:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ggolosov/article/9588357</link><title>Regional bases of party politics : a measure and its implications for the study of party system consolidation in new democracies.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:11:36">http://www.citeulike.org/group/15400/article/11855718</link><title>Speaking for Europe: languages in the European Union</title><description>The EU promotes the linguistic and cultural diversity of its peoples by supporting the teaching and learning of their languages. The EU's goal is to enable citizens to be fluent in two languages in addition to their native language. The EU institutions work with 23 official languages to ensure that all EU citizens have equal access to the policies and legislation of the European Union. This booklet looks turn at the different languages spoken in the EU, the many ways in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:13:51">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8458294</link><title>Susan B. Whitney. Mobilizing Youth: Communists and Catholics in Interwar France.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:15:15">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13358/article/7060096</link><title>Journal of humanitarian assistance</title><description>Journal of Humanitarian Assistance. Medford, MA: Feinstein International Center, Tufts University. http://jha.ac/. This journal includes scholarly articles from researchers and workers who are intimately involved with international humanitarian assistance work “on the ground.” Contains articles on providing humanitarian assistance to genocide victims, giving aid to the victims of the Rwandan genocide, and offers researchers a look at such tragedies through the perspective of those helping with the aftermath. Selected articles reaching back to the year 2000 are freely ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:16:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cheriema/article/8988093</link><title>Climate for a transport change : TERM 2007 : indicators tracking transport and environment in the European Union</title><description>The TERM 2007 report examines performance of the transport sector vis-a-vis potential future targets for greenhouse gas emission reductions and concludes that technology measures are insufficient to meet likely targets. Policy-makers have to address the growth in transport demand.--Publisher's description. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:17:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/psique/article/5398929</link><title>Public biotech 2008[mdash]the numbers</title><description>The sour global economy has left many small public firms gasping for air. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:18:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/7404648</link><title>Drinking at European universities? A review of students' alcohol use</title><description>High volumes of alcohol consumption and risky single occasion drinking (RSOD) among university students have been shown to be associated with considerable harm to both those who consume alcohol and their fellow students. The vast majority of these studies are based on US and Canadian samples. The present article provides an overview of the characteristics of alcohol-consuming university students in Europe. 65 relevant articles published within the last 20 years using European student populations could be identified. Sociodemographic, individual, social, and university-related ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:20:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/france/article/563005</link><title>A History of the University in Europe (A History of the University in Europe)</title><description>This is the first of four volumes that will comprise A History of the University in Europe, covering the development of the university in Europe (East and West) from its origins to the present day. No other up-to-date, comprehensive history of this type exists: its originality lies in focusing on a number of major themes viewed from a European perspective, and in its interdisciplinary, collaborative and transnational character. Volume I, covering the Middle Ages, places the medieval European ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7423-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7423_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:21:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kelbr11/article/11689406</link><title>The Dropout Crisis: Promising Approaches in Prevention and Recovery</title><description>The number of high school age students who do not complete high school is receiving increased attention as a serious challenge facing the educational system. This is happening for several reasons. New research estimates that about 30 percent of high school students fail to earn a diploma in the standard number of years, a higher figure than state and local education officials typically cite. In many states, barely half of African-Americans and Latinos graduate from high school. The magnitude of the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>