<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:23:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:23:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Flit/article/1397340</link><title>Biodiverity and the Ecosystem Approach in Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries</title><description>This document contains the proceedings of a meeting of the Food and Agricultural Organization's Inter-Departmental Working Group on Biological Diversity for Food and Agriculture, held in October 2002, in Rome. The meeting aimed to improve awareness of the importance of biological diversity and to support the ecosystem approach to all types of production systems. Presentations and discussions covered grasslands in South Africa, mahogany forests in Mexico, rice ecology in Asia and organic agriculture systems around the world. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:23:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alinarahim/article/3862167</link><title>Microbiological Quality of Ready-to-Eat Food Served in Schools in Wales, United Kingdom</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:24:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/9869724</link><title>2010 position paper of the Italian Society of Hypertension (SIIA): angiotensin receptor blockers and risk of cancer.</title><description>Antihypertensive therapy has been demonstrated to significantly reduce cardiovascular and non-cardiovascular mortality in randomized controlled clinical trials. In the past, however, doubts have been raised on the safety of one class of blood pressure lowering drugs, namely the angiotensin II type 1 receptor antagonists (angiotensin receptor blockers [ARBs]), in terms of increased risk of myocardial infarction. Several comprehensive meta-analyses have definitely demonstrated no significant increased risk of myocardial infarction in patients treated with ARBs compared with placebo or any other active ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:24:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/josiasporter/article/6132179</link><title>History Meets Fiction in Doctor Who, ?The Fires of Pompeii?: A BBC Reception of Ancient Rome on Screen and Online</title><description>The door of the iconic police box squeaks open. The camera pans, following a dark-haired man as he emerges, pushes through a curtained doorway, and, with a glint in his eye, glee in his smile, and a touch of London in his voice, announces their destination to his redhead companion. So begins , the second episode in the fourth season of the current BBC (British Broadcasting Corporation) science-fiction drama Doctor Who. And so, no doubt, began the scribbling of pens on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:24:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hnuhoglu/article/2853096</link><title>A system dynamics modeling framework for the strategic supply chain management of food chains</title><description>The need for holistic modeling efforts that capture the extended supply chain enterprise at a strategic level has been clearly recognized first by industry and recently by academia. Strategic decision-makers need comprehensive models to guide them in efficient decision-making that increases the profitability of the entire chain. The determination of optimal network configuration, inventory management policies, supply contracts, distribution strategies, supply chain integration, outsourcing and procurement strategies, product design, and information technology are prime examples of strategic decision-making that affect the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:25:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Kerrybot/article/12274201</link><title>Determination of Seven Certified Color Additives in Food Products Using Liquid Chromatography</title><description>This study describes a new method for determining FD&amp;C Blue No. 1, FD&amp;C Blue No. 2, FD&amp;C Green No. 3, FD&amp;C Red No. 3, FD&amp;C Red No. 40, FD&amp;C Yellow No. 5, and FD&amp;C Yellow No. 6 in food products. These seven color additives are water-soluble dyes that are required to be batch certified by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) before they may be used in food and other FDA-regulated products. In the new method, the color additives are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:25:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/srl/article/392489</link><title>The Bulldozer in the Countryside : Suburban Sprawl and the Rise of American Environmentalism (Studies in Environment and History)</title><description>Modern American environmentalism owes much to such predecessors as Henry Thoreau, John Muir, and Theodore Roosevelt. But it owes much more, suggests historian Adam Rome, to the sprawling suburbs of the postwar era, when great sections of the country fell under the bulldozer to make way for the vaunted American Dream.&lt;p&gt; Homebuilders of the immediate postwar era did not, as a rule, take into account the environmental costs of their work--nor did they have to. "To take advantage of the cheap, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:25:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/swifters/article/9482481</link><title>Consumer Food Handling in the Home: A Review of Food Safety Studies</title><description>Epidemiological data from Europe, North America, Australia, and New Zealand indicate that a substantial proportion of foodborne disease is attributable to improper food preparation practices in consumers' homes. International concern about consumer food safety has prompted considerable research to evaluate domestic food-handling practices. The majority of consumer food safety studies in the last decade have been conducted in the United Kingdom and Northern Ireland (48%) and in the United States (42%). Surveys (questionnaires and interviews), the most frequent means of data ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:26:11">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7600173</link><title>Prevalence of Listeria monocytogenes in Ready-to-Eat Foods Sampled from the Point of Sale in Wales, United Kingdom</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:26:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/10001565/article/8055797</link><title>Food labeling toward national uniformity</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>