<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:48" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CharmyonneBailey/article/6695012</link><title>Close up in Black : African American film posters from the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:23:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9766067</link><title>An exact method for graph coloring</title><description>We are interested in the graph coloring problem. We propose an exact method based on a linear-decomposition of the graph. The complexity of this method is exponential according to the linearwidth of the entry graph, but linear according to its number of vertices. We present some experiments performed on literature instances, among which COLOR02 library instances. Our method is useful to solve more quickly than other exact algorithms instances with small linearwidth, such as mug graphs. Moreover, our algorithms are the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:25:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9766044</link><title>Variable space search for graph coloring</title><description>Let G=(V,E) be a graph with vertex set V and edge set E. The k-coloring problem is to assign a color (a number chosen in 1,...,k) to each vertex of G so that no edge has both endpoints with the same color. We propose a new local search methodology, called Variable Space Search, which we apply to the k-coloring problem. The main idea is to consider several search spaces, with various neighborhoods and objective functions, and to move from one to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:27:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9766058</link><title>A Metaheuristic Approach for the Vertex Coloring Problem</title><description>Given an undirected graph G = (V, E), the vertex coloring problem (VCP) requires to assign a color to each vertex in such a way that colors on adjacent vertices are different and the number of colors used is minimized. In this paper, we propose a metaheuristic approach for VCP that performs two phases: the first phase is based on an evolutionary algorithm, whereas the second one is a postoptimization phase based on the set covering formulation of the problem. Computational ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:29:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9177207</link><title>Coloring large graphs based on independent set extraction</title><description>This paper presents an effective approach (EXTRACOL) to coloring large graphs. The proposed approach uses a preprocessing method to extract large independent sets from the graph and a memetic algorithm to color the residual graph. Each preprocessing application identifies, with a dedicated tabu search algorithm, a number of pairwise disjoint independent sets of a given size in order to maximize the vertices removed from the graph. We evaluate EXTRACOL on the 11 largest graphs (with 1000 to 4000 vertices) of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:30:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9766153</link><title>A graph coloring heuristic using partial solutions and a reactive tabu scheme</title><description>Most of the recent heuristics for the graph coloring problem start from an infeasible k-coloring (adjacent vertices may have the same color) and try to make the solution feasible through a sequence of color exchanges. In contrast, our approach (called FOO-PARTIALCOL), which is based on tabu search, considers feasible but partial solutions and tries to increase the size of the current partial solution. A solution consists of k disjoint stable sets (and, therefore, is a feasible, partial k-coloring) and a set ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:32:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/9766116</link><title>A search space "cartography" for guiding graph coloring heuristics</title><description>We present a search space analysis and its application in improving local search algorithms for the graph coloring problem. Using a classical distance measure between colorings, we introduce the following clustering hypothesis: the high quality solutions are not randomly scattered in the search space, but rather grouped in clusters within spheres of specific diameter. We first provide intuitive evidence for this hypothesis by presenting a projection of a large set of local minima in the 3D space. An experimental confirmation is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:33:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/armanboyaci/article/6640411</link><title>An evolutionary approach with diversity guarantee and well-informed grouping recombination for graph coloring</title><description>We present a diversity-oriented hybrid evolutionary approach for the graph coloring problem. This approach is based on both generally applicable strategies and specifically tailored techniques. Particular attention is paid to ensuring population diversity by carefully controlling spacing among individuals. Using a distance measure between potential solutions, the general population management strategy decides whether an offspring should be accepted in the population, which individual needs to be replaced and when mutation is applied. Furthermore, we introduce a special grouping-based multi-parent crossover operator ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:33:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eeruowl/article/9804431</link><title>Fiber delivered probe for efficient CARS imaging of tissues</title><description>We demonstrate a fiber-based probe for maximum collection of the coherent anti-Stokes Raman scattering (CARS) signal in biological tissues. We discuss the design challenges including capturing the backscattered forward generated CARS signal in the sample and the effects of fiber nonlinearities on the propagating pulses. Three different single mode fibers (fused silica fiber, photonic crystal fiber and double-clad photonic crystal fiber) were tested for the probe design. We investigated self-phase modulation, stimulated Raman scattering (SRS) and four-wave-mixing (FWM) generation in the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:34:55">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14714/article/8881093</link><title>All-fiber CARS microscopy of live cells</title><description>Using an all-fiber laser system consisting of a femtosecond Er/Yb fiber oscillator as the pump and an ultra-highly nonlinear fiber for Stokes generation, we demonstrate multimodal (TPF+SHG+CARS) non-linear optical microscopy of both tissue samples and live cells. Multimodal imaging was successfully performed with pixel dwell times as short as 4 µs at low laser powers (&lt; 40 mW total). ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>