<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7426">game bmx boy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:36" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rezash/article/10997138</link><title>Assessment in Game-Based Learning</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:36:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tjhickey/article/9007002</link><title>Game design for ad-hoc multi-touch gameplay on large tabletop displays</title><description>This paper examines game design for multi-touch enabled systems, focusing on tabletop computers that are exposed to the public. We first elaborate on the requirements for ad-hoc collaborative multi-touch gameplay. As our main contribution, we identified particular gameplay aspects and formalized them in reference to formal elements of gameplay: The game mechanics should support different scopes of involvement and make use of spatial conflicts that relate to the player resources. The game should further offer outcomes that can be achieved in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:37:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mattjb/article/1597681</link><title>Game Theory, Complexity And Simplicity Part III: Critique and Prospective</title><description>this paper. The details are not important here. What is important is that they all have been essentially normative solutions. Given that we require that a solution satisfies various axioms concerning efficiency, symmetry, bargaining power, additivity and other conditions, then the solution tells us which set of outcomes have the required properties. The Nash noncooperative equilibrium can also be considered axiomatically where efficiency is given up but mutual consistency of individual... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:39:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/keller91711/article/1838010</link><title>A Game of Hearts</title><description>ft to implement the decision making functions for passing cards, for choosing the lead and for following the suit. I separated these functions into the separate file "control.c" and called them respectively PickPassCard(), PickDumpCard(), PickAnyCard(), PickNoHeartCard() and PickSuitCard(). Through these functions my player is communicating with the external world. The player program is split into two classes: the Agent class and the Engine class. The Engine class is the external class that... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:41:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/marianap/article/1142770</link><title>Comparative Video Game Criticism</title><description>This article explores comparative criticism and video game software development through the figure of the bricoleur, the handyman who assembles units of preexisting meaning to form new structures. An intersection of these two domains--what the author calls comparative video game criticism--suggests a more intimate interrelation between criticism and production. The author offers a critique of functionalist approaches to video game analysis and argues instead for a comparative analysis of the expressive capacity of games and how they relate to other forms ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:42:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/milando0/article/4081344</link><title>The advantages and disadvantages of non-surgical management of the diabetic foot.</title><description>It is frequently stated that diabetic foot ulcers should be managed by a multidisciplinary team, comprising individuals who can deliver all the necessary and wide-ranging skills: medical and surgical, podiatric, nursing and orthotic. Whilst there are some data to support this multidisciplinary approach there is little to guide us in ensuring the patient is seen by the right professional for the right treatment at the right time.This article will examine the evidence supporting the most effective use of the multidisciplinary team. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:43:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dtsamis/article/5156097</link><title>Game theoretic rate control for mobile devices</title><description>Modern mobile devices offer increased connectivity to heterogeneous wireless networks such as WiFi and 3G. These networks typically exhibit high variability in their characteristics, which poses extra challenges to applications developed to run over them. To address this issue, we propose a game-theoretic rate control scheme for mobile devices. In this noncooperative game formulation of the system the users are assumed the to be selfish in terms of their resource (bandwidth) requests. The information requirements within the model are then simplified ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:44:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/12737681</link><title>Osteomyelitis in the diabetic foot: diagnosis and management.</title><description>Although osteomyelitis of the foot in diabetes remains common in specialist foot clinics across the world, the quality of published work to guide clinicians in the diagnosis and management is generally poor. Diagnosis should be based primarily on clinical signs supported by results of pathologic and radiologic investigations. Although the gold standard comes from the histologic and microbiological examination of bone, clinicians should be aware ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:45:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dquest/article/881997</link><title>GAME: detecting cis-regulatory elements using a genetic algorithm.</title><description>MOTIVATION: Identification of a transcription factor binding sites is an important aspect of the analysis of genetic regulation. Many programs have been developed for the de novo discovery of a binding motif (collection of binding sites). Recently, a scoring function formulation was derived that allows for the comparison of discovered motifs from different programs [S.T. Jensen, X.S. Liu, Q. Zhou and J.S. Liu (2004) Stat. Sci., 19, 188-204.] A simple program, BioOptimizer, was proposed in [S.T. Jensen and J.S. Liu (2004) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7426-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7426_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:45:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/boosda/article/2428763</link><title>Perceived Complexity and Cognitive Stability in Human-Centered Design</title><description>Perceived complexity is analyzed in conjunction with cognitive stability in the context of potential use in human-centered design. These human factors are useful in the process of understanding co-adaptation of people and technology, and consequently for the evaluation of the maturity of a product. Expertise and experience play an important role in the definition and refinement of these two concepts. This paper presents a first account of such concepts in the context of aircraft cockpit design. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>