<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7427">k3 mamase</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:47:31" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:47:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stieberg/article/4131032</link><title>Freedom and Constraints in the K3 Landscape</title><description>We consider "magnetized brane" compactifications of the type I/heterotic string on K3 with U(1) background fluxes. The gauge group and matter content of the resulting six-dimensional vacua are parameterized by a matrix which encodes a lattice contained within the even, self-dual lattice Gamma^3,19. Mathematical results of Nikulin on lattice embeddings make possible a simple classification of all such solutions. We find that every six-dimensional theory parameterized in this way by a negative semi-definite matrix whose trace satisfies a simple tadpole constraint can be realized as a K3 compactification. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:49:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/4414179</link><title>K3 Surfaces and String Duality</title><description>The primary purpose of these lecture notes is to explore the moduli space of type IIA, type IIB, and heterotic string compactified on a K3 surface. The main tool which is invoked is that of string duality. K3 surfaces provide a fascinating arena for string compactification as they are not trivial spaces but are sufficiently simple for one to be able to analyze most of their properties in detail. They also make an almost ubiquitous appearance in the common statements concerning string duality. We review the necessary ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:50:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/philom/article/4371157</link><title>Maps, sheaves, and K3 surfaces</title><description>The conjectural equivalence of curve counting on Calabi-Yau 3-folds via stable maps and stable pairs is discussed. By considering Calabi-Yau 3-folds with K3 fibrations, the correspondence naturally connects curve and sheaf counting on K3 surfaces. New results and conjectures (with D. Maulik) about descendent integration on K3 surfaces are announced. The recent proof of the Yau-Zaslow conjecture is surveyed. The paper accompanies my lecture at the Clay research conference in Cambridge, MA in May 2008. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:51:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/5636856</link><title>Compactification with Flux on K3 and Tori</title><description>We study compactifications of Type IIB string theory on a K3 × T^2/Z_2 orientifold in the presence of RR and NS flux. We find the most general supersymmetry preserving, Poincare invariant, vacua in this model. All the complex structure moduli and some of the Kahler moduli are stabilised in these vacua. We obtain in an explicit fashion the restrictions imposed by supersymmetry on the flux, and the values of the fixed moduli. Some T-duals and Heterotic duals are also discussed, these are non-Calabi-Yau spaces. A superpotential is constructed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:52:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/6502968</link><title>K3 Orientifolds</title><description>We study string theory propagating on R^6 times K3 by constructing orientifolds of Type IIB string theory compactified on the T^4/Z_N orbifold limits of the K3 surface. This generalises the Z_2 case studied previously. The orientifold models studied may be divided into two broad categories, sometimes related by T-duality. Models in category A require either both D5- and D9-branes, or only D9-branes, for consistency. Models in category B require either only D5-branes, or no D-branes at all. This latter case is an example of a consistent purely closed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:54:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stieberg/article/6974611</link><title>Notes on the K3 Surface and the Mathieu group M_24</title><description>We point out that the elliptic genus of the K3 surface has a natural decomposition in terms of dimensions of irreducible representations of the largest Mathieu group M_24. The reason is yet a mystery. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:54:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/5075035</link><title>Mirror symmetry on K3 surfaces via Fourier-Mukai transform</title><description>We use a relative Fourier-Mukai transform on elliptic K3 surfaces $X$ to describe mirror symmetry. The action of this Fourier-Mukai transform on the cohomology ring of $X$ reproduces relative T-duality and provides an infinitesimal isometry of the moduli space of algebraic structures on $X$ which, in view of the triviality of the quantum cohomology of K3 surfaces, can be interpreted as mirror symmetry. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:55:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/umesh/article/5649166</link><title>Vector bundles on a K3 surface</title><description>A K3 surface is a quaternionic analogue of an elliptic curve from a view point of moduli of vector bundles. We can prove the algebraicity of certain Hodge cycles and a rigidity of curve of genus eleven and gives two kind of descriptions of Fano threefolds as applications. In the final section we discuss a simplified construction of moduli spaces. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:56:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NitinCR/article/6056415</link><title>Orientifolds of K3 and Calabi-Yau Manifolds with Intersecting D-branes</title><description>We investigate orientifolds of type II string theory on K3 and Calabi-Yau 3-folds with intersecting D-branes wrapping special Lagrangian cycles. We determine quite generically the chiral massless spectrum in terms of topological invariants and discuss both orbifold examples and algebraic realizations in detail. Intriguingly, the developed techniques provide an elegant way to figure out the chiral sector of orientifold models without computing any explicit string partition function. As a new example we derive a non-supersymmetric Standard-like Model from an orientifold of type IIA on the quintic Calabi-Yau 3-fold with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7427-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7427_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:57:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/damiantrj/article/2599199</link><title>K3-mediated evasion of CD8(+) T cells aids amplification of a latent gamma-herpesvirus.</title><description>The murine gamma-herpesvirus-68 (MHV-68) K3 protein, like that of the Kaposi's sarcoma associated herpesvirus, down-regulates major histocompatibility complex (MHC) class I expression. However, how this contributes to viral replication in vivo is unclear. After intranasal MHV-68 infection, K3 was transcribed both during acute lytic infection in the lung and during latency establishment in lymphoid tissue. K3-deficient viruses were not cleared more rapidly from the lung, but the number of latently infected spleen cells was reduced and the frequency of virus-specific CD8(+) ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>