<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7437">free aldi meyola songs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:52:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:52:24">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7162972</link><title>Editorial [ Hot topic:Metabolic Syndrome - Modern Pharmacological, Genetic, Clinical and Environmental Contributions (Guest Editor: Aldi T. Kraja)]</title><description>This article is currently available as a free download on IngentaConnect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:54:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/flatliner_uk/article/9095745</link><title>Free software, free society : selected essays of Richard Stallman</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:56:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/federicapace/article/8614115</link><title>Recurring patterns in the songs of humpback whales (Megaptera novaeangliae)</title><description>Humpback whales, unlike most mammalian species, learn new songs as adults. Populations of singers progressively and collectively change the sounds and patterns within their songs throughout their lives and across generations. In this study, humpback whale songs recorded in Hawaii from 1985 to 1995 were analyzed using self-organizing maps (SOMs) to classify the sounds within songs, and to identify sound patterns that were present across multiple years. These analyses supported the hypothesis that recurring, persistent patterns exist within whale songs, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:58:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1993135</link><title>Partially Ordered Multiset Context-Free</title><description>We present a new formalism, partially ordered multiset context-free grammars (pomsCFG) , along with an Earley-style parsing algorithm. The formalism, which can be thought of as a generalization of context-free grammars with partially ordered right-hand sides, is of interest in its own right, and also as infrastructure for obtaining tighter complexity bounds for more expressive context-free formalisms intended to express free or multiple word-order, such as ID/LP grammars. We reduce ID/LP... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:01:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8920894</link><title>On the edge: the Irish in Britain as a troubled and troubling presence in the work of Jimmy McGovern and Alan Bleasdale</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:02:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/livingthingdan/article/7853563</link><title>Evolutionary parsing for a probabilistic context free grammar</title><description>Abstract. Classic parsing methods are based on complete search techniques to find the different interpretations of a sentence. However, the size of the search space increases exponentially with the length of the sentence or text to be parsed, so that exhaustive search methods can fail to reach a solution in a reasonable time. Nevertheless, large problems can be solved approximately by some kind of stochastic techniques, which do not guarantee the optimum value, but allow adjusting the probability of error by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:03:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/adamimos/article/6250821</link><title>Free Will, Physics, Biology, and the Brain</title><description>This introduction reviews the traditionally conceived question of free will from the point of view of a physicist turned neurobiologist. I discuss the quantum mechanic evidence that has brought us to the view that the world, including our brains, is not completely determined by physics and that even very simple nervous systems are subject to deterministic chaos. However, it is unclear how consciousness or any other extra-physical agent could take advantage of this situation to effect a change in the world, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:05:04">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16440/article/7791869</link><title>Free-space quantum cryptography in daylight</title><description>Quantum cryptography is an emerging technology in which two parties may simultaneously generate shared, secret cryptographic key material using the transmission of quantum states of light. The security of these transmissions is based on the inviolability of the laws of quantum mechanics and information-theoretically secure post-processing methods. An adversary can neither successfully tap the quantum transmissions, nor evade detection, owing to Heisenberg's uncertainty principle. In this paper we describe the theory of quantum cryptography, and the most recent results from our ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:05:56">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16440/article/7791872</link><title>Present and future free-space quantum key distribution</title><description>Free-space quantum key distribution (QKD), more popularly know as quantum cryptography, uses single-photon free-space optical communications to distribute the secret keys required for secure communications. At Los Alamos National Laboratory we have demonstrated a fully automated system that is capable of operations at any time of day over a horizontal range of several kilometers. This has proven the technology is capable of operation from a spacecraft to the ground, opening up the possibility of QKD between any group of users anywhere ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7437-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7437_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:06:59">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2108103</link><title>II. From the Songs of Ecstasy</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>