<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:07:40" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:07:43">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5655/article/1202229</link><title>Imagined Communities: Awareness, Information Sharing, and Privacy on the Facebook</title><description>Online social networks such as Friendster, MySpace, or the Facebook have experienced exponential growth in membership in recent years. These networks offer attractive means for interaction and communication, but also raise privacy and security concerns. In this study we survey a representative sample of the members of the Facebook (a social network for colleges and high schools) at a US academic institution, and compare the survey data to information retrieved from the network itself. We look for underlying demographic or behavioral ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:08:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ShantanuPal/article/11071152</link><title>Facebook and Privacy: It's Complicated</title><description>We measure users' attitudes toward interpersonal privacy concerns on Facebook and measure users' strategies for reconciling their concerns with their desire to share content online. To do this, we recruited 260 Facebook users to install a Facebook application that surveyed their privacy concerns, their friend network compositions, the sensitivity of posted content, and their privacy-preserving strategies. By asking participants targeted questions about people randomly selected from their friend network and posts shared on their profiles, we were able to quantify the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:09:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/12793762</link><title>The Post Anachronism: The Temporal Dimension of Facebook Privacy</title><description>This paper reports on two studies that investigate empirically how privacy preferences about the audience and emphasis of Facebook posts change over time. In a 63-participant longitudinal study, participants gave their audience and emphasis preferences for up to ten of their Facebook posts in the week they were posted, again one week later, and again one month later. In a 234-participant retrospective study, participants expressed their preferences about posts made in the past week, as well as one year prior. We ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:09:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amcunningham/article/7549372</link><title>Facebook privacy settings: Who cares?</title><description>With over 500 million users, the decisions that Facebook makes about its privacy settings have the potential to influence many people. While its changes in this domain have often prompted privacy advocates and news media to critique the company, Facebook has continued to attract more users to its service. This raises a question about whether or not Facebook's changes in privacy approaches matter and, if so, to whom. This paper examines the attitudes and practices of a cohort of 18- and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:10:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/9391749</link><title>An Alternative View of Privacy on Facebook</title><description>The predominant analysis of privacy on Facebook focuses on personal information revelation. This paper is critical of this kind of research and introduces an alternative analytical framework for studying privacy on Facebook, social networking sites and web 2.0. This framework is connecting the phenomenon of online privacy to the political economy of capitalism—a focus that has thus far been rather neglected in research literature about Internet and web 2.0 privacy. Liberal privacy philosophy tends to ignore the political economy of privacy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:10:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ShantanuPal/article/10333745</link><title>Examining privacy and disclosure in a social networking community</title><description>The polularity of social networking websites such as Facebook and the subsequent levels and depth of online disclosures have raised several concerns for user privacy. Previous research into these sites has indicated the importance of disclosures between users as well as an under-utilization of extensive privacy options. This study qualitatively examines college students' disclosure and privacy behaviors and attitudes on Facebook.com. Results support current research into social networking and privacy and provide user-generated explanations for observed disclosure and privacy trends. Implications ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:11:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/10778009</link><title>Privacy Compliance Risks for Facebook</title><description>Facebook is an Internet and societal phenomenon. In just a few years it has claimed a significant proportion of the world's population as regular users, becoming by far the most dominant Online Social Network (OSN). With its success has come a good deal of controversy, especially over privacy. Does Facebook and its kin herald a true shift in privacy values, or despite occasional reckless revelations, are most users actually as reserved as ever? We argue it's too early to draw conclusions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:12:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ShantanuPal/article/10611075</link><title>Privacy attacks in social media using photo tagging networks: a case study with Facebook</title><description>Social-networking users unknowingly reveal certain kinds of personal information that malicious attackers could profit from to perpetrate significant privacy breaches. This paper quantitatively demonstrates how the simple act of tagging pictures on the social-networking site of Facebook could reveal private user attributes that are extremely sensitive. Our results suggest that photo tags can be used to help predicting some, but not all, of the analyzed attributes. We believe our analysis make users aware of significant breaches of their privacy and could ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:12:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tnhh/article/11067600</link><title>The Political Economy of Privacy on Facebook</title><description>This article provides an analysis of the political economy of privacy and surveillance on Facebook. The concepts of socialist privacy and socialist internet privacy are advanced here. Capital accumulation on Facebook is based on the commodification of users and their data. One can in this context speak, based on Dallas Smythe, of the exploitation of the internet prosumer commodity. Aspects of a socialist internet privacy strategy are outlined and it is shown how they can be applied to social networking sites. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:13:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/k7lim/article/480486</link><title>Information revelation and privacy in online social networks</title><description>Participation in social networking sites has dramatically increased in recent years. Services such as Friendster, Tribe, or the Facebook allow millions of individuals to create online profiles and share personal information with vast networks of friends - and, often, unknown numbers of strangers. In this paper we study patterns of information revelation in online social networks and their privacy implications. We analyze the online behavior of more than 4,000 Carnegie Mellon University students who have joined a popular social networking site ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>