<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:22:52" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:22:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/skyhisi/article/4186416</link><title>Implementing mode changes with shared resources in Ada</title><description>The ability to support mode changes is a desirable feature for many real-time systems in which the functionality provided may vary as the mission progresses. The addition and deletion of tasks, the change of task profiles, the coherent management of resources and, at the same time, the required timeliness guarantee is an exercise of coordination of activities in a real-time system. In this paper we suggest how to safely implement mode changes in Ada, taking resource management into account. We consider ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:23:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jwong/article/2238955</link><title>Mode Change Protocols for Real-Time Systems: A Survey and a New Proposal</title><description>This paper contains both a survey of mode change protocols for single-processor, fixed-priority, preemptively scheduled real-time systems, and a proposal of several new protocols along with their corresponding schedulability analysis and configuration methods. First, a classification of the protocols found in the literature is given and a set of requirements is proposed for their evaluation. Then, the new protocols are introduced and discussed in the light of the stated requirements. A number of mode change protocols are based on delaying the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:24:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/I_Biomed/article/2256434</link><title>Functional Imaging and Modeling of the Heart: Third International Workshop, FIMH 2005, Barcelona, Spain, June 2-4, 2005, Proceedings (Lecture Notes in Computer Science)</title><description>&lt;P&gt;This book constitutes the refereed proceedings of the Third International Workshop on Functional Imaging and Modeling of the Heart, FIMH 2005, held in Barcelona, Spain in June 2005.&lt;/P&gt; &lt;P&gt;The 47 revised full papers presented were carefully reviewed and selected from numerous submissions. The papers are organized in topical sections on modeling of the heart: anatomy extraction and description; electro-physiology and electro- and magnetography; modeling of the cardiac mechanisms and functions; and cardiac motion estimation.&lt;/P&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:25:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alex_ren/article/12720347</link><title>TLSF: A New Dynamic Memory Allocator for Real-Time Systems</title><description>Dynamic storage allocation (DSA) algorithms playan important role in the modern software engineeringparadigms and techniques (such as object oriented programming).Using DSA increases the flexibility and functionalitiesof applications. There exists a large number ofreferences to this particular issue in the literature. However,the use of DSA has been considered a source of indeterminismin the real-time domain, due to the unconstrained responsetime of DSA algorithms and the fragmentation problem.Nowadays, new real-time applications require more flexibility:the ability to adjust system configuration in responseto workload changes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:26:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3830686</link><title>The interaction of metonymy and metaphor in the meaning and form of 'bahuvrihi' compounds</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:27:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8629837</link><title>Metonymic inferencing and second language acquisition</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:27:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/liuxin9023/article/9024208</link><title>The Markets for Real Estate Assets and Space: A Conceptual Framework</title><description>In this study, we present a simple analytic framework that divides the real estate market into two markets: the market for real estate space and the market for real estate assets. After describing the size and character of flows and stocks in the U.S. real estate market, we use our framework to demonstrate the important connections between the space and asset markets. We illustrate how these real estate markets are affected by the nation's macroeconomy and financial markets, tracing out the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/artestre/article/1297660</link><title>Variables associated with diagnostic delay in immigrant groups with tuberculosis in Madrid</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:58">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3764799</link><title>Whither Superfund?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7440-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7440_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:29:41">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13537/article/10041946</link><title>Diccionario de la Lengua Espanola (Spanish Edition) (2 volumes)</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>