<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12891090</link><title>Single muscle fiber adaptations with marathon training</title><description>The purpose of this investigation was to characterize the effects of marathon training on single muscle fiber contractile function in a group of recreational runners. Muscle biopsies were obtained from the gastrocnemius muscle of seven individuals (22 ± 1 yr, 177 ± 3 cm, and 68 ± 2 kg) before, after 13 wk of run training, and after 3 wk of taper. Slow-twitch myosin heavy chain [(MHC) I] and fast-twitch (MHC IIa) muscle fibers were analyzed for size, strength (Po), speed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:55:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ftv88/article/12898997</link><title>Transient myocardial tissue and function changes during a marathon in less fit marathon runners.</title><description>Although regular physical activity improves health, strenuous exercise might transiently increase cardiac risk. Training and fitness might provide protection. We prospectively studied 20 recreational marathon runners without known cardiovascular disease or symptoms: at peak training before, immediately after, and 3 months after a 42.2-km marathon. Changes in global/segmental myocardial function, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:56:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/robock193/article/8412780</link><title>Effects of cognitive training interventions with older adults: a randomized controlled trial.</title><description>CONTEXT: Cognitive function in older adults is related to independent living and need for care. However, few studies have addressed whether improving cognitive functions might have short- or long-term effects on activities related to living independently. OBJECTIVE: To evaluate whether 3 cognitive training interventions improve mental abilities and daily functioning in older, independent-living adults. DESIGN: Randomized, controlled, single-blind trial with recruitment conducted from March 1998 to October 1999 and 2-year follow-up through December 2001. SETTING AND PARTICIPANTS: Volunteer sample of 2832 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:56:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/amandaalders/article/2215883</link><title>Effects of cognitive training interventions with older adults: a randomized controlled trial.</title><description>Cognitive function in older adults is related to independent living and need for care. However, few studies have addressed whether improving cognitive functions might have short- or long-term effects on activities related to living independently. To evaluate whether 3 cognitive training interventions improve mental abilities and daily functioning in older, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:57:43">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18054/article/12398785</link><title>Post-marathon paradox in IDDM: unchanged insulin sensitivity in spite of glycogen depletion.</title><description>Acute physical exercise usually enhances insulin sensitivity. We examined the effect of a competitive 42 km marathon run on glucose uptake and lipid oxidation in 7 runners with insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus (IDDM), aged 36 +/- 3 yr, BMI 23.9 +/- 0.5 kg m-2, VO2max 46 +/- 1 ml kg-1 min-1, HbA1c 7.7 +/- 0.3%, duration of diabetes 16 +/- 5 yr, runtime 3 h 47 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:58:33">http://www.citeulike.org/group/18054/article/7077498</link><title>Risks of marathon running and hypoglycaemia in Type 1 diabetes.</title><description>Exercise-induced hypoglycaemia is common in people with insulin-treated diabetes and if severe can provoke neurological morbidity including coma and seizures. Depending on the duration and demands of the physical activity, various strategies can be used to limit the risk of hypoglycaemia with strenuous exercise. However, metabolic events occurring in the 48 h before the exercise can influence the risk and responses to exercise-induced hypoglycaemia. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:59:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/8254388</link><title>Cognitive function in elderly marathon runners: Cross-sectional data from the marathon trial (apsoem)</title><description>BACKGROUND: Cognitive impairment of the elderly contributes to morbidity, loss of quality of life, and impairment of work ability in aging western societies. Thus strategies to maintain cognitive function at an advanced age imply a great challenge to Occupational Medicine. AIM: To study whether intensive endurance exercise training is associated with better cognitive performance and increases brain-derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF) and insulin-like growth factor (IGF). METHODS: Active elderly marathon runners or bicyclists older than 60 years were recruited and matched with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rodney/article/8068227</link><title>Metabolic Factors Limiting Performance in Marathon Runners</title><description>Each year in the past three decades has seen hundreds of thousands of runners register to run a major marathon. Of those who attempt to race over the marathon distance of 26 miles and 385 yards (42.195 kilometers), more than two-fifths experience severe and performance-limiting depletion of physiologic carbohydrate reserves (a phenomenon known as ‘hitting the wall’), and thousands drop out before reaching the finish lines (approximately 1–2% of those who start). Analyses of endurance physiology have often either used coarse ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/llaineey/article/9743997</link><title>Provision of physiotherapy at the Tsing Ma Bridge international marathon and 10 km race in Hong Kong.</title><description>This report examines the delivery of sports physiotherapy at the Tsing Ma Bridge marathon and 10 km race in Hong Kong. The incidence, type of injury encountered, and treatment modalities selected are examined. The report also highlights the flexibility required when planning the provision of such a service. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:01:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ruru1958/article/10336675</link><title>Evaluation of a Suicide Prevention Training Program for Mental Health Services Staff.</title><description>Training for health services staff often focuses on improving individual practitioner's knowledge and skills, with less emphasis given to the broader organizational context, in particular those elements that support successful implementation of changes post-training. This paper compares the effectiveness of a standard training model for suicide prevention to an enhanced training model. The training involved the public mental health workforce throughout the State of Queensland, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>