<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:12" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:17">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14287/article/8309871</link><title>The effects of pulse charging on cycling characteristics of commercial lithium-ion batteries</title><description>The effects of a pulse charging technique on charge–discharge behavior and cycling characteristics of commercial lithium-ion batteries were investigated by comparison with the conventional direct current (dc) charging. The impedance spectra and cycling voltammograms of Li-ion batteries cycled by both protocols have been measured. The individual electrodes in the batteries have also been examined using XRD and SEM. The results show that pulse charging is helpful in eliminating concentration polarization, increasing the power transfer rate, and lowering charge time by removing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lizilopez/article/11335553</link><title>Plant-Microbe Interactions in the Rhizosphere and Nutrient Cycling</title><description>Microbial communities carry out fundamental processes that contribute to nutrient cycling, plant growth and root health. Microorganisms play a key role in nutrient cycling because they (1) decompose organic material (plant residues and soil organic matter) and release inorganic nutrients that can then be taken up by plants; (2) affect nutrient availability by solubilisation, chelation, oxidation and reduction; (3) store nutrients in, and release nutrients from, the microbial biomass; and (4) affect plant growth by release of stimulating or inhibiting substances. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:03:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fisiopatologia/article/9675006</link><title>[Antiarrhythmic effect of cardiac resynchronization].</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:04:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jnpatt/article/10634780</link><title>13C NMR isotopomer analysis reveals a connection between pyruvate cycling and glucose-stimulated insulin secretion (GSIS).</title><description>Cellular metabolism of glucose is required for stimulation of insulin secretion from pancreatic beta cells, but the precise metabolic coupling factors involved in this process are not known. In an effort to better understand mechanisms of fuel-mediated insulin secretion, we have adapted 13C NMR and isotopomer methods to measure influx of metabolic fuels into the tricarboxylic acid (TCA) cycle in insulinoma cells. Mitochondrial metabolism of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:15">http://www.citeulike.org/group/48/article/258763</link><title>The Art of Urban Cycling : Lessons from the Street</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Urban Cycling Manual&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;dismantles the urban bicycling experience and slides it under the microscope, piece by piece. The book's primary concern is safety, but this book goes well beyond the usual tips and how-to, diving in to the realms of history, psychology, sociology, and economics. It empowers readers with the Big Picture of urban cycling--and gives urban cyclists many useful insights to consider while pedaling the next commute or grocery run. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:55">http://www.citeulike.org/group/7731/article/3863897</link><title>Redox cycling in nanofluidic channels using interdigitated electrodes</title><description>Abstract  Amperometric detection is ideally suited for integration into micro- and nanofluidic systems as it directly yields an electrical signal and does not necessitate optical components. However, the range of systems to which it can be applied is constrained by the limited sensitivity and specificity of the method. These limitations can be partially alleviated through the use of redox cycling, in which multiple electrodes are employed to repeatedly reduce and oxidize analyte molecules and thereby amplify the detected signal. We have developed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:06:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LondonAnalytics/article/384387</link><title>Developing a framework for assessment of the environmental determinants of walking and cycling.</title><description>The focus for interventions and research on physical activity has moved away from vigorous activity to moderate-intensity activities, such as walking. In addition, a social ecological approach to physical activity research and practice is recommended. This approach considers the influence of the environment and policies on physical activity. Although there is limited empirical published evidence related to the features of the physical environment that influence physical activity, urban planning and transport agencies have developed policies and strategies that have the potential ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:07:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LondonAnalytics/article/1223593</link><title>Models of perceived cycling risk and route acceptability</title><description>Perceived cycling risk and route acceptability to potential users are obstacles to policy support for cycling and a better understanding of these issues will assist planners and decision makers. Two models of perceived risk, based on non-linear least squares, and a model of acceptability, based on the logit model, have been estimated for whole journeys based on responses from a sample of 144 commuters to video clips of routes and junctions. The risk models quantify the effect of motor traffic volumes, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:07:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pjryan/article/9601151</link><title>Endurance sport practice as a risk factor for atrial fibrillation and atrial flutter.</title><description>Although the benefits of regular exercise in controlling cardiovascular risk factors have been extensively proven, little is known about the long-term cardiovascular effects of regular and extreme endurance sport practice, such as jogging, cycling, rowing, swimming, etc. Recent data from a small series suggest a relationship between regular, long-term endurance sport practice and atrial fibrillation (AF) and flutter. Reported case control studies included less than ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7446-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7446_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:08:43">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3621855</link><title>Drivers and barriers for shifting towards more service-oriented businesses: Analysis of the PSS field and contributions from Sweden</title><description>Abstract  This paper reviews the discourse and research in the area of product service systems. It shows how the idea of shifting from products to services has evolved during the last decade and identifies potential areas for further advances. The paper then analyses and systematises drivers and barriers for companies to engage in devising strategies and developing business applications based on service-oriented solutions. It then further tests the perception of Swedish companies about these factors, substantiates them with examples, and analyses their ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>