<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:09:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:09:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abesselink/article/6486318</link><title>The Effect of Running Shoes on Lower Extremity Joint Torques</title><description>Objective: To determine the effect of modern-day running shoes on lower extremity joint torques during running. Design: Two-condition experimental comparison. Setting: A 3-dimensional motion analysis laboratory. Participants: A total of 68 healthy young adult runners (37 women) who typically run in running shoes. Methods: All subjects ran barefoot and in the same type of stability running footwear at a controlled running speed. Three-dimensional motion capture data were collected in synchrony with ground reaction force data from an instrumented treadmill for each of the 2 conditions. Main ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:10:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zentrification/article/5055495</link><title>Is your prescription of distance running shoes evidence-based?</title><description>ObjectivesTo determine whether the current practice of prescribing distance running shoes featuring elevated cushioned heels and pronation control systems tailored to the individual's foot type is evidence-based. Data sourcesMEDLINE (1950-May 2007), CINAHL (1982-May 2007), EMBASE (1980-May 2007), PsychInfo (1806-May 2007), Cochrane Database of Systematic Reviews (2nd Quarter 2007), Cochrane Central Register of Controlled trials (2nd Quarter 2007), SPORTSDiscus (1985-May 2007) and AMED (1985-May 2007). Review methodsEnglish language articles were identified via keyword and medical subject headings (MeSH) searches of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:10:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/llaineey/article/10744916</link><title>Injury reduction effectiveness of assigning running shoes based on plantar shape in Marine Corps basic training.</title><description>Shoe manufacturers market motion control, stability, and cushioned shoes for plantar shapes defined as low, normal, and high, respectively. This assignment procedure is presumed to reduce injuries by compensating for differences in running mechanics. Assigning running shoes based on plantar shape will not reduce injury risk in Marine Corps basic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:11:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/claytonvanlinder/article/1032802</link><title>Endurance running and the evolution of Homo</title><description>Striding bipedalism is a key derived behaviour of hominids that possibly originated soon after the divergence of the chimpanzee and human lineages. Although bipedal gaits include walking and running, running is generally considered to have played no major role in human evolution because humans, like apes, are poor sprinters compared to most quadrupeds. Here we assess how well humans perform at sustained long-distance running, and review the physiological and anatomical bases of endurance running capabilities in humans and other mammals. Judged ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:12:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alt/article/6341576</link><title>Biomechanics of walking, running, and sprinting.</title><description>A biomechanical study of 13 runners which consisted of 2 male sprinters, 5 experienced joggers, and 6 elite long-distance runners were studied. We obtained hip, knee, and ankle joints motions in the sagittal plane and electromyographic data from specific muscle groups. As the speed of gait increased, the length of stance phase progressively decreased from 62% for walking to 31% for running and to 22% for sprinting. The sagittal plane motion increased as the speed of gait increased. Generally speaking, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:12:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abesselink/article/9979408</link><title>Peak running velocity is highly related to distance running performance.</title><description>This study examined the relationship between the peak running velocity (PRV) obtained during a horizontal, incremental treadmill test and distance running performance in a group of highly-trained male (N = 14) and female (N = 9) distance runners. Performance (5 km run time) was assessed with a self-paced time trial under laboratory conditions in an attempt to minimize extraneous variables which could affect performance (i.e. environmental conditions, terrain, etc.); relationships with recent best 5 km race time were also determined. PRV ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:13:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lorevial/article/7364162</link><title>Runners anxiety and mood on running and non-running days: An &lt;i&gt;in situ&lt;/i&gt; daily monitoring study</title><description>Most of our knowledge on the effects of exercise on anxiety and mood relies on two, pre-and post-treatment, measurements. In this study a simple question was raised: disregarding all but very stressful life events, are runners less anxious and/or in a better mood on their running days as opposed to their non-running days? Forty runners completed a set of questionnaires every evening, before bed, for 21 consecutive days. Average values for anxiety and mood were calculated for running and non-running days. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:14:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abesselink/article/9979836</link><title>Physiological factors associated with middle distance running performance.</title><description>Middle distance running involves popular race distances with performance dependent on a number of physiological factors. The physiological characteristics of successful runners are different from those of sprinters and long distance runners. Maximal oxygen uptake (VO2max), running economy and the anaerobic threshold are variables that have been shown to limit performance during long distance running, and rapid velocity and anaerobic variables have been shown to limit performance during sprinting. Success with middle distance running is dependent on an integrative contribution from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:15:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abesselink/article/9979412</link><title>Peak running velocity, submaximal energy expenditure, VO2max, and 8 km distance running performance.</title><description>The purposes of this study were to examine (1) if the peak running velocity achieved during maximal treadmill testing is related to 8 km distance running performance (DRP) and (2) if the relationship between selected physiological determinants are consistant for two 8 km races within a competitive season. Seven members of a University cross-country team (mean +/- SE) (age, 19.4 +/- 0.5 years, VO2max 67.0 +/- 1.0 ml/kg/min were tested 2-3 days following a mid-season race (Race M) and the season-ending ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:15:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alt/article/4301650</link><title>Walking, running and the evolution of short toes in humans</title><description>The phalangeal portion of the forefoot is extremely short relative to body mass in humans. This derived pedal proportion is thought to have evolved in the context of committed bipedalism, but the benefits of shorter toes for walking and/or running have not been tested previously. Here, we propose a biomechanical model of toe function in bipedal locomotion that suggests that shorter pedal phalanges improve locomotor performance by decreasing digital flexor force production and mechanical work, which might ultimately reduce the metabolic ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>