<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7449">Asics GT 2000</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:17" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardo/article/2140538</link><title>Extending the notation of Rational Rose 98 for use with formal methods Extending the notation of Rational Rose 98 for use with formal methods</title><description>The Unified Modeling Language (UML) has been incorporated into the CASE tool, Rational Rose98, offering the user the capability of specifying systems using UML notation, Booch notation, or Rumbaugh notation. Through this research effort, Rose98 has been extended to allow formal notation to be entered in the class diagram text fields. Rose scripts were developed to transform the resulting extended Rose model into Z (zed) specifications in LATEX format. Z specifications are developed for the object model, dynamic model, and functional ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mbiro/article/12028239</link><title>Project control : the human factor : proceedings of ESCOM-SCOPE 2000 : 18-20 April 2000, Munich, Germany</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:24:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardo/article/889496</link><title>Generating statechart designs from scenarios</title><description>This paper presents an algorithm for automatically generating UML statecharts from a collection of UML sequence diagrams. Computer support for this transition between requirements and design is important for a successful application of UML's highly iterative, distributed software development process. There are three main issues which must be addressed when generating statecharts from sequence diagrams. Firstly, conflicts arising from the merging of independently developed sequence diagrams must be detected and resolved. Secondly, different sequence diagrams often contain identical or similar behaviors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:25:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/michaelbanks/article/3472048</link><title>Unwinding Possibilistic Security Properties</title><description>Unwinding conditions are helpful to prove that deterministic systems fulfill non-interference. In order to generalize non-interference to non-deterministic systems various possibilistic security properties have been proposed. In this paper, we present generic unwinding conditions which are applicable to a large class of such security properties. That these conditions are sufficient to ensure security is demonstrated by unwinding theorems. In certain cases they are also necessary. The practical usefulness of our results is illustrated by instantiating the generic unwinding conditions for well-known ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:26:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/andreff/article/1338412</link><title>Case study of feature location using dependence graph</title><description>Software change requests are often formulated as requests to modify or to add a specific feature or concept. To implement these changes, the features or concepts must be located in the code. We describe the scenarios of the feature and concept location. The scenarios utilize a computer-assisted search of software dependence graph. Scenarios are demonstrated by a case study of NCSA Mosaic source code ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:27:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ddahlem/article/3410126</link><title>A framework for Response Surface Methodology for simulation optimization</title><description>We develop a framework for automated optimization of stochastic simulation models using Response Surface Methodology. The framework is especially intended for simulation models where the calculation of the corresponding stochastic response function is very expensive or time-consuming. Response Surface Methodology is frequently used for the optimization of stochastic simulation models in a non-automated fashion. In scientific applications there is a clear need for a standardized algorithm based on Response Surface Methodology. In addition, an automated algorithm is less time-consuming, since there ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:27:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardo/article/3394576</link><title>A stochastic extension of a behavioural subset of UML statechart diagrams</title><description>We present a stochastically timed extension of UML statechart diagrams. The extension is rather simple both from a notational point of view and from a semantics point of view. In particular we enrich a state/transition formal operational semantics we proposed in (Latella et al., 1999) with random clocks for expressing time values. We do this in an orthogonal way, which means that the enriched semantics preserves all the properties of the untimed one. We show, by means of a simple example, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:28:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asderina/article/2642352</link><title>Discriminant snakes for 3D reconstruction in medical images</title><description>We propose a new statistic deformable model that we call discriminant snake for 3D reconstruction in volumetric images. Our discriminant snake generalises the classical snake attracted by edge points; it deforms due to a generalised contour representation. The snake selects and classifies image features by a parametric classifier and each snaxel deforms to minimise the dissimilarity between the learned and found image features inside the feature space. We apply our statistic snake to segment anatomical organs and the results are very ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:29:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/leonardo/article/2942424</link><title>A semantics of UML state-machines using synchronous pre-order transition systems</title><description>The synchronous model of concurrency has demonstrated its practicality for the design of circuits, embedded systems, reactive and distributed systems. This model allows to design systems around an idealized notion of deterministic concurrency, which is much easier to deal with than classical, nondeterministic, asynchronous concurrency. Compiling, optimizing, and verifying programs are done using powerful techniques. We take advantage of this rich background by presenting a translation of UML state-machines into a pivot synchronous calculus, based on mathematical notions of pre-orders, in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7449-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7449_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:29:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/michaelbanks/article/1261774</link><title>Disappearing formal methods</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>