<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:30:21" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:30:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ErickaDouglas/article/5864923</link><title>Columbus world travel guide. [2006-2007].</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:30:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pointblank187/article/6032892</link><title>Mental Health Problems Among Adults in Tsunami-Affected Areas in Southern Thailand</title><description>Context On December 26, 2004, an undersea earthquake occurred off the northwestern coast of Sumatra, Indonesia. The tsunami that followed severely affected all 6 southwestern provinces of Thailand, where 5395 individuals died, 2991 were unaccounted for, and 8457 were injured. Objective To assess the prevalence of symptoms of posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD), anxiety, and depression among individuals residing in areas affected by the tsunami in southern Thailand as part of a public health emergency response and rapid assessment. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:31:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/avulanov/article/8845558</link><title>Automatic Construction of Travel Itineraries using Social Breadcrumbs</title><description>Vacation planning is one of the frequent—but nonetheless laborious—tasks that people engage themselves with online; requiring skilled interaction with a multitude of resources. This paper constructs intra-city travel itineraries automatically by tapping a latent source reflecting geo-temporal breadcrumbs left by millions of tourists. For example, the popular rich media sharing site, Flickr, allows photos to be stamped by the time of when they were taken and be mapped to Points Of Interests (POIs) by geographical (i.e. latitudelongitude) and semantic (e.g., tags) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:32:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Lamminghim/article/9030008</link><title>Patients beyond borders : everybody's guide to affordable, world-class medical travel</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:32:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vanessazitafurtado/article/6081897</link><title>Cohort Analysis of Online Travel Information Search Behavior: 1995-2000</title><description>The objective of this study was to distinguish changes in online travel information search behavior among generational (baby boomer and Generation X) cohorts between 1995 and 2000. Although significant increases in travel information search behavior were found across all cohorts between the two periods, the study also found that older baby boomer cohorts reported greater increases in the likelihood of travel information search behavior than Generation Xers at large. This empirically validates the notion that boomers adopted the Internet earlier than ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:33:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/robertlischke/article/2869979</link><title>Consistency: a Factor that Links the Usability of</title><description>An underlying assumption of component-based software engineering for interactive systems is that the overall usability of a new assembled device mainly depends on the usability of its individual components. This paper challenges this assumption by presenting findings from a series of lab experiments in which 48 subjects operated several consumer devices. The experiments focussed on the effect inconsistency may have on the usability of individual components. The results indicate that... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:33:53">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5303/article/10858601</link><title>Citadel: a community platform for archiving travel data</title><description>The emergence of smart phones with embedded sensors has led to an explosion in the number of transport related research projects that leverage the widespread uptake of mobile devices. However, the process of collecting and managing travel-based sensor data in the field on a large-scale is difficult and resource-intensive. The process of obtaining a suitable dataset also provides an unnecessary distraction to researchers who are consequently unable to focus on the primary goals of their research such as gaining a better ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:34:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/datkin/article/911386</link><title>Consumption and Income Seasonality in Thailand</title><description>Many households in developing countries rely on seasonal agriculture for their incomes. This paper investigates whether household consumption expenditure tracks income across seasons. Using data from Thailand, I contrast the seasonal consumption patterns of households with different seasonal income patterns and estimate the responsiveness of seasonal consumption to seasonal income. I find little evidence that consumption tracks income over the course of the year. The findings suggest that observed seasonal consumption patterns are the result of seasonal variations in preferences or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:35:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/datkin/article/912084</link><title>Transport Infrastructure and Industrial Location: The Case of Thailand</title><description>This paper addresses the impact of transport infrastructure projects of manufacturing employment in Thai regions. After a theoretical review we consider the impact of various transport modes: road, rail and ports. We find that roads and ports have a positive impact on industrial location, although the size of the impact is modest. Labor appears to be a more important location factor in Thailand. For the analysis of the data, geographical information systems (GIS) appear to be a quite useful tool. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:35:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/katholt/article/5042972</link><title>Risk of travel-associated typhoid and paratyphoid fevers in various regions.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Although enteric fever (typhoid and paratyphoid fevers) is a major global public health problem, comparable data on the risks of contracting travel-associated enteric fever in various regions of the world are scarce. METHODS: From the Swedish database on notifiable communicable diseases, we retrieved all case records from 1997 to 2003 on typhoid and paratyphoid fevers. The data set was compared with data on travel patterns obtained from a comprehensive travel database with information from interviews with more than 16,000 Swedish ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>