<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:36:34" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:36:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jphekman/article/2867503</link><title>Hormones as indicators of stress</title><description>Animal welfare is of increasing importance and absence of chronic stress is one of its prerequisites. During stress, various endocrine responses are involved to improve the fitness of the individual. The front-line hormones to overcome stressful situations are the glucocorticoids and catecholamines. These hormones are determined as a parameter of adrenal activity and thus of disturbance. The concentration of glucocorticoids (or their metabolites) can be measured in various body fluids or excreta. Above all, fecal samples offer the advantage that they ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:37:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/worrawanwan/article/2721059</link><title>An assessment of laboratory mouse welfare in UK animal units</title><description>The welfare of conventional stock laboratory mice has been assessed in 46 UK animal units using an expert-defined welfare assessment protocol containing 119 measures of mouse welfare. These were recorded using a questionnaire and observations made during a one-day visit to each unit. The standard of mouse welfare was considered to be good with widespread use of substrate and nesting material and space allowances in most cases well above the minimum recommended levels. Education and training was available and encouraged by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:38:03">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5457/article/2902558</link><title>Applying animal learning theory: training captive animals to comply with veterinary and husbandry procedures</title><description>Animals within zoo environments are learning continuously: they learn signals that predict when food is going to arrive or that the presence of a certain person means that something unpleasant may happen. They may learn to control their environment and care-givers: for example, they may learn that if they perform a particular behaviour (eg repetitive behaviour) they will receive a reward (ie food or attention from a caregiver). Using standard operant conditioning and classical conditioning techniques we can easily modify the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:38:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EEsterling/article/12096934</link><title>Impact of consumption of animal products on cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and cancer in developed countries</title><description>Meat and milk represent an energy-dense, protein-rich food source that also contributes significantly to the required intake of a range of micronutrients. With increasing economic prosperity, populations tend to increase their consumption of such animal products. However, in the longer established “developed” countries, there has been a significant shift from red meat and full-fat milk toward poultry and fat-reduced dairy products. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:38:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/PoloVet/article/1426250</link><title>The journey to animal welfare improvement</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:39:47">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5457/article/2867491</link><title>Evaluation of welfare state based on interpretation of multiple indices</title><description>Welfare is a multidimensional construct and its quantification is of major scientific, societal and economic importance in veterinary medicine. The construction of indices that measure welfare validly and reliably remains a considerable challenge. A general methodology for constructing welfare indices can be adapted from human medicine (in particular, from methodologies to assess Quality of Life [QoL]) and modified to reflect the fact that all assessments of animal welfare must be observer-based. The methodology is based on the creation of individual, composite ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:40:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rosemaryannerodd/article/5116778</link><title>Public opinion on UK milk marketing and dairy cow welfare</title><description>Interview questionnaires were administered to the general public in central Scotland and northern England during summer 2007 to investigate consumer awareness of UK dairy production methods, welfare issues and recognition of 'quality assurance' product logos. Fifty percent of respondents gave UK dairy animal welfare a positive rating. Recognition of individual quality assurance logos was poor and 75% of respondents stated that they did not intentionally seek to buy products with any of the logos. Respondents' perceptions of good dairy welfare included: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:40:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/oinkies09/article/3943765</link><title>Painful dilemmas: the ethics of animal-based pain research</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:41:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jenmy/article/1426218</link><title>Bridging consumer perception and on-farm assessment of animal welfare</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:42:30">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6039559</link><title>Stakeholder, citizen and consumer interests in farm animal welfare</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>