<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:43:00" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:43:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/stephenmillerrichard/article/11863258</link><title>Arizona geology</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:43:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mrobles/article/10540379</link><title>Magnitudes and Timing of Seasonal Peak Snowpack Water Equivalents in Arizona: A Preliminary Study of the Possible Effects of Recent Climatic Change</title><description>ABSTRACT Field measurements and computer-based predictions suggest that the magnitudes of seasonal peak snowpack water equivalents are becoming less and the timing of these peaks is occurring earlier in the snowmelt-runoff season of the western United States. These changes in peak snowpack conditions have often been attributed to a warming of the regional climate. To determine if these changes are also occurring in Arizona, almost 75 years of water equivalent measurements on snow courses maintained by the U.S. Natural Resources Conservation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:44:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/emptiness-co/article/10111180</link><title>The Stanley Fish Reader (Blackwell Readers)</title><description>The Stanley Fish Reader assembles for the first time the best work of this brightest intellectual light. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:45:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bouffana/article/2899420</link><title>PASSIVE AND ACTIVE FLOW CONTROL BY SWIMMING FISHES AND MAMMALS</title><description>Abstract What mechanisms of flow control do animals use to enhance hydrodynamic performance? Animals are capable of manipulating flow around the body and appendages both passively and actively. Passive mechanisms rely on structural and morphological components of the body (i.e., humpback whale tubercles, riblets). Active flow control mechanisms use appendage or body musculature to directly generate wake flow structures or stiffen fins against external hydrodynamic loads. Fish can actively control fin curvature, displacement, and area. The vortex wake shed by the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:46:39">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5179385</link><title>Groundwater water treatment for iron and manganese reduction and fish rearing studies applied to the design of the Ruth Burnett Sport Fish Hatchery, Fairbanks, Alaska</title><description>Studies at the Fairbanks Experimental Fish Hatchery (FEFH) were conducted to investigate the operational characteristics of media filtration groundwater treatment for iron and manganese reduction, water reuse and recirculation technologies for fish rearing, and conditions of fish gill tissue during rearing. Results were used to aid in the design and planned operation of the Ruth Burnett Sport Fish Hatchery (RBSFH), currently under construction in Fairbanks, Alaska. Under a two-stage filtration scenario, with hydraulic loading rates of 0.39 and 0.43 cm/s for Stages ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:47:21">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14582/article/12728310</link><title>Sexual behavior in fish</title><description>Reproductive strategies differ remarkably among fish species, including the means by which fish find and attract mates, secure breeding sites and care for their eggs and offspring. These range from simple release of eggs and sperm in the water column to elaborate mating ceremonies, leading to fertilization in a protected place or inside the female body. The diversity in fish reproductive behavior is controlled by a complex neuroendocrine system that lends itself to future research not only in basic biology but ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:48:35">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7474488</link><title>Development, characterization, conservation and storage of fish cell lines: a review</title><description>Cell lines provide an important biological tool for carrying out investigations into physiology, virology, toxicology, carcinogenesis and transgenics. Teleost fish cell lines have been developed from a broad range of tissues such as ovary, fin, swim bladder, heart, spleen, liver, eye muscle, vertebrae, brain, skin. One hundred and twenty-four new fish cell lines from different fish species ranging from grouper to eel have been reported since the last review by Fryer and Lannan (J Tissue Culture Methods 16: 87–94, 1994). Among ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:49:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14582/article/12728315</link><title>Behavioral assessment of the visual capabilities of fish</title><description>A rich repertoire of behavioral methods is available to assay visual function and its adaptive changes in fish. Most methods are available for adults but some can be applied to larvae, enabling powerful genetic and imaging approaches particularly in zebrafish. Some methods involve training – from quick classical conditioning to sophisticated training – others profitably use spontaneous reflexes or naturally occurring behaviors that rely on accurate vision. Here, we introduce an assortment of these behavioral methods to describe how behavior has ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:50:01">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14582/article/12728306</link><title>Endocrine regulation of fish reproduction</title><description>Brain neurohormones and gonadal steroids regulate the production and release of follicle-stimulating hormone (FSH) and luteinizing hormone (LH) from the pituitary gland. Each of these gonadotropins is composed of a shared α-subunit and a distinct β-subunit specific to either FSH or LH. The LH receptor in the gonads is specific to LH, while the FSH receptor is less specific and may be activated by LH as well. FSH predominates during the early phases of gonadal development and vitellogenesis in the females ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:50:43">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14055/article/2551928</link><title>A test of the sequential assessment game: fighting in the cichlid fish</title><description>Many species have a repertoire of behaviour patterns that are used in contests over resources. It is likely that the function of these behaviour patterns is the assessment of asymmetries between contestants in physical variables (e.g. size or strength). Theoretical models of fighting behaviour such as the war of attrition and the hawk-dove game do not incorporate any behavioural mechanisms allowing assessment, and, therefore, yield no predictions about the use of behaviour patterns. In a sequential assessment game, on the other ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>