<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:10:29" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:10:37">http://www.citeulike.org/group/12231/article/10848033</link><title>Modeling and assessment of combined GPS/GLONASS precise point positioning</title><description>A combination of GPS and GLONASS observations can offer improved reliability, availability and accuracy for precise point positioning (PPP). We present and analyze a combined GPS/GLONASS PPP model, including both functional and stochastic components. Numerical comparison and analysis are conducted with respect to PPP based on only GPS or GLONASS observations to demonstrate the benefits of the combined GPS/GLONASS PPP. The observation residuals are analyzed for more appropriate stochastic modeling for observations from different navigation systems. An analysis is also made ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:11:44">http://www.citeulike.org/group/12231/article/10428856</link><title>GPS-PWV estimation and validation with radiosonde data and numerical weather prediction model in Antarctica</title><description>Three permanent GPS tracking stations in the trans Antarctic mountain deformation (TAMDEF) network were used to estimate precipitable water vapor (PWV) using measurement series covering the period of 2002–2005. TAMDEF is a National Science Foundation funded joint project between The Ohio State University and the United States Geological Survey. The TAMDEF sites with the longest GPS data spans considered in this research are Franklin Island East (FIE0), the International GNSS Service site McMurdo (MCM4), and Cape Roberts (ROB1). For the experiment, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:12:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/snedkov/article/1207532</link><title>Comparing GPS-only with GPS + GLONASS positioning in a regional permanent GNSS network</title><description>Within the regional EUREF Permanent Network (EPN) all positioning is purely based on GPS. This paper investigates, using the Bernese GNSS analysis software, the influence of adding GLONASS observations to the EPN processing using fixed orbits from the International GNSS Service (IGS) as well as from the CODE analysis centre. The GPS-only coordinates and GPS + GLONASS coordinates will be compared and the change in their repeatabilities will be investigated. The influence of the used orbits will also be outlined. The results show ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:12:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fish2000/article/1477362</link><title>Absolute Positioning with Single-Frequency GPS Receivers</title><description>The use of precise post-processed satellite orbits and satellite clock corrections in absolute positioning, using one GPS receiver only, has proven to be an accurate alternative to the more commonly used differential techniques for many applications in georeferencing. The absolute approach is capable of centimeter accuracy when using state-of-the-art, dual-frequency GPS receivers. When using observations from single-frequency receivers, however, the accuracy, especially in height, decreases. The obvious reason for this degradation in accuracy is the effect of unmodeled ionospheric delay. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:13:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/snedkov/article/8927450</link><title>An experimental performance analysis of real-time kinematic positioning with NASA’s Internet-Based Global Differential GPS</title><description>The Global Differential GPS (GDGPS) system developed by JPL aims at seamless global real-time positioning at the dm accuracy level for dual-frequency receivers either fixed or mobile, anywhere and at any time. The GDGPS system relies on GPS data transmitted in real-time to a central processing center at JPL from a global network of permanently operating GPS dual-frequency receivers. At the processing center, the Internet-based Global Differential GPS (IGDG) system, the heart of JPL’s GDGPS, generates and disseminates over the open ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:13:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/snedkov/article/8927507</link><title>A combined algorithm of improving INS error modeling and sensor measurements for accurate INS/GPS navigation</title><description>Although the integrated system of a differential global positioning system (DGPS) and an inertial navigation system (INS) had been widely used in many geodetic navigation applications, it has sometimes a major limitation. This limitation is associated with the frequent occurrence of DGPS outages caused by GPS signal blockages in certain situations (urban areas, high trees, tunnels, etc.). In the standard mechanization of INS/DGPS navigation, the DGPS is used for positioning while the INS is used for attitude determination. In case of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:14:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kpal/article/11069244</link><title>Automated GPS processing for global total electron content data</title><description>A software package known as MIT Automated Processing of GPS (MAPGPS) has been developed to automate the processing of GPS data into global total electron density (TEC) maps. The goal of the MAPGPS software is to produce reliable TEC data automatically, although not yet in real time. Observations are used from all available GPS receivers during all geomagnetic conditions where data has been successfully collected. In this paper, the architecture of the MAPGPS software is described. Particular attention is given to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:15:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/snedkov/article/8927520</link><title>GPS RTK positioning via Internet-based 3G CDMA2000/1X wireless technology</title><description>The latest evolution in digital wireless technology, third-generation (3G) Code Division Multiple Access/Single Carrier (CDMA2000/1X) wireless network, is applicable for transmitting real-time kinematic (RTK) GPS correction messages. Fast and reliable, publicly available wireless networks, combined with highly accessible Internet connectivity, allows the multicasting of messages to mobile users, who are no longer restricted to traditional private UHF wireless networks. Nationwide public wireless network systems continue to expand and can provide an inexpensive infrastructure for the emerging multi-reference network system. Transmission performance ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:15:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/snedkov/article/2772212</link><title>Smoothing GPS carrier phase double differences using inertial measurements for high performance applications</title><description>This paper will describe an enhancement to the GPS double difference carrier phase measurements on a single airborne platform by smoothing them with inertial measurements while preserving the dynamic bandwidth. This enhancement will reduce the impact of carrier phase multipath and carrier phase noise on baseline determination between multiple antennas on an aircraft when in flight. This type of measurement system has numerous applications where platform pointing and relative body motion must be determined at the mm-level for applications such as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:16:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kpal/article/11328051</link><title>Multipath Mitigation of Continuous GPS Measurements Using an Adaptive Filter</title><description>Though state-of-the-art dual-frequency receivers are employed in the continuous Global Positioning System (CGPS) arrays, the CGPS coordinate time series are typically very noisy due to the effects of atmospheric biases, multipath, receiver noise, and so on, with multipath generally being considered the major noise contributor. An adaptive finite-duration impulse response filter, based on a least-mean-square algorithm, has been developed to derive a relatively noise-free time series from the CGPS results. Furthermore, this algorithm is suitable for real-time applications. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>