<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:23:40" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:23:42">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EzosSchmidt1/article/3630659</link><title>Gene Nomenclature System for Rice</title><description>Abstract  The Committee on Gene Symbolization, Nomenclature and Linkage (CGSNL) of the Rice Genetics Cooperative has revised the gene nomenclature system for rice (Oryza) to take advantage of the completion of the rice genome sequence and the emergence of new methods for detecting, characterizing, and describing genes in the biological community. This paper outlines a set of standard procedures for describing genes based on DNA, RNA, and protein sequence information that have been annotated and mapped on the sequenced genome assemblies, as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:24:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/drjohnhammond/article/10049332</link><title>mRNA-Seq Reveals a Comprehensive Transcriptome Profile of Rice under Phosphate Stress</title><description>Plants have developed several morphological and physiological strategies to adapt to phosphate stress. We analyzed the inducible transcripts associated with phosphate starvation and over-abundant phosphate supply to characterize the transcriptome in rice seedlings using the mRNA-Seq strategy. Fifty-three million reads obtained from 16 libraries under various phosphate stress and recovery treatments were uniquely mapped to the rice genome. Transcripts identified specifically tagged to 40,574 (root) and 39,748 (shoot) Rice Annotation Project (RAP) transcripts. Additionally, we detected uniquely 10,388 transcripts with no ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:24:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/drjohnhammond/article/5665931</link><title>Rice Root Genetic Architecture: Meta-analysis from a Drought QTL Database</title><description>During the last 10 years, a large number of quantitative trait loci (QTLs) controlling rice root morphological parameters have been detected in several mapping populations by teams interested in improving drought resistance in rice. Compiling these data could be extremely helpful in identifying candidate genes by positioning consensus QTLs with more precision through meta-QTL analysis. We extracted information from 24 published papers on QTLs controlling 29 root parameters including root number, maximum root length, root thickness, root/shoot ratio, and root penetration index. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:25:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/drjohnhammond/article/6000068</link><title>Stress Response Versus Stress Tolerance: A Transcriptome Analysis of Two Rice Lines Contrasting in Tolerance to Phosphorus Deficiency</title><description>Transcriptional profiling has identified genes associated with adaptive responses to phosphorus (P) deficiency; however, distinguishing stress response from tolerance has been difficult. We report gene expression patterns in two rice genotypes (Nipponbare and NIL6-4 which carries a major QTL for P deficiency tolerance (Pup1)) grown in soil with/without P fertilizer. We tested the hypotheses that tolerance of NIL6-4 is associated with (1) internal P remobilization/redistribution; (2) enhanced P solubilization and/or acquisition; and (3) root growth modifications that maximize P interception. Genes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:25:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SZappala/article/9276090</link><title>The Endosperm Morphology of Rice and its Wild Relatives as Observed by Scanning Electron Microscopy</title><description>While cultivated rice, Oryza sativa, is arguably the world’s most important cereal crop, there is little comparative morphological information available for the grain of rice wild relatives. In this study, the endosperm of 16 rice wild relatives were compared to O. sativa subspecies indica and O. sativa subspecies japonica using scanning electron microscopy. Although the aleurone, starch granules, protein bodies and endosperm cell shapes of the cultivated and non-cultivated species were similar, several differences were observed. The starch granules of some ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:26:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lecosepsci/article/3630666</link><title>Rice Metabolomics</title><description>Metabolomics is a recently developed technology for comprehensive analysis of metabolites in organisms. Plant metabolites that are produced for the growth, development, and chemical defense of plants against climatic alterations or natural predators are also useful to us as nutrients or medicines; hence, it is important to comprehend the amounts and varieties of plant metabolites. Besides providing an understanding of the metabolic state in plants under various circumstances, metabolomic techniques are applicable to the clarification of the functions of unknown genes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:26:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/arunswarnaraj/article/3630661</link><title>The Relevance of Rice</title><description>Research into rice—the world’s most important food crop—is crucial for the development of technologies that will increase productivity for farmers who rely on rice for their livelihood. This is particularly the case throughout the developing countries of Asia and is also true for much of Latin America and, increasingly, Africa. The benefits of such increased productivity will flow through to rice-growing countries’ landless rural and urban poor, all of whom (1) are net consumers of rice and (2) spend a large ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:27:01">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10695097</link><title>Nomenclature report on rice WRKY's - Conflict regarding gene names and its solution</title><description>Background Since whole genome sequences of rice were made publically accessible, the number of articles on new rice genes has increased remarkably. The Committee on Gene Symbolization, Nomenclature and Linkage (CGSNL) of the Rice Genetics Cooperative published the gene nomenclature system for rice and encouraged researchers to follow the rules before publishing their results. The CGSNL provides an on-line registration system for newly identified rice genes to prevent conflicts and/or duplication of gene name in journal articles. Findings Recently, the CGSNL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:27:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/feralryan/article/278280</link><title>The map-based sequence of the rice genome</title><description>Rice, one of the world's most important food plants, has important syntenic relationships with the other cereal species and is a model plant for the grasses. Here we present a map-based, finished quality sequence that covers 95% of the 389 Mb genome, including virtually all of the euchromatin and two complete centromeres. A total of 37,544 non-transposable-element-related protein-coding genes were identified, of which 71% had a putative homologue in Arabidopsis. In a reciprocal analysis, 90% of the Arabidopsis proteins had a putative ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:28:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/SZappala/article/3829652</link><title>Molecular Genetics of Rice Root Development</title><description>Plant roots have a large range of functions, including acquisition of water and nutrients, as well as structural support. Dissecting the genetic and molecular mechanisms controlling rice root development is critical for the development of new rice ideotypes that are better adapted to adverse conditions and for the production of sustainably achieved rice yield potential. Most knowledge regarding the gene networks involved in root development has been accumulated in the model dicotyledon plant species Arabidopsis thaliana . Rice, the model monocotyledon ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>