<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:41:54" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:41:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/abrentnall/article/8232579</link><title>The National Lung Screening Trial: Overview and Study Design</title><description>The National Lung Screening Trial (NLST) is a randomized multicenter study comparing low-dose helical computed tomography (CT) with chest radiography in the screening of older current and former heavy smokers for early detection of lung cancer, which is the leading cause of cancer-related death in the United States. Five-year survival rates approach 70% with surgical resection of stage IA disease; however, more than 75% of individuals have incurable locally advanced or metastatic disease, the latter having a 5-year survival of less ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:42:34">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13751/article/7532370</link><title>Technology: Software bugs cost big bucks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:43:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/matthewtam/article/10055982</link><title>Endovascular aneurysm repair versus open repair in patients with abdominal aortic aneurysm (EVAR trial 1): randomised controlled trial.</title><description>Although endovascular aneurysm repair (EVAR) has a lower 30-day operative mortality than open repair, the long-term results of EVAR are uncertain. We instigated EVAR trial 1 to compare these two treatments in terms of mortality, durability, health-related quality of life (HRQL), and costs for patients with large abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:43:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/matthewtam/article/10055984</link><title>Endovascular aneurysm repair and outcome in patients unfit for open repair of abdominal aortic aneurysm (EVAR trial 2): randomised controlled trial.</title><description>Endovascular aneurysm repair (EVAR) to exclude abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) was introduced for patients of poor health status considered unfit for major surgery. We instigated EVAR trial 2 to identify whether EVAR improves survival compared with no intervention in patients unfit for open repair of aortic aneurysm. We did a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:44:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/8145516</link><title>B vitamins in patients with recent transient ischaemic attack or stroke in the VITAmins TO Prevent Stroke (VITATOPS) trial: a randomised, double-blind, parallel, placebo-controlled trial.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Epidemiological studies suggest that raised plasma concentrations of total homocysteine might be a risk factor for major vascular events. Whether lowering total homocysteine with B vitamins prevents major vascular events in patients with previous stroke or transient ischaemic attack is unknown. We aimed to assess whether the addition of once-daily supplements of B vitamins to usual medical care would lower total homocysteine and reduce the combined incidence of non-fatal stroke, non-fatal myocardial infarction, and death attributable to vascular causes in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:44:45">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9982200</link><title>Design, history and results of the Thiazolidinedione Intervention with vitamin D Evaluation (TIDE) randomised controlled trial</title><description>Aims/objective Conflicting data regarding cardiovascular effects of thiazolidinediones (TZDs) and extra-skeletal effects of vitamin D supported the need for a definitive trial. The Thiazolidinedione Intervention with vitamin D Evaluation (TIDE ) trial aimed to assess the effects of TZDs (rosiglitazone and pioglitazone) on cardiovascular outcomes and the effects of vitamin D (cholecalciferol) on cancers and mortality. Methods A large multicentre 3 × 2 factorial double-blind placebo-controlled randomised trial recruited from outpatient primary care and specialty clinics in 33 countries. From June ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:45:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zmarty/article/8429198</link><title>Identifying Differences in News Coverage between Cultural/Ethnic Groups</title><description>Large-scale analysis over historical news corpora provides us with unique opportunities to examine sociological issues with respect to local and mass media. In particular, we combine the Lydia named entity recognition system with an name-based ethnicity classification engine to examine issues of ethnic and geocentric sentiment/coverage bias in newspapers. We describe new methods for ethnicity and nationality detection for news entities (people), and build on this to identify interesting temporal, geospatial, and association trends in the coverage with respect to 13 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:45:48">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4746242</link><title>Rationale, design, and baseline characteristics of the Acetylcystein for Contrast-Induced nephropaThy (ACT) Trial: a pragmatic randomized controlled trial to evaluate the efficacy of acetylcysteine for the prevention of contrast-induced nephropathy</title><description>Background: Aceltylcysteine has been evaluated in several small trials as a means of reducing the risk of contrast-induced nephropathy (CIN), however systematic reviews of these studies do not provide conclusive answers. Therefore, a large randomized controlled trial (RCT) is needed to provide a reliable answer as to whether acetylcysteine is effective in decreasing the risk of CIN in high-risk patients undergoing angiographic procedures. Methods: ACT is a RCT of acetylcysteine versus placebo in 2,300 patients at-risk for CIN undergoing an intravascular angiographic procedure. The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:46:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/2764302</link><title>Effects of Ramipril and Rosiglitazone on Cardiovascular and Renal Outcomes in People With Impaired Glucose Tolerance or Impaired Fasting Glucose: Results of the Diabetes REduction Assessment with ramipril and rosiglitazone Medication (DREAM) trial</title><description>OBJECTIVE--Impaired glucose tolerance (IGT) and/or impaired fasting glucose (IFG) are risk factors for diabetes, cardiovascular disease (CVD), and kidney disease. We determined the effects of ramipril and rosiglitazone on combined and individual CVD and renal outcomes in people with IGT and/or IFG in the Diabetes REduction Assessment With ramipril and rosiglitazone Medication (DREAM) trial. RESEARCH DESIGN AND METHODS--A total of 5,269 people aged [≥]30 years, with IGT and/or IFG without known CVD or renal insufficiency, were randomized to 15 mg/day ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:47:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MaineC/article/5043997</link><title>Meme-tracking and the dynamics of the news cycle</title><description>Tracking new topics, ideas, and "memes" across the Web has been an issue of considerable interest. Recent work has developed methods for tracking topic shifts over long time scales, as well as abrupt spikes in the appearance of particular named entities. However, these approaches are less well suited to the identification of content that spreads widely and then fades over time scales on the order of days - the time scale at which we perceive news and events. We develop a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>