<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:55:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:55:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/7058036</link><title>Gene-based therapy in prostate cancer.</title><description>Prostate cancer is one of the commonest causes of illness and death from cancer. Radical prostatectomy, radiotherapy, and hormonal therapy are the main conventional treatments. However, gene therapy is emerging as a promising adjuvant to conventional strategies, and several clinical trials are in progress. Here, we outline several approaches to gene therapy for prostate cancer that have been investigated. Methods of gene delivery are described, particularly those that have commonly been used in research on prostate cancer. We discuss efforts to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:56:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/556452</link><title>Molecular pathology of prostate cancer: the key to identifying new biomarkers of disease.</title><description>Microarray technology has recently accelerated the study of the molecular events involved in prostate cancer, offering the prospect of more precise prognosis and new therapeutic strategies. This review summarises current knowledge of the molecular pathology of prostate cancer. The expression and function of numerous genes have been shown to be altered in prostate cancer. Many of these genes are involved in cell cycle regulation, steroid hormone metabolism or regulation of gene expression. The mechanisms by which androgen independence arises are discussed, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:56:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cancerresearch/article/6756257</link><title>Achieving hypoxia-inducible gene expression in tumors.</title><description>Hypoxia is an inevitable feature of solid tumors and a common cause of treatment failure. Hypoxia acts as a trigger to genetic instability, apoptosis and possibly metastases. The adaptive response to cellular hypoxia involves the modulation of the synthesis of multiple proteins controlling processes such as glucose homeostasis, angiogenesis, vascular permeability and inflammation. The hypoxia responsive element (HRE) sequences isolated from oxygen-responsive genes have been shown to selectively induce gene expression in response to hypoxia when placed upstream of a promoter. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:57:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nbr/article/5398217</link><title>Saint Paul and the New Man</title><description>doi: 10.1086/599591 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:58:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/13112922</link><title>Jeremiah Hackett , ed. A Companion to Meister Eckhart . Brill’s Companions to the Christian Tradition 36. Leiden: Brill, 2013. xxx + 782 pp. $271. ISBN: 978-90-04-18347-6.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:59:07">http://www.citeulike.org/group/596/article/439310</link><title>Secrets of Hollywood Special Effects</title><description>Whether you are a working professional, a performance student or just interested in the techniques behind the effects, Secrets of Hollywood Special Effects provides the insights you've been looking for. This text is the comprehensive guide to special effects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Many different kinds of effects are covered, including chemicals, pyrotechnics, weapons, levitation and weather. Written by a recognized expert in the field, this book contains over 200 illustrations and diagrams providing in depth coverage of every detail. Case studies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:59:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cinnazimt/article/7131535</link><title>Performativity, Citationality, Ritualization</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:00:27">http://www.citeulike.org/article/12274312</link><title>Paul Hollywood's Bread</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:01:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cannedAir/article/1001417</link><title>The Classical Hollywood Cinema: Film Style &amp; Mode of Production to 1960</title><description>&lt;P&gt;How films are conceived,planned, and produced leaves a mark upon the films, directly and structurally. The relations between film style and mode of production are, according to the authors, reciprocal and mutually influencing. The authors trace such topics as style, economics, and technology over time, demonstrating how significant changes occurrred in Hollywood from the earliest days through the sixties.&lt;/P&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:01:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/randomaxes/article/1026829</link><title>Genre and Hollywood</title><description>&lt;P&gt;In this comprehensive introduction to the study of genre, Steve Neale discusses all the major concepts, theories and accounts of Hollywood and genre, as well as the key genres which theorists have written about, from horror to the Western. Taking issue with much genre theory, which has provided only a partial and misleading account of Hollywood's output, Neale calls for broader and more flexible conceptions of genre, for the nature and range of Hollywood's films to be looked at in more ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>