<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7465">xman sequel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:12:56" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:12:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/umit/article/3128945</link><title>xMAN: extreme MApping of OligoNucleotides</title><description>BACKGROUND:The ability to rapidly map millions of oligonucleotide fragments to a reference genome is crucial to many high throughput genomic technologies.RESULTS:We propose an intuitive and efficient algorithm, titled extreme MApping of OligoNucleotide (xMAN), to rapidly map millions of oligonucleotide fragments to a genome of any length. By converting oligonucleotides to integers hashed in RAM, xMAN can scan through genomes using bit shifting operation and achieve at least one order of magnitude speed increase over existing tools. xMAN can map the 42 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:13:28">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5344006</link><title>A tetrathiafulvalene–perylene diimide conjugate prepared via click chemistry</title><description>A new tetrathiafulvalene (TTF)–perylene diimide (PDI) conjugate is prepared from an azide-functionalized TTF and an acetylenic PDI employing a Cu(I)-catalyzed Huisgen-Meldal-Sharpless reaction (“click chemistry”). Thus, the TTF donor and PDI acceptor units are linked together by a 1,2,3-triazole unit. The molecules are found to assemble on a mica surface, forming fibrilar structures. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:14:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pilho/article/752976</link><title>SEQUEL: A structured English query language</title><description>In this paper we present the data manipulation facility for a structured English query language (SEQUEL) which can be used for accessing data in an integrated relational data base. Without resorting to the concepts of bound variables and quantifiers SEQUEL identifies a set of simple operations on tabular structures, which can be shown to be of equivalent power to the first order predicate calculus. A SEQUEL user is presented with a consistent set of keyword English templates which reflect how people ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:16:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9292718</link><title>On the thermal expansion of molecules: a sequel</title><description>In a recent article (Varga Z, Hargittai M, Bartell LS (2011) Struct Chem 22: 111–121), we showed with the example of lanthanide triiodide that contrary to previous claims by others, simple metal trihalide molecules do expand with increasing temperature. This sequel is meant to strengthen our argument and the validity of the method we used besides correcting a numerical error. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:17:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davidmam/article/10779809</link><title>SEQuel: improving the accuracy of genome assemblies</title><description>Motivation: Assemblies of next-generation sequencing (NGS) data, although accurate, still contain a substantial number of errors that need to be corrected after the assembly process. We develop SEQuel, a tool that corrects errors (i.e. insertions, deletions and substitution errors) in the assembled contigs. Fundamental to the algorithm behind SEQuel is the positional de Bruijn graph, a graph structure that models k-mers within reads while incorporating the approximate positions of reads into the model.Results: SEQuel reduced the number of small insertions and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:19:19">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2166805</link><title>Sequel</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:20:35">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9662848</link><title>The long-term box office performance of sequel movies</title><description>With a 26-year-long database of nationally distributed movies, we estimate the prevalence and effectiveness of sequels over time, while controlling for other factors that might influence demand. In particular, we examine whether the effectiveness of a strategy increases over time (possibly due to managerial learning) or decreases (possibly because its effectiveness is competed away or because of consumer satiation). After taking into account both supply side and demand side effects by using simultaneous equations, we find that sequels have a positive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:21:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3630641</link><title>The effect of sequel symptoms and signs of Complex Regional Pain Syndrome type 1 on upper extremity disability and quality of life</title><description>Abstract  Although properly treated, patients with Complex Regional Pain Syndrome type 1 (CRPS type 1) of upper limb may continue to have sequel signs and symptoms of the disease in long-term. The aim of this study is to analyse the effect of the sequel findings of CRPS type 1 on upper limb disability and quality of life. Thirty patients with CRPS type 1 of the upper extremity were re-evaluated for the sequel sign and symptoms of CRPS type 1 after 18 months (8–60 months). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:22:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/peterheng/article/4030748</link><title>Towards the ultimate conservative difference scheme. V - A second-order sequel to Godunov's method</title><description>A method of second-order accuracy is described for integrating the equations of ideal compressible flow. The method is based on the integral conservation laws and is dissipative, so that it can be used across shocks. The heart of the method is a one-dimensional Lagrangean scheme that may be regarded as a second-order sequel to Godunov's method. The second-order accuracy is achieved by taking the distributions of the state quantities inside a gas slab to be linear, rather than uniform as in Godunov's method. The Lagrangean results are remapped with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7465-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7465_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:22:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/peterheng/article/3783011</link><title>Towards the Ultimate Conservative Difference Scheme V. A Second-Order Sequel to Godunov's Method</title><description>A method of second-order accuracy is described for integrating the equations of ideal compressible flow. The method is based on the integral conservation laws and is dissipative, so that it can be used across shocks. The heart of the method is a one-dimensional Lagrangean scheme that may be regarded as a second-order sequel to Godunov's method. The second-order accuracy is achieved by taking the distributions of the state quantities inside a gas slab to be linear, rather than uniform as in ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>