<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:23:44" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:23:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nfarring/article/5750737</link><title>Optical Interconnects in Next Generation Data Centers: An End to End View</title><description>Bandwidth hungry applications such as real-time video processing are expected to strain data center networking infrastructure. Optics enables massive data transmission rates: in telecom settings researchers have demonstrated rates in excess of 20 Tbps, however, the data center presents a different set of challenges. Low cost, low power dissipation, low latency, small physical size, and the ability to integrate with mainstream silicon electronics are more important than the ability to transmit signals over long distances, the traditional telecoms focus. We seek ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:25:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/covertaffairs31/article/6601212</link><title>The association of use of sunbeds with cutaneous malignant melanoma and other skin cancers: A systematic review.</title><description>Exposure to solar ultraviolet (UV) radiation is a known cause of skin cancer. Sunbed use represents an increasingly frequent source of artificial UV exposure in light-skinned populations. To assess the available evidence of the association between sunbed use and cutaneous malignant melanoma (melanoma) and other skin cancers, a systematic review of the literature till March 2006 on epidemiological and biological studies on sunbed use was performed in Pubmed, ISI Web of Science, Embase, Pascal, Cochrane library, Lilacs and Medcarib. Search for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:26:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/7887826</link><title>Consensus document on controversial issues in the treatment of complicated skin and skin-structure infections.</title><description>BACKGROUND: Complicated skin and skin-structure infections (cSSSI), including surgical site infections (SSI), cellulitis, and abscesses, have been extensively studied, but controversial issues still exist. CONTROVERSIAL ISSUES: The aim of this GISIG (Gruppo Italiano di Studio sulle Infezioni Gravi) working group - a panel of multidisciplinary experts - was to define recommendations for the following controversial issues: (1) What is the efficacy of topical negative pressure wound treatment as compared to standard of care in the treatment of severe surgical site infections, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:26:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/10911270</link><title>Comparison between metallic carbon nanotube and copper future VLSI nano-interconnects</title><description>This paper addresses the problem of scaling interconnects to nanometric dimensions in future VLSI applications. Traditional copper interconnects are compared to innovative ones made by bundles of metallic carbon nanotubes. A new model is presented to describe propagation along CNT bundles, in the framework of the classical transmission line theory. A possible future scaled CNT bundle microstrip is analyzed and compared to a conventional microstrip. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:28:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hengel2/article/2207590</link><title>Image-Based BRDF Measurement</title><description>We present a new image-based process for measuring the bidirectional reflectance of homogeneous surfaces rapidly, completely, and accurately. For simple sample shapes (spheres and cylinders) the method requires only a digital camera and a stable light source. Adding a 3D scanner allows a wide class of curved near-convex objects to be measured. With measurements for a variety of materials from paints to human skin, we demonstrate the new method's ability to achieve high resolution and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:29:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/10910396</link><title>Metallic Carbon Nanotube Interconnects, Part II: a Transmission Line Model</title><description>In this paper a transmission line model is derived to describe the propagation along single-wall carbon nanotubes, candidate to be used as interconnects in nanoelectronics applications. The model is obtained in a consistent way from a fluid model of the electron conduction along such a nanostructure. The per-unit-length parameters are strongly dependent on the effects related to the electron inertia and the quantum fluid pressure. The values of the signal propagation velocity, characteristic impedance and characteristic damping of the obtained transmission ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:30:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/victor_rodriguez_toro/article/10911198</link><title>Metallic Carbon Nanotube Interconnects, Part I: a Fluid Model and a 3D Integral Formulation</title><description>This paper illustrates the inclusion, in a 3D integral formulation of Maxwell equations, of a fluid model for the study of the electrodynamics of metallic carbon nanotubes in the frequency domain. The effective conduction electrons are modeled as an infinitesimally thin cylindrical layer of compressible fluid, whose dynamics are described by means of the linearized Euler's equation. The resulting integral equations are solved numerically by the finite element method, using the facet elements and the null-pinv decomposition. The proposed formulation is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:30:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/RAFielder/article/5770912</link><title>Skin surface lipid and skin friction: relation to age, sex and anatomical region.</title><description>Differences in the skin surface lipid content (SSL) and the dynamic friction coefficient (mu) were investigated with respect to age, sex, and anatomical region in 29 volunteers. The group consisted of (a) 7 young adult females (24.9 +/- 1.1 years old, mean +/- SD), (b) 7 old females (75.3 +/- 2.4 years old), (c) 7 young adult males (28.7 +/- 0.5 years old), and (d) 8 old males (73.8 +/- 1.9 years old). Measurements were obtained on 11 anatomical regions, namely, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:31:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nfarring/article/4369931</link><title>Rationale and challenges for optical interconnects to electronic chips</title><description>The various arguments for introducing optical interconnections to silicon CMOS chips are summarized, and the challenges for optical, optoelectronic, and integration technologies are discussed. Optics could solve many physical problems of interconnects, including precise clock distribution, system synchronization (allowing larger synchronous zones, both on-chip and between chips), bandwidth and density of long interconnections, and reduction of power dissipation. Optics may relieve a broad range of design problems, such as crosstalk, voltage isolation, wave reflection, impedence matching, and pin inductance. It may ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:31:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/freddan/article/4847144</link><title>Enclosed SU-8 and PDMS microchannels with integrated interconnects for chip-to-chip and world-to-chip connections</title><description>This paper presents the simulation, fabrication and testing of fluid-tight enclosed microchannels with integrated interconnects for modular snap-together chip-to-chip and world-to-chip connections. Components consisting of microchannels with integrated interconnect were fabricated in SU-8 photopolymer and polydimethylsiloxane (PDMS). Simulations were performed in ANSYS for component microchannels with chip-to-chip and world-to-chip interconnects in order to determine the expected flow profile and pressure drop. Components with world-to-chip structures were then experimentally pressurized to 252 kPa and 148 kPa for SU-8 and PDMS respectively, without ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>