<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:45:39" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:45:44">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10935/article/4952962</link><title>Climate change and biodiversity</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:46:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wqunit/article/12372866</link><title>Climate change in Queensland what the science is telling us 2010</title><description>http://www.ehp.qld.gov.au/climatechange/centre/pdf/climate-change-in-queensland-2010.pdf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:48:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/IIL/article/4955698</link><title>Technologies, policies and measures for mitigating climate change</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:49:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jsholtes/article/1277492</link><title>Climate Change 2007: The Physical Science Basis</title><description>The Climate Change 2007 volumes of the Fourth Assessment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) provide the most comprehensive and balanced assessment of climate change available. This IPCC Working Group I report brings us completely up-to-date on the full range of scientific aspects of climate change. Written by the world's leading experts, the IPCC volumes will again prove to be invaluable for researchers, students, and policymakers, and will form the standard reference works for policy decisions for government ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:50:49">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10935/article/5044750</link><title>Climate change impacts and adaptation : a Canadian perspective</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:51:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mfisk/article/1099588</link><title>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;Network Configuration Management via Model Finding</title><description>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;Complex, end-to-end network services are set up via the configuration method: each component has a finite number of configuration parameters each of which is set to a definite value. End-to-end network service requirements can be on connectivity, security, performance and fault-tolerance. However, there is a large conceptual gap between end-to-end requirements and detailed component configurations. To bridge this gap, a number of subsidiary requirements are created that constrain, for example, the protocols to be used, and the logical structures ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:52:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mfisk/article/1099585</link><title>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;Visualizing NetFlows for Security at Line Speed: The SIFT Tool Suite</title><description>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;The first step in improving Internet security is measurementsecurity events must be made visible. The irony in making this happen is that there is no lack of security measurement data, in fact, quite the opposite. However, making security manifest faces a major challenge: the large volume and multi-dimensional nature of security data typically obscures valuable security events. NCSA has developed a suite of tools that solves this problem and is making this software available to the Internet community. &lt;p&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:53:55">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16133/article/1277490</link><title>Climate Change 2007 - Impacts, Adaptation and Vulnerability: Working Group II contribution to the Fourth Assessment Report of the IPCC (Climate Change 2007)</title><description>The Climate Change 2007 volumes of the Fourth Assessment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) provide the most comprehensive and balanced assessment of climate change available. This IPCC Working Group II volume brings us completely up-to-date on the vulnerability of socio-economic and natural systems to climate change. Written by the world's leading experts, the IPCC volumes will again prove to be invaluable for researchers, students, and policymakers, and will form the standard reference works for policy decisions for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:55:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mfisk/article/1099589</link><title>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;About the Integration of Mac OS X Devices into a Centrally Managed UNIX Environment</title><description>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;The UNIX flavors in use today have so much in common that centralized management of UNIX systems has become almost standard. Since Mac OS X is based on BSD-UNIX it is a promising candidate for integration into a centrally managed UNIX environment. &lt;p&gt; Starting from generic administration concepts, this paper develops an integrated management concept that handles fully automated installation and configuration of hosts. The concept includes a centralized application management system for console and graphical Mac OS X ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:56:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ghunter/article/2909211</link><title>Effect of interstitial fluid on a granular flowing layer</title><description>A dominant aspect of granular flows is flow in thin surface layers. While an understanding of the dynamics of dry granular surface flow has begun to emerge, the case of flow when air is completely replaced by a liquid is largely unexplored. Experiments were performed using particle tracking velocimetry (PTV) in a quasi-two-dimensional rotating tumbler to measure the velocity field within the flowing layer of monodisperse spherical particles fully submerged in liquids, a granular slurry, for a range of Froude numbers, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>