<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7469">ibm thinkpad t43 change fan</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:57:10" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:57:14">http://www.citeulike.org/user/yezhenyu/article/9861216</link><title>Practical computer vision: Example techniques and challenges</title><description>Humans, as well as many living organisms, are gifted with the power of “seeing” and “understanding” the environment around them using their eyes. The ease with which humans process and understand the visual world is very deceiving and often prompts us to underestimate the effort and methods needed to build practical, effective, and inexpensive computer vision systems. In essence, humans have a 500-million-year head start due to evolution; it is extremely difficult at this point to build a computer vision system ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:58:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/11271838</link><title>IBM Scale out File Services: Reinventing network-attached storage</title><description>This paper focuses on the challenges of creating a scalable network-attached storage (NAS) filer with hundreds of nodes on top of the IBM General Parallel File System™ (GPFS™). The filer is created as a multiheaded data exporter over Ethernet and uses the Common Internet File System (CIFS) as implemented by the Samba open-source project and a Network File System (NFS) protocol server. Special focus is given to ensure the consistency of data in an efficient manner for applications that have complex ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:59:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/10686778</link><title>Decimal floating-point support on the IBM System z10 processor</title><description>The latest IBM zSeries® processor, the IBM System z10™ processor, provides hardware support for the decimal floating-point (DFP) facility that was introduced on the IBM System z9® processor. The z9® processor implements the facility with a mixture of low-level software and hardware assists. Recently, the IBM POWER6™ processor-based System p™ 570 server introduced a hardware implementation of the DFP facility. The latest zSeries processor includes a decimal floating-point unit based on the POWER6 processor DFP unit that has been enhanced to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:59:58">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1375736</link><title>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;Understanding and Addressing Blocking-Induced Network Server Latency</title><description>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;We investigate the origin and components of network server latency under various loads and find that filesystem-related kernel queues exhibit head-of-line blocking, which leads to bursty behavior in event delivery and process scheduling. In turn, these problems degrade the existing fairness and scheduling policies in the operating system, causing requests that could have been served in memory, with low latency, to unnecessarily wait on disk-bound requests. While this batching behavior only mildly affects throughput, it severely degrades latency. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:01:13">http://www.citeulike.org/group/10935/article/4952962</link><title>Climate change and biodiversity</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:01:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wqunit/article/12372866</link><title>Climate change in Queensland what the science is telling us 2010</title><description>http://www.ehp.qld.gov.au/climatechange/centre/pdf/climate-change-in-queensland-2010.pdf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:03:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/IIL/article/4955698</link><title>Technologies, policies and measures for mitigating climate change</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:03:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/9247748</link><title>A Rational approach to model-driven development</title><description>Models, modeling, and model transformation form the basis for a set of software development approaches that are known as model-driven development (MDD). Models are used in reasoning about a problem domain and the corresponding solution domain for some area of interest. In this paper, we explore model-driven approaches to the realization of solutions for today's enterprise systems. In particular, we describe the key elements of MDD as they have emerged from the support of IBM Rational® for model-driven approaches over more ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:04:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jsholtes/article/1277492</link><title>Climate Change 2007: The Physical Science Basis</title><description>The Climate Change 2007 volumes of the Fourth Assessment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) provide the most comprehensive and balanced assessment of climate change available. This IPCC Working Group I report brings us completely up-to-date on the full range of scientific aspects of climate change. Written by the world's leading experts, the IPCC volumes will again prove to be invaluable for researchers, students, and policymakers, and will form the standard reference works for policy decisions for government ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7469-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7469_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:05:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mfisk/article/1099582</link><title>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;High Performance VMM-Bypass I/O in Virtual Machines</title><description>&lt;!-- CHANGE --&gt;Currently, I/O device virtualization models in virtual machine (VM) environments require involvement of a virtual machine monitor (VMM) and/or a privileged VM for each I/O operation, which may turn out to be a performance bottleneck for systems with high I/O demands, especially those equipped with modern high speed interconnects such as InfiniBand. &lt;P&gt; In this paper, we propose a new device virtualization model called &lt;EM&gt;VMM-bypass&lt;/EM&gt; I/O, which extends the idea of OS-bypass originated from user-level ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>