<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7470">is sugar poison</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:06:21" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:06:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/3785874</link><title>Sugar industry in Egypt</title><description>Abstract  Sugar industry in Egypt started back in the year 710. Egyptians are considered to be the pioneers in refined sugar industry since ninth and tenth centuries. The total production of sugar in Egypt in 2007–2008 is 1,582 million tonnes and the consumption is 2,485 million tonnes. Sugar beet grown in 247 million hectares and produces 482 mt of white sugar with an average of 50.7 ton/ha. However the sugarcane is grown in 136 million hactares and produces 1075184 metric ton of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:06:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/3785873</link><title>Development of sugar industry in Africa</title><description>Abstract  The most important sugar producing regions in Africa are north and southern regions. North African region is the oldest one in the sugar industry. African sugar producing countries need to increase the share of the contribution to the GDP. Sugar industry in Africa is one of the key industries which contributes in providing jobs for the growing unemployment as well as instrumental in rural development. This will reduce the high rates of migration from rural to urban areas and many associated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:07:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/3829183</link><title>Status and trends of sugar industry in China</title><description>Abstract  The sugar industry in China is becoming increasingly important both domestically and internationally because of its rapid development. Significant progress has been achieved not only in sugar production, but also in the integrated utilization, developments and as productions of sugar-based products cane by-products, and environment-friendly management of vinasse. These developments are the result of the combined impact of governmental policies, management creativity, and technological innovations. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:08:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/3829184</link><title>Sugarcane cultivation and sugar industry in Japan</title><description>Abstract  In Japan, sugarcane is grown only in the South-western Islands, at the southern most end of the Japanese Archipelago. Most of these islands are in the subtropics, natural and environmental conditions are fairly severe to sugarcane cultivation because of frequent typhoons, droughts in summer, low temperatures in winter and poor soil fertility. In recent years, sugarcane production has been sluggish due to the lack of labour caused by the aging of farmers, a delay of mechanization in cultivation and unfavorable weather ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:08:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/4020057</link><title>Identification of new microsatellite DNA markers for sugar and related traits in sugarcane</title><description>Abstract  Molecular studies in sugarcane are relatively limited because of the complex genetic structure, long life cycle and non availability of reliable sugarcane specific molecular markers. The use of DNA markers for the genetic analysis and manipulation of desirable agronomic traits has become an increasingly useful tool in sugarcane breeding. The objective of the present study was to evaluate the polymorphic potential of sugarcane microsatellite markers developed at National Research Centre on Plant Biotechnology, IARI, New Delhi in high and low sugar ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:10:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/3785872</link><title>Sugar Crops Research Institute, Giza (Egypt): A Profile</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:11:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EEsterling/article/7231500</link><title>Is Sugar Consumption Detrimental to Health? A Review of the Evidence 19952006</title><description>Many countries set quantitative targets for added sugars, justifying this by expressing concern about the likely impact of sugar on weight control, dental health, diet quality, or metabolic syndrome. This review considers whether current intakes of sugar are harmful to health, and analyses recent literature using a systematic approach to collate, rank, and evaluate published studies from 19952006. Results from high quality obesity studies did not suggest a positive association between body mass index and sugar intake. Some studies, specifically on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:12:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/saeedahmed/article/4020063</link><title>Centralisation of sugarcane milling operations: matching agronomics with economics</title><description>Abstract  Drastic changes in the sugar trade agreements call for urgent management adaptation to ensure the economic sustainability of the Mauritian sugarcane sector. In-line with improvement being made at the level of labour and machine efficiency, an extension of the harvest season is being envisaged. It has been noted that cane harvested early in the season is characterized by low sucrose contents and high levels of impurities resulting in less efficient manufacturing processes. While investments are being made in the breeding of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:13:57">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10039243</link><title>The Indian Sugar Industry: An Overview</title><description>Sugar industry is the second largest agro-based industry in India and contributes significantly to the socio-economic development of rural population. It supports 50 million farmers and their families and provides direct employment to over 0.5 million skilled and semi-skilled persons in sugar mills and integrated industries. The Indian sugar industry plays a leading role in global sugar market being the world’s second largest producer after Brazil, producing nearly 15 and 25% of global sugar and sugarcane, respectively. The sugar industry which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7470-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7470_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:15:15">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8708520</link><title>Traditional Breeding in Sugar Beet</title><description>With rapidly changing agricultural practices, target environments, and biotic and abiotic stresses, plant breeders face the task of continually selecting plants with desirable traits with the goal to assemble advantageous combinations of genes in new varieties. Sugar beet has been selectively bred since the early nineteenth century with the principle objective to develop varieties with the maximum root and sucrose yield potential at the lowest economic and environmental costs possible. Historically, the most productive developments in sugar beet breeding have been ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>