<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7471">php foreach</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:16:12" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:16:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EdisonRivas/article/9089548</link><title>Principles of Object Orientation in PHP</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:17:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/citeulike4me/article/2084045</link><title>PHP in a Nutshell</title><description>Now installed on more than 20 million Internet domains around the world, PHP is an undisputed leader in web programming languages. Database connectivity, powerful extensions, and rich object-orientation are all reasons for its popularity, but nearly everyone would agree that, above all, PHP is one of the easiest languages to learn and use for developing dynamic web applications. The ease of development and simplicity of PHP, combined with a large community and expansive repository of open source PHP libraries, make it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:18:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TaniaEiko/article/9089564</link><title>PHP</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:19:50">http://www.citeulike.org/group/5863/article/3000027</link><title>PHP Developer's Cookbook (Developer's Library)</title><description>Bringing together hundreds of problems and solutions, _PHP Developer's Cookbook_ is an excellent resource for any PHP developer. Both the authors are members of the PHP development team, and with a foreword from Rasmus Lerdorf, the creator of PHP, there is no doubting the book's authority. The introduction notes that some sections cover previously undocumented material, making it particularly valuable for advanced PHP programmers. It is based on PHP 4. Each chapter follows the same basic format. A short problem, such as "you want to find the time that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:21:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/karenmariel/article/667658</link><title>Web Database Applications with PHP &amp; MySQL</title><description>PHP and MySQL go hand in hand; the former has been carefully adapted, through the efforts of the open-source community, to the latter. For situations that require dynamic content but don't merit the complexity and development time of Java or .NET enterprise applications, the PHP language and the MySQL database server fit the bill perfectly. That's the point Hugh Williams and David Lane make in &lt;I&gt;Web Database Applications with PHP &amp; MySQL&lt;/I&gt;, which combines language tutorials with application design advice to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:21:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/druvus/article/3022271</link><title>CodeIgniter for Rapid PHP Application Development</title><description>CodeIgniter (CI) is a powerful open-source PHP framework with a very small footprint, built for PHP coders who need a simple and elegant toolkit to create full-featured web applications. CodeIgniter is an MVC framework, similar in some ways to the Rails framework for Ruby, and is designed to enable, not overwhelm. This book explains how to work with CodeIgniter in a clear logical way. It is not a detailed guide to the syntax of CodeIgniter, but makes an ideal complement to the existing online CodeIgniter user guide, helping ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:22:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bblainey/article/7059743</link><title>Evaluation of a just-in-time compiler retrofitted for PHP</title><description>Programmers who develop Web applications often use dynamic scripting languages such as Perl, PHP, Python, and Ruby. For general purpose scripting language usage, interpreter-based implementations are efficient and popular but the server-side usage for Web application development implies an opportunity to significantly enhance Web server throughput. This paper summarizes a study of the optimization of PHP script processing. We developed a PHP processor, P9, by adapting an existing production-quality just-in-time (JIT) compiler for a Java virtual machine, for which optimization technologies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:23:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fabiolljunior/article/10011112</link><title>PHP 5 in Practice</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:25:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/weelassie/article/667659</link><title>PHP for the World Wide Web Visual Quickstart Guide</title><description>Need to learn PHP fast? Try a Visual QuickStart! &lt;P&gt;Takes an easy, visual approach to teaching PHP scripting, using pictures to guide you through the language and show you what to do. &lt;P&gt;Works like a reference book--you look up what you need and then get straight to work. &lt;P&gt;No long-winded passes--concise, straightforward commentary explains what you need to know. &lt;P&gt;Companion Web site contains complete source code for examples in the book, online resources, updates, and more. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7471-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7471_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:26:53">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1570/article/358736</link><title>PHP and MySQL Web Development (3rd Edition) (Developer's Library)</title><description>The PHP server-side scripting language and the MySQL database management system (DBMS) make a potent pair. Both are open-source products--free of charge for most purposes--remarkably strong, and capable of handling all but the most enormous transaction loads. Both are supported by large, skilled, and enthusiastic communities of architects, programmers, and designers. &lt;I&gt;PHP and MySQL Web Development&lt;/I&gt; introduces readers (who are assumed to have little or no experience with the title subjects) to PHP and MySQL for the purpose of creating dynamic ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>