<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:27:28" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:27:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/muratsincan/article/9824325</link><title>C and C++ Programming with NumPy Arrays Python Scripting for Computational Science</title><description>Our purpose with this chapter is to implement the gridloop1 and gridloop2 functions from Chapter 9 in C and C++. The goal is the same: we want to increase the computational efficiency by moving loops from Python to compiled code, but now we use C and C++ instead of Fortran. Before proceeding the reader should be familiar with the gridloop1 and gridloop2 functions and the calling Python code as defined in Chapter 9.1. It is not necessary to have digested the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:28:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/agupta0318/article/2230965</link><title>Learning Python, 3rd Edition</title><description>The authors of &lt;I&gt;Learning Python&lt;/I&gt; show you enough essentials of the Python scripting language to enable you to begin solving problems right away, then reveal more powerful aspects of the language one at a time. This approach is sure to appeal to programmers and system administrators who have urgent problems and a preference for learning by semi-guided experimentation.&lt;p&gt; First off, &lt;I&gt;Learning Python&lt;/I&gt; shows the relationships among Python scripts and their interpreter (in a mostly platform-neutral way). Then, the authors address the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:28:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/julesal/article/12618536</link><title>Python and Java: The Best of Both Worlds</title><description>This paper describes a new working implementation of the Python language; built on top of the Java language and run-time environment. This is in contrast to the existing implementation of Python, which has been built on top of the C language and run-time environment. Implementing Python in Java has a number of limitations when compared to the current implementation of Python in C. These include about 1.7X slower performance, portability limited by Java VM availability, and lack of compatibility with existing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:29:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chradcliffe/article/3138439</link><title>Python in Education: Raising a Generation of Native Speakers</title><description>Primarily because of its young age, Python is still a language that people only discover after having digested a few others: while many of its users love it enthusiastically, almost nobody is a native speaker of it, in the sense of having been exposed to it before any other. As computer literacy evolves from desirable to necessary for people from all backgrounds, computer professionals and academics are responsible for taking a long-term view on how best to educate the next few ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:30:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Marechal/article/808843</link><title>The Python Language Reference Manual</title><description>This manual is the definitive language reference for Python. It describes the syntax of Python and its built-in datatypes in depth. &lt;P&gt;Python is an interpreted object-oriented programming language, suitable for rapid application development and scripting. Python's syntax emphasizes readability, which reduces the cost of program maintenance. &lt;P&gt;This manual covers advanced topics, and is suitable for readers who need to be familiar with the details and rules of the Python language and its object system. A tutorial suitable for those new to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:32:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wbsnipes/article/6614568</link><title>How to Write and Read a Scientific Evaluation Paper</title><description>Scientific evaluation papers investigate existing problem situations or validate proposed solutions with scientific means, such as by experiment or case study. There is a growing amount of literature about how to report about empirical research in software engineering, but there is still some confusion about the difference between a scientific evaluation paper and other kinds of research papers. This is related to lack of clarity about the relation between empirical research, engineering, and industrial practice. In this minitutorial we give a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:32:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Marechal/article/1001737</link><title>Dive Into Python</title><description>&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Dive Into Python&lt;/STRONG&gt; is a hands-on guide to the Python language. Each chapter starts with a real complete code sample, proceeds to pick it apart and explain the pieces, and then puts it all back together again in a summary at the end.&lt;/P&gt; &lt;P&gt;&lt;/P&gt; &lt;P&gt;Python is a new and innovative scripting language. It is set to replace Perl as the programming language of choice for shell scripters, and for serious application developers wanting a feature rich yet simple language to deploy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:33:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hugoabonizio/article/10657540</link><title>Introduction: Welcome to Maya Python</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:34:34">http://www.citeulike.org/user/l-alex/article/379140</link><title>Programming with Python</title><description>Python is a powerful, easy-to-use programming language based on other traditional languages. In this article, the author discusses why his company, NovaSys Health, chose Python as its primary programming language. The author notes that Python is generally better suited to current operating systems, networks, and hardware because of its simplicity and that Python's simple syntax and built-in data structures helped NovaSys Health focus on creating a flexible layout process for transmitting its medical data. The article includes instructions on how to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:35:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Borelli/article/2069733</link><title>Python in a Nutshell, Second Edition (In a Nutshell (O'Reilly))</title><description>&lt;p&gt; This book offers Python programmers one place to look when they need help remembering or deciphering the syntax of this open source language and its many powerful but scantily documented modules. This comprehensive reference guide makes it easy to look up the most frequently needed information--not just about the Python language itself, but also the most frequently used parts of the standard library and the most important third-party extensions. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Ask any Python aficionado and you'll hear that Python ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>