<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:36:33" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:36:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jherpers/article/12722491</link><title>Criteria for assessment of noise annoyance</title><description>Day-night average sound level (DNL) and the relationship between DNL and community annoyance to noise are often presented to a community as part of a noise-assessment process, usually as established scientific fact. In reality, there is great scatter and variability in the attitudinal survey data that are the basis for the DNL-response relationship. As a result, there is significant uncertainty around the corresponding curves that are fitted to the data. This paper collects, tabulates, and compares recommended minimum DNL criterion levels ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:37:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/asteroid13/article/1583707</link><title>Publication of "Handbook to Deal with Low Frequency Noise (2004)"</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:39:15">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1844/article/961908</link><title>Adaptive noise canceling for speech signals</title><description>A least mean-square (LMS) adaptive filtering approach has been formulated for removing the deleterious effects of additive noise on the speech signal. Unlike the classical LMS adaptive filtering scheme, the proposed method is designed to cancel out the clean speech signal. This method takes advantage of the quasi-periodic nature of the speech signal to form an estimate of the clean speech signal at time t from the value of the signal at time t minus the estimated pitch period. For additive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:39:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suizan/article/1907277</link><title>Differential Gene Expression Following Noise Trauma in Birds and Mammals.</title><description>Acoustic overstimulation has very different outcomes in birds and mammals. When noise exposure kills hair cells in birds, these cells can regenerate and hearing will recover. In mammals, however, the hair cell loss, and resulting hearing loss, is permanent. Changes in gene expression form the basis for important biological processes, including repair, regeneration, and plasticity. We are therefore using a battery of molecular approaches to identify and compare changes in gene expression following noise trauma in birds and mammals. Both differential ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:40:30">http://www.citeulike.org/group/2/article/276212</link><title>A Descriptive Cross-Sectional Study of Annoyance from Low Frequency Noise Installations in an Urban Environment</title><description>In order to improve the living conditions for respondents highly exposed to traffic noise, it has been recommended that one side of the building should face a "quiet side". Quiet may, however, be spoilt by noise from installations such as ventilation and air-conditioning systems. The noises generated by installations of this kind often have a dominant portion of low frequencies (20-200 Hz) and may be a source of great annoyance and sleep disturbance. This paper describes the cross-sectional part of an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:40:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/84469</link><title>Children's Cognition and Aircraft Noise Exposure at Home - The West London Schools Study</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:41:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/knud/article/1284628</link><title>Place-Its: A Study of Location-Based Reminders</title><description>Context-awareness can improve the usefulness of automated reminders. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:42:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Weisskittelchen/article/2702192</link><title>Oral, Dental, and Supportive Care in the Cancer Patient Head and Neck Cancer</title><description>Patients undergoing chemotherapy and/or head and neck radiation treatment may have multiple side effects occurring simultaneously such as mucositis, candidiasis, herpetic stomatitis or xerostomia. It is important to make the diagnosis(es) and treat the patient as effectively as possible on the basis of the diagnosis(es). Therapeutic management is generated by the diagnosis (Table 2). The oral and dental care management should be individualized on a case by case basis as there are so many variables involved with the cancer patient. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:44:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phshow/article/379696</link><title>Aircraft and road traffic noise and children's cognition and health: a cross-national study</title><description>SummaryBackgroundExposure to environmental stressors can impair children's health and their cognitive development. The effects of air pollution, lead, and chemicals have been studied, but there has been less emphasis on the effects of noise. Our aim, therefore, was to assess the effect of exposure to aircraft and road traffic noise on cognitive performance and health in children.MethodsWe did a cross-national, cross-sectional study in which we assessed 2844 of 3207 children aged 9-10 years who were attending 89 schools of 77 approached ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:45:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/wardywilbury/article/10255383</link><title>Noise-induced tinnitus: a comparison between four clinical groups without apparent hearing loss.</title><description>The number of people with normal hearing thresholds seeking medical help for tinnitus and other hearing problems is increasing. For diagnostic purposes, existence/nonexistence of lesions or combinations of lesions in the inner ear not reflected in the audiogram was evaluated with advanced hearing tests applied to tinnitus patients with certain backgrounds, including noise exposure. For forty-six patients with pronounced tinnitus, and other symptoms, tentative diagnoses ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>