<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7474">php convert special symbols to html</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:46:14" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:46:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scis0000001/article/894370</link><title>On the Enumerative Sequences of Regular</title><description>The main result is a characterization of enumerative sequences of regular languages on k symbols. We prove that a sequence is the generating series s(z) of a regular language on k symbols if and only if it is the generating series of a language over a k-letter alphabet and if both series s(z) and (kz) s(z) are regular. The proof uses transformations on linear representations called inductions. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:47:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/EdisonRivas/article/9089548</link><title>Principles of Object Orientation in PHP</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:49:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/citeulike4me/article/2084045</link><title>PHP in a Nutshell</title><description>Now installed on more than 20 million Internet domains around the world, PHP is an undisputed leader in web programming languages. Database connectivity, powerful extensions, and rich object-orientation are all reasons for its popularity, but nearly everyone would agree that, above all, PHP is one of the easiest languages to learn and use for developing dynamic web applications. The ease of development and simplicity of PHP, combined with a large community and expansive repository of open source PHP libraries, make it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:50:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/courtneyingalls/article/8748498</link><title>Post-School Outcomes for Students in the State of Washington, USA, Receiving Special Education Services</title><description>States in the U.S. are required to provide transition services to young people in special education to increase the likelihood of positive post-school outcomes (Individuals with Disabilities Education Act of 1990, IDEA, amended 1997). Fourteen years later the Individuals with Disabilities Education Improvement Act of 2004 strengthened transition requirements and required that each state follow-up with former special education students to determine their post-school outcomes. These outcomes include the percent of youth that have been employed, enrolled in some type of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:51:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eduarte/article/625722</link><title>Early understanding and production of graphic symbols.</title><description>Young children's ability to understand and produce graphic symbols within an environment of social communication was investigated in two experiments. Children aged 2, 3, and 4 years produced graphic symbols of simple objects on their own, used them in a social communicative game, and responded to experimenter's symbols. In Experiment 1 (N = 48), 2-year-olds did not effectively produce symbols or use the experimenter's symbols in the choice task, whereas 3- and 4-year-olds improved their drawings following the game and performed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:52:08">http://www.citeulike.org/article/398865</link><title>Europe and the Crisis in Scientific Vocations</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:53:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TaniaEiko/article/9089564</link><title>PHP</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:53:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Demeter/article/4796621</link><title>The Essential Guide to CSS and HTML Web Design</title><description>The Essential Guide to CSS and HTML Web Design is a special book—it will tell you _all_ you _need_ to know to design great web sites that are standards compliant, usable, and look great, but not overwhelm you with waffle, theory, and obscure details. It is designed to be invaluable to you, whatever stage you are at in your career, with a mixture of practical tutorials and reference material—beginners will quickly pick up the basics, while more experienced web designers and developers will keep returning to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:54:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/albertodiaspro/article/7679284</link><title>Guest Editorial: Special Section on Visible Fluorescent Proteins</title><description>This Special Section Guest Editorial provides an overview of the topical area and an introduction to the articles featured in the special section. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7474-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7474_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:55:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/weelassie/article/667659</link><title>PHP for the World Wide Web Visual Quickstart Guide</title><description>Need to learn PHP fast? Try a Visual QuickStart! &lt;P&gt;Takes an easy, visual approach to teaching PHP scripting, using pictures to guide you through the language and show you what to do. &lt;P&gt;Works like a reference book--you look up what you need and then get straight to work. &lt;P&gt;No long-winded passes--concise, straightforward commentary explains what you need to know. &lt;P&gt;Companion Web site contains complete source code for examples in the book, online resources, updates, and more. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>