<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:56:44" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:56:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ShakeeraDMyers/article/6875232</link><title>Family expenditures for clothing : Five regions, by... Economics division, bureau of home economics...</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:58:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dingx/article/789077</link><title>Technology as enabler: keeping work distinct from home while working at home</title><description>it focus on how technology can enable working at home. but tend to be old-fashioned.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:58:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/erimbau/article/3797921</link><title>When Home Becomes Work: Work and Family Time among Workers at Home</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:00:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5285558</link><title>Is it all bad? Rewards and challenges of mothering children with hidden disabilities</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:01:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/reinhardt/article/2421052</link><title>Step-by-Step Guide to Building a CMDB</title><description>While a lot of CMDB information is available, there is no guide that essentially spells out the steps you need to take to effectively build a CMDB. And that is how Malcolm Fry came up with the idea for this book. He decided that the market could benefit from his experience and that of others to put down on paper a common sense, step-by-step project approach to building a CMDB. The idea is that you can take what you need from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:02:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pccoutinho/article/3112675</link><title>Software: Hero or Zero?</title><description>People might love to support underdogs, but they also love to kick them when they're down. And, at this point in time at least, software is the world's technological underdog! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:03:12">http://www.citeulike.org/group/4049/article/2890741</link><title>Should You Adopt Open Source Software?</title><description>Many organizations use open source infrastructure software such as Linux, and open source software (OSS) is generally considered a viable technology. Both professional and academic literature devote much attention to the OSS phenomenon. However, decision makers considering the adoption of OSS face a plethora of books, research papers, and articles highlighting OSS's advantages and disadvantages. Different articles attach different levels of importance to these advantages or factors related to the adoption decision. Reasons for adopting OSS vary from the pragmatic. Organizations ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:04:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/flatliner_uk/article/9095745</link><title>Free software, free society : selected essays of Richard Stallman</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:05:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jzavalar/article/3644967</link><title>What is software?</title><description>This paper suggests that there may be other types of software besides computer software. The paper identifies parallels between computer software and such other societal artifacts as laws, processes, recipes, and instructions (e.g. for driving and kitbuilding), and suggests that there are similar parallels in the ways in which these artifacts are built and evolved. The paper suggests that technologies for supporting the automation of computer software development and evolution might facilitate work in these other domains. It also suggests that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:07:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/AlexFortitude/article/8400919</link><title>Evaluation of the trial of 'Back to work' group sessions</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>