<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:17:49" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:17:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tryan61/article/1352410</link><title>AVIAN INFLUENZA: Indonesia Earns Flu Accord at World Health Assembly</title><description>10.1126/science.316.5828.1108 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:18:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/72081</link><title>IN THE NEWS: Bird flu scare</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:19:46">http://www.citeulike.org/user/MariaCantillo/article/8361941</link><title>China in the world : contemporary issues and perspectives</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:20:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vmoraru2012/article/12332715</link><title>Modeling the spread of bird flu and predicting outbreak diversity</title><description>Avian influenza, commonly known as bird flu, is an epidemic caused by H5N1 virus that primarily affects birds like chickens, wild water birds, etc. On rare occasions, these can infect other species including pigs and humans. In the span of less than a year, the lethal strain of bird flu is spreading very fast across the globe mainly in South East Asia, parts of Central Asia, Africa and Europe. In order to study the patterns of spread of epidemic, we made ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:21:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kristindenexter/article/8986631</link><title>South East Asia</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:22:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jillh/article/7104986</link><title>A rapid method for assessing social versus independent interest in health issues: A case study of ‘bird flu’ and ‘swine flu’</title><description>Effective communication strategies regarding health issues are affected by the way in which the public obtain their knowledge, particularly whether people become interested independently, or through their social networks. This is often investigated through localized ethnography or surveys. In rapidly-evolving situations, however, there may also be a need for swift, case-specific assessment as a guide to initial strategy development. With this aim, we analyze real-time online data, provided by the new ‘Google Trends’ tool, concerning Internet search frequency for health-related issues. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:24:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/1855668</link><title>Hydrological response units (HRU's) as modelling entities for hydrological river basin simulation and their methodological potential for modelling complex environmental process systems. Results from the Sieg catchment</title><description>During the past two decades environmental studies have become of increasing importance to the population and decision makers worldwide. The term 'ecology' in Geography frequently is used to indicate that the problem under investigation is dealing with different aspects of interlinked ecosystems (Grunert 1991: Kummert and Stumm 1992; Jeffries and Mills 1990: DFG 1986). Geography as a scientific discipline traditionally is investigating interlinked process systems in nature and their interaction with human economic development. The latter is influencing these process systems, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:25:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/FabbioHu/article/6997244</link><title>Un Lun Dun</title><description>Stumbling into an alternate funhouse version of her home city, twelve-year-old Londoner Deeba finds herself trapped in a world of killer giraffes, animated umbrellas, ghost children, and flying double-decker buses and menaced by a choking black smog, and is forced to take on the role of unlikely savior to prevent utter destruction. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:26:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11289477</link><title>Bird watching in China reveals bird distribution changes</title><description>Using China Bird Report (2003–2007) as data source in combination with descriptions about bird habitats, we built up the China Bird Watching Database. We also developed spherical GIS software “Global Analyst” to create the point-based database which contains accurate spatial-temporal information. The China Bird Watching Database can reflect the achievement of Chinese bird watchers and complement the basic knowledge of bird distribution. Now a total of 30936 records from 17 Orders, 70 Families and 1078 Species of 5 years are included ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:27:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rhonddawildlifediary/article/7571533</link><title>The effect of observer experience on English Breeding Bird Survey population trends</title><description>&lt;b&gt;Capsule&lt;/b&gt; Including observer effects in population models is unlikely to improve population trend estimates. &lt;b&gt;Aims&lt;/b&gt; We test the hypothesis that the observer's experience has a significant effect on the detection of birds, and subsequently impacts on estimates of abundance and population trends. &lt;b&gt;Methods&lt;/b&gt; Two models were used to test the effect of observer experience: (1) assuming that effects of observer naïvety operate only in the first year, and express experience as a binomial variable; (2) assuming effects of experience improve year-on-year, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>