<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:28:58" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:29:03">http://www.citeulike.org/user/online/article/217397</link><title>On the recommending of citations for research papers</title><description>Collaborative filtering has proven to be valuable for recommending items in many different domains. In this paper, we explore the use of collaborative filtering to recommend research papers, using the citation web between papers to create the ratings matrix. Specifically, we tested the ability of collaborative filtering to recommend citations that would be suitable additional references for a target research paper. We investigated six algorithms for selecting citations, evaluating them through offline experiments against a database of over 186,000 research papers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:30:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/knoxtim/article/2976332</link><title>Assessing Students for Online Learning</title><description>Distance education has dramatically increased the educational opportunities for underserved populations. This is evidenced by the fairly recent proliferation and success of online universities, and it is happening in spite of criticism of e-learning and online degree programs among academia and the popular press. As a result, many institutions, including traditional and respected universities across the country – who were once among the harshest critics – are now offering distance education courses. However, not all students who wish to enroll in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:31:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mkrain/article/9920661</link><title>Universal Duties: The Responsibility to Protect, the Duty to Prevent (Genocide) and Extraterritorial Human Rights Obligations</title><description>Human rights are (universally) declared to be universal, yet under the dominant interpretation the responsibility to protect these rights have been severely restricted by territorial considerations. In that way, while a state has human rights obligations within its own territory, these obligations either change or else disappear altogether when it is acting outside those borders. This article examines three recent challenges to the territorial approach to human rights. The Responsibility to Protect (R2P) initiative to prevent widespread human suffering involves domestic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:32:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/allyharp/article/5649707</link><title>From KISS to KIDS – An ‘Anti-simplistic’ Modelling Approach</title><description>A new approach is suggested under the slogan “Keep it Descriptive Stupid” (KIDS) that encapsulates a trend in increasingly descriptive agent-based social simulation. The KIDS approach entails one starts with the simulation model that relates to the target phenomena in the most straight-forward way possible, taking into account the widest possible range of evidence, including anecdotal accounts and expert opinion. Simplification is only applied if and when the model and evidence justify this. This contrasts sharply with the KISS approach where ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:33:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NML/article/430882</link><title>Playing the Future : What We Can Learn from Digital Kids</title><description>Three years after the original publication of &lt;I&gt;Playing the Future: What We Can Learn from Digital Kids&lt;/I&gt; in 1996, this breathlessly polemical defense of the techno-savvy youth culture of the '90s already reads like a document from another era. Back then, the Internet was still a strange new force, instinctively embraced by kids who'd grown up playing video games, instinctively distrusted by the grownups who ran the mainstream media. Standing up for the emergent digital culture--loosely associated with suspicious activities like ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:35:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Manakel/article/2195818</link><title>Synchronization in Massive Multiplayer</title><description>Revenues generated by video games typically surpass those provided by the cinematography industry. The pace of development in hardware and software networking technologies is enabling a fast evolution of these kinds of online applications. This large and emerging game market is thus driving researchers and practitioners to develop innovative software techniques that allow game players to enjoy exciting and interactive game experiences, even when modern wireless handheld devices are used. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:37:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/DanielToohey/article/7118382</link><title>Why People Use Social Networking Sites Online Communities and Social Computing</title><description>One of the recent popular social media platforms is the social networking site (SNS). Thus far, few previous studies have empirically investigated people’s motivations for SNS usage, especially not outside the U.S. This study combines a large-scale quantitative and qualitative research design, by asking 1,200 SNS users an open question regarding their reasons for using SNSs. An important conclusion drawn from a preliminary content analysis is that people often report many motivational reasons for using SNSs . The most important reason ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:38:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alanvelander/article/12824026</link><title>Percutaneous left atrial appendage closure for stroke prophylaxis in patients with atrial fibrillation: 2.3-Year Follow-up of the PROTECT AF (Watchman Left Atrial Appendage System for Embolic Protection in Patients with Atrial Fibrillation) Trial.</title><description>The multicenter PROTECT AF study (Watchman Left Atrial Appendage System for Embolic Protection in Patients With Atrial Fibrillation) was conducted to determine whether percutaneous left atrial appendage closure with a filter device (Watchman) was noninferior to warfarin for stroke prevention in atrial fibrillation. Patients (n=707) with nonvalvular atrial fibrillation and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:39:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/CDDU/article/5376360</link><title>Student Support Services and Student Satisfaction in Online Education</title><description>This paper investigates the relationship between quality of support services in online education and the level of satisfaction of e-learners with these services. Case study was employed to measure University of Surrey's virtual MBA students' satisfaction with course facilitator, personal tutor and help desk functions designed for online education. The research revealed strong positive correlation between quality attributes of these support services and overall level of satisfaction with the support services. It suggests that any increase in quality level of services ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:39:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/elixr/article/938288</link><title>A flexible framework for online collaborative learning</title><description>This paper presents a framework for online collaborative learning, also known as telecollaboration. At the centre of this flexible framework are online collaborative educational experiences where knowledge creation and knowledge in action are the nexus of social, teaching and cognitive presence based on the Community of Inquiry model of Garrison, Anderson and Archers [Garrison, D.R., Anderson, T., and Archer, W. (1999). Critical thinking in a text-based environment: Computer conferencing in higher education. Internet and Higher Education, 2(2-3), 87-105]. The framework provided ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>