<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:40:31" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:40:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucaPappalardoPhD/article/2670653</link><title>Social network size in humans</title><description>This paper examines social network size in contemporary Western society based on the exchange of Christmas cards. Maximum network size averaged 153.5 individuals, with a mean network size of 124.9 for those individuals explicitly contacted; these values are remarkably close to the group size of 150 predicted for humans on the basis of the size of their neocortex. Age, household type, and the relationship to the individual influence network structure, although the proportion of kin remained relatively constant at around 21%. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:41:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucaPappalardoPhD/article/1679333</link><title>Discrete hierarchical organization of social group sizes.</title><description>The 'social brain hypothesis' for the evolution of large brains in primates has led to evidence for the coevolution of neocortical size and social group sizes, suggesting that there is a cognitive constraint on group size that depends, in some way, on the volume of neural material available for processing and synthesizing information on social relationships. More recently, work on both human and non-human primates ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:43:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/theshadowhost/article/4155538</link><title>Perspective-taking and memory capacity predict social network size</title><description>Human social networks typically consist of a hierarchically organized series of grouping levels. There is, however, considerable variation between individuals in the sizes of any given network layer. We test between two possible factors (memory capacity and theory of mind) that might limit the size of two different levels within human social networks (support cliques and sympathy groups). We show that the size of an individual's support clique (the number of individual's in the innermost circle of friends) is better explained ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:43:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucaPappalardoPhD/article/10273288</link><title>Is Dunbar's number up?</title><description>This article is a commentary on ‘Relationships and the social brain: Integrating psychological and evolutionary perspectives’ (Sutcliffe, Dunbar, Binder, &amp; Arrow, 2011). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:44:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/karhai/article/666144</link><title>Are social networks technologically embedded?</title><description>Communication mediated by various technologies (from ordinary mail to today's Information and Communication Technologies (ICT)) provides important evidence for the study of social networks. Given that networks generate the possibility of interpersonal communication, data on technology use can provide important information on sociability. However, it is also true that personal networks not only shape, but also are shaped by technological means for communication, since these entail the re-constituting of social ties and the re-drawing of social boundaries. We use material from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:45:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucaPappalardoPhD/article/280459</link><title>Neocortex size and group size in primates: a test of the hypothesis</title><description>In this paper, the analysis of the factors influencing the evolution of neocortex size in primates given in Dunbar (1992) is extended in three specific ways. (1) An independent test is undertaken of the hypothesis that group size is a function of relative neocortex size in primates by using estimates of neocortex size to predict group size for those species that were not involved in the original analysis. The results confirm the results of the earlier analysis. (2) A more satisfactory ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:46:35">http://www.citeulike.org/user/LucaPappalardoPhD/article/3709757</link><title>Neocortex size as a constraint on group size in primates</title><description>Two general kinds of theory (one ecological and one social) have been advanced to explain the fact that primates have larger brains and greater congnitive abilities than other animals. Data on neocortex volume, group size and a number of behavioural ecology variables are used to test between the various theories. Group size is found to be a function of relative neocortical volume, but the ecological variables are not. This is interpreted as evidence in favour of the social intellect theory and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:48:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ding424/article/3036497</link><title>Who benefits from network analysis: ethics of social network research</title><description>The success of social network research (SNR) has led to expectations that in addition to academic research, SNR can introduce people to one another, solve organizational problems, map the epidemiology of AIDS, and catch criminals and terrorists. Since SNR requires that names of both respondents and their contacts be collected and used in most analyses, Institutional Review Boards become very concerned. Experiences of the author, participants in the 2003 Sun Belt Conference and the Social Network List Serve illustrate ethical issues. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:48:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/spool/article/658726</link><title>Effects of missing data in social networks</title><description>We perform sensitivity analyses to assess the impact of missing data on the structural properties of social networks. The social network is conceived of as being generated by a bipartite graph, in which actors are linked together via multiple interaction contexts or affiliations. We discuss three principal missing data mechanisms: network boundary specification (non-inclusion of actors or affiliations), survey non-response, and censoring by vertex degree (fixed choice design), examining their impact on the scientific collaboration network from the Los Alamos E-print ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7479-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7479_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:49:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/maqbes/article/278955</link><title>Centrality in social networks conceptual clarification</title><description>The intuitive background for measures of structural centrality in social networks is reviewed and existing measures are evaluated in terms of their consistency with intuitions and their interpretability. Three distinct intuitive conceptions of centrality are uncovered and existing measures are refined to embody these conceptions. Three measures are developed for each concept, one absolute and one relative measure of the centrality of positions in a network, and one reflecting the degree of centralization of the entire network. The implications of these ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>