<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7480">phd comics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:50:47" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:50:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ThomasWilson2/article/6938005</link><title>Batman vs. Two-Face.</title><description>"A collection of ten terrifying tales of Batman's most twisted foe!"--Cover. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:51:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/TomRoberts/article/5086366</link><title>Comics as Literature?</title><description>Not all comics are art. What about the comics that are art? What sort of art are they? In particular, are comics a form of literature? For a variety of reasons it is tempting to think that at least some comics are literature. Nevertheless, many theorists reject the ‘comics as literature’ view. And although some reasons for resisting that view are misguided, I shall argue that there are other good reasons for being hesitant about treating comics as a form of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:52:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Torsten_Holmer/article/138217</link><title>Comics &amp; Sequential Art</title><description>Based on the popular course Eisner taught for several years at New York's School of Visual Arts, this lovingly written book on visual storytelling contains an accumulation of his ideas, theories and advice on the practice of graphic story-telling and the uses to which the comic book art form can be applied. Whether you're a film student, literature student, artist or simply a fan of good storytelling, you'll love this book filled with Eisner's cartoons. Legendary comics creator Will Eisner ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:53:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Lets_Manga/article/126553</link><title>Understanding Comics: The Invisible Art</title><description>As all good card-carrying comic-book fans know, their sheer passion will never overcome narrow-minded critics and their baying cries of derision. There is far more to this perpetually underrated medium than a mix of art and prose. With this indispensable, spellbinding tome, writer/artist Scott McCloud rises to the challenge of dissecting what remains the most enigmatic of art forms. After all, says McCloud, "No other art form gives so much to its audience while asking so much from them as well". Over the course of 215 impeccably formed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:53:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/silberbauer/article/12668899</link><title>Discerning pictures: how we look at and understand images in comics</title><description>Scott McCloud (1993) has used a realism continuum to classify comics characters between the points of realism and iconic abstraction. Before him, other theorists (Gropper 1963; Knowlton 1966; Dwyer 1972; Wileman 1993) have used this continuum as a means to judge the communicative and instructional potential of pictures as they become more distant from the realistic.At the same time, all comic artists employ at least some level of distillation or abstraction, some removal of realistic detail. This approach can allow for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:54:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Lets_Manga/article/772078</link><title>Comics, Comix &amp; Graphic Novels: A History Of Comic Art</title><description>For many years, those interested in the history of the art of comics--from scholars to fans--had very few options. The available books were either filled with glaring errors or far too limited in their scope. Along comes Roger Sabin and his near-definitive history. The best thing about this book is that it begins with a strong foundation--that comics is a separate and unique artistic medium--and goes on to leave practically no stone unturned, from mainstream superheroes to underground work to Japanese ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:55:10">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Torsten_Holmer/article/355983</link><title>Reinventing Comics : How Imagination and Technology Are Revolutionizing an Art Form</title><description>Scott McCloud's &lt;I&gt;Reinventing Comics&lt;/I&gt;, the sequel to his groundbreaking work &lt;I&gt;Understanding Comics&lt;/I&gt;, is a study of two revolutions: a failed one and a potential one. His 1993 book was not only a chronicle of the potential breakthrough of comics (which he redefined as "sequential art") into a legitimate art form but a sterling example itself of the medium's astonishing untapped potential. Now, seven years later, he chronicles the failure of the comic book industry to fulfill that promise, but also explores ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:56:28">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zhall001/article/10319825</link><title>The absence of black supervillains in mainstream comics</title><description>Both the DC and Marvel universes feature a litany of supervillains who wield great power and great intellect and who pose a true threat to the superheroes in these respective universes. However, relatively few of these supervillains are black. As this essay shall suggest, a number of narratological constraints and tendencies that historically have been replete in mainstream comics are largely the cause of this absence. Following a delimiting of the terms black and supervillain, this essay ? through an overview ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:57:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mstone/article/963602</link><title>Understanding Comics</title><description>A comic book about comic books. McCloud, in an incredibly accessible style, explains the details of how comics work: how they're composed, read and understood. More than just a book about comics, this gets to the heart of how we deal with visual languages in general. "The potential of comics is limitless and exciting!" writes McCloud. This should be required reading for every school teacher. Pulitzer Prize-winner Art Spiegelman says, "The most intelligent comics I've seen in a long time." Praised ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7480-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7480_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:58:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Torsten_Holmer/article/2353465</link><title>The Language of Comics (Intertext)</title><description>The Intertext series has been specifically designed to meet the needs of contemporary English Language Studies. Working with Texts: A core introduction to language analysis (second edition, 2001) is the foundation text, which is complemented by a range of 'satellite' titles. These provide students with hands-on practical experience of textual analysis through special topics and can be used individually or in conjunction with Working with Texts.&lt;br&gt; The Language of Comics: *includes a large number of real comics, from individual ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>