<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:59:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:59:54">http://www.citeulike.org/group/4364/article/7878116</link><title>Double-dose versus standard-dose clopidogrel and high-dose versus low-dose aspirin in individuals undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention for acute coronary syndromes (CURRENT-OASIS 7): a randomised factorial trial.</title><description>Clopidogrel and aspirin are the most commonly used antiplatelet therapies for percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI). We assessed the effect of various clopidogrel and aspirin regimens in prevention of major cardiovascular events and stent thrombosis in patients undergoing PCI. The CURRENT-OASIS 7 trial was undertaken in 597 centres in 39 countries. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:00:52">http://www.citeulike.org/group/4364/article/7878097</link><title>Dose comparisons of clopidogrel and aspirin in acute coronary syndromes.</title><description>Clopidogrel and aspirin are widely used for patients with acute coronary syndromes and those undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI). However, evidence-based guidelines for dosing have not been established for either agent. We randomly assigned, in a 2-by-2 factorial design, 25,086 patients with an acute coronary syndrome who were referred for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:01:17">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2119881</link><title>6. Monetary Policy Transmission and the Financial System in Germany</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:02:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pedagand/article/2096761</link><title>Can we contain Internet worms?</title><description>Worm containment must be automatic because worms can spread too fast for humans to respond. Recent work has proposed a network centric approach to automate worm containment: network traffic is analyzed to derive a packet classifier that blocks (or rate-limits) worm propagation. This approach has fundamental limitations because the analysis has no information about the application vulnerabilities exploited by worms. This paper proposes Vigilante, a new host centric approach for automatic worm... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:03:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/thonnardo/article/710518</link><title>Modeling the spread of active worms</title><description>Active worms spread in an automated fashion and can flood the Internet in a very short time. Modeling the spread of active worms can help us understand how active worms spread, and how we can monitor and defend against the propagation of worms effectively. In this paper, we present a mathematical model, referred to as the Analytical Active Worm Propagation (AAWP) model, which characterizes the propagation of worms that employ random scanning. We compare our model with the Epidemiological model... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:04:37">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4404703</link><title>Nexus VII: Relationships Between Architecture and Mathematics</title><description>Abstract.  Sylvie Duvernoy reports on the seventh international, interdisciplinary Nexus conference for architecture and mathematics. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:05:16">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9006726</link><title>Empirical likelihood based confidence regions for first order parameters of heavy-tailed distributions</title><description>Let X1,…,Xn be some i.i.d. observations from a heavy-tailed distribution F, i.e. the common distribution of the excesses over a high threshold un can be approximated by a generalized Pareto distribution Gγ,σn with γ&gt;0\. This paper deals with the problem of finding confidence regions for the couple (γ,σn): combining the empirical likelihood methodology with estimation equations (close but not identical to the likelihood equations) introduced by Zhang (2007), asymptotically valid confidence regions for (γ,σn) are obtained and proved to perform better ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:05:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8999356</link><title>Nexus 2010: Relationships between Architecture and Mathematics</title><description>The eighth edition of the international, interdisciplinary Nexus conference on architecture and mathematics took place from Sunday 13 June through Tuesday 15 June 2010, in Porto, Portugal. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:06:21">http://www.citeulike.org/article/60238</link><title>The Maturing of British Commercial Cartography: William Faden (1749-1836) and the Map Trade</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7481-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7481_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:07:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pedagand/article/382114</link><title>Vigilante: end-to-end containment of internet worms</title><description>Worm containment must be automatic because worms can spread too fast for humans to respond. Recent work has proposed network-level techniques to automate worm containment; these techniques have limitations because there is no information about the vulnerabilities exploited by worms at the network level. We propose Vigilante, a new end-to-end approach to contain worms automatically that addresses these limitations. Vigilante relies on collaborative worm detection at end hosts, but does not require hosts to trust each other. Hosts run instrumented software ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>