<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:08:48" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:08:52">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14517/article/7095583</link><title>What is Twitter, a social network or a news media?</title><description>Twitter, a microblogging service less than three years old, commands more than 41 million users as of July 2009 and is growing fast. Twitter users tweet about any topic within the 140-character limit and follow others to receive their tweets. The goal of this paper is to study the topological characteristics of Twitter and its power as a new medium of information sharing. We have crawled the entire Twitter site and obtained 41.7 million user profiles, 1.47 billion social relations, 4,262 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:09:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xsongx/article/10239773</link><title>Predicting popular messages in Twitter</title><description>Social network services have become a viable source of information for users. In Twitter, information deemed important by the community propagates through retweets. Studying the characteristics of such popular messages is important for a number of tasks, such as breaking news detection, personalized message recommendation, viral marketing and others. This paper investigates the problem of predicting the popularity of messages as measured by the number of future retweets and sheds some light on what kinds of factors influence information propagation in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:09:57">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14517/article/2580227</link><title>Why we twitter: understanding microblogging usage and communities</title><description>Microblogging is a new form of communication in which users can describe their current status in short posts distributed by instant messages, mobile phones, email or the Web. Twitter, a popular microblogging tool has seen a lot of growth since it launched in October, 2006. In this paper, we present our observations of the microblogging phenomena by studying the topological and geographical properties of Twitter's social network. We find that people use microblogging to talk about their daily activities and to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:10:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/musen/article/8512222</link><title>Twitter use by the U.S. Congress</title><description>Twitter is a microblogging and social networking service with millions of members and growing at a tremendous rate. With the buzz surrounding the service have come claims of its ability to transform the way people interact and share information and calls for public figures to start using the service. In this study, we are interested in the type of content that legislators are posting to the service, particularly by members of the United States Congress. We read and analyzed the content ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:11:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/darbabe6949/article/3909297</link><title>Ethical guidelines for promoting prosocial messages through the popular media</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:13:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/benhorrigan/article/7510011</link><title>Seems stupid until you try it: press coverage of Twitter, 2006-9</title><description>While critics of Twitter, the most popular microblogging application, dismiss the service as frivolous, proponents tout a variety of educational, political and commercial uses. Drawing from social construction theories of technology, this research uses the grounded theory approach to analyze press coverage of this emerging technology from 2006 through the first months of 2009. While the specifics of Twitter may be new, this research demonstrates that the public response to this web tool is similar to the public reaction to earlier ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:14:53">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16434/article/9723144</link><title>Geography of Twitter networks</title><description>The paper examines the influence of geographic distance, national boundaries, language, and frequency of air travel on the formation of social ties on Twitter, a popular micro-blogging website. Based on a large sample of publicly available Twitter data, our study shows that a substantial share of ties lies within the same metropolitan region, and that between regional clusters, distance, national borders and language differences all predict Twitter ties. We find that the frequency of airline flights between the two parties is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:15:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/xsongx/article/10176678</link><title>A Sentiment Analysis of Audiences on Twitter: Who Is the Positive or Negative Audience of Popular Twitterers? Convergence and Hybrid Information Technology</title><description>Microblogging is a new informal communication medium of blogging that differs from a traditional blog in which content is much shorter. Microbloggers post about topics that describe their current status. Twitter is a popular microblogging service and social media where users read and write millions of short messages on any topics within the 140-character limit. Twitter is used to find the context of social trend. Popular or influential users tweet about their status and are retweeted, mentioned or replied to by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:16:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pgsimoes/article/8850489</link><title>Twitter use by the U.S. Congress</title><description>Twitter is a microblogging and social networking service with millions of members and growing at a tremendous rate. With the buzz surrounding the service have come claims of its ability to transform the way people interact and share information and calls for public figures to start using the service. In this study, we are interested in the type of content that legislators are posting to the service, particularly by members of the United States Congress. We read and analyzed the content ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:17:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/pgsimoes/article/9075424</link><title>Information credibility on twitter</title><description>We analyze the information credibility of news propagated through Twitter, a popular microblogging service. Previous research has shown that most of the messages posted on Twitter are truthful, but the service is also used to spread misinformation and false rumors, often unintentionally. On this paper we focus on automatic methods for assessing the credibility of a given set of tweets. Specifically, we analyze microblog postings related to "trending" topics, and classify them as credible or not credible, based on features extracted ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>