<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:18:51" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:18:55">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16963/article/3972982</link><title>Learning Facebook Platform Fundamentals</title><description>As mentioned in Chapter 1, there are five main components of the Facebook platform: API calls, Facebook Markup Language (FBML), Facebook Query Language (FQL), Facebook JavaScript (FBJS), and the client libraries. I consider the client libraries for the various languages to be part of the platform because they are useful abstractions for the specific language in which you are implementing your code. The examples in this chapter will utilize the PHP client library from Facebook, so if you’re using a different ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:20:04">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16963/article/3972988</link><title>Introducing the Facebook Platform</title><description>Facebook (http://www.facebook.com) has grown phenomenally over the past several years from an Ivy League social web application to the second largest social web site on the Internet. The creators of Facebook have done an impressive job focusing their social software on the college demographic. In a natural progression of the social network, Facebook recently extended its network by developing a platform for developers to create new applications to allow Facebook users to interact in new and exciting ways. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:20:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dmaweb/article/3280465</link><title>Building a Facebook Application, Start to Finish</title><description>By now you should have a good understanding of how Facebook allows you to implement your own code to extend its platform. I’ve covered how the different parts work, and I hope you’ve been able to take portions of the platform for a test-drive. However, I haven’t talked about how all these pieces fit together. To that end, this chapter focuses on developing a Facebook application from start to finish. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:21:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/davidallmandring/article/8974798</link><title>Facebook marketing : an hour a day</title><description>"Packed with smart tactics and invaluable tips, this unique book shows you how to leverage everything Facebook has to offer, from events and applications to pay-per-click advertising, analytics, Facebook Connect, and much more. See how other companies are succeeding, find out what to do and what not to do, and produce a winning campaing with this hands-on guide" --Cover, p. 4. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:23:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/incubos/article/12721473</link><title>Finding a Needle in Haystack: Facebookâs Photo Storage</title><description>This paper describes Haystack, an object storage system optimized for Facebookâs Photos application. Facebook currently stores over 260 billion images, which translates to over 20 petabytes of data. Users upload one billion new photos (â¼60 terabytes) each week and Facebook serves over one million images per second at peak. Haystack provides a less expensive and higher performing solution than our previous approach, which leveraged network attached storage appliances over NFS. Our key observation is that this traditional design incurs an excessive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:23:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fmccown/article/3840244</link><title>Poking facebook: characterization of osn applications</title><description>Facebook is one of the most popular Internet sites today. A key feature that arguably contributed to Facebook's unprecedented success is its application platform, which enables the development of third-party social-networking applications. Understanding how these applications are installed and used is important for the function and utility of web-based online social networks, e.g. to better engineer them and/or to design advertising campaigns. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:24:47">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16963/article/8529418</link><title>Students’ and teachers’ use of Facebook</title><description>The purpose of this article is to review current published research studies focusing on the use of Facebook by students and teachers. The aim of the review is not to solely discuss Facebook in relation to teaching or learning purposes, or about its educational value per se, but also to present a detailed account of the participants’ Facebook usage profile or the extent to which users are engaged in Facebook activities. The emphasis of this review will be upon empirical findings ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:25:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ricardopetri/article/7356276</link><title>Personality and motivations associated with Facebook use</title><description>Facebook is quickly becoming one of the most popular tools for social communication. However, Facebook is somewhat different from other Social Networking Sites as it demonstrates an offline-to-online trend; that is, the majority of Facebook Friends are met offline and then added later. The present research investigated how the Five-Factor Model of personality relates to Facebook use. Despite some expected trends regarding Extraversion and Openness to Experience, results indicated that personality factors were not as influential as previous literature would suggest. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:26:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kajakbent/article/3292392</link><title>Facebook: the missing manual</title><description>Facebook is the wildly popular, free social networking site that combines the best of blogs, online forums, photo sharing, clever applications, and interaction among friends. The one thing it doesn't have is a user's guide to help you truly take advantage of it. Until now. Facebook: The Missing Manual gives you a crystal clear and entertaining look at everything this fascinating Facebook phenomenon has to offer. Teeming with high-quality color graphics, each page in this Missing Manual is uniquely designed to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:27:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/aletteschoon/article/10678818</link><title>A Review of Facebook Research in the Social Sciences</title><description>With over 800 million active users, Facebook is changing the way hundreds of millions of people relate to one another and share information. A rapidly growing body of research has accompanied the meteoric rise of Facebook as social scientists assess the impact of Facebook on social life. In addition, researchers have recognized the utility of Facebook as a novel tool to observe behavior in a naturalistic setting, test hypotheses, and recruit participants. However, research on Facebook emanates from a wide variety ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>