<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:28:30" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:28:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Montxolopez/article/4225804</link><title>Response analysis of a submarine cable under fault movement</title><description>Based on the performance of submarine cables in past earthquakes, an analytical method to determine cable performance under seabed fault movement is proposed in this paper. First, common types of earthquake damage to submarine cables are summarized, which include seabed displacement induced by fault movement, submarine landslides and seabed soil liquefaction, etc. The damage is similar to damage observed to buried pipelines following land earthquakes. The Hengchun earthquake of Dec. 26, 2006 is used as a case study. The M7.2 earthquake ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:29:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/10291085</link><title>Experimental study on the seismic response of braced reinforced concrete frame with irregular columns</title><description>A 15-storey K-braced reinforced concrete model frame with irregular columns, i.e., T-shaped, L-shaped, as well as +-shaped columns, was constructed and tested on the six-degree-of-freedom shaking table at the State Key Laboratory for Disaster Reduction in Civil Engineering in Tongji, China. Two types of earthquake records, El-Centro wave (south-north direction) and Shanghai artifi cial wave (SHAW) with various peak accelerations and principal-secondary sequences, were input and experimentally studied. Based on the shaking table tests and theoretical analysis, several observations can be ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:31:02">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9974469</link><title>Seismic design analysis of the country masonry school buildings in the meizoseismal area</title><description>Several reinforcing schemes are illustrated that are based on the loading characteristics of typical country masonry school buildings with sparsely spaced transversal walls and large depth. From the seismic damage observed following the Wenchuan Earthquake, the effects of reinforcing schemes, tie-columns and tie-beams on the seismic resistance of masonry buildings are analyzed. The concept of improving the ductility of these types of buildings is presented. Finally, some suggestions are proposed for the design of masonry buildings with sparsely spaced transversal walls ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:32:06">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11284849</link><title>Evaluation of earthquake signal characteristics for early warning</title><description>This paper evaluates different characteristics for earthquake early warning. The scaling relationships between magnitude, epicenter distance and calculated parameters are derived from earthquake event data from USGS. The standard STA/LTA method is modified by adding two new parameters to eliminate the effects of the spike-type noise and small pulsetype noise ahead of the onset of the P-wave. After the detection of the P-wave, the algorithm extracts 12 kinds of parameters from the first 3 seconds of the P-wave. Then stepwise regression ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:33:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/person/article/5317988</link><title>Empirical equations for the prediction of the equivalent number of cycles of earthquake ground motion</title><description>Estimates of the number of cycles of ground motion expected from earthquake scenarios are required for the assessment of liquefaction hazard and the hazard of seismically induced landslides. There are currently very few equations available for the prediction of this parameter despite its importance for several geotechnical applications. In this study, the strong-motion database assembled in the Next Generation of Attenuation (NGA) project is used to derive equations for two different measures of the effective numbers of cycles of ground motion ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:33:48">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11284844</link><title>Simulation of the response of base-isolated buildings under earthquake excitations considering soil flexibility</title><description>The accurate analysis of the seismic response of isolated structures requires incorporation of the flexibility of supporting soil. However, it is often customary to idealize the soil as rigid during the analysis of such structures. In this paper, seismic response time history analyses of base-isolated buildings modelled as linear single degree-of-freedom (SDOF) and multi degree-of-freedom (MDOF) systems with linear and nonlinear base models considering and ignoring the flexibility of supporting soil are conducted. The flexibility of supporting soil is modelled through ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:34:56">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11284845</link><title>Towards multiple hazard resilient bridges: a methodology for modeling frequent and infrequent time-varying loads Part II, Examples for live and earthquake load effects</title><description>The current AASHTO load and resistance factor design (LRFD) guidelines are formulated based on bridge reliability, which interprets traditional design safety factors into more rigorously deduced factors based on the theory of probability. This is a major advancement in bridge design specifications. However, LRFD is only calibrated for dead and live loads. In cases when extreme loads are significant, they need to be individually assessed. Combining regular loads with extreme loads has been a major challenge, mainly because the extreme loads ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:36:04">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9308144</link><title>Preliminary analysis of a soft-storey mechanism after the 2009 L'Aquila earthquake</title><description>Abstract Observation of damage caused by the recent Abruzzo earthquake on April 6th 2009 showed how local interaction between infills and RC structures can lead to soft-storey mechanisms and brittle collapses. Results of the present case study are based on observed damage caused by the earthquake in the zone of Pettino. Analytical model based on simulated design procedure was built up and time history analyses were employed to verify the causes of the structural collapse, as highlighted by observed damage. This ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:37:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gastonfermandois/article/7765878</link><title>Performance-based earthquake early warning</title><description>Significant investments are undergoing internationally to develop earthquake early warning (EEW) systems. So far, reasonably, the most of the research in this field was lead by seismologists as the issues to determine essential feasibility of EEW were mainly related to the earthquake source. Many of them have been brilliantly solved, and the principles of this discipline are collected in the so-called real-time seismology. On the other hand, operating EEW systems rely on general-purpose intensity measures as proxies for the impending ground ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7484-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7484_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:37:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/10291084</link><title>Vulnerability of ordinary moment resistant concrete frames</title><description>The effects of structural modeling (bar slip in lap splice), ground motion selection process (epsilon effect) and size of a structure (number of bays and stories) on the fragility of reinforced concrete ordinary moment resisting frames are investigated. An analytical model is developed to account for bar slip in lap splice, which exhibits good correlation with existing experimental data. Then, incremental dynamic analysis is used to derive the fragility curves for four model structures. The model structures simulate frames with a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>