<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:50:13" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:50:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10902952</link><title>The Routledge International Handbook of Teacher and School Development</title><description>The International Handbook of Teacher and School Development brings together a collection of research and evidence-based authoritative writings which focus on international teacher and school development. Drawing on research from 18 countries across 7 continents, the 40 chapters are grouped into 10 themes which represent key aspects of teacher and school development: (1) Issues of Professionalism and Performativity; (2) What Being an Effective Teacher Really Means; (3) Reason and Emotion in Teaching; (4) Schools in Different Circumstances; (5) Student Voices in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:51:20">http://www.citeulike.org/group/902/article/1420168</link><title>Intestinal Bacteria Trigger T Cell-Independent Immunoglobulin A2 Class Switching by Inducing Epithelial-Cell Secretion of the Cytokine APRIL</title><description>Summary Bacteria colonize the intestine shortly after birth and thereafter exert several beneficial functions, including induction of protective immunoglobulin A (IgA) antibodies. The distal intestine contains IgA2, which is more resistant to bacterial proteases than is IgA1. The mechanism by which B cells switch from IgM to IgA2 remains unknown. We found that human intestinal epithelial cells (IECs) triggered IgA2 class switching in B cells, including IgA1-expressing B cells arriving from mucosal follicles, through a CD4+ T cell-independent pathway involving a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:52:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ideas/article/5822979</link><title>Children's Observations, Ideas, and Development of Classroom Theories about Light.</title><description>Involves students in a study designed to examine the interaction between children's observations of light and shadows and their developing theories in the context of a series of lessons in a third-grade classroom. Results suggest that student's observation of light led to the development of a limited theory about light that was largely useful in explaining classroom investigations. (ZWH) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:53:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cobi/article/5720739</link><title>Science: Can We Trust the Experts? (Debating Matters)</title><description>Controversies surrounding a plethora of issues, from the MMR vaccine to mobile phones, from BSE to genetically-modified foods, have led many to ask how the public's faith in government advice can be restored. At the heart of the matter is the role of the expert and the question of whose opinion to trust. In this book, prominent participants in the debate tell us their views. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:55:18">http://www.citeulike.org/group/9645/article/1204557</link><title>Botany in a Day: The Patterns Method of Plant Identification</title><description>Looking for a faster, easier, and fun way to identify plants? Botany in a Day teaches you the patterns method of plant identification, so that you can discover the wonderful world of plants around you, wherever you go. &lt;P&gt;Instead of trying to identify plants one-at-a-time, Botany in a Day give you a way to learn them by the hundreds, based on the principle that related plants have similar patterns for indentification, and they often have similar uses. &lt;P&gt;The one-day ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:56:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/zbuck/article/9312368</link><title>Learning science: A Deweyan perspective</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:57:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/damiantrj/article/7241781</link><title>Lymphoma B Cells Evade Apoptosis through the TNF Family Members BAFF/BLyS and APRIL</title><description>The mechanisms underlying the autonomous accumulation of malignant B cells remain elusive. We show in this study that non-Hodgkin's lymphoma (NHL) B cells express B cell-activating factor of the TNF family (BAFF) and a proliferation-inducing ligand (APRIL), two powerful B cell-activating molecules usually expressed by myeloid cells. In addition, NHL B cells express BAFF receptor, which binds BAFF, as well as transmembrane activator and calcium modulator and cyclophilin ligand interactor (TACI) and B cell maturation Ag (BCMA), which bind both BAFF ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:57:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/boesswetter/article/6252356</link><title>Interactive ROLAP on Large Datasets: A Case Study with UB-Trees</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:59:07">http://www.citeulike.org/user/boesswetter/article/6252343</link><title>Interval Processing with the UB-Tree</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7487-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7487_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:00:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/boesswetter/article/6252360</link><title>Bulk Loading a Data Warehouse Built Upon a UB-Tree</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>