<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:04" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/ehchalus/article/138952</link><title>Shop Design and the Display of Goods in Eighteenth-Century London</title><description>A good background piece on the nature and detail of 18C shops, their construction, fittings, decor, etc. Some excellent images of trade cards and engravings.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:02:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vmantas/article/5176486</link><title>Deciding on Open Innovation: An Exploration of How Firms Create and Capture Value with Open Source Software Open IT-Based Innovation: Moving Towards Cooperative IT Transfer and Knowledge Diffusion</title><description>Open innovation is a paradigm that proposes that firms can and should use external as well as internal innovations/ideas. A popular example of open innovation has been open source software (OSS). The key issues facing organizational decision makers considering OSS strategies is, how does the firm create value for the customer while simultaneously extracting value for itself? However, the adoption of OSS as part of an open innovation strategy is a recent phenomenon and many unanswered questions remain. Taking the viewpoint ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:03:27">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alanebeatrizvermelho/article/9787343</link><title>The ecology of open-source software development</title><description>Open Source Software (ass) is an innovative method of developing software applications that has been very successful over the past eight to ten years. A number of theories have emerged to explain its success, mainly from economics and law. We analyze a very large sample of ass projects and find striking patterns in the overall structure of the development community. The distribution of projects on a range of activity measures is spectacularly skewed, with only a relatively tiny number of projects ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:04:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/8886930</link><title>The Our House DIY Club</title><description>• This article explores the rise of do-it-yourself (DIY) amateur home renovation practices, within the context of cultural, media and leisure studies debates about amateurs, experts and the circulation of knowledge, and, in particular, the increasingly visible role of lifestyle media experts. Lifestyle television fosters a neoliberal system of governance at a distance which seeks to create enterprising citizens. Through a digital ethnography of the Our House DIY Club — a home-improvement online forum — this article argues that amateur DIYers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:05:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/iCeGS/article/9401850</link><title>Beyond Reasonable Doubt: A Guide to Designing Experiments in the Behavioural Sciences</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:06:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9038976</link><title>DIY Home Improvements in a Post-Soviet Housing Market: A Socio-Spatial Analysis of Vilnius, Lithuania</title><description>As part of the Large Analysis and Review of European housing and health Status (LARES), the WHO collected data in eight European cities during 2001 and 2002. Using this data, the paper analyses home-related do-it-yourself (DIY) activities in Vilnius, Lithuania where housing was privatized following the collapse of Communism. The paper investigates whether DIY activities were prevalent near the Old Town where officials encouraged renovation. It was found that overall, DIY activities were prevalent among households in 20012002 regardless of socio-economic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:07:55">http://www.citeulike.org/user/vmantas/article/5037467</link><title>Community for Innovations: Developing an Integrated Concept for Open Innovation Open IT-Based Innovation: Moving Towards Cooperative IT Transfer and Knowledge Diffusion</title><description>This paper presents a research project called GENIE. It aims at developing a concept for integrating external stakeholders into a company’s innovation management through a virtual community. This novel instrument for opening up a company’s innovation process to external stakeholders enables collaborative creation and implementation of innovations along the entire innovation process. We focus on software companies and aim at developing and testing this approach in several real-world settings. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:08:56">http://www.citeulike.org/group/13894/article/8960164</link><title>Open educational practices and resources: OLCOS Roadmap 2012</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:09:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tcook202/article/5346766</link><title>Can Knowledge Management be Open Source?</title><description>As we move further into a knowledge economy where collaboration and innovation are increasingly central to organisational effectiveness, enterprises need to pay more attention to the informal networks that exist within the organisation. Wikis may provide a more appropriate knowledge management capability and environment to capture tacit knowledge. Where traditional organisational cultures see that knowledge management must be tightly protected, Wikis opt for an open source approach where knowledge is shared and distributed for innovation to continue. This paper aims to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7488-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7488_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:10:26">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/9040079</link><title>Choice or necessity? A review of the role of DIY in tackling housing repair and maintenance</title><description>Do-it-yourself (DIY) is a staple element of the spare time activities of many households, but little is known about the extent to which basic repair work is carried out through DIY and about the quality of this work. Through secondary analyses of UK government data (English House Condition Survey and Family Expenditure Survey), this paper examines the scale of DIY work by owner-occupiers, how work is organized, the interrelationship of DIY work, the use of unpaid help, and the use of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>