<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:11:35" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:11:40">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14100/article/2812704</link><title>The Best of MAKE (Make)</title><description>After two years, MAKE has become one of most celebrated new magazines to hit the newsstands, and certainly one of the hottest reads. If you're just catching on to the MAKE phenomenon and wonder what you've missed, this book contains the best DIY projects from the magazine's first ten volumes -- a surefire collection of fun and challenging activities going back to MAKE's launch in early 2005. Find out why MAKE has attracted a passionate following of tech and DIY enthusiasts worldwide with one million web site visitors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:12:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Cyron/article/5804298</link><title>Novel multidisciplinary approach for treatment of langerhans cell histiocytosis of the skull base.</title><description>Langerhans cell histiocytosis frequently manifests as lesions of the skull. The disease can present with a wide spectrum of forms, from an isolated eosinophilic granuloma to multiple lesions with diffuse systemic involvement. The authors report the case of a 12-year-old boy with a 1-month history of left temporal and periorbital pain and headaches. Noncontrast computed tomography of the head was done at the time of initial presentation and was interpreted as normal. Over the next month, the patient continued to have ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:12:59">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6397953</link><title>Sustainability and innovation through the recession</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:13:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/2874430</link><title>How can we assess outcomes of clinical trials: the MCID approach.</title><description>Interpreting changes in outcomes of clinical trials in chronic obstructive pulmonary disease should be viewed from a broader perspective than only the statistical significance of the findings. The minimal clinical difference in outcome measures provides a conceptual framework to assist in clinical trial interpretation and a methodology to assess the clinical relevance of study results. Use of distribution-based techniques, comparison with other external measures, and opinions from experts, clinicians and patients can assist in minimal clinically important difference development. Although the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:15:02">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7377306</link><title>Emerging economies, sun care and sustainability</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:16:00">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9359551</link><title>Asian growth, Chinese investments, but prices increase</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:16:41">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10168745</link><title>Sensory perception, other innovations and investment locations</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:18:12">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10380288</link><title>Asian oleochemicals, company strategies and megatrends</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:18:53">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10692939</link><title>Southeast asian investments, sustainable developments, and treatment for premature infants</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:19:18">http://www.citeulike.org/article/11242419</link><title>Eurozone crisis, green chemistry, and fundamental research</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>