<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:19:45" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:19:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/398865</link><title>Europe and the Crisis in Scientific Vocations</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:20:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/verderadiante/article/3361043</link><title>The mp3 as cultural artifact</title><description>The mp3 lies at the center of important debates around intellectual property and file-sharing, but it is also a cultural artifact in its own right. This article examines the design of the mp3 from both industrial and psychoacoustic perspectives to explain better why mp3s are so easy to exchange and the auditory dimensions of that process of exchange. As a container technology for recorded sound, the mp3 shows that the quality of portability' is central to the history ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:21:37">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Amazoness/article/2900995</link><title>MP3 players and hearing loss: adolescents' perceptions of loud music and hearing conservation.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To explore adolescents' behaviors and opinions about exposure to loud music from MP3 players. STUDY DESIGN: We conducted a qualitative analysis of focus-group discussions with adolescents aged 12 to 18 years from 2 large secondary schools (1 urban and 1 rural) for pre-vocational and pre-university education. The semi-structured question route was theoretically framed within the protection motivation theory. RESULTS: Most adolescents-especially male students and students from pre-vocational schools-indicated that they often played their MP3 players at maximum volume. Although they ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:22:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/songpku/article/7432942</link><title>convert: A user-friendly program to reformat diploid genotypic data for commonly used population genetic software packages</title><description>convert is a user-friendly, 32-bit Windows program that facilitates ready transfer of codominant, diploid genotypic data amongst commonly used population genetic software packages. convert reads input files in its own 'standard' data format, easily produced from an excel file of diploid, codominant marker data, and can convert these to the input formats of the following programs: gda, genepop, arlequin, popgene, microsat, phylip, and structure. convert can also read input files in genepop format. In addition, convert can produce a summary table ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:23:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kris246/article/6661276</link><title>Adolescents and MP3 Players: Too Many Risks, Too Few Precautions</title><description>OBJECTIVE. The goal was to assess risky and protective listening behaviors of adolescent users of MP3 players and the association of these behaviors with demographic characteristics and frequency of use. METHODS. In 2007, 1687 adolescents (12-19 years of age) in 68 classes in 15 Dutch secondary schools were invited to complete questionnaires about their music-listening behaviors. RESULTS. Ninety percent of participants reported listening to music through earphones on MP3 players; 32.8% were frequent users, 48.0% used high volume settings, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:24:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brainsman2000/article/9698080</link><title>Lower Malignancy Rates in Renal Allograft Recipients Converted to Sirolimus-Based, Calcineurin Inhibitor-Free Immunotherapy: 24-Month Results From the CONVERT Trial.</title><description>BACKGROUND.: Long-term immunosuppression imposes increased malignancy risk in renal allograft recipients, significantly contributing to overall morbidity and mortality. This study examined malignancy rates in renal allograft recipients at 2 years after conversion to a sirolimus (SRL)-based, calcineurin inhibitor (CNI)-free regimen. METHODS.: This open-label, randomized, multicenter study (the CONVERT Trial) randomly assigned 830 patients to SRL conversion (n=555) or CNI continuation (n=275). Patients with history of posttransplant lymphoproliferative disease or known/suspected malignancy within 5 years before screening were excluded. As part of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:25:40">http://www.citeulike.org/article/398861</link><title>Scientific Vocations in Crisis in France: explanatory social developments and mechanisms</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:26:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/legend4431/article/6602377</link><title>Audio-text synchronization inside mp3 files: a new approach and its implementation</title><description>The large usage of multimedia portable devices has contributed to a rapid increase in the demand for multimedia entertainment services. We focus on the karaoke service: several systems have been proposed but they are too difficult to be used directly over audio devices. Conversely, we propose a very simple approach to providing a karaoke-like service over any audio device that can play out mp3 files. Our approach is essentially new, as no additional files, beyond the mp3 file, are necessary. A ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:27:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/6185000</link><title>Conversion from calcineurin inhibitors to sirolimus maintenance therapy in renal allograft recipients: 24-month efficacy and safety results from the CONVERT trial.</title><description>BACKGROUND: The efficacy and safety of converting maintenance renal transplant recipients from calcineurin inhibitors (CNIs) to sirolimus (SRL) was evaluated. METHODS: Eight hundred thirty renal allograft recipients, 6 to 120 months posttransplant and receiving cyclosporine or tacrolimus, were randomly assigned to continue CNI (n=275) or convert from CNI to SRL (n=555). Primary endpoints were calculated Nankivell glomerular filtration rate (GFR; stratified at baseline: 20-40 vs. &gt;40 mL/min) and the cumulative rates of biopsy-confirmed acute rejection (BCAR), graft loss, or death at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7490-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7490_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:29:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fjc1/article/320246</link><title>Preferential conformation of substance P in solution.</title><description>The three-dimensional structure of substance P has been studied by 1H-NMR, (500 MHz), and by circular dichroism (CD) in different solvents. The analysis of the different NMR parameters suggest that substance P adopts a rather extended structure in dimethylsulfoxide and pyridine. In water, besides the aggregation phenomenon, the monomeric substance P presents a complex conformational equilibrium. The addition of sodium dodecylsulfate to the aqueous solution induces, as shown by CD spectroscopy, a preferential alpha-helical conformation. And in methanol three structural conclusions ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>