<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:29:40" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:29:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/songpku/article/7432942</link><title>convert: A user-friendly program to reformat diploid genotypic data for commonly used population genetic software packages</title><description>convert is a user-friendly, 32-bit Windows program that facilitates ready transfer of codominant, diploid genotypic data amongst commonly used population genetic software packages. convert reads input files in its own 'standard' data format, easily produced from an excel file of diploid, codominant marker data, and can convert these to the input formats of the following programs: gda, genepop, arlequin, popgene, microsat, phylip, and structure. convert can also read input files in genepop format. In addition, convert can produce a summary table ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:31:16">http://www.citeulike.org/user/scis0000001/article/984274</link><title>TBPG -- A Techniques-Based</title><description>In this work we address program generation for simulation models in a restricted class of ecological domain. A first approach to deal with this problem, the EL Program Generation System was presented in [Robertson et al. 91]. That system produced a Prolog program by assembling modular predicate-level definitions obtained from a library of program schemata. The approach presented here is to use Prolog Programming Techniques as the element of program construction which acting in a clause-level,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:32:33">http://www.citeulike.org/article/398865</link><title>Europe and the Crisis in Scientific Vocations</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:33:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/verderadiante/article/3361043</link><title>The mp3 as cultural artifact</title><description>The mp3 lies at the center of important debates around intellectual property and file-sharing, but it is also a cultural artifact in its own right. This article examines the design of the mp3 from both industrial and psychoacoustic perspectives to explain better why mp3s are so easy to exchange and the auditory dimensions of that process of exchange. As a container technology for recorded sound, the mp3 shows that the quality of portability' is central to the history ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:34:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Amazoness/article/2900995</link><title>MP3 players and hearing loss: adolescents' perceptions of loud music and hearing conservation.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: To explore adolescents' behaviors and opinions about exposure to loud music from MP3 players. STUDY DESIGN: We conducted a qualitative analysis of focus-group discussions with adolescents aged 12 to 18 years from 2 large secondary schools (1 urban and 1 rural) for pre-vocational and pre-university education. The semi-structured question route was theoretically framed within the protection motivation theory. RESULTS: Most adolescents-especially male students and students from pre-vocational schools-indicated that they often played their MP3 players at maximum volume. Although they ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:35:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/4145621</link><title>Changes in albumin excretion in the diabetes prevention program.</title><description>OBJECTIVE: Increased urinary albumin excretion rates have been linked to nephropathy and macrovascular disease. We here describe the baseline prevalence and effect of Diabetes Prevention Program (DPP) interventions on the development and reversal of elevated albumin excretion. RESEARCH DESIGN AND METHODS: Urine albumin-to-creatinine ratios (ACRs) were calculated from untimed urine collections. Analyses compared participants by treatment group, diabetes and hypertension status, and use of ACE inhibitors or angiotensin II receptor blockers (ARBs). RESULTS: Elevated ACR levels (&gt;or=30 mg/g creatinine) were present ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:36:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/michaelbanks/article/5095768</link><title>Combining Different Proof Techniques for Verifying Information Flow Security</title><description>When giving a program access to secret information, one must ensure that the program does not leak the secrets to untrusted sinks. For reducing the complexity of such an information flow analysis, one can employ compositional proof techniques. In this article, we present a new approach to analyzing information flow security in a compositional manner. Instead of committing to a proof technique at the beginning of a verification, this choice is made during verification with the option of flexibly migrating to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:37:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kris246/article/6661276</link><title>Adolescents and MP3 Players: Too Many Risks, Too Few Precautions</title><description>OBJECTIVE. The goal was to assess risky and protective listening behaviors of adolescent users of MP3 players and the association of these behaviors with demographic characteristics and frequency of use. METHODS. In 2007, 1687 adolescents (12-19 years of age) in 68 classes in 15 Dutch secondary schools were invited to complete questionnaires about their music-listening behaviors. RESULTS. Ninety percent of participants reported listening to music through earphones on MP3 players; 32.8% were frequent users, 48.0% used high volume settings, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:39:21">http://www.citeulike.org/user/brainsman2000/article/9698080</link><title>Lower Malignancy Rates in Renal Allograft Recipients Converted to Sirolimus-Based, Calcineurin Inhibitor-Free Immunotherapy: 24-Month Results From the CONVERT Trial.</title><description>BACKGROUND.: Long-term immunosuppression imposes increased malignancy risk in renal allograft recipients, significantly contributing to overall morbidity and mortality. This study examined malignancy rates in renal allograft recipients at 2 years after conversion to a sirolimus (SRL)-based, calcineurin inhibitor (CNI)-free regimen. METHODS.: This open-label, randomized, multicenter study (the CONVERT Trial) randomly assigned 830 patients to SRL conversion (n=555) or CNI continuation (n=275). Patients with history of posttransplant lymphoproliferative disease or known/suspected malignancy within 5 years before screening were excluded. As part of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7491-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7491_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:40:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/398861</link><title>Scientific Vocations in Crisis in France: explanatory social developments and mechanisms</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>