<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:41:40" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:41:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Scis0000002/article/5778107</link><title>GraPHIA: a computational model for identifying phonological jokes.</title><description>Currently in humor research, there exists a dearth of computational models for humor perception. The existing theories are not quantifiable and efforts need to be made to quantify the models and incorporate neuropsychological findings in humor research. We propose a new computational model (GraPHIA) for perceiving phonological jokes or puns. GraPHIA consists of a semantic network and a phonological network where words are represented by nodes in both the networks. Novel features based on graph theoretical concepts are proposed and computed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:42:58">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jennybargelski/article/987741</link><title>Graeme Ritchie, The Linguistic Analysis of Jokes</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:44:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/11896481</link><title>Math Jokes 4 Mathy Folks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:45:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Laurentjp/article/5981184</link><title>The functional anatomy of humor: segregating cognitive and affective components</title><description>Humor, a unique human characteristic, is critical in thought, communication and social interaction. Successful jokes involve a cognitive juxtaposition of mental sets, followed by an affective feeling of amusement; we isolated these two components of humor by using event-related fMRI on subjects who listened to auditorily presented semantic and phonological jokes (puns) and indicated whether or not they found the items amusing. Our findings suggest that whereas there are modality-specific pathways for processing the juxtaposition of mental sets necessary for the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:46:23">http://www.citeulike.org/article/89085</link><title>Hair color changes caused by dyeing and thermal treatments</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:47:32">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4944931</link><title>Identification and characterization of a novel Tritimovirus species isolated from wild Trisetum flavescens L., family Poaceae</title><description>Abstract  Yellow oat-grass plants (Trisetum flavescens L.) with mild mosaic and pronounced dwarfing symptoms were observed at different locations in the Czech Republic. Electron microscope observations of symptomatic plants revealed the presence of filamentous particles and inclusion bodies characteristic of the family Potyviridae. The virus was readily mechanically transmitted to its original host plus a narrow host range of monocot species. Serological assays of infected plant extracts using antiserum specific to the closest species in the family Potyviridae were negative. The 3′ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:48:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/WilliamHartPhD/article/10801797</link><title>The truth (with jokes)</title><description>Nearly a year after the presidential election of 2004, Al Franken is still checking facts, exposing lies, and trying to clear the record as he sees it. Sneering at President Bush's declaration of a mandate after a two-and-a-half percent victory, he deconstructs Bush's 2004 platform of "fear, smear, and queers," and explains how the president has done some flip-flopping of his own. He offers comment on well-known stories, including the Terri Schiavo case, and some more obscure, such as reports of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:49:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jennybargelski/article/6242716</link><title>The Comparative Study of Jokes</title><description>Abstract  Jokes can only properly be studied comparatively and in relation to differences in the social structure and culture of the two or more countries where they are told. This is best done by looking at how joke cycles, large aggregates of jokes, change as they move between two countries that have the same language. American stupidity jokes about Poles and blondes changed significantly when they came to be told in Britain about the Irish and about Essex Girls, even though the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:50:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/natkhoo/article/2278487</link><title>More Than “Just a Joke”: The Prejudice-Releasing Function of Sexist Humor</title><description>The results of two experiments supported the hypothesis that, for sexist men, exposure to sexist humor can promote the behavioral release of prejudice against women. Experiment 1 demonstrated that hostile sexism predicted the amount of money participants were willing to donate to a women's organization after reading sexist jokes but not after reading nonhumorous sexist statements or neutral jokes. Experiment 2 showed that hostile sexism predicted the amount of money participants cut from the budget of a women's organization relative to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:51:01">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tamakat/article/197294</link><title>Jokes and Their Relation to the Unconscious</title><description>Freud argues that the "joke-work" is intimately related to the "dream-work" which he had analyzed in detail in his Interpretation of Dreams, and that jokes (like all forms of humor) attest to the fundamental orderliness of the human mind. While in this book Freud tells some good stories with his customary verve and economy, its point is wholly serious. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>