<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:52:16" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:52:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sobolevnrm/article/12034685</link><title>Public response to alerts and warnings using social media : report of a workshop on current knowledge and research gaps</title><description>"Following an earlier NRC workshop on public response to alerts and warnings delivered to mobile devices, a related workshop was held on February 28 and 29, 2012 to look at the role of social media in disaster response. This was one of the first workshops convened to look systematically at the use of social media for alerts and warnings, an event that brought together social science researchers, technologists, emergency management professionals, and other experts on how the public and emergency managers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:53:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fuzbug/article/9075258</link><title>The Impact of Social Media on Children, Adolescents, and Families</title><description>Using social media Web sites is among the most common activity of today's children and adolescents. Any Web site that allows social interaction is considered a social media site, including social networking sites such as Facebook, MySpace, and Twitter; gaming sites and virtual worlds such as Club Penguin, Second Life, and the Sims; video sites such as YouTube; and blogs. Such sites offer today's youth a portal for entertainment and communication and have grown exponentially in recent years. For this reason, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:54:42">http://www.citeulike.org/group/16823/article/10375831</link><title>Why do we converse on social media?: an analysis of intrinsic and extrinsic network factors</title><description>We are motivated in our work by the following question: what factors influence individual participation in social media conversations? Conversations around user posted content, is central to the user experience in social media sites, including Facebook, YouTube and Flickr. Therefore, understanding why people participate, can have significant bearing on fundamental research questions in social network and media analysis, such as, network evolution, and information diffusion. Our approach is as follows. We first identify several key aspects of social media conversations, distinct ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:56:08">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14517/article/8859590</link><title>Communication structure and collective actions in social media</title><description>In this paper I present results a study of different types of social media communication and networking channels that allow for collective action (CA): Twitter, Jaiku / Qaiku, Ning and Facebook. My preliminary findings indicate, that the visual outlining and the structure of communication create different kinds of collectivity and collective actions. A status stream is effective for simple and fast repetitive mass actions and for individual mass broadcasting, while channels and threads are needed as a backchannel for more complicated, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:56:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lorinflores/article/6868245</link><title>Media portrayals of girls and women</title><description>"This section of the site provides a snapshot of the issues around the media's portrayal of women and girls-from effects on body image and self-identity to ramifications in sports and politics. It looks at the economic interests behind the objectification and eroticization of females by the media as well as efforts to counter negative stereotyping. And it provides the latest articles and studies that explore the ways in which media both limit and empower women and girls in society"--Title screen. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:58:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/GertieB/article/7680645</link><title>World social science report 2010: knowledge divides</title><description>Social science from Western countries continues to have the greatest global influence, but the field is expanding rapidly in Asia and Latin America, particularly in China and Brazil. In sub-Saharan Africa, social scientists from South Africa, Nigeria and Kenya produce 75% of academic publications. In South Asia, barring some centres of excellence in India, social sciences as a whole have low priority. These are a few of the findings from World Social Science Report, 2010: Knowledge divides. Produced by the International ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:58:49">http://www.citeulike.org/group/14517/article/5948091</link><title>Users of the world, unite! The challenges and opportunities of Social Media</title><description>The concept of Social Media is top of the agenda for many business executives today. Decision makers, as well as consultants, try to identify ways in which firms can make profitable use of applications such as Wikipedia, YouTube, Facebook, Second Life, and Twitter. Yet despite this interest, there seems to be very limited understanding of what the term “Social Media” exactly means; this article intends to provide some clarification. We begin by describing the concept of Social Media, and discuss how ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:59:43">http://www.citeulike.org/user/oliverthellriegel/article/10711247</link><title>Soziale Netzwerke: Facebook schluckt das Web Social Media in der Medienarbeit</title><description>Soziale Netzwerke zählten schon zu den Treffpunkten der ersten Internet-Tage. Foren haben überlebt, Compuserve ging 2009 vom Netz und gehört heute zu AOL. Die Anwendungen sind vielfältiger und trotzdem einfacher geworden, das Web ist schneller, überall und mobil. Darauf bauen die neuen Austauschplätze für Inhalte, Begegnung und Gespräch. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:00:32">http://www.citeulike.org/user/joannewhite/article/3352953</link><title>Conceptualizing personal media</title><description>The digitalization and personal use of media technologies have destabilized the traditional dichotomization between mass communication and interpersonal communication, and therefore between mass media and personal media (e.g. mobile phones, email, instant messenger, blogs and photo-sharing services). As private individuals use media technologies to create and share personal expressions through digital networks, previous characteristics of mass media as providers of generally accessible information are no longer accurate. This article may be situated within a medium-theoretical tradition, as it elucidates technical and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:01:31">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mkuhn/article/10376284</link><title>Leveraging social media for scalable object detection</title><description>In this manuscript we present a method that leverages social media for the effortless learning of object detectors. We are motivated by the fact that the increased training cost of methods demanding manual annotation, limits their ability to easily scale in different types of objects and domains. At the same time, the rapidly growing social media applications have made available a tremendous volume of tagged images, which could serve as a solution for this problem. However, the nature of annotations (i.e. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>