<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:02:06" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:02:08">http://www.citeulike.org/user/chigliak/article/6702695</link><title>FESTIVAL VISITOR MOTIVATION FROM THE ORGANIZERS POINTS OF VIEW</title><description>Festivals and special events serve as important attractors for tourists and provide unique experiences for attendees. These events may also provide both tangible and intangible benefits for communities. Most of the studies dealing with festivals and events have focused on either understanding attendees' behavior or delineating the economic impacts of visitation upon communities in which such events are held. Sporadic attention has also been paid to such issues as sponsorship, volunteerism, the role of community involvement in staging events, and perceptions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:03:15">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kailuettger/article/4307513</link><title>What makes a Good Festival? Understanding the Event Experience</title><description>This article explores the nature of extraordinary experiences through a netnographic analysis of the views of committed attendees at the 2005 Sidmouth Folk Festival. After uncertainty over finance and the withdrawal of the previous event management company, the festival eventually went ahead under a different, collaborative organization and on a reduced scale. The new format was vigorously debated by posters to an Internet message board, Mudcat Cafe, providing a wide-ranging and unprompted set of opinions on the criteria for a successful ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:03:50">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hannahparry/article/4689601</link><title>The Predictive Validity of Alternative Approaches to Evaluating Quality of a Festival</title><description>Alternative conceptualizations of the quality and satisfaction constructs are presented from both the leisure/tourism and the marketing literatures, and differences between them are noted. The predictive validity of seven alternative operationalizations of quality that were suggested by the literature were measured by evaluating them against an overall measure of quality in the context of a festival. Results showed that the most valid measures of quality were the performance-based operationalizations; the least valid were the disconfirmation-based operationalizations; and the inclusion of importance ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:04:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/annvs/article/3283727</link><title>The influence of aggressive and neutral cartoons and toys on the behaviour of preschool children</title><description>This study addressed an issue of current community concern about which there is little relevant research, namely the behavioural effects of viewing an aggressive cartoon and playing with the toys associated with it, in comparison to a neutral cartoon and toys. Sixty preschool children were observed in groups of five after viewing either an aggressive cartoon, a neutral cartoon, or no cartoon, when playing with each type of toy in turn. Levels of aggression were considerably higher when children played with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:05:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/burtsev/article/10583114</link><title>The media and the irony of politically serious situations: consequences of the Muhammed cartoons in Finland</title><description>This article discusses the connections between political conflicts and situational irony and their relationship to the media. The focus is on a continuum of ironic events that started from the crisis following the publication of the Muhammed cartoons in the Danish newspaper Jyllands-Posten, which led to a satirical comic strip being published on the web pages of Kaltio, a small cultural journal produced in Oulu, Northern Finland, and ended in the dismissal of the journal’s editor. The empirical discussion concentrates on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:06:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/bballrhuse1/article/7866205</link><title>Television Cartoons: Do Children Notice It's a Boy's World?</title><description>This study involved structured interviews with 89 children ranging in age from 4 to 9 years to determine how they perceived the presentation of male and female characters in cartoons. Approximately 85% of the respondents were Caucasian, and 15% were African American. Consistent with a recent content analysis of cartoons, the children perceived most cartoon characters in stereotypical ways—boys were violent and active and girls were domestic, interested in boys, and concerned with appearances. Significant relationships were observed between noticing gender-stereotypic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:06:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/suizan/article/598980</link><title>A Review of Festival and Event Motivation Studies</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:07:54">http://www.citeulike.org/group/1964/article/1031697</link><title>Animation: from cartoons to the user interface</title><description>An abstract is not available. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:08:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mani79/article/9918430</link><title>Cantonese opera film retrospective</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7494-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7494_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:08:56">http://www.citeulike.org/user/cheng5550888/article/8183226</link><title>&lt;&gt;.</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>