<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:21:18" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:21:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/lpark/article/1341545</link><title>IEEE Standard Glossary of Software Engineering Terminology</title><description>Describes the IEEE Std 610.12-1990, IEEE standard glossary of software engineering terminology, which identifies terms currently in use in the field of software engineering. Standard definitions for those terms are established.&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:22:29">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mmuecke/article/4001400</link><title>IEEE Standard for Floating-Point Arithmetic</title><description>This standard specifies interchange and arithmetic formats and methods for binary and decimal floating-point arithmetic in computer programming environments. This standard specifies exception conditions and their default handling. An implementation of a floating-point system conforming to this standard may be realized entirely in software, entirely in hardware, or in any combination of software and hardware. For operations specified in the normative part of this standard, numerical results and exceptions are uniquely determined by the values of the input data, sequence of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:23:22">http://www.citeulike.org/user/computertechmba/article/11458821</link><title>News of the IEEE</title><description>WESCON program places heavy emphasis on computers and changes in electronic markets for the seventies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:24:41">http://www.citeulike.org/user/dinnouti/article/1341525</link><title>IEEE Standard for Software Unit Testing</title><description>The standard is presented. The primary objective is to specify a standard approach to software unit testing that can be used as a basis for sound software engineering practice. A second objective is to describe the software engineering concepts and testing assumptions on which the standard approach is based. A third objective is to provide guidance and resource information to assist with the implementation and usage of the standard unit testing approach.&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:25:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guelke/article/1284144</link><title>IEEE Recommended Practice for Software Requirements Specifications</title><description>The content and qualities of a good software requirements specification (SRS) are described, and several sample SRS outlines are presented. This recommended practice is aimed at specifying the requirements of software to be developed, but can also be applied to assist in the selection of in-house and commercial software products. Guidelines for compliance with IEEE/EIA Std 12207.1-1997 are also provided ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:26:24">http://www.citeulike.org/user/akreh/article/1654521</link><title>IEEE Standard for Information Technology --- Telecommunications and Information Exchange Between Systems --- Local and Metropolitan Area Networks --- Specific Requirements --- Part 11: Wireless LAN Medium Access Control (MAC) and Physical Layer (PHY) Specifications</title><description>This revision specifies technical corrections and clarifications to IEEE Std 802.11 for wireless local area networks (WLANS) as well as enhancements to the existing medium access control (MAC) and physical layer (PHY) functions. It also incorporates Amendments 1 through 8 including a corrigendum. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:26:54">http://www.citeulike.org/user/duelines/article/6345806</link><title>Reliability Optimization of Series-Parallel Systems Using a Genetic Algorithm</title><description>This paper describes the use of a genetic algorithm (GA) to determine solutions to the redundancy allocation problem for a series-parallel system. In this problem formulation, there is a specified number of subsystems and, for each subsystem, there are multiple component choices which can be selected, with replacement, and used in parallel. For those systems designed using off-the-shelf component types, with known cost, reliability and weight, system design and component selection becomes a combinatorial 2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:28:20">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jrcoffi/article/4297292</link><title>IEEE Transactions on Fuzzy Systems (2001) DENFIS: Dynamic Evolving Neural-Fuzzy Inference System and Its Application for Time-Series Prediction</title><description>Abstract. This paper introduces a new type of fuzzy inference systems, denoted as DENFIS (dynamic evolving neural-fuzzy inference system), for adaptive on-line and off-line learning, and their application for dynamic time series prediction. DENFIS evolve through incremental, hybrid (supervised/unsupervised), learning and accommodate new input data, including new features, new classes, etc. through local element tuning. New fuzzy rules are created and updated during the operation of the system. At each time moment the output of DENFIS is calculated through a fuzzy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:29:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/queelius/article/13091589</link><title>Hiding information and signatures in trapdoor knapsacks</title><description>Ahwcz--The knapsack problem is aa Np-complete combinatorial problem that is strongly believed to be computationally difficult to solve in general. Specific instances of this problem tbat appear very difficult to solve unless one pawses âtrapdoor information â used in the design of the problem are demonstrated. Because only the designer can easily solve problems, others can send bim ioformation hidden in the solution to the problems without fear that au eavesdropper will be able to extract the information. This approach differs ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:30:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gvdh/article/1341526</link><title>IEEE Standard for a Software Quality Metrics Methodology</title><description>A methodology for establishing quality requirements and identifying, implementing, analyzing and validating the process and product software quality metrics is defined. The methodology spans the entire software life-cycle. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>