<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7497">shostakovich life</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:31:21" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:31:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/2012178497/article/9086100</link><title>Older Americans and the internet</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:31:59">http://www.citeulike.org/user/gareth/article/7577862</link><title>Differential item functioning (DIF) analyses of health-related quality of life instruments using logistic regression</title><description>BACKGROUND: Differential item functioning (DIF) methods can be used to determine whether different subgroups respond differently to particular items within a health-related quality of life (HRQoL) subscale, after allowing for overall subgroup differences in that scale. This article reviews issues that arise when testing for DIF in HRQoL instruments. We focus on logistic regression methods, which are often used because of their efficiency, simplicity and ease of application. METHODS: A review of logistic regression DIF analyses in HRQoL was undertaken. Methodological ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:32:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/BisLibrary/article/12333583</link><title>Teens and social media the use of social media gains a greater foothold in teen life as they embrace the conversational nature of interactive online media</title><description>This December 2007 report finds that "The use of social media -- from blogging to online social networking to creation of all kinds of digital material -- is central to many teenagers' lives." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:33:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/susz/article/3331882</link><title>Advanced Paediatric Life Support: The Practical Approach</title><description>This course book gives guidance on life-threatening emergencies in children. It incorporates subjects such as recognition of the seriously ill child,  basic life support, shock, and the structured approach to the seriously injured child. **Contents:** * Introduction * Life Support * the seriously ill child * the seriously injured child * practical procedures * appendices ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:34:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/susz/article/3331887</link><title>Pre Hospital Paediatric Life Support: The Practical Approach</title><description>This practical book written especially for prehospital staff provides all the information needed to deal with children in life threatening situations before arriving at hospital. It is a complementary volume to the best-selling Advanced Paediatric Life Support ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:35:57">http://www.citeulike.org/user/nbekko/article/9605515</link><title>The WHO quality of life assessment instrument (WHOQOL-Bref): the importance of its items for cross-cultural research.</title><description>One of the fundamental issues in the area of assessment of quality of life is to determine what is important to the individuals' quality of life. This is even more crucial when the instrument is for use in diverse cultural settings. This paper reports on the importance ratings on WHOQOL-Bref items obtained as a part of WHOQOL pilot field trial on 4804 respondents from 15 centres from 14 developed and developing countries using 12 languages. All items were rated as moderately ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:36:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Gkisakis/article/9743930</link><title>Life cycle assessment framework in agriculture on the farm level</title><description>Life Cycle Assessment (LCA) is a method that can be used to assess the environmental impact of agriculture, but impact categories and the functional unit of classical LCA’s must be adapted to the specific agricultural production process. Serving as an example, the framework of a LCA of 18 grassland dairy farms covering three farming intensity levels and carried out in the Allgäu region in southern Germany is presented. By focussing on the chosen impact categories and the respective, suitable functional units, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:36:51">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10110350</link><title>Development and validation of the Impact of Dry Eye on Everyday Life (IDEEL) questionnaire, a patient-reported outcomes (PRO) measure for the assessment of the burden of dry eye on patients</title><description>ObjectiveTo develop and validate a comprehensive patient-reported outcomes instrument focusing on the impact of dry eye on everyday life (IDEEL). Methods: Development and validation of the IDEEL occurred in four phases: 1) focus groups with 45 dry eye patients to develop a draft instrument, 2) item generation, 3) pilot study to assess content validity in 16 patients and 4) psychometric validation in 210 subjects: 130 with non-Sjogren's keratoconjunctivitis sicca, 32 with Sjogren's syndrome and 48 controls, and subsequent item reduction. Results: Focus groups identified symptoms ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:37:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/e10101/article/9061744</link><title>When technology fails</title><description>This November 2008 report finds that "48% of technology users need help from others with new devices and many tech users encounter problems with their internet connections, home computers or cell phones. As gadgets become more important to people, their patience wears thin when things break." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7497-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7497_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:39:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/kslibrarian/article/10787907</link><title>Publication of Controversial Papers in Life</title><description>Life (ISSN 2075-1729, http://www.mdpi.com/journal/life/) is a new journal that deals with new and sometime difficult interdisciplinary matters. Consequently, the journal will occasionally be presented with submitted articles that are controversial and/or outside conventional scientific views. Some papers recently accepted for publication in Life have attracted significant attention. Moreover, members of the Editorial Board have objected to these papers; some have resigned, and others have questioned the scientific validity of the contributions. In response I want to first state some basic facts ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>