<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7501">criquet miler</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:00:10" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:00:13">http://www.citeulike.org/article/6059477</link><title>The Limitations of Heuristics for Political Elites</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:00:42">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2500955</link><title>Non-enzymatic hydrolysis of fluorescein diacetate (FDA) in a Mediterranean oak (Quercus ilex L.) litter</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:01:22">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9496308</link><title>Anthropogenic metal loads and their sources in stream sediments of the Meža River catchment area (NE Slovenia)</title><description>The Meža River Valley has been a centre of mining, ore processing and iron- and steel-based metallurgical industry for more than 300 a. This paper deals with stream sediments draining this area. Loads of potentially toxic metals and metal-bearing phases were investigated 10 a after the cessation of Pb and Zn mining. Sediments in the upper Meža River Valley show significant pollution with Pb and Zn as a consequence of mining and ore processing. The highest contents of Pb and Zn ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:02:47">http://www.citeulike.org/article/9772845</link><title>Characteristics and potential environmental influences of mine waste in the area of the closed Mežica Pb-Zn mine (Slovenia)</title><description>About 19 million tons of Pb-Zn ore were excavated and processed during more than 300 years of mining and metallurgical activities in the Meža Valley, leaving behind large amounts of mine and ore processing wastes, which were deposited as spoil heaps in narrow valleys and on steep slopes of small streams and in abandoned mine shafts at about 30 locations. After the mine and processing facilities were closed in 1995, dumps of low-grade ore and ore processing wastes persisted as a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:03:36">http://www.citeulike.org/article/4114138</link><title>Guest Editors' Introduction</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:04:41">http://www.citeulike.org/article/3725332</link><title>Interaction of bilirubin with human lymphocytes and granulocytes — the effect on bilirubin metabolism</title><description>Abstract  Anin vitro degradation of bilirubin by isolated human granulocytes and lymphocytes is described. Changes in the bilirubin concentration during interaction with these cells were determined spectrophotometrically. The dependence of the reaction velocity on the original bilirubin concentration followed an adsorption isotherm, typical of enzyme processes with aK m of 79 μm at a cell concentration of 500/νL. The primary event is the adsorption of bilirubin to the cell surface and, in addition, its detoxication. Cyanide and sonic treatment of cells inhibit ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:05:29">http://www.citeulike.org/article/5667326</link><title>Degradation of acetic acid with sulfate radical generated by persulfate ions photolysis</title><description>The photolysis of inlMMLBox was studied for the removal of acetic acid in aqueous solution and compared with the H 2 O 2 /UV system. The inlMMLBox radicals generated from the UV irradiation of inlMMLBox ions yield a greater mineralization of acetic acid than the OH radicals. Acetic acid is oxidized by inlMMLBox radicals without significant formation of intermediate by-products. Increasing system pH results in the formation of OH radicals from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:06:34">http://www.citeulike.org/article/8892285</link><title>Electron beam irradiation of aqueous solution of persulfate ions</title><description>The radiolysis of persulfate (S2O82−) aqueous solution was studied for the enhancement of electron beam process applied to water treatment. It was shown that the persulfate ion reacts with aqueous electron and produces additional radical species in aqueous solution. The oxidative radical species formed (sulfate radical SO4-•) is a very strong oxidant able to react with various recalcitrant pollutants. A model of the evolution of persulfate concentration in solution was performed. It was shown that the presence of persulfate induces a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:07:04">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10165267</link><title>Electron beam irradiation of citric acid aqueous solutions containing persulfate</title><description>The electron beam irradiation of aqueous solutions of citric acid was studied. The results showed the effectiveness of the degradation of the carboxylic acid by the radiation process. The impact of pH was examined. It was demonstrated that the increase of pH induces a drop of the degradation due to the scavenging of radicals by the inorganic carbon. Moreover the interest of persulfate (S2O82-) addition that induces the formation of sulfate radicals (SO4-•) by the reaction of persulfate with the hydrated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7501-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7501_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:08:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/hugoc/article/7405630</link><title>How to cope with a superior enemy? Plant defence strategies in response to annual herbivore outbreaks</title><description>1\. The perfoliate pondweed Potamogeton perfoliatus L. constitutes large monospecific macrophyte patches in many Central European lakes. Correlative evidence from the field suggests that P. perfoliatus is under an increasing grazing pressure during its short vegetation period from May to September due to seasonal outbreaks of the aquatic moth Acentria ephemerella Denis &amp; Schiffermüller. We used a mesocosm experiment to determine the influence of A. ephemerella herbivory on P. perfoliatus shoot development and resting bud production and to study the defence ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>