<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:15:52" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:15:52">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Benthamite/article/8242376</link><title>Perón y los alemanes: la verdad sobre el espionaje nazi y los fugitivos del Reich</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:16:38">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Benthamite/article/8018021</link><title>La auténtica Odessa: la fuga nazi a la Argentina de Perón</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:17:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/uki/article/220516</link><title>Readings in information retrieval</title><description>An abstract is not available. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:18:18">http://www.citeulike.org/user/uki/article/4212975</link><title>Search Engines: Information Retrieval in Practice</title><description>**KEY BENEFIT**: Written by a leader in the field of information retrieval, this text provides the background and tools needed to evaluate, compare and modify search engines. **KEY TOPICS**: Coverage of the underlying IR and mathematical models reinforce key concepts. Numerous programming exercises make extensive use of Galago, a Java-based open source search engine. **MARKET**: A valuable tool for search engine and information retrieval professionals. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:18:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/uki/article/105906</link><title>Foundations of Statistical Natural Language Processing</title><description>"Statistical natural-language processing is, in my estimation, one of the most fast-moving and exciting areas of computer science these days. Anyone who wants to learn this field would be well advised to get this book. For that matter, the same goes for anyone who is already in the field. I know that it is going to be one of the most well-thumbed books on my bookshelf." -- Eugene Charniak, Department of Computer Science, Brown University &lt;P&gt;Statistical approaches to processing natural language ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:20:12">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jaeyoung/article/12463317</link><title>Instability of pedestrian flow and phase structure in a two-dimensional optimal velocity model</title><description>A two-dimensional optimal velocity model was proposed for the study of pedestrian and granular flow. We investigate the stability of homogeneous flow in the linear approximation and show the phase diagram of the model. We also investigate the property of the model by numerical simulation in the cases of unidirectional and counter flow. From these results, we present a unified understanding of the behavior of pedestrians and other related systems. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:20:47">http://www.citeulike.org/user/booker/article/3152512</link><title>DNA-binding activity of NF-[kappa]B and phosphorylation of p65 are induced by N-acetylcysteine through phosphatidylinositol (PI) 3-kinase</title><description>N-Acetylcysteine (NAC) has been widely used as an antioxidant in research, however, it has also been found to reduce the binding of TNF to its receptor independent of its antioxidative role. In this study, we investigated the effect of NAC on NF-[kappa]B activation. In HeLa cells, Hep3B cells, and A549 cells, DNA-binding activity of NF-[kappa]B was induced by NAC without any other stimulation but not by tetramethylthiourea (TMTU) or vitamin C, suggesting that ROS is not involved in the effect of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:21:38">http://www.citeulike.org/article/10364209</link><title>Potent activation of tumor necrosis factor-α production by a polysaccharide found in a marine brown alga &lt;i&gt;Chordaria flagelliformis&lt;/i&gt;</title><description>In a search for new antitumor drugs, we collected 334 species of marine algae from the Japanese coastline and screened these for tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α) production-promoting activity in an in vitro assay with the mouse macrophage-derived cell line RAW264.7. A phosphate-buffered saline extract from the marine brown alga Chordaria flagelliformis was found to strongly promote TNF-α activity. Further purification of this alga by precipitation with ethanol and two-step chromatography yielded an approximately 3,000-kDa polysaccharide as the active substance, which we ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:22:31">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2176461</link><title>Hyponatremic seizure associated with acute respiratory infection</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7503-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7503_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:23:17">http://www.citeulike.org/user/eisei/article/2698025</link><title>Prostaglandin E2 Up-Regulates Macrophage-Derived Chemokine Production but Suppresses IFN-Inducible Protein-10 Production by APC</title><description>PGE2 has been known to suppress Th1 responses. We studied the role of PGE2 in two representative chemokines, macrophage-derived chemokine (MDC) and IFN-inducible protein-10, production by LPS- or CD40-stimulated spleen cells. The production of MDC, one of the ligands for CCR4 preferentially expressed on Th2, was enhanced in nonstimulated, LPS-, CD40-, or CD3-stimulated spleen cells by the pretreatment with PGE2, while the production of IFN-inducible protein-10, a representative ligand for CXC chemokine receptor 3 expressed on Th1, was suppressed. MDC production ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>