<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:24:13" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:24:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/verylikeawhale/article/5207906</link><title>The `smaller' the school, the better? the Smaller Learning Communities (SLC) program in US high schools</title><description>Given the widening achievement gap between whites and students of color in US schools, Small Learning Communities have emerged as a reform measure claimed to boost achievement in general and among racial minorities. This article examines this claim by reviewing the major policy documents and literature on SLC and analyzing SLC using Frank's (1972) policy assessment criteria. The SLC program was found to be theoretically grounded in social capital theory, to be feasible politically and financially given strong federal and private ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:24:44">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jpb1301/article/10228473</link><title>Working together to safeguard children : a guide to inter-agency working to safeguard and promote the welfare of children.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:25:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/warters/article/8310619</link><title>Setting expectations and resolving conflicts in graduate education</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:25:48">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fuzbug/article/8678657</link><title>Youth Gangs and Schools</title><description>Few schools escape dynamics and behaviors that are associated with gangs. Think, for example, about bullying, disruptive intergroup conflicts, drug sales and abuse, and vandalism such as theft, graffiti, and other forms of property damage. From both a policy and practice perspective, it is essential for schools to understand and address gang-related problems that interfere with productive schooling. Drawing on recent documents from authoritative resources, the first section of this policy and practice analysis brief defines what a youth gang is, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:26:53">http://www.citeulike.org/user/mawds/article/6669710</link><title>Caveats for the journal and field normalizations in the CWTS ("Leiden") evaluations of research performance</title><description>The Center for Science and Technology Studies at Leiden University advocates the use of specific normalizations for assessing research performance with reference to a world average. The Journal Citation Score (JCS) and Field Citation Score (FCS) are averaged for the research group or individual researcher under study, and then these values are used as denominators of the (mean) Citations per publication (CPP). Thus, this normalization is based on dividing two averages. This procedure only generates a legitimate indicator in the case of underlying normal distributions. Given the skewed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:27:26">http://www.citeulike.org/article/2871434</link><title>Canaries, coal mines and the drug supply</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:28:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10929445</link><title>MIXED ABILITY TEACHING IN MATHEMATICS</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:29:30">http://www.citeulike.org/user/phillipkent/article/10907092</link><title>Crossing Subject Boundaries (Mathematics for the Majority)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:30:49">http://www.citeulike.org/user/booker/article/6071774</link><title>Low production capacity of interleukin-10 associates with the metabolic syndrome and type 2 diabetes : the Leiden 85-Plus Study.</title><description>It has been suggested that the metabolic syndrome and type 2 diabetes are manifestations of the inflammatory host response. This host response is orchestrated by the production of pro- and anti-inflammatory cytokines that are under genetic control. We therefore hypothesized that a low production capacity of interleukin-10 (IL-10), a centrally operating cytokine with strong anti-inflammatory properties, associates with the metabolic syndrome and type 2 diabetes in old age. In the current study, 599 inhabitants of the city of Leiden, age 85 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:31:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/NLRG/article/774252</link><title>Equal Access to State Funding: the case of Muslim schools in Britain</title><description>The decision to award government funding to four independent Muslim schools in Britain placed the spotlight on the issue of the public purse being used for private institutions, and also brought to an end the 15-year battle that Muslim communities waged in order to receive equality of treatment. This article provides an overview of this movement and highlights the issues surrounding equitable treatment of minority groups in society. There are presently around 100 independent Muslim schools in Britain today, a percentage ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>