<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:32:00" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:32:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/6496351</link><title>Comparing Ethnic Conflicts: Common Patterns, Shared Challenges</title><description>Notwithstanding predictions over the past century and a half that minorities defined in ethnic, linguistic, or cultural terms would gradually reconcile themselves to coexistence in states dominated by metropolitan cultures, difficulties arising from the mobilization of minority communities continue to be pronounced at the beginning of the twenty-first century. This article provides an overview of the extent of ethnic division in modern states, describes characteristic patterns of ethnic mobilization and focuses on a smaller set of illustrative cases that reveal many ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:32:45">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/10097269</link><title>National identity and ethnic diversity</title><description>In countries with high levels of ethnic diversity, “nation building” has been proposed as a mechanism for integration and conflict reduction. We find no evidence of lower intensity of national sentiment in more ethnically fragmented countries or in minority groups. National feelings in a minority can be higher or lower than in a majority, depending on the degree of ethnic diversity of a country. On the one hand, in countries with high ethnic diversity, nationalist feelings are less strong in minority ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:33:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/5458153</link><title>Ethnic tourism: A framework and an application</title><description>Ethnic tourism is employed by many countries to facilitate economic and cultural development and to assist in heritage preservation. Although a substantial literature is devoted to the impacts of ethnic tourism, little research has been done on planning ethnic attractions or related management issues. This paper addresses this gap by examining the socio-cultural issues associated with ethnic tourism and exploring planning strategies for its development based upon empirical research in a well-known tourist destination in China – Xishuangbanna, Yunnan Province. A ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:34:33">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/2240558</link><title>Ethnic and Cultural Diversity by Country*</title><description>For their empirical evaluation, several active research programs in economics and political science require data on ethnic groups across countries. “Ethnic group,” however, is a slippery concept. After addressing conceptual and practical obstacles, I present a list of 822 ethnic groups in 160 countries that made up at least 1 percent of the country population in the early 1990s. I compare a measure of ethnic fractionalization based on this list with the most commonly used measure. I also construct an index ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:35:23">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/3843054</link><title>Ethnic diversity and economic development</title><description>This paper analyzes the role that different indices and dimensions of ethnicity play in the process of economic development. Firstly, we discuss the advantages and disadvantages of alternative data sources for the construction of indices of religious and ethnic heterogeneity. Secondly, we compare the index of fractionalization and the index of polarization. We argue that an index of the family of discrete polarization measures is the adequate indicator to measure potential conflict. We find that ethnic (religious) polarization has a large ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:36:00">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/8990998</link><title>The Role of Gender in the Racial and Ethnic Socialization of African American Adolescents</title><description>Scholars in the field of African American family studies recognize the influence of gender on socialization. However, few studies investigate how gender influences the racial and ethnic socialization of African American youth. To examine the role of gender (both caregiver and adolescent) in socialization practices, data were obtained from 218 African American adolescents attending a public high school in the northeastern United States. Participants reported on the socialization messages provided by their caregivers by completing the Adolescent Racial and Ethnic Socialization ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:36:36">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/3210502</link><title>Transforming Clinical Practice to Eliminate Racial–Ethnic Disparities in Healthcare</title><description>Racial–ethnic minorities receive lower quality and intensity of health care compared with whites across a wide range of preventive, diagnostic, and therapeutic services and disease entities. These disparities in health care contribute to continuing racial–ethnic disparities in the burden of illness and death. Several national medical organizations and the Institute of Medicine have issued position papers and recommendations for the elimination of health care disparities. However, physicians in practice are often at a loss for how to translate these principles and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:37:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/8457481</link><title>Promoting Ethnic Tolerance and Patriotism: The Role of Education System Characteristics</title><description>The literature on political socialization has overlooked the influence of system characteristics of schooling on civic values and youth political identities. This article addresses that gap by investigating the degree to which system differentiation relates to the values of ethnic tolerance and patriotism. We distinguish between pedagogical differentiation and territorial differentiation. While the first concept relates to the contrast between early tracking and comprehensive education, the second term captures the contrast between federal versus unitary states. We find that comprehensive schooling ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:38:25">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/8487005</link><title>Genetic features of Mongolian ethnic groups revealed by Y-chromosomal analysis</title><description>About 20 ethnic groups reside in Mongolia. On the basis of genetic and anthropological studies, it is believed that Mongolians have played a pivotal role in the peopling of Central and East Asia. However, the genetic relationships among these ethnic groups have remained obscure, as have their detailed relationships with adjacent populations. We analyzed 16 binary and 17 STR polymorphisms of human Y chromosome in 669 individuals from nine populations, including four indigenous ethnic groups in Mongolia (Khalkh, Uriankhai, Zakhchin, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:39:09">http://www.citeulike.org/user/Ethnic/article/9193565</link><title>The effect of ethnic diversity on expatriate managers in their host country</title><description>Expatriate managers often encounter considerable obstacles in their overseas workplaces. While there is significant research on expatriate management and adjustment, relying on social identity and acculturation theories, little research addresses the expatriate experience of ethnic diversity in the host country. To address this gap, the aim of this study is to explore how Australian expatriate managers interpret their experience of working in a new and ethnically diverse workplace in Malaysia. The qualitative analysis suggests that the key to performing in such ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>