<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7506">I touch myself singer dead</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:39:46" name="CiteULike" id="FW14-e005"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:39:51">http://www.citeulike.org/user/sarabcampbell/article/6775682</link><title>Touch attenuates infants physiological reactivity to stress</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:40:39">http://www.citeulike.org/user/rgarfinkel/article/4039220</link><title>Using SAS PROC MIXED to Fit Multilevel Models, Hierarchical Models, and Individual Growth Models</title><description>SAS PROC MIXED is a flexible program suitable for fitting multilevel models, hierarchical linear models, and individual growth models. Its position as an integrated program within the SAS statistical package makes it an ideal choice for empirical researchers and applied statisticians seeking to do data reduction, management, and analysis within a single statistical package. Because the program was developed from the perspective of a “mixed” statistical model with both random and fixed effects, its syntax and programming logic may appear unfamiliar ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:42:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/matthewlewis/article/9533071</link><title>Rotational Invariants and Dynamic Touch</title><description>Skilled users of a long-cane are quite fluid in registering the layout of surfaces that surround them. What they need to know, of course, concerns properties with consequences for behavior—whether the ground is sufficiently flat and solid to be negotiated safely, whether discontinuities in that ground surface are gaps that can be stepped over or brinks that must be descended. At first blush, this skill may seem like a remarkable cognitive achievement, one in which the unsighted individual has managed to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:43:11">http://www.citeulike.org/user/alucchi/article/2404348</link><title>ThinSight: versatile multi-touch sensing for thin form-factor displays</title><description>ThinSight is a novel optical sensing system, fully integrated into a thin form factor display, capable of detecting multi-ple fingers placed on or near the display surface. We describe this new hardware in detail, and demonstrate how it can be embedded behind a regular LCD, allowing sensing without degradation of display capability. With our approach, fingertips and hands are clearly identifiable through the display. The approach of optical sensing also opens up the exciting possibility for detecting other physical objects and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:44:19">http://www.citeulike.org/user/guhjy/article/9266011</link><title>Dead cell counts during serum cultivation are underestimated by the fluorescent live/dead assay.</title><description>The live/dead fluorescent assay provides a quick method for assessing the proportion of live and dead cells in cell culture systems or tissues and is widely used. Dead cells are detected by the fluorescence produced when propidium iodide (PI) binds to DNA; PI and similar molecules are excluded from live cells but can penetrate dead cells because of their loss of membrane integrity. Here we investigated the effect of serum in the culture medium on the reliability of the method. We ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:45:13">http://www.citeulike.org/user/jwong/article/2402987</link><title>A Practical Guide to Ethical Research Involving Humans Guide to Advanced Empirical Software Engineering</title><description>The popularity of empirical methods in software engineering research is on the rise. Surveys, experiments, metrics, case studies, and field studies are examples of empirical methods used to investigate both software engineering processes and products. The increased application of such methods has also brought about an increase in discussions about adapting these methods to the particularities of software engineering. In contrast, the ethical issues raised by empirical methods have received little attention in the software engineering literature. In this chapter, we ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:46:03">http://www.citeulike.org/article/7762734</link><title>Elementary topical functions on b-complete semimodules over b-complete idempotent semifields</title><description>We extend some results of Rubinov and Singer [13] and Rubinov et al. [14] on topical functions on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:46:40">http://www.citeulike.org/user/tatsuyasaito/article/356511</link><title>Integration of Touch and Sound in Auditory Cortex</title><description>SummaryTo form a coherent percept of the environment, our brain combines information from different senses. Such multisensory integration occurs in higher association cortices; but supposedly, it also occurs in early sensory areas. Confirming the latter hypothesis, we unequivocally demonstrate supra-additive integration of touch and sound stimulation at the second stage of the auditory cortex. Using high-resolution fMRI of the macaque monkey, we quantified the integration of auditory broad-band noise and tactile stimulation of hand and foot in anaesthetized animals. Integration was ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:47:06">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fabianhemmert/article/2794696</link><title>The aesthetics of touch in interaction design</title><description>The sense of touch has been traditionally neglected in aesthetics. However, interaction design seems to always require some level of tactility or body activity for the experience. In this paper, I first give an overview of the historical arguments against a tactile aesthetics and offer reasons why these reasons are no longer valid. In the second section, I briefly present two design projects exploring unique tactile interfaces in an attempt to reconcile tactility with the aesthetics of interaction. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e005-7506-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e005/7506_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:48:05">http://www.citeulike.org/user/fpoll/article/12136200</link><title>TUIC: enabling tangible interaction on capacitive multi-touch displays</title><description>We present TUIC, a technology that enables tangible interaction on capacitive multi-touch devices, such as iPad, iPhone, and 3M's multi-touch displays, without requiring any hardware modifications. TUIC simulates finger touches on capacitive displays using passive materials and active modulation circuits embedded inside tangible objects, and can be used with multi-touch gestures simultaneously. TUIC consists of three approaches to sense and track objects: spatial, frequency, and hybrid (spatial plus frequency). The spatial approach, also known as 2D markers, uses geometric, multi-point touch ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>