<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:52:36" name="bleacher report" id="FW14-e159"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:52:36">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2016982-2014-stanley-cup-playoffs-your-guide-to-everything-you-need-to-know?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>2014 Stanley Cup Playoffs: Your Guide to Everything You Need to Know</title><description>The Stanley Cup playoffs are here at long last—they open Wednesday with three games—and that means the long, seemingly never-ending 82-game season has come to a close...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:54:40">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027583-pacquiao-vs-bradley-2-round-by-round-assessment-and-final-judges-scorecard?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>Pacquiao vs. Bradley 2 Round-by-Round Assessment and Final Judges' Scorecard</title><description>Even after once again outclassing Timothy Bradley in Las Vegas' MGM Grand Garden Arena, Manny Pacquiao must have felt a tad nervous while waiting for the judges to declare a winner...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:56:22">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028010-how-the-bulls-overcame-the-loss-of-d-rose-became-the-team-no-one-wants-to-face?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>How the Bulls Overcame the Loss of D-Rose, Became the Team No One Wants to Face</title><description>CHICAGO — It is late in the third quarter, and the United Center is booming. The score is tight, the tension is high and 22,000 wind-scorched Bulls fans are on their feet, screaming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:48">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028235-renewed-bubba-watson-escapes-pressures-looks-dominant-after-2014-masters?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>Renewed Bubba Watson Escapes Pressures, Looks Dominant After 2014 Masters</title><description>AUGUSTA, Ga. — He's won that second major, and do not forget the adage: Anyone can win one, but it takes a great golfer to win two or more. What Bubba Watson won't forget is how he reacted to the first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:00:53">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2029345-what-roger-federer-must-do-at-monte-carlo-to-build-momentum-for-2014-french-open?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>What Roger Federer Must Do at Monte Carlo to Build Momentum for 2014 French Open</title><description>Roger Federer has never won the Monte Carlo Masters title, but the Swiss star is ready to compete. He hopes to add this clay-court trophy to the largest collection of tennis hardware ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:04:03">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2029436-magnus-talks-sting-tna-world-title-sacrifice-and-more-on-ring-rust-radio?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>Magnus Talks Sting, TNA World Title, Sacrifice and More on Ring Rust Radio</title><description>TNA superstar Magnus was the World Heavyweight champion for an astonishing 128 days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:09:37">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2029855-colorado-avalanche-transform-into-cup-contender-in-a-season-for-the-ages?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>Colorado Avalanche Transform into Cup Contender in a Season for the Ages</title><description>"Some guys are more worried about their Vegas trip at the end of the season than playing the games. Quite frankly, I don't care about your Vegas trip right now... It's embarrassing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:13:29">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2030074-lance-armstrong-teaches-fans-how-to-change-a-tire-in-depressing-video?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>Lance Armstrong Teaches Fans How to Change a Tire in Depressing Video</title><description>If you were wondering what embattled cyclist Lance Armstrong has been up to, the answer seems to be making fairly depressing how-to videos on changing bike tires. So there's that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-09"><link>http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2030685-auburn-football-last-years-a-day-mvp-justin-garrett-ready-to-break-out?search_query=I'm on the road again</link><title>Auburn Football: Last Year's A-Day MVP, Justin Garrett, Ready to Break Out</title><description>Justin Garrett is standing tall once again. The junior from Tucker, Ga., was on track to be the star of Auburn defense last season in more ways than one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:55">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2030694-how-paul-george-used-kobe-bryant-as-his-guide-in-becoming-an-nba-star?search_query=I'm%20on%20the%20road%20again</link><title>How Paul George Used Kobe Bryant as His Guide in Becoming an NBA Star</title><description>If you're Kobe Bryant , it's an awkward time. You've never been further from where you want to be, you've never had less time to get there and you've never been more uncertain if your body will let you even try...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>