<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:43" name="bleacher report" id="FW14-e159"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:43">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2005311-nick-saban-vs-gus-malzahn-keeps-iron-bowl-as-college-footballs-best-rivalry?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Nick Saban vs. Gus Malzahn Keeps Iron Bowl as College Football's Best Rivalry</title><description>The best rivalry in college football lived up to the hype last season. Auburn topped Alabama 34-28 when Chris Davis returned a missed field goal 109 yards for a touchdown as time ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:41:12">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2020245-tiger-woods-injury-update-latest-on-golf-stars-recovery-from-back-surgery?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Tiger Woods Injury Update: Latest on Golf Star's Recovery from Back Surgery</title><description>With the extraordinary accomplishments Tiger Woods has on his golfing resume while battling constant health issues, it was discouraging when he revealed he'd be unable to compete in the 2014 Masters Tournament...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:45:25">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2022138-masters-2014-leaderboard-day-4-scores-results-and-analysis?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Masters 2014 Leaderboard: Day 4 Scores, Results and Analysis</title><description>Bubba Watson's (-8) unparalleled driving skills gave him the edge over partner Jordan Spieth to carry him to the 2014 Masters Championship! Watson donned his second green jacket ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:46:40">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027072-masters-2014-what-to-expect-from-golfs-top-stars-on-day-4?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Masters 2014: What to Expect from Golf's Top Stars on Day 4</title><description>Following an epic third round at the 2014 Masters Tournament , Augusta National Golf Club is prepped for a thrilling finish during Sunday's final 18 holes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:50:28">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027203-masters-tv-schedule-2014-day-4-tee-times-coverage-and-live-stream-info?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Masters TV Schedule 2014: Day 4 Tee Times, Coverage and Live Stream Info</title><description>Golf fans from around the world have been treated to an incredible 2014 Masters tournament through three days, and the stage has been set for an even better finish to one of the most exciting events of the year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:51:17">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027274-masters-odds-2014-latest-vegas-lines-and-predictions-for-final-round?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Masters Odds 2014: Latest Vegas Lines and Predictions for Final Round</title><description>All that remains between the top golfers in the world and the coveted green jacket is one round at Augusta. It sounds so simple, doesn't it? Except very few players near the top of the leaderboard have put together three consistent days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:52:11">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027298-the-masters-2014-top-odds-predictions-and-storylines-for-day-4?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>The Masters 2014: Top Odds, Predictions and Storylines for Day 4</title><description>After three rounds of twists and turns and unexpected storylines, the 2014 Masters Tournament enters the home stretch of Sunday's final round with everything still up for grabs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:56:05">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027325-the-masters-2014-grading-the-performance-of-golfs-top-stars-at-augusta?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>The Masters 2014: Grading the Performance of Golf's Top Stars at Augusta</title><description>Professional golf has evolved into the sport's best players setting up their schedules so their games are sharp four times a year: the majors. They know that ultimately they will be judged by how they perform in majors and how many they win...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:57:14">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027337-masters-2014-predictions-live-stream-and-tv-coverage-hub-for-day-4?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Masters 2014: Predictions, Live Stream and TV Coverage Hub for Day 4</title><description>The prospect of watching a Sunday of the Masters without Tiger Woods or Phil Mickelson may seem depressing, disappointing and downright strange...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:00:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027441-tiger-woods-absence-looms-large-over-2014-masters?search_query=golf%20games</link><title>Tiger Woods' Absence Looms Large over 2014 Masters</title><description>The most legitimate comparison to Michael Jordan is not LeBron James, nor is it Kobe Bryant—it’s Tiger Woods ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>