<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:02:00" name="bleacher report" id="FW14-e159"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:02:01">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2022299-2014-nfl-mock-draft-best-possible-move-for-every-1st-round-nfl-franchise?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>2014 NFL Mock Draft: Best Possible Move for Every 1st-Round NFL Franchise</title><description>As the May 8 date approaches for the first round of the 2014 NFL draft, all 32 franchises have pivotal decisions to make, but they also have one of the best arrays of players to choose from in history...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:04:54">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2023436-nfl-mock-draft-2014-best-value-picks-for-all-32-first-round-selections?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>NFL Mock Draft 2014: Best Value Picks for All 32 First-Round Selections</title><description>If there is a common phrase that all 32 teams use in the NFL draft, it is value. The goal of adding talent to a roster is to get the most bang for your buck, whether it's drafting a promising player or signing an undrafted free agent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:07:47">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027830-nfl-mock-draft-2014-latest-projections-for-every-nfl-franchise?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>NFL Mock Draft 2014: Latest Projections for Every NFL Franchise</title><description>As pro days bleed into spring games for collegiate teams, each team's stars of the past will instead hear their names called at the 2014 NFL draft. That's about the extent of what fans know at this point...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:11:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028598-johnny-weir-and-victor-voronov-reportedly-to-reconcile-following-public-split?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>Johnny Weir and Victor Voronov Reportedly to Reconcile Following Public Split</title><description>A little less than a month after publicly announcing a contentious breakup, retired American figure skater Johnny Weir and husband Victor Voronov have reportedly had a change of heart...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:14:09">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028620-2014-draft-why-no-quaterbacks-are-locks-to-be-drafted-in-the-top-10?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>2014 Draft: Why No Quarterbacks Are Locks to Be Drafted in the Top 10</title><description>Six weeks ago, the general consensus among draft analysts was that three or four quarterbacks could be drafted within the top 10 picks of the 2014 NFL draft. While many still adhere to that theory, I am not one and never have been...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:14:53">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2030547-2014-nfl-mock-draft-latest-forecast-for-each-selection-in-first-round?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>2014 NFL Mock Draft: Latest Forecast for Each Selection in First Round</title><description>The upcoming NFL draft is filled with uncertainty. It starts with the Houston Texans and the No. 1 pick and filters down from there. Most of the blame for this falls on the quarterbacks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:17:10">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031216-will-aaron-murray-be-more-than-a-career-backup-in-the-nfl?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>How Good Can Aaron Murray Be in the NFL?</title><description>There's an old joke that goes a little something like this: "Do you know what the most important element of comedy is?" ...It's been a long time since NFL draft experts have disagreed this much about who the best available quarterbacks are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:18:47">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031338-texas-am-football-qb-matt-joeckel-will-transfer-from-aggies?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>Texas A&amp;M Football: QB Matt Joeckel Will Transfer from Aggies</title><description>The competition to replace Johnny Manziel as Texas A&amp;M's starting quarterback gained a little more clarity Wednesday, with the school announcing that senior Matt Joeckel, last year's backup, will transfer out of the program...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:22:11">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031349-aggie-quarterback-matt-joeckel-to-transfer?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>Aggie Quarterback Matt Joeckel to Transfer</title><description>The race to replace Heisman-winning quarterback Johnny Manziel at Texas A&amp;M University just got a little less crowded. The university announced Wednesday morning that Aggie quarterback Matt Joeckel will transfer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:25:46">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031791-assigning-odds-to-every-potential-houston-texans-1st-round-pick?search_query=little%20johnny</link><title>Assigning Odds to Every Potential Houston Texans 1st-Round Pick</title><description>All the speculation surrounding the Houston Texans first-round pick is due to the fact they get to choose the very first player. This may leave the field wide open to them, but it doesn't make a decision any easier...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>