<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:48:32" name="bleacher report" id="FW14-e159"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-01"><link>http://bleacherreport.com/best_web</link><title>B/R's Best of the Web</title><description>Bleacher Report's new section featuring links to the best sports-related content from around the web.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:51:39">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2013700-who-is-darren-sharper-date-rape-allegations-raise-serious-questions?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>Who Is Darren Sharper? Date-Rape Allegations Raise Serious Questions</title><description>On a cool November night last year in Tempe, Ariz., a woman awoke groggy and disoriented on a gray sectional couch, according to a Tempe, Ariz., police report...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:53:36">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027885-celtics-lakers-and-knicks-all-miss-playoffs-together-for-the-1st-time?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>Celtics, Lakers and Knicks All Miss Playoffs Together for the 1st Time</title><description>With the NBA season coming to a close, some playoff positioning still needs sorting, but for the first time in league history, the Boston Celtics , Los Angeles Lakers and New ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:55:00">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027888-the-future-of-the-lakers-part-ii-how-to-overhaul-the-roster?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>The Future of the Lakers, Part II: How to Overhaul the Roster</title><description>The following is Part II of a three-part series on the future of the Los Angeles Lakers , written by Kevin Ding, who has covered the team since 1999. Part I was on the front office, Part III on the upcoming draft...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:57:52">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2027894-the-future-of-the-lakers-part-iii-the-importance-of-the-2014-draft?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>The Future of the Lakers, Part III: The Importance of the 2014 NBA Draft</title><description>The following is Part III of a three-part series on the future of the Los Angeles Lakers, written by Kevin Ding, who has covered the team since 1999. Part I was on the front office, Part II on the team's roster ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:01:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028019-nba-rumors-latest-chatter-on-lamar-odom-jodie-meeks-and-more?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>NBA Rumors: Latest Chatter on Lamar Odom, Jodie Meeks and More</title><description>With the NBA postseason imminent, there isn't much to speak of in the way of rumors, save for two of the Association's most celebrated franchises and their plans for the future...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:05:07">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028492-2014-nba-free-agents-list-of-top-available-players-this-offseason?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>2014 NBA Free Agents: List of Top Available Players This Offseason</title><description>The beginning of NBA free agency still feels strangely off in the distance. It doesn't feel like something teams have already begun to prepare for behind the scenes, as their playoff hopes wash away one more time on the season's final night...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:11:15">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028505-why-chicago-bulls-are-new-york-knicks-biggest-threat-to-carmelo-anthony?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>Why Chicago Bulls Are New York Knicks' Biggest Threat to Carmelo Anthony</title><description>Retaining Carmelo Anthony has gone from a virtual certainty to a ubiquitous question mark for the New York Knicks , who have sullied their appeal with losing and negligent spending, and must now fear the fury and mystique of the Chicago Bulls ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:12:12">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028586-gm-mitch-kupchak-lakers-have-great-interest-in-re-signing-pau-gasol?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>GM Mitch Kupchak: Lakers Have 'Great Interest' in Re-Signing Pau Gasol</title><description>Los Angeles Lakers veteran big man Pau Gasol won’t play again during the 2013-14 campaign due to a bout of vertigo. He's set to become an unrestricted free agent this offseason...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7460-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7460_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:12:53">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2029242-los-angeles-lakers-offseason-will-define-kobe-bryants-final-chapter?search_query=kobe%20bryant%20news</link><title>Los Angeles Lakers' Offseason Will Define Kobe Bryant's Final Chapter</title><description>Years from now, long after Kobe Bryant has scored his final points and hung up his Los Angeles Lakers jersey for good, this summer will be looked at as the offseason that salvaged ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>