<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:10:31" name="bleacher report" id="FW14-e159"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:10:32">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2013700-who-is-darren-sharper-date-rape-allegations-raise-serious-questions?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Who Is Darren Sharper? Date-Rape Allegations Raise Serious Questions</title><description>On a cool November night last year in Tempe, Ariz., a woman awoke groggy and disoriented on a gray sectional couch, according to a Tempe, Ariz., police report...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:15:01">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2016982-2014-stanley-cup-playoffs-your-guide-to-everything-you-need-to-know?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>2014 Stanley Cup Playoffs: Your Guide to Everything You Need to Know</title><description>The Stanley Cup playoffs are here at long last—they open Wednesday with three games—and that means the long, seemingly never-ending 82-game season has come to a close...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:18:26">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2026979-how-will-alex-ovechkin-recover-from-dream-season-that-turned-into-a-nightmare?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>How Will Alex Ovechkin Recover from Dream Season That Turned into a Nightmare?</title><description>This was supposed to be Alex Ovechkin's year. This was supposed to be the year Ovechkin would rip two large gorillas off his back by raising an Olympic gold medal and the Stanley Cup...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:22:32">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028128-kimi-raikkonens-character-lost-in-the-midfield-with-ferrari?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Kimi Raikkonen's Character Lost in the Midfield with Ferrari</title><description>Formula One is as much about entertainment as it is about cold-blooded competition. That is why double points will be awarded for the final race this season, and that is why so many ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:23:17">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2028404-manchester-united-transfer-news-marco-reus-key-to-summer-revamp-for-david-moyes?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Manchester United Transfer News: Marco Reus Key to Summer Revamp for David Moyes</title><description>Marco Reus posted another memorable performance during Borussia Dortmund 's 3-0 hammering of Bayern Munich, an individual display that showcased why David Moyes should use the German forward as a key figure in his summer rebuild...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:25:58">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2030866-the-cardinals-are-rediscovering-what-made-them-the-class-of-the-nl-central?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>The Cardinals Are Rediscovering What Made Them the Class of the NL Central</title><description>Fueled by a batch of struggling stars Tuesday night, the St. Louis Cardinals cooled off the red-hot Milwaukee Brewers on the road for a second straight game, proving that they're ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:27:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031421-fashion-wars-nba-playoffs-are-a-whole-new-season-starting-with-players-styles?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Fashion Wars: NBA Playoffs Are a Whole New Season, Starting with Players' Styles</title><description>Calyann Barnett still remembers the emails and phone calls she received after NBA All-Star Weekend in 2009...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:28:56">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2031734-evolution-eric-young-and-latest-wwe-news-and-rumors-from-ring-rust-radio?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Evolution, Eric Young and Latest WWE News and Rumors from Ring Rust Radio</title><description>Ring Rust Radio is the best wrestling show on the airwaves, and this week was no different. With strong opinions on Evolution, Kane and more, this is where you need to go to get all of your weekly WWE nuggets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:30:21">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2032322-why-no-2-overall-pick-is-the-most-important-of-the-2014-nfl-draft?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Why No. 2 Overall Pick Is the Most Important of the 2014 NFL Draft</title><description>In most NFL drafts over the years, the prestige of being the first overall pick makes that selection the most talked about option in the draft...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e159-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e159/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:33:17">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2032878-dana-white-im-very-confident-gina-carano-is-on-her-way-back?search_query=popular%20twitter%20stars</link><title>Dana White: I'm Very Confident Gina Carano Is on Her Way Back</title><description>In order for the UFC to attract Gina Carano away from her ultra-successful Hollywood career, it's going to have to pull all the right strings. First off, Carano needs to be compensated heavily...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>