<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:21:36" name="Nick jr" id="FW14-e090"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:21:37">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/dora-crayon-caddy.jhtml</link><title>Dora the Explorer Crayon Caddy</title><description>...can also do it by hand, or with fabric glue. Watch Dora Every Day on Nick...machine, needle and thread, or fabric glue Scissors Blue, orange...Dora Crayon Caddy Templates Fabric glue Grosgrain ribbon Supplies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:22:21">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/boots-no-sew-scarf.jhtml</link><title>Boots No-Sew Scarf</title><description>...felt, our templates, and some fabric glue to get started! Watch Dora...blue, and pale pink or tan Fabric glue (such as Sobo) Fabric paints...pink/purple, black, and white fabric paint. Glue the red boots onto the other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:25:42">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/perrito-puppy-hand-puppet.jhtml</link><title>Fuzzy Perrito Hand Puppet</title><description>...fur. Whip up this puppet with fabric glue, or use a sewing machine if...blue, and yellow felt Fabric glue or a sewing machine Directions...pieces. Cut out the shapes with fabric scissors. Step 2 Glue or stitch around the perimeter...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:26:53">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/pablo-no-sew-scarf.jhtml</link><title>Pablo No-Sew Scarf</title><description>...Fashion Pablo using fleece, fabric glue (not sewing) and your...blue Straight pins Fabric glue (such as Sobo) Scissors...directions for the 3-D fabric paint or wait a couple...the scarf. Tip: Use glue sparingly so it won't...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:07">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/uniqua-halloween-costume.jhtml</link><title>Uniqua Costume</title><description>...pink when she sees this costume. Sew it together or use fabric glue. The design is simple. And the headband can be...4-yard hot pink felt 1 yard pale pink ribbon Fabric glue or pink thread Stiff pink felt and fine elastic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:51">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/tolee-panda-bath-mitt.jhtml</link><title>Tolee's Panda Bath Mitt</title><description>...washcloth for the ears, you can use fabric glue instead. Watch Kai-lan weekdays... Needle and black thread Fabric glue Tip: Store-bought bath...pieces. Secure them to the mitt with fabric glue. More Ni Hao, Kai-lan ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:45">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/bubble-puppy-no-sew-pillow.jhtml</link><title>Bubble Puppy Plush Doll</title><description>...black, green, and pink felt scraps Bubble Puppy Plush Doll Templates Fabric scissors (adults only) Fabric paints (optional) Water-resistant fabric glue (Fabri-Tac or something similar) Pillow stuffing (cotton or polyester...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:37:53">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/boots-no-sew-snuggle-pillow.jhtml</link><title>Boots No-Sew Snuggle Pillow</title><description>...white felt Sheet black felt Fabric glue Fabric scissors (adult use only) Fiberfill...reflections, either draw them with white fabric paint or cut out two tiny circles...Once the face has been glued down, glue the belly piece on, then glue...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:42:24">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/peter-rabbit-no-sew-craft.jhtml</link><title>Peter Rabbit No-Sew Pillow</title><description>...white, and green felt scraps Peter Rabbit No-Sew Pillow Templates Fabric scissors (adults only) Brown fabric paint (optional) Water-resistant fabric glue (Fabri-Tac or something similar) Pillow stuffing (cotton or polyester...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e090-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e090/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:44:52">http://www.nickjr.com/crafts/gil-no-sew-pillow.jhtml</link><title>Gil No-Sew Pillow</title><description>...green, and light green felt scraps Gil No-Sew Pillow Templates Fabric scissors (adults only) Black and white fabric paint (optional) Water-resistant fabric glue (Fabri-Tac or something similar) Pillow stuffing (cotton or...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>