<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:56" name="NCSU Library " id="FW14-e030"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:58">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU1476304</link><title>Test of courage : the Michel Thomas story</title><description>Test of courage : the Michel Thomas story</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:12:03">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU1333214</link><title>Hydrogeology in the vicinity of test holes and wells on St. Croix, St. Thomas, and St. John, U.S. Virgin Islands</title><description>Hydrogeology in the vicinity of test holes and wells on St. Croix, St. Thomas, and St. John, U.S. Virgin Islands</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:16">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2037951</link><title>A Word in season [electronic resource] : the writings of Noah and Thomas Worcester brought to the test concerning an answer : and a bridle for disputants.</title><description>A Word in season [electronic resource] : the writings of Noah and Thomas Worcester brought to the test concerning an answer : and a bridle for disputants.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:17:43">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2031728</link><title>Select pamphlets. [electronic resource] : Containing: Sampson against the Philistines. Politics for American farmers. Test of government. Dissertations on the first principles of government--By Thomas Paine. Speech of Thomas Paine, July 7, 1795. Law of nations--By W.J. Duane. Decline and fall of English system of finance. Debates of the United States.</title><description>Select pamphlets. [electronic resource] : Containing: Sampson against the Philistines. Politics for American farmers. Test of government. Dissertations on the first principles of government--By Thomas Paine. Speech of Thomas Paine, July 7, 1795. Law of nations--By W.J. Duane. Decline and fall of English system of finance. Debates of the United States.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:52">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2106916</link><title>A test of the religious principles of Thomas Jefferson. [microform] : [Two lines from Washington]</title><description>A test of the religious principles of Thomas Jefferson. [microform] : [Two lines from Washington]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:21:33">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2995351</link><title>A catalogue of books, [electronic resource] : Including the libraries of the following gentlemen, lately deceased, viz. Francis Hiorne, Esq; F. A. S. of Warwick; The Reverend Thomas Osborne, D. D. Rector of Clifton, Bedfordshire. Henry Brooker. Esq; late Keeper of the Records in the Augmentation Office; Marmaduke Overend, Esq; of Chiswick; The Collection of Books of Architecture of Kenton Couse, Esq; late of the Board of Works; And the Medical Library of a Physician, who has left Practice: Also a singular Assemblage of Old English Poetry and Plays. Amongst others equally valuable are Military and Religious Orders, 800 Drawings, in colours, 8 vol. Morocco Antichita D'ercolano, 8 vol. Russ. Hodges's Views in India, on silk paper Piranesi's Works, 17 vol. Russ. Vitrovius Britannicus, 5 vol. large paper Atlantic Neptune, by Des Barres, 4 vol. Merian's Views, 11 vol. Graevius, Gronovius, &amp; Burmann. 70 vol. Hill's Vegetable System, 26 vol. Seba Thesaur. Rer. Natur. 4 vol. Russ. Catesby's Carolina, 2 vol. coloured Weinman's Flowers and Fruits, 8 vol. do. Merian's Surinam Insects, ditto. Merian's European Insects, 3 vol. coloured by the Author Martyn, Born and Knott's Shells, ditto. Cramer, Ernst, Wilkes and Harris's Moths and Flies, ditto Sepp, Rosell, and Stoll's Insects, ditto Edwards, Lewin, Seligman and Brown's Birds, ditto Scheffer's Birds, Insects, &amp;c. 12 vol. ditto Miller and Plenck's Plants, 4 vol. ditto Knott's Petrifactions, 4 vol. ditto Petiveri Opera, 3 vol. Moracco Morisoni Hist. Plant. 2 vol. ditto Salvianus de Piscibus Cowper, Albinus, Hunter and Smellie Biblia Polyglotta Waltoni, 8 vol. Russ. Biblia Polyglotta, Montani, 8 vol. Kennicol's Bible, and Woide's Test. 3 vol. Erasmi Opera, 11 vol. Lactantius, 1468-T. Aquinas, 1469 V. Max. Spira, 1471-Plinius Jenson, 1472 Herodotus, 1474-Diog. Laertius, 1475 Astronomi Veteres, ap. Aldum Breydenback Peregrinationes - 1486 Caesaris Comment. Clarkii, Morocco Platonis Opera, Serrani, 3 vol. ditto Doleti Comment. Ling. Lat. 2 vol. Russ. Stephani Thesaur. Gr. 6 vol. - Ducange &amp; Carpentier Gloss. 10 vol. Meninski, Golii &amp; Giggaei Lexicon Encyclopedie, 33 tom. - Paris Moutfaucon, &amp; Supplem. 15 t. gr. papier. Fables de la Fontaine, 4 tom. ditto Polyphih Hypnerotomachia - Ald. Speculum Salvationis, MS. Domesday Book, 2 vol. Russia State Trials, 11 vol. large paper, Russ. Froissart and Hollinshed's Chronicles, ib. Drake's York, and Harris's Kent. l. paper Stukeley's Stonehenge and Abury, 2 vol. Edmondson's Peerage, 6 vol. Nisbet's System of Heraldry, 2 vol. Various Heraldical Manuscripts Purchas and Hackluyt's Voyages Montfaucon in English, 7 vol. large paper Shakspeare, 1st, 2d and 3d edit. Caxton's History of Troy Boke of Faytes and Armes, Caxton The Book of St. Albons, MS. Spectator, Tatler and Guardian, 6 vol. orig. edit. Prevost, Recueil des Voyages, 26 tom. Harding's Bandello, 3 vol. large paper Tacitus, Brotier, 4 vol. cb. max. Aristides, a Jebb, 2 vol. ditto Silius Italicus, Drakenborch, ditto Ovidius Burmanni, 4 vol. ditto Horatius Bentleii, ditto Elziver Classics, 93-vol. Morocco Painter's Palace of Pleasure, 2 vol. Political State of Great Britain, 60 vol. Parliamentary Debates, &amp;c. 136 vol. which are now selling, 1791 (for ready Money) By Thomas and John Egerton, (successors to Mr. Millan) at the Military Library, Whitehall. - The full Value given for Libraries.</title><description>A catalogue of books, [electronic resource] : Including the libraries of the following gentlemen, lately deceased, viz. Francis Hiorne, Esq; F. A. S. of Warwick; The Reverend Thomas Osborne, D. D. Rector of Clifton, Bedfordshire. Henry Brooker. Esq; late Keeper of the Records in the Augmentation Office; Marmaduke Overend, Esq; of Chiswick; The Collection of Books of Architecture of Kenton Couse, Esq; late of the Board of Works; And the Medical Library of a Physician, who has left Practice: Also a singular Assemblage of Old English Poetry and Plays. Amongst others equally valuable are Military and Religious Orders, 800 Drawings, in colours, 8 vol. Morocco Antichita D'ercolano, 8 vol. Russ. Hodges's Views in India, on silk paper Piranesi's Works, 17 vol. Russ. Vitrovius Britannicus, 5 vol. large paper Atlantic Neptune, by Des Barres, 4 vol. Merian's Views, 11 vol. Graevius, Gronovius, &amp; Burmann. 70 vol. Hill's Vegetable System, 26 vol. Seba Thesaur. Rer. Natur. 4 vol. Russ. Catesby's Carolina, 2 vol. coloured Weinman's Flowers and Fruits, 8 vol. do. Merian's Surinam Insects, ditto. Merian's European Insects, 3 vol. coloured by the Author Martyn, Born and Knott's Shells, ditto. Cramer, Ernst, Wilkes and Harris's Moths and Flies, ditto Sepp, Rosell, and Stoll's Insects, ditto Edwards, Lewin, Seligman and Brown's Birds, ditto Scheffer's Birds, Insects, &amp;c. 12 vol. ditto Miller and Plenck's Plants, 4 vol. ditto Knott's Petrifactions, 4 vol. ditto Petiveri Opera, 3 vol. Moracco Morisoni Hist. Plant. 2 vol. ditto Salvianus de Piscibus Cowper, Albinus, Hunter and Smellie Biblia Polyglotta Waltoni, 8 vol. Russ. Biblia Polyglotta, Montani, 8 vol. Kennicol's Bible, and Woide's Test. 3 vol. Erasmi Opera, 11 vol. Lactantius, 1468-T. Aquinas, 1469 V. Max. Spira, 1471-Plinius Jenson, 1472 Herodotus, 1474-Diog. Laertius, 1475 Astronomi Veteres, ap. Aldum Breydenback Peregrinationes - 1486 Caesaris Comment. Clarkii, Morocco Platonis Opera, Serrani, 3 vol. ditto Doleti Comment. Ling. Lat. 2 vol. Russ. Stephani Thesaur. Gr. 6 vol. - Ducange &amp; Carpentier Gloss. 10 vol. Meninski, Golii &amp; Giggaei Lexicon Encyclopedie, 33 tom. - Paris Moutfaucon, &amp; Supplem. 15 t. gr. papier. Fables de la Fontaine, 4 tom. ditto Polyphih Hypnerotomachia - Ald. Speculum Salvationis, MS. Domesday Book, 2 vol. Russia State Trials, 11 vol. large paper, Russ. Froissart and Hollinshed's Chronicles, ib. Drake's York, and Harris's Kent. l. paper Stukeley's Stonehenge and Abury, 2 vol. Edmondson's Peerage, 6 vol. Nisbet's System of Heraldry, 2 vol. Various Heraldical Manuscripts Purchas and Hackluyt's Voyages Montfaucon in English, 7 vol. large paper Shakspeare, 1st, 2d and 3d edit. Caxton's History of Troy Boke of Faytes and Armes, Caxton The Book of St. Albons, MS. Spectator, Tatler and Guardian, 6 vol. orig. edit. Prevost, Recueil des Voyages, 26 tom. Harding's Bandello, 3 vol. large paper Tacitus, Brotier, 4 vol. cb. max. Aristides, a Jebb, 2 vol. ditto Silius Italicus, Drakenborch, ditto Ovidius Burmanni, 4 vol. ditto Horatius Bentleii, ditto Elziver Classics, 93-vol. Morocco Painter's Palace of Pleasure, 2 vol. Political State of Great Britain, 60 vol. Parliamentary Debates, &amp;c. 136 vol. which are now selling, 1791 (for ready Money) By Thomas and John Egerton, (successors to Mr. Millan) at the Military Library, Whitehall. - The full Value given for Libraries.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:23:39">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2925412</link><title>A dialogue between old Mr. Pious and Madam Finic his wife [electronic resource] : occasioned by young Spoil-Text preaching his approbation sermon; who was made an able minister Of A Very New Test Ament: by The Rev. And Learned Dr. Know-Little, Dr. Grimace, Dr. Strut, and Dr. Reader, Heads Of The Academy, At -- , compiled from some fragments found amongst th papers of the late Mr. Thomas Gurney, Author of The Perfections of God a standing Rule to try all Doctrines and Experience by; The Mongrel Preacher, and other Poems. By one of his intimate friends.</title><description>A dialogue between old Mr. Pious and Madam Finic his wife [electronic resource] : occasioned by young Spoil-Text preaching his approbation sermon; who was made an able minister Of A Very New Test Ament: by The Rev. And Learned Dr. Know-Little, Dr. Grimace, Dr. Strut, and Dr. Reader, Heads Of The Academy, At -- , compiled from some fragments found amongst th papers of the late Mr. Thomas Gurney, Author of The Perfections of God a standing Rule to try all Doctrines and Experience by; The Mongrel Preacher, and other Poems. By one of his intimate friends.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:28:16">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2972360</link><title>A catalogue of a very large and curious collection of books, [electronic resource] : In which are included the Libraries of Samuel Crisp, Esq; of Surrey, The Rev. Dr. Kennicott, of Oxford, And the Rev. Mr. Green, Deceased; And several other Collections; Also a great Number of scarce Pamphlets. Amongst the Books are, viz. Folio. Homer, Eustathii, 4 t. chart max. cor. russ. Idem. 4 tom. ch. max. cario russ. Glasg. Plato, Serrani, 3 t. corio turcico Astonomici Veteres, corio turc. ap. Ald. Politian, corio turcico ap. Ald. Theodori Gazae, corio russ. ap. Ald. Herodotus, Gr. lin. rub. elegantis. ap. Ald. Plutarchi, 2 t. cor. russ. - Vitae, Lat. 2 t. corio turc. 1478 Caesar, a Clarke, corio russ. eleg. Ptolemaeus, a Serveto, corio russ. Valerius maximus, edit, princeps, corin turc. Herodotus, Gronovii, chart. max. corio russ. Strabo Geograph. 2 t. chart. max. Montfaucon, 15 t. grand papier Mezeray Hist. de France, 3 t. moroq. blue Voyages par Le Bruyn, 3 t. grand papier Les Artes &amp; Metiers, complete Blackwell's Herbal, 2 v. coloured, russia Sloane's Jamaica, 2 v. Brown's Jamaica Spence's Polymetis, best edition Florae Danicae, 5 t. colorat. Numismata, a Pembroche, ch. max. russ. Dict. de Moreri, 10 t. meilleur edition Meninski Lexicon, 5 t. in 4. H. Stephani Thesaurus Ling. Lat. 5 tom. chart. max. Biblia Heb. a Bomberg, 4 t. corio russ. Scheuchzeri Physica Sacra, 4 t. elegantis. Augustinus de Civitate Dei, cor. russ. 1470 Test. Gr. corio turcico Mabillon de Re Diplomatica Norden's Travels, 2 v. l. p. State Trials, 11 v. l. p. russia Dugdale's Monast. Anglic. 5 t. russia - Warwickshire, russia - Summons Chauncey's Hertfordshire Harris's Voyages, 2 v. russia Churchill's Voyages, 6 vol. Which will be sold, for Ready Money only, this Day 1784, and continue on Sale till all are sold, By Thomas Payne and Son, booksellers, At the Mews Gate, in Castle Street, St. Martin's. Catalogues to be had, with Prices printed (price 6d) at Mr. Sewell's, Bookseller, Cornhill; Mr. Owen's, Bookseller, near Temple-Bar, Fleet Street; Mr. Lewis, Bookseller, Russel Street, Covent Garden; Mr. Walter, Bookseller, at Charing Cross; Mr. Robson, Bookseller, New Bond Street; of the Booksellers at Oxford and Cambridge, and at the Place of Sale. Where may be had the full Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</title><description>A catalogue of a very large and curious collection of books, [electronic resource] : In which are included the Libraries of Samuel Crisp, Esq; of Surrey, The Rev. Dr. Kennicott, of Oxford, And the Rev. Mr. Green, Deceased; And several other Collections; Also a great Number of scarce Pamphlets. Amongst the Books are, viz. Folio. Homer, Eustathii, 4 t. chart max. cor. russ. Idem. 4 tom. ch. max. cario russ. Glasg. Plato, Serrani, 3 t. corio turcico Astonomici Veteres, corio turc. ap. Ald. Politian, corio turcico ap. Ald. Theodori Gazae, corio russ. ap. Ald. Herodotus, Gr. lin. rub. elegantis. ap. Ald. Plutarchi, 2 t. cor. russ. - Vitae, Lat. 2 t. corio turc. 1478 Caesar, a Clarke, corio russ. eleg. Ptolemaeus, a Serveto, corio russ. Valerius maximus, edit, princeps, corin turc. Herodotus, Gronovii, chart. max. corio russ. Strabo Geograph. 2 t. chart. max. Montfaucon, 15 t. grand papier Mezeray Hist. de France, 3 t. moroq. blue Voyages par Le Bruyn, 3 t. grand papier Les Artes &amp; Metiers, complete Blackwell's Herbal, 2 v. coloured, russia Sloane's Jamaica, 2 v. Brown's Jamaica Spence's Polymetis, best edition Florae Danicae, 5 t. colorat. Numismata, a Pembroche, ch. max. russ. Dict. de Moreri, 10 t. meilleur edition Meninski Lexicon, 5 t. in 4. H. Stephani Thesaurus Ling. Lat. 5 tom. chart. max. Biblia Heb. a Bomberg, 4 t. corio russ. Scheuchzeri Physica Sacra, 4 t. elegantis. Augustinus de Civitate Dei, cor. russ. 1470 Test. Gr. corio turcico Mabillon de Re Diplomatica Norden's Travels, 2 v. l. p. State Trials, 11 v. l. p. russia Dugdale's Monast. Anglic. 5 t. russia - Warwickshire, russia - Summons Chauncey's Hertfordshire Harris's Voyages, 2 v. russia Churchill's Voyages, 6 vol. Which will be sold, for Ready Money only, this Day 1784, and continue on Sale till all are sold, By Thomas Payne and Son, booksellers, At the Mews Gate, in Castle Street, St. Martin's. Catalogues to be had, with Prices printed (price 6d) at Mr. Sewell's, Bookseller, Cornhill; Mr. Owen's, Bookseller, near Temple-Bar, Fleet Street; Mr. Lewis, Bookseller, Russel Street, Covent Garden; Mr. Walter, Bookseller, at Charing Cross; Mr. Robson, Bookseller, New Bond Street; of the Booksellers at Oxford and Cambridge, and at the Place of Sale. Where may be had the full Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:32:13">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2972325</link><title>A catalogue of a large and curious collection of books [electronic resource] : Containing several libraries lately purchased, In all Languages and Faculties; Amongst great Numbers of valuable Articles are the following, viz. Folio Hollinshed's Chronicle, 3 vol. Rymer's Foedera, 20 tom. in 10 vol. Madox's Exchequer, 2 vol. l. p. Plott's Staffordshire, l. p. morocco Purchas's Pilgrims, 5 vol. Spelman's Glossary, best edit. H. Stephani Glossar. Gr. St. Chrysostom, 13 tom. Edit. Benedicti Nov. Test. Gr. cor. turc. R. Steph. Bacon's Abridgment, 5 vol. Year Books, 9 vol. Repertorium Juridicum Precedents in Chancery Bracton de Legibus, corio turt. Rhetores Graece, compleat Comment. in Aristotelis omnes Willoughby on Birds \- on Fishes R. Stephani Thesaurus, 4 tom. cor. russ. Chronique de Monstrelet - de Froissart Plinii Hist. Naturalis, 3 tom. Tanner Biblioth. Britan. - Monasticon Constantini Lexicon A compleat and fine Sett of Philosophical Transactions to the present Time State Trials, 10 vol. Dugdale's Monasticon, 3 tom. - Warwickshire - Baronage - Origines Juridiciales Thoresby's Nottinghamshire Stukeley's Itinerary, Stone-Henge, and Abury, 4 vol. mariana's Hist. of Spain, l. p. Ancient and Mod. History, 24 vol. Norden's Travels, 2 vol. l. paper Harris's Voyages, 2 vol. Hakluyt's Voyages, 3 vol. Voyages par Le Bruyn, 3 tom. James's Dictionary, 3 vol. Bayle and Biograph. Brit. 12 vol. Vocab. della Crusca, 6 vol. Diccionar. Espanola, 6 tom. H. Stephani Thesaur. Gr. 5 tom. Hickes Thesaur. Ling. Septentrion. 3 tom. Meninski Thes. Linguar. Orient. 4 tom. Giggei Thesaur. Ling. Arab. 4 tom. Encyclopedie, 28 tom. Du Fresne Glossarium, 6 tom. Pindar - Oxon. Caesaris Comment. a Clarke Xenophon, Gr. - ap. Ald. Plutarchi Opera, 2 tom. Par. Diodorus Sicusus, 2 tom. Polybius, Casauboni Homer, 4 tom. ch. max. Glasg. Biblia Hebraica, a Houbegant, 4 tom. Montfaucon, 15 tom. gr. pap. Graevius &amp; Gronovius, cum Suppl. 57 tom. Hayes's Birds, coloured Hippocratis &amp; Galen, 9 tom. Sandrart Academ. Ars Pict. Ramelli's Machines Bieau's Atlas, 12 vol. De Liste's Atlas, l. paper And many others equally good, which will be sold, for Ready Money only, this Day, July 1779, and continue on Sale till all are sold, By Thomas Payne and Son, booksellers, Next the Mews Gate, in Castle Street, St. Martin's. Catalogues to be had, with Prices printed (price 6d) at Mr. Sewell's, Bookseller, Cornhill; Mr. Owen's, Bookseller, near Temple-Bar, Fleet-Street; Mr. Lewis, Bookseller, Russel Street, Covent Garden; Mr. Walter, Bookseller, at Charing Cross; Mr. Ridley, Bookseller, St. James's Street; Mr. Robson, Bookseller, New Bond Street; of the Booksellers at Oxford and Cambridge, and at the Place of Sale. Where may be had the full Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</title><description>A catalogue of a large and curious collection of books [electronic resource] : Containing several libraries lately purchased, In all Languages and Faculties; Amongst great Numbers of valuable Articles are the following, viz. Folio Hollinshed's Chronicle, 3 vol. Rymer's Foedera, 20 tom. in 10 vol. Madox's Exchequer, 2 vol. l. p. Plott's Staffordshire, l. p. morocco Purchas's Pilgrims, 5 vol. Spelman's Glossary, best edit. H. Stephani Glossar. Gr. St. Chrysostom, 13 tom. Edit. Benedicti Nov. Test. Gr. cor. turc. R. Steph. Bacon's Abridgment, 5 vol. Year Books, 9 vol. Repertorium Juridicum Precedents in Chancery Bracton de Legibus, corio turt. Rhetores Graece, compleat Comment. in Aristotelis omnes Willoughby on Birds \- on Fishes R. Stephani Thesaurus, 4 tom. cor. russ. Chronique de Monstrelet - de Froissart Plinii Hist. Naturalis, 3 tom. Tanner Biblioth. Britan. - Monasticon Constantini Lexicon A compleat and fine Sett of Philosophical Transactions to the present Time State Trials, 10 vol. Dugdale's Monasticon, 3 tom. - Warwickshire - Baronage - Origines Juridiciales Thoresby's Nottinghamshire Stukeley's Itinerary, Stone-Henge, and Abury, 4 vol. mariana's Hist. of Spain, l. p. Ancient and Mod. History, 24 vol. Norden's Travels, 2 vol. l. paper Harris's Voyages, 2 vol. Hakluyt's Voyages, 3 vol. Voyages par Le Bruyn, 3 tom. James's Dictionary, 3 vol. Bayle and Biograph. Brit. 12 vol. Vocab. della Crusca, 6 vol. Diccionar. Espanola, 6 tom. H. Stephani Thesaur. Gr. 5 tom. Hickes Thesaur. Ling. Septentrion. 3 tom. Meninski Thes. Linguar. Orient. 4 tom. Giggei Thesaur. Ling. Arab. 4 tom. Encyclopedie, 28 tom. Du Fresne Glossarium, 6 tom. Pindar - Oxon. Caesaris Comment. a Clarke Xenophon, Gr. - ap. Ald. Plutarchi Opera, 2 tom. Par. Diodorus Sicusus, 2 tom. Polybius, Casauboni Homer, 4 tom. ch. max. Glasg. Biblia Hebraica, a Houbegant, 4 tom. Montfaucon, 15 tom. gr. pap. Graevius &amp; Gronovius, cum Suppl. 57 tom. Hayes's Birds, coloured Hippocratis &amp; Galen, 9 tom. Sandrart Academ. Ars Pict. Ramelli's Machines Bieau's Atlas, 12 vol. De Liste's Atlas, l. paper And many others equally good, which will be sold, for Ready Money only, this Day, July 1779, and continue on Sale till all are sold, By Thomas Payne and Son, booksellers, Next the Mews Gate, in Castle Street, St. Martin's. Catalogues to be had, with Prices printed (price 6d) at Mr. Sewell's, Bookseller, Cornhill; Mr. Owen's, Bookseller, near Temple-Bar, Fleet-Street; Mr. Lewis, Bookseller, Russel Street, Covent Garden; Mr. Walter, Bookseller, at Charing Cross; Mr. Ridley, Bookseller, St. James's Street; Mr. Robson, Bookseller, New Bond Street; of the Booksellers at Oxford and Cambridge, and at the Place of Sale. Where may be had the full Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:33:05">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU3001148</link><title>A catalogue of a valuable collection of books; consisting of several libraries, and particularly those of the Rev. Thomas Negus, D. D. Rector of St. Mary's Rotherhithe, and Mr. William Price, a very ingenious Painter of Glass, Both lately deceased, [electronic resource] : this collection comprehends near ten thousand Volumes in various Languages, and in almost every Class of Learning, and many of them in the most elegant Bindings. Among them are the following, Recueil D'fstampes par Crozat, 2 vol. Ehret Plantae, per Trew, vivis coloribus. British Zoology. cuts coloured. Some original Drawings of the Zoology. ... Petiveri opera Botanica, &amp;c. 3 vol. Philosoph. Transact. at large, 4to. comp. Hill's natural Hist. 3 vol. cuts. Antoniana Margarita, 2 vol. cor. Ture. Hippoctates &amp; Galen, Charterii, 13 vol. De Bry India orient. &amp; occident. 4 vol. Russ. Assemanni Biblioth. orient. 4 vol. Giggei Lexicon Arabicum, 4 vol. ... H. Steph. Critici Sacri, 9 vol. Ed. Opt. Clericus in vet. &amp; nov. Test. 6 vol. Ruins of Palmyra, Balbec and Athens. Overbeke's Ruins of Rome. Antiquarian Society's Prints. Harris and Churchill's Voyages. General Dictionary, 10 vol. Russia. Biographia Britannica, 7 vol. compleat. Camden's Britannia, 2 vol. Russia. Horseley's Britannia Romana, 2 vol. State Trials, 6 vol. last edit. Johnson, Miller, Chambers, James and Ainsworth's Dictionaries. Patrick, Lowth, and Whithy, 6 vol. ... Statutes at large, by Cay and Russhead. Spence's Polymetis, Morocco. Cowper and Albinus's Anatomy. Cowper and Albinus's Anatomy. Ceremories Religieuses, 7 tom. Gr. pap. Medailles de Louis le Grand. Maroq. Du Halde Descript. de la Chine 4 tom. G. P. Sir Tho. Hanmer's Shakespear, 6 vol. 4 to. Ld. Sommers's Tracts, 16 vol. 4to compl. Moliere, Oeuvres de, 6 tom. 4 to. Marcq. Racine, Oeuvres de, 3 tom. 4to. Maroq. Parliam. Hist. and Chandler's Dub. 46 v. Political States, 59 vol. Svo. And many other Articles of equal Value, which will begin selling very reasonable, The Prices being printed in the Catalogue, and marked in the first Leaf of every Book. On Tuesday, March 18, 1766, and continue on Sale daily. By Benjamin White, Removed to Horace's Head, Fleet-Street, next White-Friers, Who gives the utmost Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</title><description>A catalogue of a valuable collection of books; consisting of several libraries, and particularly those of the Rev. Thomas Negus, D. D. Rector of St. Mary's Rotherhithe, and Mr. William Price, a very ingenious Painter of Glass, Both lately deceased, [electronic resource] : this collection comprehends near ten thousand Volumes in various Languages, and in almost every Class of Learning, and many of them in the most elegant Bindings. Among them are the following, Recueil D'fstampes par Crozat, 2 vol. Ehret Plantae, per Trew, vivis coloribus. British Zoology. cuts coloured. Some original Drawings of the Zoology. ... Petiveri opera Botanica, &amp;c. 3 vol. Philosoph. Transact. at large, 4to. comp. Hill's natural Hist. 3 vol. cuts. Antoniana Margarita, 2 vol. cor. Ture. Hippoctates &amp; Galen, Charterii, 13 vol. De Bry India orient. &amp; occident. 4 vol. Russ. Assemanni Biblioth. orient. 4 vol. Giggei Lexicon Arabicum, 4 vol. ... H. Steph. Critici Sacri, 9 vol. Ed. Opt. Clericus in vet. &amp; nov. Test. 6 vol. Ruins of Palmyra, Balbec and Athens. Overbeke's Ruins of Rome. Antiquarian Society's Prints. Harris and Churchill's Voyages. General Dictionary, 10 vol. Russia. Biographia Britannica, 7 vol. compleat. Camden's Britannia, 2 vol. Russia. Horseley's Britannia Romana, 2 vol. State Trials, 6 vol. last edit. Johnson, Miller, Chambers, James and Ainsworth's Dictionaries. Patrick, Lowth, and Whithy, 6 vol. ... Statutes at large, by Cay and Russhead. Spence's Polymetis, Morocco. Cowper and Albinus's Anatomy. Cowper and Albinus's Anatomy. Ceremories Religieuses, 7 tom. Gr. pap. Medailles de Louis le Grand. Maroq. Du Halde Descript. de la Chine 4 tom. G. P. Sir Tho. Hanmer's Shakespear, 6 vol. 4 to. Ld. Sommers's Tracts, 16 vol. 4to compl. Moliere, Oeuvres de, 6 tom. 4 to. Marcq. Racine, Oeuvres de, 3 tom. 4to. Maroq. Parliam. Hist. and Chandler's Dub. 46 v. Political States, 59 vol. Svo. And many other Articles of equal Value, which will begin selling very reasonable, The Prices being printed in the Catalogue, and marked in the first Leaf of every Book. On Tuesday, March 18, 1766, and continue on Sale daily. By Benjamin White, Removed to Horace's Head, Fleet-Street, next White-Friers, Who gives the utmost Value for any Library or Parcel of Books.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>