<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:46:14" name="NCSU Library " id="FW14-e030"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:46:16">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2987539</link><title>A new catalogue of a valuable and choice collection of books [electronic resource] : Being the libraries of An eminent judge, The Reverend Mr. Kent, and of Gilbert Dawson Esq; all deceas'd. Consisting of a large Collection of Books, Manuscripts, and State-Tracts, relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain, Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa, and America: Together with a compleat Set of Elzevir Classicks bound in 50 vol. in Morocco; the Royal Classicks in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Edition in Quarto; the best Edition of the Classicks cum Notis Variorum; the Louvre Classicks; the Pocket Classicks by Vascosan, Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Stephens, Aldus, and Sedan Editions; The Byzantine Historians, 31 vol. Prynn's Records, 3 vol. Rymer's F dera, 20 vol. Les Oeuvres de Plutarque par Amyot, 13 vol. in Morocco; Montfaucon's Antiquities, 15 vol. large Paper; all the old Chronicles; Sir Wm. Dugdale's Works; and the History of the several Counties in England. Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Mathematicks, the Benedictine Editions of the Fathers, Books of Physick, Anatomy, Surgery; a large Collection of Voyages and Natural History; the best Dictionaries and Lexicons, great numbers on large Paper, and several Hundred Volumes curiously bound in Morocco. Also a compleat Set of Common, Civil, and Canon Law. Which will begin to be Sold very Cheap (the lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's Shop in Gray's-Inn, on Monday the 17th Day of May, 1736, and will continue Selling all the Month of May and June. Catalogues to be had at the Place of Sale, and Money for any Library or Parcel of Books.</title><description>A new catalogue of a valuable and choice collection of books [electronic resource] : Being the libraries of An eminent judge, The Reverend Mr. Kent, and of Gilbert Dawson Esq; all deceas'd. Consisting of a large Collection of Books, Manuscripts, and State-Tracts, relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain, Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa, and America: Together with a compleat Set of Elzevir Classicks bound in 50 vol. in Morocco; the Royal Classicks in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Edition in Quarto; the best Edition of the Classicks cum Notis Variorum; the Louvre Classicks; the Pocket Classicks by Vascosan, Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Stephens, Aldus, and Sedan Editions; The Byzantine Historians, 31 vol. Prynn's Records, 3 vol. Rymer's F dera, 20 vol. Les Oeuvres de Plutarque par Amyot, 13 vol. in Morocco; Montfaucon's Antiquities, 15 vol. large Paper; all the old Chronicles; Sir Wm. Dugdale's Works; and the History of the several Counties in England. Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Mathematicks, the Benedictine Editions of the Fathers, Books of Physick, Anatomy, Surgery; a large Collection of Voyages and Natural History; the best Dictionaries and Lexicons, great numbers on large Paper, and several Hundred Volumes curiously bound in Morocco. Also a compleat Set of Common, Civil, and Canon Law. Which will begin to be Sold very Cheap (the lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's Shop in Gray's-Inn, on Monday the 17th Day of May, 1736, and will continue Selling all the Month of May and June. Catalogues to be had at the Place of Sale, and Money for any Library or Parcel of Books.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:49:34">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2987540</link><title>Bibliotheca splendidissima [electronic resource] : or, a catalogue of the valuable libraries of John Owen, Esq; Late Recorder of Windsor; Mr. John Ecton, Late Receiver of the Tenths of the Clergy: and that ingenious architect Capt. Edward Stanton. To which are added, A very fine collection, lately imported from Abroad, chiefly collected by the celebrated Mr. Colbert, first Minister of State to the late King of France: As likewise, by the learned Abbot Bignon, Librarian to the present King of France. The whole consisting of a Large and Numerous collection of books, relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain, Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa and America. The Best Editions of the classicks, by Vascosan, Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Stephens, Aldus, Sedan, the Louvre, the Royal Classicks, in usum Delphini, cum Notis variorum, &amp; Elzevir. Curiously bound in Morocco, and several with the Colbert and Bignon Arms on the Sides. Some curious Manuscripts upon Vellum. A compleat Set of the Histories of the several Counties in England. All the old Chronicles. A fine Collection of large and curious Bibles, printed by Field and others, with curious Cuts by Silvester, &amp;c. Sir William Dugdale's Works. All the best and scarcest Dictionaries and Lexicons. A fine Collection of Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Mathematicks, the Benedictine Editions of the Fathers, a compleat Set of the Common Law, Civil and Canon; a large Number of Voyages and Natural History; most of the antient and modern Books of Physick, Anatomy, Surgery, &amp;c. Great Numbers on Large Paper, and several Hundred Volumes bound in Morocco. Which will begin to be sold very cheap (the lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's shop in Gray's-Inn, on Monday the 17th day of November 1735. Catalogues may be had at the Place of Sale, and Money for any Library or Parcel of Books.</title><description>Bibliotheca splendidissima [electronic resource] : or, a catalogue of the valuable libraries of John Owen, Esq; Late Recorder of Windsor; Mr. John Ecton, Late Receiver of the Tenths of the Clergy: and that ingenious architect Capt. Edward Stanton. To which are added, A very fine collection, lately imported from Abroad, chiefly collected by the celebrated Mr. Colbert, first Minister of State to the late King of France: As likewise, by the learned Abbot Bignon, Librarian to the present King of France. The whole consisting of a Large and Numerous collection of books, relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain, Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa and America. The Best Editions of the classicks, by Vascosan, Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Stephens, Aldus, Sedan, the Louvre, the Royal Classicks, in usum Delphini, cum Notis variorum, &amp; Elzevir. Curiously bound in Morocco, and several with the Colbert and Bignon Arms on the Sides. Some curious Manuscripts upon Vellum. A compleat Set of the Histories of the several Counties in England. All the old Chronicles. A fine Collection of large and curious Bibles, printed by Field and others, with curious Cuts by Silvester, &amp;c. Sir William Dugdale's Works. All the best and scarcest Dictionaries and Lexicons. A fine Collection of Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Mathematicks, the Benedictine Editions of the Fathers, a compleat Set of the Common Law, Civil and Canon; a large Number of Voyages and Natural History; most of the antient and modern Books of Physick, Anatomy, Surgery, &amp;c. Great Numbers on Large Paper, and several Hundred Volumes bound in Morocco. Which will begin to be sold very cheap (the lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's shop in Gray's-Inn, on Monday the 17th day of November 1735. Catalogues may be had at the Place of Sale, and Money for any Library or Parcel of Books.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:52:00">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2989512</link><title>Bibliotheca Wincupiana &amp; Martyniana [electronic resource] : or, a catalogue of the libraries of the Revd Dr. Wincup, and of Robert Martyn, Of the Inner-Temple, Esq; Consisting of a Large and Curious Collection of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, &amp;c. Among which are most of the scarce Volumes of the King of France's Cabinet, bound in Morocco, the Byzantine Historians, 33 vol. Rymer's Foedera, 17 vol. Tractatus Tractatuum, 28 vol. several of the Louvre Editions of the Greek and Latin Classicks, all the Pocket-Classicks by Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Sedan, Aldus, Stephens, Elzevir, &amp;c. A Large Collection of Books of Sculpture, and single Prints, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law, Civil and Canon, Benedictine, and best Editions of the Fathers. A Great Number of Books of Voyages, and Natural History, most of the ancient and modern Physicians, Books of Anatomy, Surgery, &amp;c. Several of the scarce Dictionaries, as Doletus's, Stephens's, &amp;c. and a complete Collection of the Common Law-Books. Which will begin to be sold very Cheap (the Lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's shop in Gray's-Inn, on Tuesday the 19th of this instant Febuary, 1733-4.</title><description>Bibliotheca Wincupiana &amp; Martyniana [electronic resource] : or, a catalogue of the libraries of the Revd Dr. Wincup, and of Robert Martyn, Of the Inner-Temple, Esq; Consisting of a Large and Curious Collection of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, &amp;c. Among which are most of the scarce Volumes of the King of France's Cabinet, bound in Morocco, the Byzantine Historians, 33 vol. Rymer's Foedera, 17 vol. Tractatus Tractatuum, 28 vol. several of the Louvre Editions of the Greek and Latin Classicks, all the Pocket-Classicks by Colinaeus, Seb. Gryphius, Sedan, Aldus, Stephens, Elzevir, &amp;c. A Large Collection of Books of Sculpture, and single Prints, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law, Civil and Canon, Benedictine, and best Editions of the Fathers. A Great Number of Books of Voyages, and Natural History, most of the ancient and modern Physicians, Books of Anatomy, Surgery, &amp;c. Several of the scarce Dictionaries, as Doletus's, Stephens's, &amp;c. and a complete Collection of the Common Law-Books. Which will begin to be sold very Cheap (the Lowest Price fixed in each Book) at T. Osborne's shop in Gray's-Inn, on Tuesday the 19th of this instant Febuary, 1733-4.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:53:48">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2992187</link><title>A catalogue of the library of the late eminent and learned John Coleman Esq; Deceased. [electronic resource] : To which is added, An Appendix of books collected since from the several Auctions this Winter. The Whole is an Excellent Collection, and in fine Condition, being handsomely bound, gilt, or letter'd, in almost all Parts of Polite Literature; viz. The History, Antiquity, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland; France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, &amp;c. but more particularly what relates to Great Britain and Ireland. Likewise History, Divinity, Mathematicks, Philosophy, Physick, Surgery, &amp;c. A good Collection of the Greek and Latin Historians, chiefly of the best Editions, Classicks in Usum Sereniss. Delphini Par. Edit. &amp; cum Notis varior. and those by the several famous Printers, viz. Juntae, Aldus, Stephens's, Colinaeus, Vascosan, &amp;c. Books of Antiquity, Medals, Architecture, and Sculpture; likewise Law Civil, Common, and Canon; as also a good Collection of Lexicographers. Which will be Sold very Cheap (the Price being fixed on the first Leaf of each Book) on Tuesday the 21st of this instant April, 1730. By Harmen Noorthouck, In the Great Piazza Covent-Garden. N.B The books may be viewed three Days before the Sale begins, which will be at Nine a-Clock in the Morning. Catalogues to be had gratis at the Place of Sale.</title><description>A catalogue of the library of the late eminent and learned John Coleman Esq; Deceased. [electronic resource] : To which is added, An Appendix of books collected since from the several Auctions this Winter. The Whole is an Excellent Collection, and in fine Condition, being handsomely bound, gilt, or letter'd, in almost all Parts of Polite Literature; viz. The History, Antiquity, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland; France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, &amp;c. but more particularly what relates to Great Britain and Ireland. Likewise History, Divinity, Mathematicks, Philosophy, Physick, Surgery, &amp;c. A good Collection of the Greek and Latin Historians, chiefly of the best Editions, Classicks in Usum Sereniss. Delphini Par. Edit. &amp; cum Notis varior. and those by the several famous Printers, viz. Juntae, Aldus, Stephens's, Colinaeus, Vascosan, &amp;c. Books of Antiquity, Medals, Architecture, and Sculpture; likewise Law Civil, Common, and Canon; as also a good Collection of Lexicographers. Which will be Sold very Cheap (the Price being fixed on the first Leaf of each Book) on Tuesday the 21st of this instant April, 1730. By Harmen Noorthouck, In the Great Piazza Covent-Garden. N.B The books may be viewed three Days before the Sale begins, which will be at Nine a-Clock in the Morning. Catalogues to be had gratis at the Place of Sale.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:55:05">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU3024235</link><title>Nobilissimi illustrissimique Domini, Domini Henrici, Marchionis de la Bazoniere, bellovacorum in Normannia pr&amp;#xFFFD;positi pr&amp;#xFFFD;clarissimi, bibliothec&amp;#xFFFD; catalogus. Catalogue of the Library of the most Illustrious Henry Marquis de la Bazoniere, Governor of Bayeux in Normandy. Consisting of a large Series of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, &amp;c. The particular Histories of their Principalities and Towns, with many private State-Pieces. The Byzantine Historians in Thirty one Volumes. Du Chesne's Historia Francorum five Volumes large Paper. All the Louvre Editions of the Latin and Greek and Latin Classicks in Folio, most of them in large Paper, bound in Morocco. An entire Set of the Old Elzevir Classicks in Fifty Volumes in Morocco, bound by the Abb&amp;#xFFFD;e Du Sueil, and many in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Editions. Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law Civil and Canon, Benedictine and best Editions of the Fathers, &amp;c. Great Numbers on large Paper; and many printed on Vellum, with several hundred Volumes in Folio, bound in Morocco by the Abb&amp;#xFFFD;e Du Sueil. Which will begin to be sold very Cheap (the Price mark'd in each Book) at James Woodman's and David Lyon's shop in Russel-Street, Covent-Garden, on Monday the first of February, 1724. Catalogues may be had Gratis at the Place of Sale [electronic resource].</title><description>Nobilissimi illustrissimique Domini, Domini Henrici, Marchionis de la Bazoniere, bellovacorum in Normannia pr&amp;#xFFFD;positi pr&amp;#xFFFD;clarissimi, bibliothec&amp;#xFFFD; catalogus. Catalogue of the Library of the most Illustrious Henry Marquis de la Bazoniere, Governor of Bayeux in Normandy. Consisting of a large Series of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great-Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, &amp;c. The particular Histories of their Principalities and Towns, with many private State-Pieces. The Byzantine Historians in Thirty one Volumes. Du Chesne's Historia Francorum five Volumes large Paper. All the Louvre Editions of the Latin and Greek and Latin Classicks in Folio, most of them in large Paper, bound in Morocco. An entire Set of the Old Elzevir Classicks in Fifty Volumes in Morocco, bound by the Abb&amp;#xFFFD;e Du Sueil, and many in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Editions. Books of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law Civil and Canon, Benedictine and best Editions of the Fathers, &amp;c. Great Numbers on large Paper; and many printed on Vellum, with several hundred Volumes in Folio, bound in Morocco by the Abb&amp;#xFFFD;e Du Sueil. Which will begin to be sold very Cheap (the Price mark'd in each Book) at James Woodman's and David Lyon's shop in Russel-Street, Covent-Garden, on Monday the first of February, 1724. Catalogues may be had Gratis at the Place of Sale [electronic resource].</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:56:31">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2976692</link><title>Illustrissimi &amp; excellentissimi Ludovici Henrici, [electronic resource] : Comitis Castri-Briennij, Ludovico XIV. a Secretis, &amp; ad Romam Legati, Bibliothecae, Ad ejusdem Filium Constantiae in Normannia Episcopum pertinentis, catalogus. A catalogue of the Library of his Excellency Louis Henry de Lomente, Count de Brienne, Secretary of State of Louis XIV. and Ambassador at Rome, belonging to his Son the late Bishop of Coutance in Normandy. Consisting of a Large Series of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa; and America. The particular Histories and Antiquities of their Principalities and Towns, with several Thousand Private State-Pieces. The first Edition of the Bible printed on Vellum 1462. The Journal of the House of Lords from their Beginning to the Year 1665 in eighty Volumes in Folio. The Byzantine writers, thirty-one Volumes in Folio, in Morocco. All Du Chesne's Works in twenty-seven Volumes in Morocco. Theodore de Brie's Voyages compleat. Thuanos, large Paper, 5 vol. All the Greek and Latin Classick Authors, and most of them on large Paper. An entire Set of the Old Elzevir Classicks in Morocco, and many in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Editions. Book, of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law Civil and Canon, all the Benedictine and best Editions of the Fathers and Councils, Divinity, &amp;c. Great Numbers on large Paper, and many printed on Vellum, with several hundred Volumes in Folio, bound in Morocco by the Famous Abbe du Sueil. Which will begin to be Sold very Cheap (the Price marked in each Book) at James Woodman's and David Lyon's Shop in Russel-Street, Covent-Garden, on Tuesday the 28th of April, 1724.</title><description>Illustrissimi &amp; excellentissimi Ludovici Henrici, [electronic resource] : Comitis Castri-Briennij, Ludovico XIV. a Secretis, &amp; ad Romam Legati, Bibliothecae, Ad ejusdem Filium Constantiae in Normannia Episcopum pertinentis, catalogus. A catalogue of the Library of his Excellency Louis Henry de Lomente, Count de Brienne, Secretary of State of Louis XIV. and Ambassador at Rome, belonging to his Son the late Bishop of Coutance in Normandy. Consisting of a Large Series of Books relating to the History, Antiquities, and Constitution of Great Britain and Ireland, France, Italy, Spain, Germany, Muscovy, Poland, Sweden, Denmark, Asia, Africa; and America. The particular Histories and Antiquities of their Principalities and Towns, with several Thousand Private State-Pieces. The first Edition of the Bible printed on Vellum 1462. The Journal of the House of Lords from their Beginning to the Year 1665 in eighty Volumes in Folio. The Byzantine writers, thirty-one Volumes in Folio, in Morocco. All Du Chesne's Works in twenty-seven Volumes in Morocco. Theodore de Brie's Voyages compleat. Thuanos, large Paper, 5 vol. All the Greek and Latin Classick Authors, and most of them on large Paper. An entire Set of the Old Elzevir Classicks in Morocco, and many in Usum Delphini, of the Paris Editions. Book, of Sculpture, Architecture, Medals, Painting, Law Civil and Canon, all the Benedictine and best Editions of the Fathers and Councils, Divinity, &amp;c. Great Numbers on large Paper, and many printed on Vellum, with several hundred Volumes in Folio, bound in Morocco by the Famous Abbe du Sueil. Which will begin to be Sold very Cheap (the Price marked in each Book) at James Woodman's and David Lyon's Shop in Russel-Street, Covent-Garden, on Tuesday the 28th of April, 1724.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:58:15">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2909048</link><title>A vindication of the constitution of the English monarchy, and the just rights of the people. [electronic resource] : Or, faction, and corruption, enemies to religion, liberty, and property. Being a Brief and Impartial Account of the Times; Shewing the Origine of Faction; the Corrupt and Male-Administration in the Government; and the present ill Circumstance of Affairs in Germany and Italy: And also, the only Means by which these Evils may or can be Removed; the Exorbitant Power of the French King Reduced; and the Peace of the Kingdom Preserved and Stablished. Humbly offered to the Consideration of the Honourable House of Commons. By a lover of his countrey; and Her Majesty's faithful subject.</title><description>A vindication of the constitution of the English monarchy, and the just rights of the people. [electronic resource] : Or, faction, and corruption, enemies to religion, liberty, and property. Being a Brief and Impartial Account of the Times; Shewing the Origine of Faction; the Corrupt and Male-Administration in the Government; and the present ill Circumstance of Affairs in Germany and Italy: And also, the only Means by which these Evils may or can be Removed; the Exorbitant Power of the French King Reduced; and the Peace of the Kingdom Preserved and Stablished. Humbly offered to the Consideration of the Honourable House of Commons. By a lover of his countrey; and Her Majesty's faithful subject.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:59:55">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2943449</link><title>A new account of Italy. [electronic resource] : Containing a description of all its countries, the various constitutions, under several sovereign princes and states, their strength, riches, revenues, trade, and coins, their curiosities, rarities, and wonders, the customs, manners, and trade of the people. Together with a particular description of Rome, Venice, Genoa, Millain, and all the other remarkable cities.</title><description>A new account of Italy. [electronic resource] : Containing a description of all its countries, the various constitutions, under several sovereign princes and states, their strength, riches, revenues, trade, and coins, their curiosities, rarities, and wonders, the customs, manners, and trade of the people. Together with a particular description of Rome, Venice, Genoa, Millain, and all the other remarkable cities.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:00:33">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU2235084</link><title>Low-metallicity star formation : from the first stars to dwarf galaxies : proceedings of the 255th Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Rapallo (Genova), Italy, June 16-20, 2008</title><description>Low-metallicity star formation : from the first stars to dwarf galaxies : proceedings of the 255th Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Rapallo (Genova), Italy, June 16-20, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e030-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e030/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:02:22">http://catalog.lib.ncsu.edu/record/NCSU3031132</link><title>Interacting binaries [electronic resource] : accretion, evolution, outcomes : Cefalù, Sicily 4-10 July 2004</title><description>Interacting binaries [electronic resource] : accretion, evolution, outcomes : Cefalù, Sicily 4-10 July 2004</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>