<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7001">LHC collision publications</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:41" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Hf5BHTr0N-YC&amp;pg=PA125&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Large Hadron Collider \- Page 125</title><description>One argument raised against doomsday fears was that collisions at energies equivalent to and higher than those of the LHC have been ... and Igor Tkachev, of the Institute for Nuclear Research in Moscow — to monitor the latest concerns about the LHC collisions.353 On 20 ... which endorsed its conclusions in a press release that announced the publication.352,356 Following the July 2008 release of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QKVfSKhXoWMC&amp;pg=PA7&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Dijet Angular Distributions in Proton-Proton Collisions: ... - Page 7</title><description>Since in the initial phase of LHC, protons only collide at half their nominal energy, ATLAS has performed its first measurement of dijet angular distributions at √ s = 7 TeV. ... The work in this thesis was published in a number of publications.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:32">http://books.google.nl/books?id=-Fnsg7hEYgUC&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Large Hadron Collider: Unraveling the Mysteries of the ... - Page 48</title><description>The initial November re-start collisions were performed with the beam energy held back to a mere 450 GeV, but with the ... the first research paper based upon data collected with the LHC was accepted for publication on December 1, 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:01">http://books.google.nl/books?id=MXrdJrzdfy0C&amp;pg=PT345&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Collisions and Collaboration: The Organization of Learning ...</title><description>ATLAS stands for A Toroidal Lhc ApparatuS, CMS for Compact Muon Solenoid, ALICE for A Large Ion Collider ... 10 It should be noted that the publication policies are not entirely determined by the collaborations alone, since, as a last step in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:33">http://books.google.nl/books?id=JfZwj0a9NroC&amp;pg=PA1121&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Issues in General Physics Research: 2013 Edition - Page 1121</title><description>For more information on this research see: First Event-by-Event Fluctuation Studies in Pb-Pb Collisions at LHC Energy by ... Progress of Theoretical Physics Supplement can be contacted at: Progress Theoretical Physics Publication Office, C, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Dy_6gr76QmkC&amp;pg=PA139&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Focus on Black Hole Research - Page 139</title><description>This is due to the fact that at high collision energies, or small distances respectively, the proton contents a high ... Figure 7: The left plot shows the differential cross section for black hole production in proton-proton-collisions at the LHC for Mr — 1 TeV. ... The importance of this process led to a high number of publications on the topic of TeV-mass black holes at colliders [34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42].</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:14">http://books.google.nl/books?id=eVxJAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA79&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>From the PS to the LHC \- 50 Years of Nobel Memories in ... - Page 79</title><description>... which one could write a sensible paper, because during this period of the war, all publications were very hard to get, and very ... At that time the idea that one could collide two beams against each other was met with two forms of scepticism.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:36">http://books.google.nl/books?id=onLbH3WDgiYC&amp;pg=PA218&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Large Hadron Collider Phenomenology - Page 218</title><description>For more information, the LHC accelerator is well documented in many publications. A design ... Later, bunched proton and antiproton beams were accelerated from 26 GeV/c to 315 GeV/c and brought into collision at the SPS (Super Proton ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=IbwYk8YpHA8C&amp;pg=PA35&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Physics at the Large Hadron Collider \- Page 35</title><description>In order to protect the magnets, the LHC requires a dedicated and special Magnet Quench Protection System including voltage tabs, ... new tighter collision focus and incorporate novel techniques of crossing angle geometry and transversely deflecting “crab” cavities to reach the ... Most appropriately for this publication, we have highlighted at some length, at the risk of losing some technical readers, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7001-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7001_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:20">http://books.google.nl/books?id=kCmpSlzWh2AC&amp;pg=PA271&amp;dq=LHC+collision+publications&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Wc9SU9asB8XOygOay4CICQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cosmic Rays for Particle and Astroparticle Physics - ... - Page 271</title><description>Moreover, additional items, not discussed here, are currently under analysis and will be addressed in forthcoming publications. ... 5. 6. 7. 8. 9. FIRST RESULTS OF LHCF; VERY FORWARD PARTICLES AT LHC COLLISION 271 6. Conclusions ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>