<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:57" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:58">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ju08AQAAIAAJ&amp;pg=PA201&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Scientific American - Page 201</title><description>NO. 26. SCIENTIFIC AMERICAN PUBLISHED WEEKLY At No. 128 Fulton street, (Snn Buildings,) New York, bt munn &amp; co. ... Single copies of the paper are on sale at the office of Eublication and at all the periodical stores In this city, trooklyn and ... to believe that common air penetrates into the vent of the volcano by a fissure, is exhaled by it and escapes heated. ... 4 IBs/. . r- □*».. — , t -/ «-.L»- □ - □ -- □ fitted in the notch, g, of the rack, A'. This movement opens the ports, N, of the two ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:28">http://books.google.nl/books?id=e88DAAAAMBAJ&amp;pg=PA84&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Fresh Air - Sep 2001 - Page 84</title><description>As it became apparent that alternative energy sources were not an answer to home heating for the average Joe — at least not yet — the buzzwords ... Mold, a microscopic plant, can grow on almost any surface, including wood, paper, carpet, fabric and foods. ... end of a cigarette or cigar and from smoke that has been exhaled by a smoker. .... Ibs. The 24-position adjustable clutch lets you perform a full range of tasks, from drilling into hard masonry to precise driving into soft woods.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:58">http://books.google.nl/books?id=_KsVIP4XG64C&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Advances in Astronautical Sciences - Volume 11 - Page 235</title><description>Four types of life support systems will be discussed, but since the scope of this paper does not permit an optimization of ... Human waste, including liquids, solids, and exhaled gases, are expelled overboard. ... The N0 weights (tanks included) are based on a consumption rate of 4.32 Ibs/man/ £ day plus a one-day reserve.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4YVqDL3_hpgC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Destined</title><description>And will Zoey be able to touch Aurox’s humanity in time to protect him – and everyone – from his own fate? Find out what’s destined in the next thrilling chapter of the House of Night series.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=puw_AAAAYAAJ&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Calendar of State Papers, Colonial Series ...: East Indies ... - Page 6</title><description>To which Vane answered he wondered much at this message, for he could not accept the States' answer, and knew ... The 158 bales in the Palsgrave were received mostly at the port where the extreme heat had exhaled the humidity to the loss of one maund in 18 whether a mand be 1 2 J Ib. avoirdupois the Hollanders have sent back 200 Ibs. of stones, besides extraordinary complaints of loss in weight.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:39:01">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8SXVAAAAMAAJ&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Littell's Living Age - Volume 27 - Page 482</title><description>for his money, no less than 45 Ibs. of water in thi; first lot, (it Ibs. in Ihe s.'Tiind ... The gases which are exhaled into the atmosphere by animal and vegetable decomposition are soluble in still larger ... be pounded and moistened, enough of the powder will be dissolved to give the water a powerful reaction on turmeric paper.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:39:32">http://books.google.nl/books?id=UhwTAAAAYAAJ&amp;pg=PA320&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Parliamentary Papers, House of Commons and Command</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:39:53">http://books.google.nl/books?id=L7_PAAAAMAAJ&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Bulletin of Hygiene - Volume 36 - Page 739</title><description>Samples of dust on filter paper ... 21, No. 6, 491-501, 8 figs. [14 refs.] The instrument, which weighs 10} Ibs., is entirely contained in a case measuring 5" X 8i" X 15"; rechargeable ... Both inhaled and exhaled air are sampled with thermal precipitators and the size distributions determined by visual and electron microscopy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:40:26">http://books.google.nl/books?id=D-ohAQAAMAAJ&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Spectator - Volume 80 - Page 479</title><description>oyer which he twinkled considerably, was not that he had detected a fraud which had, as he said, deceived 'Berlin, ... At the end of three or four minutes I handed it back to him with the short comment, ' Nineteenth century paper, my dear Sir,' and he took it away in a hurry and did not come again. ... A CORRECTION. , [TO TK» KDITOB OF IBS " SPIOIITOB. ... on every dreamer there, Every shadowy Btreet sends down her spells commingled With her silver dew exhaled, dissolved in air.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7002-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7002_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:40:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=t0NPAAAAYAAJ&amp;q=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;dq=exhaled+NO+IBS+papers&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=WdBSU_SEFMLOygPlsYLACg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Poultry Keeper - Volumes 7-8 - Page 156</title><description>I have put in no ventilator, as I wish to keep it as warm as possible without the expense of a stove. ... There are several causes for dampncss,among them the condensation of moisture from the air, the giving off of moisture by the lumber and Ihe moisture exhaled by the fowls. ... Instead of applying the tarred paper to the walls tack it on lath, so as to leave an air space. .... BONE, per 100 Ibs.,«.50: beef, (2.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>