<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7011">Vera Pavlova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:55:25" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:55:26">http://books.google.nl/books?id=-9izkTIWaWMC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>If There is Something to Desire: One Hundred Poems</title><description>The one hundred poems in this book, her first full-length volume in English, all have the same salty immediacy, as if spoken by a woman who feels that, as the title poem concludes, “If there was nothing to regret, / there was nothing to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:56:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=s6GAmj_x9EgC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A Werewolf Problem in Central Russia and Other Stories</title><description>The story, Vera Pavlovna's Ninth Dream, is on the transition from communism to capitalism as experienced by the cleaner of a public toilet, Bulldozer Driver's Day is on a hydrogen bomb assembly line, while The Ontology of Childhood compares ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:58:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=jpW7DMWcDb4C&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>An Anthology of Contemporary Russian Women Poets</title><description>Based on an exhaustive review of Russian poetry, An Anthology of Contemporary Russian Women Poets is the first comprehensive collection of its kind.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SaWCeD7RJm4C&amp;pg=PA67&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Revolution on My Mind: Writing a Diary Under Stalin - Page 67</title><description>To document their self-transformative work, diarists repeatedly invoked the concepts of “planning,” “struggle,” and “consciousness,” core Communist values of the period of the first Five-Year Plans. The young schoolteacher Vera Pavlova noted ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:02:45">http://books.google.nl/books?id=pV3vAAAAMAAJ&amp;q=Vera+Pavlova&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Russian Life - Volume 45 - Page 33</title><description>Nothing seemed to augur that Vera Pavlova would become a leading light of 21st century Russian poetry. The daughter of engineers, she became a serious student of music at the age of eight, graduated from the prestigious Gnesin Musical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:04:22">http://books.google.nl/books?id=hm8aAQAAIAAJ&amp;q=Vera+Pavlova&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Masquerade and Femininity: Essays on Russian and Polish ...</title><description>Chapter Thirteen Vera Pavlova's The Intimate Diary of an Excellent Student and the Masquerade Of Femininity Marja Rytkonen When an author constructs her writer's identity as a poetess rather than as a poet, it signals a different point of view ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:07:32">http://books.google.nl/books?id=gTx6s9JOBtcC&amp;pg=PR12&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Contemporary Russian Poetry: An Anthology - Page xii</title><description>The “crude” social poetry by Elena Fanailova and Andrey Rodionov equally disturb the ear. As never before, the diverse voices of women resonate distinctly and clearly — among them Vera Pavlova's intimate lyrical diary that is simultaneously ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:11:04">http://books.google.nl/books?id=PPwbAQAAMAAJ&amp;q=Vera+Pavlova&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Europe - Issues 313-322 - Page 9</title><description>With advice and administrative support from the International Finance Corporation (IFC), the private sector arm of the World Bank, Nizhny Novgorod became Russia's symbol of privatization when Vera Pavlova bought the ornate pre-revolu- ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:14:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=xU1EAAAAIAAJ&amp;q=Vera+Pavlova&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Sputnik Monthly Digest - Page 98</title><description>The dancers are encouraged by means of extra bonuses, free holidays at health resorts, etc. Vera Pavlova herself has received a government award and the title, Honoured Artiste of the Russian Federation. Vera Pavlova: "I am often asked ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7011-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7011_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:18:12">http://books.google.nl/books?id=9lsGa3QGP3kC&amp;pg=PA132&amp;dq=Vera+Pavlova&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=DSlTU7jeLsSsO_PVgIAD&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Essays on Karolina Pavlova \- Page 132</title><description>Perhaps more interesting in this context is Vera, the heroine of Baratynskij's Cyganka (The Gypsy Woman, 1829-31, 1842, also known as Nalozlmica [The Concubine]). After the death of her beloved, Vera's personality is deadened: "Verm vzor, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>