<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:00:48" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:00:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ODFmm0aI3F8C&amp;pg=PA183&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Corporate Finance: Theory &amp; Practice - Page 183</title><description>For instance, BMW and Volkswagen posted similar sales trends, but completely different earnings trends during 2003 because their proximity to breakeven point was very different. BMW was clearly farther ... Sales Operating income BMW C1 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:01:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1OotO6QwRaEC&amp;pg=PA19&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Motorbikes - Page 19</title><description>Like the driver of a car, the rider in a BMW C1-E is safely strapped in using seatbelts. Amazing design The BMW C1-E scooter is not powered by gas but by electricity. The C1-E is designed to be as safe as a car. The frame of the scooter is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:04:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=lDgXT42kcncC&amp;pg=PA60&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Nurturing Science-based Ventures: An International Case ... - Page 60</title><description>The C1's most innovative design feature was its emphasis on safety. BMW claimed that its crash tests showed that, in a head-on collision, the C1 offered a standard of accident protection comparable to a modern subcompact car. It was the first ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:07:50">http://books.google.nl/books?id=dzSElH5E4AQC&amp;pg=PA28&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cycle World Magazine - Jan 1998 - Page 28</title><description>Safety will be a strong selling point for the C1 Closer to reality is BMW's C1 commuter scooter, which features a shoulder harness and front crumple zone. Proposed options include a heated seat, rear storage box, CD player, navigation system ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:10:56">http://books.google.nl/books?id=eTH-0DNDblEC&amp;pg=PA21&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cycle World Magazine - Jan 1993 - Page 21</title><description>HILE OTHERS POSTUlate on the shape and form of fiature IOtOrcycles, BMW has built It example of what it sees as re ... 0n E Thompson BMW's C1 is an attempt to combine the advantages of an automobile with those of a motorcycle into a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:12:15">http://books.google.nl/books?id=CWGpAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA79&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Positioning the Brand: An Inside-Out Approach - Page 79</title><description>Partly due to the fact that a helmet was not obligatory for this vehicle, real bikers did not categorize the BMW C1 as a motorcycle. The C1 was axed in 2003. BMW could have made the C1 a success if it had come up with a separate category for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:37">http://books.google.nl/books?id=02BcbwAACAAJ&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>BMW Motorcycles: BMW R1200RT, BMW GS, BMW F650 Single, BMW ...</title><description>Please note that the content of this book primarily consists of articles available from Wikipedia or other free sources online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:16:24">http://books.google.nl/books?id=84hF-qoR5I8C&amp;pg=SA18-PA13&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Motorcycle Handling and Chassis Design: The Art and Science</title><description>The BMW C1 shown left. Fitted with full cross over seat belts this machine has been granted exemption from the helmet laws in some countries. Note the seat offering full back support and the side extensions to protect the rider's shoulders.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:19:31">http://books.google.nl/books?id=N2V4AgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PT297&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Chosen City</title><description>They won't because motor biking is often cold, frequently wet and much, much more dangerous than car driving. BMW's C1 could change that.The Bavarian car giant that failed to turn Rover around has succeeded in designing a motorbike that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7042-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7042_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:21:23">http://books.google.nl/books?id=h4PSwh_dmOEC&amp;pg=PA16&amp;dq=bmw+c1&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=IOFTU4ORK4fpywOJqIG4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>More than Bricks in the Wall: Organizational Perspectives ... - Page 16</title><description>Based on our analysis of new growth initiatives in companies such as BMW, Deutsche Bank, General Electric, and IBM, we ... However, many other examples of separate growth businesses – including the German car manufacturer BMW's C1 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>