<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:11:18" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:11:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=0jElJKoeovcC&amp;pg=PA279&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Photographs of Edouard Baldus - Page 279</title><description>“The Exhibition of Photographs and Daguerreotypes, by the London Photographic Society.” Liveqaool ... Photographs of the Auvergne, the New Louvre, and the agricultural exhibition; facsimile gravures after Lepautre. Ernest Conduché.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:14:12">http://books.google.nl/books?id=gkU_XIBaIXoC&amp;pg=PA186&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A pilgrimage to Auvergne, from Picardy to Le Velay - Page 186</title><description>The tomb of Marshal Lafayette, the respected Governor of Auvergne, was sacrificed ; all the pictures and books that could be found were burnt, the fine painted windows demolished, and now the incendiaries approached the tower of refuge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:17:02">http://books.google.nl/books?id=IuABAAAAQAAJ&amp;pg=PA20&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Noel D'Auvergne \- Page 20</title><description>The quiet smile upon D'Auvergne's sunburnt countenance broadened and became more beautiful, and the two friends ... D'Auvergne suddenly responded, glancing round his book-laden chamber ; and then, pointing to three small pictures ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:19:13">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KhoyAQAAMAAJ&amp;pg=PA186&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A Pilgrimage to Auvergne \- Volume 2 - Page 186</title><description>The tomb of Marshal Lafayette, the respected Governor of Auvergne, was sacrificed; all the pictures and books that could be found were burnt, the fine painted windows demolished, and now the incendiaries approached the tower of refuge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:20:25">http://books.google.nl/books?id=kvTFAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA213&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Local Meanings, Global Schooling: Anthropology and World ...</title><description>When I met them, they were drawing pictures describing the differences between the regions ofNormandy and Auvergne and mounting photos from the trip for a display at an upcoming parent night. Many children expressed their view to me ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:23:05">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fLs-iKyChYIC&amp;pg=PA100&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Romanesque Wooden Doors of Auvergne \- Page 100</title><description>Croiser le fer is a well-known dueling term, while persons engaged in a fight or an argument may be said to cross legs or shins, a figure of wrestling.61 Romanesque art makes frequent use of this verbal image, both in the context of heroic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:24:48">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1vUVAAAAYAAJ&amp;pg=PR5&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Auvergne, Piedmont, and Savoy: A Summer Ramble - Page v</title><description>CHAPTER I. Advantages of a holiday — Advice of Democritus, Junior — Difficulty in selecting a route — Auvergne, ... Exhibition of modern pictures at the Palais des Tuileries — Great national ' exposition' — Scenes of the late revolution ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=3DxWAAAAcAAJ&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Little Mountaineers of Auvergne; Or the Adventures of ... - Page 48</title><description>A variety of fine sculpture is to be seen'here, and in the choir are three beautiful pictures'by a celebrated artist named Cozpel; the subjects are, the descent from the cross ; the annunciation ; and the disciples of Emmeus. They now proceeded ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:30:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=sdw5AAAAIAAJ&amp;pg=PA164&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Crime and Repression in the Auvergne and the Guyenne, ... - Page 164</title><description>Many claimed to have no profession, which could mean anything from herding pigs to selling devotional pictures. A number of prisoners were not surprisingly confused about their principal occupations. One sailor who was simultaneously a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=buQYAAAAYAAJ&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=pictures+auvergne&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tv9TU6WrH4WzywOyu4C4CA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Little Mountaineers of Auvergne, Or, The Adventures of ... - Page 48</title><description>A variety of fine sculpture is to be seen here, and in the choir are three beautiful pictures by a celebrated artist named Cozpel &gt; the subjects arei the descent from the cross ; the anmn&gt; ciatioh ; and the disciples of Emmeus. They now ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>