<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:22:52" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:22:53">http://books.google.nl/books?id=rIJIank876AC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Digital Reader: Using E-books in K-12 Education</title><description>This book introduces the unique features that have established e-books as a powerful, effective learning tool for all grade levels and for students with special needs.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:24:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=2pR3MpF2p-sC&amp;pg=PA70&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kindle Touch For Dummies Portable Edition - Page 70</title><description>When you purchase Kindle e-books from Amazon, they're associated with your Amazon account. If you have more than one Kindle ... If you give a used Kindle as a gift, the content you purchased can't be given as a gift. The device must be ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:26:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=cOHAAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PT94&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kindle Paperwhite For Dummies</title><description>If you give a used Kindle as a gift, the content you purchased can't be given as a gift. The device must be deregistered and the previous content erased. You can deregister a Kindle Paperwhite on the device itself (in the Settings section) or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:28:25">http://books.google.nl/books?id=uhpS6dd3gLAC&amp;pg=PT77&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kindle Fire HD For Dummies</title><description>Removing content from Kindle Fire HD involves pressing it with your finger and choosing Remove from Device from the ... On Kindle Fire HD, items you've used recently are displayed here chronologically, with the most recent item you used on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:31:37">http://books.google.nl/books?id=OJLydG1S5x8C&amp;pg=SA3-PA22&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kindle Fire: Out of the Box - Page 3-22</title><description>Unlike Kindle apps for non-Amazon devices, the Fire (and other Kindles) allows you to receive and view your own ... If you've never used Kindle's personal document service before, all you'll find in your library is the Kindle Fire User's Guide.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:34:04">http://books.google.nl/books?id=iAgDYoo0HoIC&amp;pg=PA30&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>My Kindle Fire - Page 30</title><description>Instead, your Kindle Fire's keyboard uses touch just like the rest of the interface. At first, you might find the Kindle Fire's keyboard a bit hard to get used to, but after some time, you'll find it to be an easy way to enter data. In fact, there are some ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:35:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=VdUOGi9sUesC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>That Used To Be Us: What Went Wrong with America - and How ...</title><description>, Thomas L. Friedman and Michael Mandelbaum analyze those challenges - globalization, the revolution in information technology, the nation's chronic deficits, and its pattern of energy consumption - and spell out what needs to be done now ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:37:14">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XMCoDRVzR-kC&amp;pg=PA54&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Taking Your Kindle Fire to the Max - Page 54</title><description>Kindle Fire. While its one-touch shopping might make it easy for us to purchase books, e-journals, music, and video, ... Taking precautions with certain accessories can help make certain that your Kindle Fire is used to its full potential and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:39:48">http://books.google.nl/books?id=UXdK4epTU14C&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>I Used to Know That: Stuff You Forgot From School</title><description>Witty, engaging, entertaining-a book you'll pick up again and again. Author Caroline Taggart discovered two things while researching this book and talking with other people: One, everybody had been to school.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:43:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=o8RNnwEACAAJ&amp;dq=used+kindle&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=3GRUU_v5DcLjywP5wYCQBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>150 Tips and Tricks for the Kindle Fire and Kindle Fire HD</title><description>This is all arranged with a series of pictures of what you can do and a number of steps for each individual tip or trick. Be sure to refer to this guide often when taking a look at what you can do with your Kindle Fire.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>