<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7069">Eames chair</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:06:11" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:06:12">http://books.google.nl/books?id=RlRQAAAAMAAJ&amp;q=Eames+chair&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Eames lounge chair: an icon of modern design</title><description>This book is the first in-depth study of one of the most revered pieces of American furniture, and its equally revered creators.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:08:56">http://books.google.nl/books?id=tUHgnsOeQNAC&amp;q=Eames+chair&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The modern chair: classic designs by Thonet, Breuer, Le ...</title><description>A noted furniture designer discusses functional and aesthetic elements of more than 40 "classic" modern chairs. Profusely illustrated with photographs and explanatory drawings.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:11:13">http://books.google.nl/books?id=91T6Z8S7Zc4C&amp;pg=PA1876&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Library of Congress Subject Headings - Volume 2 - Page 1876</title><description>Eames chairs (Continued) Eames plastic side chair Eames school seating Eames stacking chair Eames tandem shell seating Eames tandem sling seating Eames wire mesh chair La chaise (Eames chair) La Fonda chairs Time-Life chair ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:12:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=JJGeC8kqrEUC&amp;pg=PA249&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Charles and Ray Eames: Designers of the Twentieth Century - Page 249</title><description>The Aluminum Group consisted of large and small lounge chairs, a dining chair, an ottoman, and dining and coffee tables with tops of slate, clear glass, or Botticino marble. The marble — an unusually luxurious choice for the Eameses ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:15:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8CtYPgAACAAJ&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Charles and Ray Eames</title><description>This engaging new series is dedicated to showcasing the very best in furniture and object design from some of the most important architects of the Twentieth-century.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:19:06">http://books.google.nl/books?id=o1fuGziJljEC&amp;pg=PT315&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Harbrace Guide to Writing, Concise Edition</title><description>But, we can also look at the first definition, “made from the crop of a single identified district in a good year,” in reference to “vintage Eames.” “SINGLE IDENTIFIED DISTRICT.” For this as well there is an EAMES vintage furniture analogy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:22:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=EwOcmmnxKbwC&amp;pg=PA136&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>American Design in the Twentieth Century: Personality and ...</title><description>Eames's experiments with laminated wood coincided with technological advances spurred by military uses for the material during the Second World War, resulting in a sophisticated state of the art after the war. The range of Eames's furniture ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:26:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=2-UCAAAAMBAJ&amp;pg=PA52&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>New York Magazine - 5 Nov 1984 - Page 52</title><description>City Barn Antiques ALWAYS HAS the Heywood-Wakefield furniture (a cabinet is $450, a coffee table $125 to $150), along ... Herman Miller CONTINUES TO make many of Charles Eames's designs, including the molded- plywood lounge chair ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:27:09">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WTvfzdpTyuUC&amp;pg=PT111&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Modern Women: Women Artists at The Museum of Modern Art</title><description>Even in 1973 Arthur Drexler's introduction to the exhibition Charles Eames: Furniture from the Design Collection did not properly credit Ray in the first draft, which mentions her only as an assistant. The manuscript of the second version, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7069-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7069_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:27:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Jr8LAQAAMAAJ&amp;q=Eames+chair&amp;dq=Eames+chair&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=A29UU7PmGoavygOM44KwAg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The work of Charles and Ray Eames: a legacy of invention</title><description>The essays in this handsome and generously illustrated volume examine the Eameses' projects in the contexts of science, corporate patronage, and politics as well as those of modern design, architecture, and art.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>