<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7079">a-team theme music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:41:32" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:41:33">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wyz_2DEah4o</link><title>The A-Team Full Theme Tune \- YouTube</title><description>Sep 15, 2007 - The A-Team Full Theme Tune \- YouTube. Subscribe 6,903. All comments (295). Share your thoughts. Top comments. Stream. Derekswearsalot Pratticurse via Google+. 8 months ago. #ATeamThem #80sTV. Reply. 16.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:42:23">http://books.google.nl/books?id=apVrGzAkCtsC&amp;pg=PA32&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Sound Targets: American Soldiers and Music in the Iraq War - Page 32</title><description>After this section, the music returns to the texture dominated by strings, brass, and snare drum. This passage of The A-Team theme clearly reveals the influence of metal and hard rock timbres. The classic hard rock backbeat with the power ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:45:33">http://books.google.nl/books?id=keFoYZYtEjEC&amp;pg=PA11&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A Team of Destiny: The Unforgettable Story of Indiana's ... - Page 11</title><description>“He's. got. the. Whole. World. in. His. Hands.” Every sports team should have a rousing song or theme that brings their emotions to the surface and the team to winning ways. Whether it is the school song or a call by the coach or captain for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:14">http://books.google.nl/books?id=vKVQaJ0pMdQC&amp;pg=PA147&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Making Things Happen: Mastering Project Management - Page 147</title><description>The B-team has a small but poorly understood issues list. Which team do you think will most likely meet its dates? I'd bet on the A-team (play A-Team theme music). If nothing else, skepticism dictates that the B-team's small issues list implies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:51:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=UUM_AAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA183&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Music Business and the Experience Economy: The ... - Page 183</title><description>Two examples illustrate the forces at work. The AFL team St Kilda, a long standing but not particularly successful Melbourne seaside club has “When the saints go marching in” as its theme song. It is an adapted version of the once gospel song ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:53:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=AKlgjBCPPnsC&amp;pg=PA24&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Encyclopedia of Television Series, Pilots and Specials</title><description>base in Texas, follows the misadventures of Sgt. Tyrone Valentine and Pvt. Tony Baker, a pair of conniving GI's, attached to ... producer: David Lloyd Producer: Richard Correll Director: James Burrows Music: David Wheatley Theme music "It's a Good Life": Judy Hart ... Though still wanted by the military police, they have become the A-Team, daring soldiers of fortune who will tackle any job — for a price.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:54:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=LQD2AAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PT73&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Putting Patients First Field Guide: Global Lessons in ...</title><description>Adapting practices to meet individual needs, such as carefully assessing the appropriateness of two hourly turns for a person in the very ... They may prefer to talk to the anesthetic technician about football or even sing their team's theme song.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:58:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8eClrLuaAekC&amp;q=a-team+theme+music&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Playing beyond the scoreboard: a team captain's guide to a ... - Page 80</title><description>Consider printing your theme on a banner and place it in your locker room as a constant reminder to everyone who enters. • Theme song — Is there a hot new song that reflects the team's makeup? Get the song and play it before games. Music ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:03:26">http://books.google.nl/books?id=BCPsX1FxxuoC&amp;pg=PA79&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Help I'M Cheating on God - Page 79</title><description>I love nerds, I hope my future husband owns a pocket protector and thick glasses. I love men that where the ... The theme song from the A team blared in my head and I was waiting for Mr. T to jump out of a trailer. I shook my head and came ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7079-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7079_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:06:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=p6dxw4TwIVoC&amp;pg=PA137&amp;dq=a-team+theme+music&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=fKFUU7GaFum8ygPm34HgDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Simply Devine: Memoirs of a Hall of Fame Coach - Page 137</title><description>Playing in the Cotton Bowl was always a happy time, but going into Dallas and playing the University of Texas was another story. ... everyone, including the officials, put their hands over their hearts when the band played "The Eyes of Texas Are Upon You," the school's theme song. ... I do vividly recall the waiters singing a heart- pounding song at a team meal: "It's not where you start, it's where you end.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>