<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:36:52" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:36:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QYYMqXUyjnUC&amp;pg=PA206&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Great Depression in America: A Cultural Encyclopedia</title><description>In 1933, one gallon of gasoline cost, on average, 19.64 cents as compared to 23.26 cents in 1926 (roughly $2.96 and $2.63, respectively, in contemporary dollars). ... Decreased driving in the Depression created fierce competition among distributors, and the ''gas'' station, as a recognizable ... To counter decreasing gasoline sales, many oil companies wanted to increase the number andkind of auxiliary ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:38:12">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4ODjVe3M21QC&amp;pg=PA25&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Popular Science - Mar 1980 - Page 25</title><description>(D) Is practical because you get more energy out of a gallon of alcohol than it takes to produce it. ... To find out, I have spent the last few weeks talking to many scientists and experts in alcohol-fuel production, and to people who are running ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:40:20">http://books.google.nl/books?id=EdqAfRb95vsC&amp;pg=PA24&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Inflation Or Depression: The Continuing Crisis of the ... - Page 24</title><description>For example, gas mileage was l6.4 per gallon in l949. It has fallen to l4-l5 miles per gallon since. Had we ... Built-in obsolescence, designing products that are built to collapse, also seems to be a necessary cost of corporate capitalism. Another ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:43:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=e-rKAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA357&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>State and Local Politics - Page 357</title><description>Populist antitax advocates became fixtures in many states: Howard Jarvis (California), Bill Sizemore (Oregon), Tim ... Exemptions date back to the 1930s, when states allowed poor homesteaders protections from foreclosure during the Great Depression. ... Gas taxes are charged per gallon, with a state rate added on top of the $0.18 per gallon ($0.24 for diesel) in tax going to the federal government.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:46:29">http://books.google.nl/books?id=G1DfAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA79&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Jordan's Journey: An Illustrated History of my Family Ancestry - Page 79</title><description>So really and truly, I mean, it just didn't hurt us too much since my daddy owned quite a bit of land and we were on his farm and would help each ... [she laughed] J: Can you remember how much flour and sugar and gas might have cost during the depression? M: Well gas, I remember when it was 17 and 18 cents a gallon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:49:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=7vADAAAAMBAJ&amp;pg=PA38&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Weekly World News - 15 Jun 1999 - Page 38</title><description>Squirting ice water in patients' ears can stop manic depression 1 • • • Igg «m»mw "** ^ww Weekly World NewsJ Medical Report By MICHAEL ... Gasoline prices have been falling for two decades but they finally □ — hit rock-bottom earlier this year. ... in interacting with other people. up a lot faster than they went down — and could be more than $2 a gallon for regular and as much as $2.50 for premium.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:50:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=tA0WUdBPtcMC&amp;pg=PA63&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Economics: Principles and Policy - Page 63</title><description>Total output lost to Bonnie was 2.7 million barrels of oil and more than 4.6 [billion cubic feet] of gas through Tuesday. ... One weak hurricane and one tropical depression in ... consider this higher tax as an addition to their costs and will pass it on to you and other consumers by raising the price of gas by 10 cents per gallon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:52:57">http://books.google.nl/books?id=RFVrcK4UW7EC&amp;pg=PA69&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Microeconomics: Principles and Policy - Page 69</title><description>Total output lost to Bonnie was 2.7 million barrels of oil and more than 4.6 [billion cubic feet] of gas through Tuesday. ... One weak hurricane and one tropical depression in July could be ... higher tax as an addition to their costs and will pass it on to you and other consumers by raising the price of gas by 10 cents per gallon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:53:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=5eMKAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PT135&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Economics: Principles and Policy</title><description>5 Puzzle Resolved Those Leaping Oil Prices The disturbing increases in the price of gasoline, and of the oil from ... Bonnie cut nearly 52 percent of total Gulf production at its peak, even though it had weakened from a tropical storm to a tropical depression by the time it entered the Gulf and never ... Service station operators will then have to collect 10 additional cents in taxes on every gallon they pump.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:56:24">http://books.google.nl/books?id=pCoK3vn7URcC&amp;pg=PA155&amp;dq=How+much+was+a+gallon+of+gas+during+depression&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tOZUU7mUCYKUOJC_gLgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Getting There: The Epic Struggle Between Road and Rail in ...</title><description>Political compromise had diluted the act, rendering it largely ineffective, and the rails continued to face many of the same ... Amazingly, people drove even more during the Great Depression. ... Watching general revenues dry up, Washington had imposed a penny-a-gallon gas tax for the first time in 1932, an ominous ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>