<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:22:30" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_01.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:22:31">http://burrsettles.com/pub/settles.activelearning.pdf</link><title>Active Learning Literature Survey \- Burr Settles</title><description>Jan 26, 2010 - Active learning is well-motivated in many modern machine learning problems, where unlabeled data may be ... This report provides a general introduction to active learning and a survey of the literature. This includes a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:23:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=plESnwEACAAJ&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Psychology: Modules for Active Learning</title><description>While the text provides a broad overview of essential psychology topics ideal for introductory courses, its modular design also readily supports more specialized curricula, allowing instructors to use the self-contained instructional units ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:25:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=eOnKAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Psychology: Modules for Active Learning \- Page 48</title><description>SURVEY QUESTION 5.4: What is a survey? Sometimes psychologists would like to ask everyone in the world a few well-chosen questions: “What form of discipline did your parents use when you were a child?” “What is the most dishonest ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:26:04">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Aza6YxtVEBYC&amp;pg=PA146&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Active Learning in the Mathematics Classroom, Grades 5-8 - Page 146</title><description>Math Topics Data collection, organization, analysis, circle graphs, ratio, percentage, measurement Active Learning Students will 1. Design a survey question, including choices for responses 2. Question 36 fellow students to collect data 3.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:27:21">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fbFdAQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PR13&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Active Learning \- Page xiii</title><description>It grew out of an informal literature survey I wrote on active learning (Settles, 2009) which in turn began as a chapter in my PhD thesis. During that phase of my career I am indebted to my committee, Mark Craven,Jude Shavlik, Xiaojin “Jerry” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:28:35">http://books.google.nl/books?id=lG7TaEWqPWkC&amp;pg=PA15&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Sociology Through Active Learning: Student Exercises - Page 15</title><description>A. Very. Short. Survey. Susan M. Collins, University of Northern Colorado, and Sue R. Crull, Iowa State University The goal for the “very short survey” is for you to join with other students to develop three survey questions during one class ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:30:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=3L-QAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA125&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Active Learning in Secondary and College Science ... - Page 125</title><description>Some are definitely not valid when an active learning environment is being evaluated. Hence, the result of most current course evaluation surveys is a reflection of “customer satisfaction” that does not provide an accurate reflection of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:30:55">http://books.google.nl/books?id=dZ-yjXxoZLsC&amp;pg=PA101&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Curious Machines: Active Learning with Structured Instances - Page 101</title><description>Chapter 7 Active Learning Literature Survey This chapter provides a general review of the literature on active learning. There have been a host of algorithms and applications for learning with queries over the years. This review is by no means ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:33:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=rqZhFbFLNC4C&amp;pg=PA52&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Effect of Active Learning Exercises on Academic ... - Page 52</title><description>The purpose of this study is to assess the effect a teaching method based on Class Participation Exercises may have on student learning factors. Your participation in this study will require that you complete a survey at the beginning of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:34:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=b66wn2rtwrkC&amp;pg=PA539&amp;dq=active+learning+survey&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=pilVU9WPE6noywPGmIK4DA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Java 6 Illuminated: An Active Learning Approach: An Active ...</title><description>An Active Learning Approach Julie Anderson, Herve J. Franceschi. read first survey while ( not end of surveys) { if answer is 0 increment counter0 else if answer is 1 increment counter1 else if answer is 2 increment counter2 else if answer is 3 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>