<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7122">horse dog pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:19" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:20">http://books.google.nl/books?id=b2Psa7aEawgC&amp;pg=PA16&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kid's Box American English Level 1 Teacher's Edition</title><description>Key language: I walk my dog, I take my cat to the vet, I brush my horse, I feed my fish ○ Additional language: Ican see ... ○ Review: pets ... required. ○ Pet flashcards (47–52) ○ Pictures of: hairbrush, dog food, vet, dog collar, leash ○ Crayons ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:37:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WNOsNscjIP0C&amp;pg=PA90&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Mental Processes in the Human Brain - Page 90</title><description>Table 6.2 illustrates picture naming by an SD patient in response to 25 different animals from the Snodgrass and ... stimulus picture naming response dog dog cat cat horse horse cow cow pig dog squirrel dog sheep dog deer dog goat dog fox ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:40:25">http://books.google.nl/books?id=VNMdAwAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA46&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Medicine Horse Woman: Lessons on Spirituality and Healing ...</title><description>The owner of an astute Corgi asked me what the dog thought of her new husband. I did not understand the image, but I described to the woman that the dog was sending me pleasant-feeling images of military insignia. The woman gasped and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:42:39">http://books.google.nl/books?id=VKS1-aBvXawC&amp;pg=PT238&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Encyclopedia of TV Pets: A Complete History of ...</title><description>... Award: Flash (a falling and lying down horse), owned and trained by Henry Willis Awards of Excellence: Shep (a dog) in A ... Pictures lst: Spike (a dog) in Old Yeller 2nd: Beauty (a horse) in Wild Is the Wind 3rd: Kelly (a dog) in Kelly and Me ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-05"><link>http://books.google.com/books?id=iaHpz5xY5IIC&amp;pg=PA185&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;ved=0CEMQ6AEwBA</link><title>The Horse who Drank the Sky: Film Experience Beyond ... - Page 185</title><description>Therefore, it makes sense to speak of the shark in this film; it makes no sense to speak of the dog. ... This (dominant) reading is also fostered by the design and limitation of visual publicity materials, including posters, trailers, published images, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:48:38">http://books.google.nl/books?id=O0Eu2DdBbHkC&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Eadweard Muybridge: The Kingston Museum Bequest - Page 48</title><description>EM6671 6677 Horse (Mahomet I and rider, run. EM6678 6679 ... EM6685 Horse and rider, run EM6686 Horse and rider, standing, small format. EM6687 ... Chrono-sequences, Pennsylvania EM6801 6323 Greyhound, run, gallop EM6824 6827 Two dogs, gallop. EM6828 ... EM7167 - 7484 Historical and contemporary artworks: engravings, paintings, drawings, etc, Marey pictures and horse skeleton, 'col.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:49:58">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4IUz3m75Cj8C&amp;pg=PT69&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Pocket Posh Christmas Logic 2: 100 Puzzles</title><description>How have the pictures been reassembied? 1. The cat's body now baiances precariousiy on the ducks' |egs. 2. The dog's head is now attached to the body of the horse. 3. The dog's |egs are in the same picture as the tiger's head. 4. The |egs of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:52:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=UB6pMpjqMMAC&amp;pg=PA79&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Dog Tales: Inspirational Stories of Humor, Adventure, and ... - Page 79</title><description>She decided to get another horse and fell in love with a beautiful white mare named Celeste. Celeste ... Francine's smile grew, and her parents took pictures as she sat up, propped by pillows, and slowly brushed Blackie with a soft bristle brush ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:52:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=qBcAxe_rmxMC&amp;q=horse+dog+pics&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The American movies reference book: the sound era - Page 612</title><description>Further, they demonstrate the importance of animals in motion pictures and television and have helped to create the impetus for ... Awards of Excellence: silver, horse, The Lone Ranger (WB). lady, dog, Goodbye, My Lady (Batjac Productions), ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7122-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7122_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:55:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=n36uEIsHpbQC&amp;pg=PT47&amp;dq=horse+dog+pics&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M3NVU92PL-LOygO71IKICA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Dog in Action</title><description>In fact, every dog must move and movement brings us right up to the study of gaits. “They are nice pictures,” he said, “but a horse does not run like this one.” Paradoxically, the walls of the bar were covered with racing photographs of which ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>