<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:16:36" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:16:37">http://books.google.nl/books?id=U2_ZGR6S3PYC&amp;pg=PA129&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Disaster Damage Estimation Models: Data Needs Vs. Ground ...</title><description>According to the 2000 US Census, Long Beach is the most ethnically diverse city in the United States, comprising 45.16% ... It is ranked 34th in population in the United States and 5th in the State of California. The City surrounds another jurisdiction called Signal Hills which is 2 square miles in area approximately (Map 5.1).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:17:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=84M96URkILgC&amp;pg=PA309&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>California Coastal Resource Guide - Page 309</title><description>City of Long Beach Monterey Style adobe of Rancho Los Cerritos. now a museum and a National Historic Landmark, ... The grassy, landscaped park surrounds an artificial lagoon and offers fishing platforms on Queensway Bay, bicycle and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:20:11">http://books.google.nl/books?id=5wGpZagXWlsC&amp;pg=PA311&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Encyclopedia of California \- Page 311</title><description>Long Beach surrounds the cities of Lakewood and Signal Hill. It spreads over a level plain to the edge of sandy bluffs overlooking the 8-1/2-mile-long, crescent-shaped beach of San Pedro Bay. From the shore it stretches north, laid out as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:23:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Q_YWq1qr28AC&amp;pg=PA17&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Game, Set, Match: Billie Jean King and the Revolution in ... - Page 17</title><description>In 1948 their second child, Randalljames (Randy), was born.5 Like much of California, Long Beach experienced dramatic ... Media writer john Leonard (who also grew up there) once described the city's suburban sprawl architecture as a place “where ... With only slight hyperbole, a sociologist once referred to “the orange curtain” that “metaphorically surrounds Orange County, California and keeps it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:25:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Q6i85oNIimEC&amp;pg=PA185&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Public Budgeting Systems - Page 185</title><description>Figure 6-3 FIRE DEPARTMENT Fire Prevention and Operations, City of Long Beach, California, 2000-2002 Mission Statement: We ... Customers Served: The residents and visitors to Long Beach, Signal Hill, and surrounding jurisdictions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:02">http://books.google.nl/books?id=FBMiQZVkmvsC&amp;pg=PA172&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Haunted Long Beach 2: The Odd and Unusual in and Around ...</title><description>The Odd and Unusual in and Around Long Beach, California Claudine Burnett. decide that someone had ... Mystery still surrounds Lenora's final resting place. One mystery is how ... When the city took over the cemetery in 1903 from the Long Beach Cemetery Association, they found the record books were a mess. The early ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:29:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=RHgWAZhOblgC&amp;pg=PA88&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Joseph W. Young, Jr., and the City Beautiful: A Biography ... - Page 88</title><description>The message beneath the two models with the Japa— nese parasol reads, “Hollywood Beach— Two Miles Long” (courtesy Harriett Ransom Collection, gift of Patricia Smith, Hollywood Historical Society). a Thousand Lights” that Young had experienced at Long Beach, California with shops ... This was to create the two ornamental lakes from a marsh and canal, and surround them with land, which would ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:30:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=DnN2GYhpkAMC&amp;pg=PA252&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>HNAI Heritage Auctions US Coin Auction Catalog #1129, Long ...</title><description>A pocket of luster surrounds each obverse star, while the reverse exhibits partial cartwheel luster. A vertical ... A Choice XF example of this earlier Carson City double eagle issue, more available than its predecessors but still plenty elusive in all grades. Glimmers of ... Ex: Palm Beach Signature (Heritage, 3/2005), lot 7193.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:33:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=PgKio2MSUGwC&amp;pg=PA472&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Modern Schools: A Century of Design for Education - Page 472</title><description>Long Beach, California 1997-1999 The International Elementary School in Long Beach is organized around a ... Introverted and isolated from the surrounding urban context for safety and security, the compact courtyard plan ... The main shared-use spaces of the program are adjacent to the courtyard at the center of the school, beneath a rooftop playground that overlooks the neighborhood and city below.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:35:31">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Co_VIPIJerIC&amp;pg=PA667&amp;dq=which+cities+surround+long+beach+ca&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=tIpVU5SzNIWl0QXE64CIBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Merriam-Webster's Geographical Dictionary - Page 667</title><description>E of Long Beach; ... City area has absorbed many towns and villages and now surrounds several incorp. cities incl. ... An important educational center: Univ. of Southern California (1880), Univ. of California at Los Angeles (1919), Occidental ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>