<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:49:11" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:49:12">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8z9aAAAAYAAJ&amp;q=Soccer+trick&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Freestyle Soccer Tricks: Tricks, Flick-Ups, Catches</title><description>The professional soccer freestyler offers tips, exercises, and drills designed to improve coordination and ball control and provides instructions for performing various types of juggling tricks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:50:48">http://books.google.nl/books?id=3T9aAAAAYAAJ&amp;q=Soccer+trick&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Freestyle Soccer Street Moves: Tricks, Stepovers, Passes</title><description>Presents a step-by-step guide to soccer tricks, including nutmegs, trick passes, and beat moves.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-03"><link>http://books.google.com/books?id=OF5MT1jlI6AC&amp;pg=PA13&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;ved=0CDUQ6AEwAg</link><title>Soccer Number 10 Blue Print - Page 13</title><description>Now for the very first time every in the history of mankind, Drunkensoccer will reveal the lost art of soccer deception! First is was ... Next, came one of my most controverial work The Doctrine Of Time “How To Trick Any One In Soccer With Ease!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:55:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=vcw0AQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PT32&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Soccer 'Cats #4: Hat Trick</title><description>SOCCER. 'CATS. #4 Hat Trick Matt Christopher Illustrated by DanielVasconcellos When Stookie Norris's older brother, Greg, gets his picture in the paper for scoring three goals in one game, Stookie is dazzled. Greg insists strikers should try to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:57:37">http://books.google.nl/books?id=F-3K2YgHz78C&amp;pg=PA57&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Dog Tricks and Training Workbook: A Step-by-Step ... - Page 57</title><description>Trick 14 TEACH: Use shaping to teach your dog to play Soccer. When we use shaping to teach our dog to roll a soccer ball into a net, we start by rewarding our dog for any interest he shows in the ball. Next, we wait for him to sniff or touch the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:00:22">http://books.google.nl/books?id=wGJJ5FJxC0UC&amp;pg=PA104&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Parrot Tricks: Teaching Parrots with Positive Reinforcement - Page 104</title><description>You might want to require him to send two balls down the alley, as in a regular game, before finishing the trick. Add each part ... Equipment: For this trick you will need a small soccer ball, found in many sizes in novelty stores. You will also need ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:02:01">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WSoQkc0YMGIC&amp;pg=PA112&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Thoughtful Soccer: The Think-First Approach to Playing and ...</title><description>The Think-First Approach to Playing and Coaching Russ Carrington. A special trick could also be used. If every single bouncer held a cross up just as a vampire was entering the club, that vampire would instantly vanish — provided that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:03:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WncFA9tjzRUC&amp;pg=PT77&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Soccer's Most WantedTM II: The Top 10 Book of More ...</title><description>TRICK. One interesting development during the WUSA's first season was the way several of the league's marquee players struggled to dominate the way they had at international level. Hamm, hobbled by a troublesome knee, didn't even crack ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:04:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=H2T0ZD5S86QC&amp;pg=PA365&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Global Art of Soccer \- Page 365</title><description>Modern professional soccer leagues in the USA such as the NASL (North American Soccer League operated from ... USA striker Bert Patenaude was the first player to score three goals (a “hat trick”) in a World Cup game, as the USA advanced ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:06:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=CpD9lkO7900C&amp;pg=PA35&amp;dq=Soccer+trick&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=d65VU5r0DOaa1AXJ-YDwBQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Youth Soccer Offensive Drills, Plays, Strategies and Games ... - Page 35</title><description>You will also need a soccer ball and a whistle to start and stop play. Working the tactic: The first thing you ... Then get 6 assistant coaches, parents or players, to help you demonstrate this trick throw in strategy. This is a trick play you can use ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>