<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:14:33" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:14:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=bx1bJXSSoQIC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Do You Think You're Clever?: The Oxford and Cambridge ...</title><description>This is a book for everyone who likes to think they're clever, or who thinks they'd like to be clever. And cleverness is not just knowing stuff, it's how laterally, deeply and interestingly you can bend your brain.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:15:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=iaHbJNClqjQC&amp;pg=PA213&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cambridge Companion to Hobbes - Page 213</title><description>It is normative as much as descriptive because its explanations of what actors do do are parasitic on its accounts of what for them is the thing to do.16 I shall use an analogy I have used before and try to place no more weight on it than I must.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:17:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=qAE4AAAAIAAJ&amp;pg=PR17&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cambridge Planning Proposals - Volume 1 - Page xvii</title><description>This being so, it seemed to us that the results of the road traffic survey, on which our proposals are based, should also be ... 3 The first assumption was that our proposals should not call for a major change in the character of central Cambridge.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:20:23">http://books.google.nl/books?id=vYb9Pi7OtNgC&amp;pg=PA15&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cambridge English for Schools 3 Workbook - Page 15</title><description>One of the greatest mysteries of all time is the Marie Celeste^- The Hindenburg was an airship that flew from Germany to France^ The Bermuda Triangle is an area in the Atlantic Oceans 3.2 Up or down? [gg] Listen to these sentences. Do they ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:21:21">http://books.google.nl/books?id=7AYWt9bQe9UC&amp;pg=PA168&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cambridge Companion to the Roman Historians - Page 168</title><description>Why is historiography not like poetry when it comes to the gods? If historians thought that the gods had influenced the past, why do they not seem to say so very often? And when they do, why do they seem so ambivalent? Where religious ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:22:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=aZOgg-x4UyIC&amp;pg=PA317&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cambridge Companion to the Philosophy of Biology - Page 317</title><description>But most importantly, they do not harm those players upon whom they depend for high payoffs. So in contrast to the selfish AS players, the nicer TFT and AA strategies have the potential to do well over the long run, by helping their partners to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:24:15">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KJQyhzY4PucC&amp;pg=PA100&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cambridge Companion to Christian Philosophical Theology</title><description>to allow a number of assumptions. First, there is a God such as we have described. The Iews and Muslims of Anselm's day would likely have been willing to grant that assumption. Secondly, the God of classical theism must do the best with the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:26:55">http://books.google.nl/books?id=c-48-3y9RVAC&amp;pg=PA93&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cambridge Introduction to Creative Writing - Page 93</title><description>As original writers, we are as hampered by what we know, or think we know, and what we do not know. We must do a lot of learning, but most of all we have to do a lot of unlearning, for our preconceptions of writing are usually based on ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:29:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=3Mt6I-jiLecC&amp;pg=PA473&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cambridge Learner's Dictionary with CD-ROM - Page 473</title><description>need some new shoes, o The country still desperately needs help, o [+ to do sth] If there's anything else you need to know, just give me a call, o We need you to look after the children for us. 2 don't need to do sth/ needn't do sth used in order to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:31:20">http://books.google.nl/books?id=z7kHX6fRnSkC&amp;pg=PA214&amp;dq=Cambridge+must+do&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ecJVU6GkG6yn0wWep4CYCQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Reports of the Cambridge Anthropological Expedition to ... - Page 214</title><description>You offer it to him without his having to ask you for some, he will then call you a good boy; but if you do not do it he will call you a bad boy." "Suppose a man send you for anything, you must do it quick — you no too much run about." " When all ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>