<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:13:59" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:14:00">http://books.google.nl/books?id=6RGLLP9KOJUC&amp;pg=PT550&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Human Development: A Life-Span View</title><description>Exercising while wearing headphones or earbuds and listening to loud music when you are young can result in serious hearing loss in later life. presbycusis reduced sensitivity to high-pitched tones PART FOUR: LATE ADULTHOOD founded ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:14:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Q2b2YDTr0vsC&amp;pg=PA330&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Disorders of Development and Learning - Volume 1 - Page 330</title><description>Prenatal Deafness can be inherited as an autosomally dominant or recessive, or X-linked, condition and can be an isolated trait or constitute ... headphones), can damage cochlear hair cells and result in a predominantly high-frequency loss.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:16:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=lesWAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA21&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Audio in Media - Page 21</title><description>Safeguards against Hearing Loss As gradual deterioration of the auditory ... Continued exposure to high sound-pressure levels can damage the sensory hair cells, and, because they are not naturally repaired or replaced, hearing loss results. ... headphones or earbuds present an increasing threat to young people, who are showing signs of hearing loss more typical of older adults. ... Hearing damage caused by exposure to loud sound varies with the exposure time and the individual.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:19:36">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KwhD5g0wbpAC&amp;pg=PA314&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Experience of Science - Page 314</title><description>The general hypothesis in both studies is that excessive use of the headphone sets can cause hearing losses, but the ... The implied hypothesis here is that the 72% of students with defective hearing owed their hearing problems to the use of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:20:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=a7CqcE1ZrFkC&amp;pg=RA1-PA1947&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Textbook of Pediatric Emergency Medicine - Page 1947</title><description>Once injured, these nerve cells may not regenerate and profound sensorineural hearing loss can develop. ... Rock concerts, stereo headphones, machinery, and explosive devices are capable of producing sound at the intensity required to produce this ... Formal audiologic testing will be normal in these patients and mental health referral is indicated to elucidate the cause of this apparent hearing loss.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:21:47">http://books.google.nl/books?id=5onBvPScUa4C&amp;pg=PA63&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>On the Job with Hearing Loss: Hidden Challenges Successful ...</title><description>When using BTE aids, snap on wireless receivers can replace one of the components of the traditional FM system. ... They may cause feedback and sound leakage at higher volume levels because the headphones do not fit tight over the ear.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:22:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=OQKS2mA5QgYC&amp;pg=PA142&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Psychology: A Journey - Volume 1 - Page 142</title><description>Many jobs, hobbies, and pastimes can cause noise-induced hearing loss, a form of sensorineural hearing loss that occurs ... that amplified musical concerts, iPod-style headphones, and “boom-box” car stereos can also damage your hearing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:24:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=t0Mh0yOH5EsC&amp;pg=PA317&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Textbook of Family Medicine - Page 317</title><description>Hearing loss can result from chronic or acute noise exposure, usually causing injury at the level of the cochlear hair cells. ... at sporting venues, motor racing events, action movies, or concerts and listening to loud music on headphones.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:25:39">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fUDt6dXQY4YC&amp;pg=PA214&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Hearing: Its Physiology and Pathophysiology - Page 214</title><description>If a successful shielding between the two windows were accomplished, the expected hearing loss would be equal to that of the loss of ... Bone conducted sound generated by the earphones that are used therefore sets the limit for the maximal conductive hearing loss that can be ... the cochlea causes deprivation of input to the auditory nervous system and that can cause expression of neural plasticity that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:29:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=BAdgaJ5r85wC&amp;pg=PA465&amp;dq=can+headphones+cause+hearing+loss&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Z9BVU_ejF-Sg0QWK-YHIAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Lawyer Barons: What Their Contingency Fees Really Cost America</title><description>After the suits were filed, some of the defendants added various warning messages, such as “Do not use headphones/headsets at high volumes for an extended period of time. Doing so can cause hearing loss.”57 Not content to seek whatever ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>