<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7145">why do cats purr</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:29:40" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:29:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SkM8dyTM4nYC&amp;q=why+do+cats+purr&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Cat: Why Do Cats Purr? and Other True Facts</title><description>But our behavior is sometimes baffling, and we're not always purr-fect. Yet you still love us! So it's time for us to set the record straight. We're ready to answer your questions and give you the cat's meow on why we do the things we do.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:32:01">http://books.google.nl/books?id=74xMAAAACAAJ&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Why Do Cats Purr?</title><description>Info Trail for ages 5-11: Enthuses all readers with attention-grabbing titles, engaging humour and inventive topics to inspire excellence and enjoyment in learning.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:33:33">http://books.google.nl/books?id=UbhoOXySYewC&amp;pg=PA26&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Why Do Cats Bury Their Poop?: More Than 200 Feline Facts, ...</title><description>IF YOU'VE HAD NOTHING to do all day and are bored enough, you might notice that your cat buries his poop after he visits ... do. cats. purr. when. you. pet. them? YOU'VE NO DOUBT HEARD that rumbling sound your cat makes — a vibrating ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:34:00">http://books.google.nl/books?id=N3uzuAAACAAJ&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Why Do Cats Purr?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:36:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=NFQ07VEQKV0C&amp;pg=PT64&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Do Cats Always Land on Their Feet?</title><description>Expert cat observers know that purring isn't just a sound of contentment. Cats also purr when they're injured, while giving birth - even when they're dying. Purring has been described as something a cat does when he's with a friend or needs a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:38:13">http://books.google.nl/books?id=7PVu-DpLmqoC&amp;pg=PA135&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Why Do Cats. 477. Love Eating Fish But Hate Getting We - Page 135</title><description>Gus the Cat at the Theatre Door in T S Eliot's Old Possums Book of Practical Cats had aspirations way beyond those of a ... DO. CATS. PURR? Those sonorous vibrations that seem to emanate from the very core of a cat must be one of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:39:31">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4avCAQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA238&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Domestic Cat: The Biology of its Behaviour - Page 238</title><description>Probably for similar reasons, the purr is used by adults in social and sexual contexts. For instance, an adult female will purr while suckling her kittens and when she courts a male. Again like the human smile, purring can be used in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:41:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=RrSvvcWLpmgC&amp;pg=PT2608&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Feline Patient</title><description>Three major types of vocalization have been identified in cats: sounds made with the mouth closed (purr and trill), sounds ... While most, if not all, cats can purr, some of the exotic species do not purr in the same manner as thedomestic cat.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:44:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ODtomlW6M7gC&amp;pg=PT104&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>So! You Want to Get a Cat: An Animal Lover¿s Guide to ...</title><description>Why do cats purr? That has been as hard a question to answer as, “which came first the chicken or the egg?” My aim is not to solve the mystery; no one really knows why. But following are some of the suspected reasons why a cat purrs.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7145-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7145_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:47:11">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fxf8FRNJvKgC&amp;pg=PA121&amp;dq=why+do+cats+purr&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=FNRVU6yeJ8va0QX7qYHIBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Your Ideal Cat: Insights Into Breed and Gender Differences ... - Page 121</title><description>Why cats do that: Purring, yawning, eating grass, and flipping out on catnip This chapter applies to all breeds and both genders. It is about the intriguing things that cats do that endear them to us, make us wonder about cat behavior, and even ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>