<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:06:38" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:06:39">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ewEJU8Sg-n8C&amp;pg=PA51&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury: Progress, Promise, and Priorities - Page 51</title><description>Progress, Promise, and Priorities Committee on Spinal Cord Injury, Board on Neuroscience and Behavioral Health, Institute ... still able to generate rhythmic movements elicited from their hind limbs weeks after their spinal cords were severed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:07:38">http://books.google.nl/books?id=TtHuTX94uZYC&amp;pg=PA215&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Form and Function in the Brain and Spinal Cord: ... - Page 215</title><description>When I went to medical school, we were taught that spinal cord injury is a disorder in which descending and ascending axons within the spinal cord are severed as a result of trauma. And we were also taught that multiple sclerosis is a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:09:16">http://books.google.nl/books?id=nVad-Q2p7FIC&amp;pg=PA1143&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Methods of Tissue Engineering - Page 1143</title><description>The consequences of spinal cord injury are many-fold, including disruptions in sensory, motor, and autonomic realms. Traumatic injuries to the spinal cord can sever or damage long descending and ascending axons, segmental connections ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:11:52">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SdM6FsykfWAC&amp;pg=PA93&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Medical and Psychosocial Aspects of Chronic Illness and ... - Page 93</title><description>OVERVIEW OF TRAUMATIC SPINAL CORD INJURY The spinal cord transmits electrical messages to and from the brain that facilitate motor, ... which part of the spinal cord is injured and whether the cord is bruised, compressed, or severed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:13:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Yo4M_dp4hdQC&amp;pg=PA369&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Human Exceptionality: School, Community, and Family - Page 369</title><description>In fact, in most people with SCIs, the spinal cord is intact, but the damage to it results in loss of functioning" (Spinal Cord Injury Resource Center, 2012). When the spinal cord is traumatized or severed, spinal cord injury (SCI) occurs. Trauma ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:15:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=s10DBsbtZh0C&amp;pg=PA29&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Myelin Changes After Spinal Cord Injury and Throughout Aging</title><description>Jurate Lasiene. an area we were unable to examine because of the interference of intense lesion-related auto fluorescence. Because intact axons were remyelinated, we sought to label RST axons, which may be severed or lack functional ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:17:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=_aNGAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA148&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Re-Engineering of the Damaged Brain and Spinal Cord: ...</title><description>Rationale for using macrophages and dendritic cells for treatment of spinal cord injury In most non-CNS tissues, ... conducted using the rat spinal cord transection model, injection of PNS co-incubated macrophages to the severed spinal cord ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:20:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=0YhCAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA90&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Transplantation of Neural Tissue into the Spinal Cord \- Page 90</title><description>The use of embryonic neural tissue transplanted into the lesion site in the host spinal cord introduced a new element to ... of the severed spinal cord (for review see Bregman et al, 2002).5 According to this hypothesis, the graft could provide a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:22:57">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8TL9IIs0OZMC&amp;pg=PA541&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury: Handbook of Clinical Neurology Series - Page 541</title><description>Spinal Cord Injury J. Verhaagen and J.W. McDonald III, Editors # 2012 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved INTRODUCTION So far, there is no clinical procedure for inducing severed nerve fibers to regenerate. The recovery of function, which to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:24:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=lc_gaHwKD3IC&amp;pg=PA78&amp;dq=severed+spinal+cord&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Lj9WU8K1MYiVyAOc_4CgAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Neural grafting : repairing the brain and spinal cord. - Page 78</title><description>since different types of injuries can result in a wide range of insults to the spinal cord (the damage done in an automobile ... the severed axons and their target sites on the other side of the wound by providing a system of intervening neurons.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>