<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:04:12" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:04:13">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Corneal_reflex</link><title>Corneal reflex \- Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><description>The corneal reflex, also known as the blink reflex, is an involuntary blinking of the eyelids elicited by stimulation of the cornea (such as by touching or by a foreign body), or bright light, though could result from any peripheral stimulus.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:05:06">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KtwFzdPQebUC&amp;pg=PA404&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Clinical Electromyography: Nerve Conduction Studies - Page 404</title><description>found that the blink reflex was abnormal, whereas brainstem auditory evoked potentials were normal, and the converse was also true, so the techniques occasionally complement each other. However, the blink reflex is no longer used for this ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:07:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=3VMGAQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA204&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Electrodiagnosis in Diseases of Nerve and Muscle: ... - Page 204</title><description>Khoshbin, S, and Hallett, M: Multimodality evoked potentials and blink reflex in multiple sclerosis. Neurology 31:138–144, 1981. Kiers, L, and Carroll, WM: Blink reflexes and magnetic resonance imaging in focal unilateral central trigeminal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:08:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1ozZS5NtNwkC&amp;pg=PA439&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Pediatric Home Care - Page 439</title><description>INFANTS Reflexes Infant reflexes that are discussed here include oral reflexes, eye reflexes, general reflexes, and ... Eye Reflexes Reflexes that involve the eyes and are present in full-term infants include the blink reflex, pupillary reflex, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-05"><link>http://books.google.com/books?id=I6Q4_5WTshUC&amp;pg=PA142&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;ved=0CEUQ6AEwBA</link><title>Essentials of Clinical Neurophysiology - Volume 1 - Page 142</title><description>The stimulus intensity is gradually increased and the H-reflex appears at a lower intensity of stimulation than the CMAP. As the ... The blink reflex can be used to evaluate patients with lesions of the facial nerve or of the brainstem. However ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:11:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=6zJoAYx0j5QC&amp;pg=PA767&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Neuromuscular Function and Disease: Basic, Clinical, and ...</title><description>Blink reflex I I, Cornea! reflex 0.2 mV 10ms Jaw - jerk 20 ms 0.5 mV 2 ms Figure 43-9. Example of a jaw jerk with an abnormal response on the right (r) and a normal response on the left (1) side, found unexpectedly in a patient with multiple ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:11:55">http://books.google.nl/books?id=uaut4LIqtFMC&amp;pg=PA277&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Clinical Neuroanatomy: Brain Circuitry and Its Disorders - Page 277</title><description>The jaw jerk, the most widely used brain stem reflex in clinical neurophysiology, had no apparent topodiagnostic value. Touching the (edge of the) cornea with a wisp of cotton elicits bilateral blinking, the corneal reflex. The blink reflex is an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:12:21">http://books.google.nl/books?id=mY-6eweiQm8C&amp;pg=PA6&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A Dictionary of Neurological Signs - Page 6</title><description>A Acousticopalpebral Reflex Achromatopsia is most conveniently tested for clinically using pseu- doisochromatic figures ... Pseudoachromatopsia; Quadrantanopia; Scotoma; Xanthopsia Acousticopalpebral Reflex - see BLINK REFLEX Action ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:14:57">http://books.google.nl/books?id=j7aawGLbtEoC&amp;pg=PA134&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Handbook of Research Methods in Social and Personality ... - Page 134</title><description>(i.e., facilitation or inhibition) in affectively toned reflexes could be used to index the basic ongoing affective state of an individual. Lang and his colleagues focused on the startle eye- blink reflex, the reflexive blinks that occur when individuals ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7180_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:16:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=j-TgnRFVVm8C&amp;pg=PA203&amp;dq=blink+reflex&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=vFpWU5zWM4L8ygOv64CwDg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Migraine Disorders Research Trends - Page 203</title><description>[22] Kimura, J. The blink reflex as a test for brainstem and higher nervous system functions. In: Desmedt JE, editor. New developments in electromyography and clinical neurophysiology. Basel: Karger; 1973, pp. 682-691. [23] Kimura, J. Effect ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>