<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:11:29" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:11:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=txh0LpjjhkoC&amp;pg=PA334&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Contraceptive Technology - Page 334</title><description>Robert Anthony Hatcher, James Trussell, Anita L. Nelson, M.D.. 7. If you are using a diaphragm or sponge, learn the danger signs for toxic shock syndrome and watch for them. These signs include sudden high fever, chills, vomiting, diarrhea, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:13:31">http://books.google.nl/books?id=aW0zkZl0JgQC&amp;pg=PA434&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Mosby's Medical Dictionary - Page 434</title><description>contraceptive diaphragm fitting contrast examination or cream up to 2 hours before coitus. Fitted between the pubic symphysis and the posterior fornix of the vagina, the diaphragm cups the cervix in a pool of spermicide so that spermatozoa ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:15:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XuX-MGTZnJoC&amp;pg=PA60&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Encyclopedia of Birth Control \- Page 60</title><description>Barrier methods of contraception rely on placing some kind of obstacle in the vagina to prevent the passage of sperm into the uterus.Some, such as the diaphragm, covered the cervix, whereas the cervical cap was designed to fit only over the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:16:22">http://books.google.nl/books?id=W27Es79DCxgC&amp;pg=PA296&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Magnetic Resonance Procedures: Health Effects and Safety, ...</title><description>DIAPHRAGMS Contraceptive diaphragms have metallic rings that serve to maintain them in position during use (Figure 14.13). The contraceptive diaphragms were shown to be attracted by the 1.5-T static magnetic field used to test these ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:18:21">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Qt4QYzrGyvMC&amp;pg=PA194&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The New Harvard Guide to Women's Health - Page 194</title><description>Like condoms, the diaphragm and the cervical cap are barrier methods of contraception — that is, methods that physically prevent sperm from gaining access to the woman's reproductive system and fertilizing an egg. Among the safest and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:19:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=5w_xQWv30bMC&amp;pg=PA118&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Primary Care Procedures in Women's Health - Page 118</title><description>You have been fitted for a contraceptive diaphragm today. In order to obtain your diaphragm, please bring your prescription to the pharmacy to be filled. In order to be effective, your diaphragm must be used properly with spermicide during ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:21:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=wgosxK2WRA0C&amp;pg=PA538&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Essential Guide to Primary Care Procedures - Page 538</title><description>2 O u ID C &gt;^ u Suppliers Diaphragms (e.g., Ortho-flex) are dispensed by prescription from pharmacies. ... Patient Education Handout A patient education handout, "The Contraceptive Diaphragm," can be found on the book's companion Web ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:22:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=sczb0Tk_2IwC&amp;pg=PA165&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Handbook of Contraception: A Guide for Practical ... - Page 165</title><description>The diaphragm must be fitted by a health care provider. The female condom and sponge are readily available over the counter. Those who often use oil-based lubricants or medications are not good candidates for a latex diaphragm (Table 1).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:23:06">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ujMefhIY4cMC&amp;pg=PA67&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Contraceptive Use and Controlled Fertility: Health Issues ... - Page 67</title><description>A clinical trial among highrisk women using contraceptive sponges impregnated with nonoxynol-9 demonstrated ... Diaphragm with Spermicide Diaphragms used with spermicidal cream or jelly are a safe method of contraception and, when ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:24:36">http://books.google.nl/books?id=_lmEDeRGHHMC&amp;pg=PA321&amp;dq=contraceptive+diaphragm&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=sZRWU5e2DOe9ygO6vIH4Aw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Atlas of Primary Care Procedures - Page 321</title><description>Contraceptive diaphragms provide effective, reversible, episodic contraception without hormonal influence. The device consists of a shallow, cup-shaped, latex or silicone sheet anchored to a circular outer spring that is contained in the rim.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>