<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:39:58" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:39:59">http://books.google.nl/books?id=TTf0Aki6AUQC&amp;pg=PA90&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kenya - Page 90</title><description>For the lowdown on various Kenyan recipes, including the ubiquitous ugali and sukuma wiki, check out www.blissites ... Swahili dishes reflect the history of contact with the Arabs and other Indian Ocean traders and incorporate the produce of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:42:14">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XR9YIaG0kIcC&amp;pg=PA140&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Disappearing Foods: Studies in Foods and Dishes at Risk : ...</title><description>'For an analysis of some Swahili foodways, see Robert A. Leonard and Wendy]. Saliba, 'Food, drink, and Swahili public space'. Proceedings of Oxford Symposium 1991. London, Prospect Books, 1992. 2In Swahili the sausage tree has several ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:44:04">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fsASi-gQsq4C&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Swahili Phrasebook</title><description>Whether you're sailing on a dhow off Zanzibar, scaling the heights of Kilimanjaro or having a quiet drink with your host in Nairobi, this book will help you communicate the way you want to - understand the correct Swahili greetings; - ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:45:43">http://books.google.nl/books?id=PVPFAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA39&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Ethnic Identity and Development: Khat and Social Change in ...</title><description>Those arriving in Mombasa instantly adopted Swahili culture and language and, upon arrival in Uganda, already spoke Swahili, cooked and ate Swahili food, and dressed like Swahili people. Consequently, it is difficult for wives and children ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:46:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=O6XFx6VNHWkC&amp;pg=PA74&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Africa on Six Wheels: A Semester on Safari - Page 74</title><description>The menu offers Swahili dishes such as coconut rice, fish, and seafood, but its best items are flavored milkshakes. Except for the shakes, dishes take hours to prepare. Carla figures that with small refrigeration space and frequent outages, few if ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:48:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=FrWgDRkS90EC&amp;pg=PA184&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Oxford Symposium on Food and Cookery 1991: Public Eating : ...</title><description>Swahili samosa are filled with spiced finely ground meat mixed with onions, perhaps peas, and often chilies. Samosa are ... The foods are transported by the children, who also sell some to other children and to adult passers-by. Ramadan ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:50:05">http://books.google.nl/books?id=gtIuj0DenGwC&amp;pg=PA355&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Frommer's Kenya and Tanzania - Page 355</title><description>If you want a superb introduction to Swahili cooking, don't miss the Swahili buffet hosted around the pool at the Serena Inn. Much of the food is cooked on barbecues in front of you, so the seafood is fresh and succulent, and the various coconut ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-08"><link>http://books.google.com/books?id=Eayxi5XzrkIC&amp;pg=PA75&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;ved=0CFkQ6AEwBw</link><title>Swahili for Starters: A Practical Introductory Course - Page 75</title><description>These may all be mixed together and brought in on a large dish, or they may be brought in separate dishes. It is not easy at first to eat rice or maize porridge with the fingers, but the trick is to form it into a sort of ball. Little dishes of fish or meat ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:53:10">http://books.google.nl/books?id=NTo6c_PJWRgC&amp;pg=PA194&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Food Cultures of the World Encyclopedia - Volume 1 - Page 194</title><description>In Swahili culture, it is only fit for small children to eat while walking on the street. There is even a saying warning against such behavior, Kula kitu kitamu kinjianjia mtu atasibiwa na shetani (One who eats delicious food while walking will be ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7258-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7258_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:54:53">http://books.google.nl/books?id=9F6hSyee9LQC&amp;pg=PR8&amp;dq=swahili+dishes&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=HkRXU9zRI6nnygOY4oKwDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Coconut Comes in Due Season - Page viii</title><description>Friends began to visit him on the island, enjoying his seafood dishes. Drawing on the success of the tourist crowd, David started a restaurant specialising in seafood and Swahili dishes. And later, he constructed rustic style residential cottages ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>