<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:26:48" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:26:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=PkmXj4DmkvcC&amp;pg=PA171&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>20 Questions to Ask If Your Child Has ADHD: Easyread Large ...</title><description>How. Do. I. Work. With. My. Child's. Teachers? In the teacher training workshops I do on ADHD, I always begin with this fill-in-the-blank exercise: ADHD is like _____. When I designed this exercise, I knew it would be a springboard to all the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:27:47">http://books.google.nl/books?id=YP1TQyYVGdkC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>ADHD: A Survival Guide for Parents and Teachers</title><description>Addresses the issues and concerns confronting parents and teachers with ADHD children. The friendly and supportive style of the book is easy for readers to understand and use.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:28:26">http://books.google.nl/books?id=zdr7fzY8dUsC&amp;pg=PT24&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>100 Questions &amp; Answers About Your Child’s ADHD: Preschool ...</title><description>If I have ADHD, will my child also have it? No, not necessarily, but the chance is definitely greater than if you did not have ADHD. For example, one-third of fathers with a history of ADHD in childhood have a child with ADHD. For mothers, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:29:11">http://books.google.nl/books?id=LeTdAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA7&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>They Say My Child Has 'adhd': Debunking the ... - Page 7</title><description>Being that ADHD is a subjective diagnosis and that stimulant treatment has been shown to have risk as detailed above, what is the effective alternative to aiding those who have been diagnosed ADHD and what actually is underlying the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:29:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=r_SUGZI5AM4C&amp;pg=PT349&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Making the System Work for Your Child with ADHD</title><description>life as normal as possible, and he knows that he has ADHD, but we don't make it a big deal. ... We emphasize the fact that everybody is different and it takes all kind of people to make a world. ... Even though I am not someone who likes to talk a lot, I force myself to listen attentively to my son and give him feedback, so that he ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:30:39">http://books.google.nl/books?id=YZ-YfOH0W8YC&amp;pg=PA194&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Homework Success for Children with ADHD: A Family-school ...</title><description>Positive reinforcement is a very powerful tool for changing behavior and is generally preferable to punishment. Parents often express their opinion that "my child misbehaves in order to get attention." Statements such as this reveal a common ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:31:25">http://books.google.nl/books?id=pI0fl1M-0eYC&amp;pg=PA16&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>100 Questions &amp; Answers about Your Child's Attention ... - Page 16</title><description>However, ADHD can also be caused or exacerbated by other factors, such as preterm birth, iron deficiency anemia, lead exposure, and other environmental factors. These factors are discussed later. 12. If I have ADHD, 'will my children also ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:32:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Q9n8FHyrncsC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Survival Guide for Kids with ADD Or ADHD</title><description>Fall behind in school? Have trouble controlling your behavior? Maybe you have ADD or ADHD. These are labels grown-ups use to understand and help kids with these types of challenges. If you've been labeled ADD or ADHD, this book is for you.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:32:32">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KStJo6hRS48C&amp;pg=PA108&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Taking Charge of ADHD, Revised Edition: The Complete, ... - Page 108</title><description>“I have a lot of problems in managing my child, but my husband has far fewer problems. Why?” One of the things I have heard repeatedly from mothers of children with ADHD is that the children seem to behave better for the fathers. When Dr.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:33:09">http://books.google.nl/books?id=R76HZfWUM9kC&amp;pg=PA142&amp;dq=does+my+child+have+adhd&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eIRYU9rIF8rUPIW_gNAP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Fix My Child: Behavior Management Techniques - Page 142</title><description>It is important to know if the child has the same symptoms equally in all environments. Children with true ADHD have the same symptoms across more than one area in their life. If a child does not have ADHD symptoms in school and the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>