<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:30:08" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:30:09">http://books.google.nl/books?id=9qDe3GZG96cC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Industrial Biotechnology: Sustainable Growth and Economic ...</title><description>From the contents: * History of industrial biotechnology * Use of renewable versus fossil resources * Systems microbial biotechnology * Metabolic engineering and modeling * Fermentation technologies * Directed evolution and production of of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:30:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=BM5yYFj-xKgC&amp;pg=PA198&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>European Kinship In The Age Of Biotechnology \- Page 198</title><description>She gained her MA and PhD at McGill University in Medical Anthropology and Anthropology, respectively, and was a postdoctoral researcher at the University of Manchester in Social Anthropology. In addition to her work on public ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:31:28">http://books.google.nl/books?id=yAOsWDyhbLgC&amp;pg=PA136&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Career Paths and Mobility of Researchers in Europe: ... - Page 136</title><description>Many of these young scientists wish to continue with a postdoctoral research period at another university in their country or abroad. Some will, for various reasons, leave the Academia and look for a job outside the academic world. ... and after spending many years at a university it is difficult to assess the options and know whether to continue the academic path, join a biotech or pharmaceutical company, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:32:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=YfCKpfDLv7gC&amp;pg=PA56&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Biomedical Globalization: The International Migration of ... - Page 56</title><description>According to an informal survey of 203 NIH European postdocs (including, among others, German, British, Spanish, and French ... Some of the European Union policy initiatives included establishing more postdoctoral opportunities in Europe; encouraging European universities to work more ... It was also suggested that European postdocs return and establish their own start-up biotechnology companies.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:32:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=7ydyhhKSoo4C&amp;pg=PA231&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Use of Agriculturally Important Genes in Biotechnology \- Page 231</title><description>week in person with the students in lthaca and the Central European colleague would do the same with students in Central Europe. ... the development of distance learning programs and serve as the central resource of knowledge and expertise in distance learning techniques and technology for the university community. ... Postdoctoral fellows/visiting staff will be a major component to advance technical and conceptual skills and to prepare returning persons for leadership positions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:33:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4WxBR3ShkeIC&amp;pg=PA131&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Coopetition Strategy: Theory, Experiments and Cases - Page 131</title><description>These aspects point out that biotech companies frequently maintain their links to universities, working closely with faculty members and postdoctoral candidates on research projects, and sometimes using university laboratories. ... due to the complementarities and non-rival positions of the partners, as universities and firms show distinctive goals, cultural norms and ... Several European countries have adopted Bayh-Dole and inspired policies aimed at pushing universities to take more ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:34:25">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ZqFanmqGIVkC&amp;pg=PA363&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Biotechnology: Between Commerce and Civil Society - Page 363</title><description>... at the Free University in Berlin and obtained his PhD in Political and Social Sciences from the European University Institute, ... Technology &amp; Society Studies, and has held an Australian Research Council Postdoctoral Research Fellowship.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:34:50">http://books.google.nl/books?id=fetjwSi-rwMC&amp;pg=PA67&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>New Scientist - 14 Aug 1986 - Page 67</title><description>... (READVERTISEMENT) Strategically located in a marine environment of a quality unmatched in Europe, University College, Galway has built up over the ... Further information may be obtained from the Registrar, University College, Galway, Ireland. ... THE UNIVERSITY OF LEEDS DEPARTMENT OF GENETICS AND THE BIOTECHNOLOGY UNIT POSTDOCTORAL RESEARCH FELLOW Applications ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:37:45">http://books.google.nl/books?id=U4taLjPrFrsC&amp;pg=PA131&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Advanced Materials Revolution: Technology and Economic ...</title><description>For example, after graduate and postdoctoral work, European scientists can achieve university tenure by remaining in the academy and writing what ... between university and industry also concerns the 1999 report on biotechnology clusters.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7423-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7423_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:38:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=y5-VzA5CxvsC&amp;pg=PP11&amp;dq=postdoc+jobs+european+university+biotech&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YKFYU93xOYiVyAO22YCwDA&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Functional Foods and Biotechnology</title><description>Kalidas Shetty, Ph.D. is a professor of food biotechnology in the Department of Food Science at the University of ... He then pursued postdoctoral studies in plant biotechnology at the National Institute of Agro- Biological Sciences, ... and he will continue to serve in this position for 5 more years following his return to the University of Massachusetts. ... food biotechnology, functional foods and dietary phytochemicals, and food safety in over 20 countries in Asia, Europe, and the Americas.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>