<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:43:48" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:43:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=DukuBXDQcS4C&amp;pg=PA463&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Integrated Circuit and System Design: Power and Timing ...</title><description>We investigate the influence of skin effect on the propagation delays of on-chip interconnects. For long wires, designed in the LC regime, on thetop metal layer in a contemporary process, we find that the skin effect causes an extra delay by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:44:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=lZuz2ig4vnIC&amp;pg=PA3&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Compact Models and Measurement Techniques for High-Speed ...</title><description>Table 1.1 Classification of interconnects based on their electrical lengths Criteria Type of interconnect Model required l\k/10 ... There are two types of loss mechanisms in high-speed interconnects, namely skin effect and dielectric losses.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:44:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=io1hL48OqBsC&amp;pg=PA114&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Design of CMOS Radio-Frequency Integrated Circuits - Page 114</title><description>4.2 INTERCONNECT AT RADIO FREQUENCIES: SKIN EFFECT At low frequencies, the properties of interconnect we care about most are resistivity, current-handling ability, and perhaps capacitance. As frequency increases, we find that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=LDwtjaI3LDAC&amp;pg=PA87&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Modeling and Simulation of High Speed VLSI Interconnects \- Page 87</title><description>Introduction Interconnects must be included in today's high- frequency circuit simulations [1]. Digital systems utilize frequencies into the GHz range. At these frequencies skin effect causes reduction of the interconnect inductance and a rapid ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:28">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Ha76NqrqPVIC&amp;pg=PA392&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>System-on-Chip for Real-Time Applications - Page 392</title><description>Wael Badawy, Graham A. Julien. Section 9.3 Skin Effects in System on a Chip Interconnects Shizhong Mei and Yehea I. [sma.il Electrical and Computer Engineering Northwestern University, Evanston. IL 60208 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:45">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WnQ4uyo8QQUC&amp;pg=PA32&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>High-Speed Photonics Interconnects \- Page 32</title><description>The temperature rise in air-gap interconnect is comparable to that in homogeneous SiOZ-based interconnect. It can be ... that occur in chip-to-chip interconnects: the conductor loss due to skin effect and dielectric loss due to lossy substrates.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:46:11">http://books.google.nl/books?id=hSRUuxI1BBsC&amp;pg=PA27&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Variation Tolerant On-Chip Interconnects \- Page 27</title><description>This phenomenon is called the skin effect since most of the current is now flowing through the skin of the conductor. This leads to current crowding primarily on the surface and the effective cross-section where current flows reduces.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:46:41">http://books.google.nl/books?id=AcqwbVZWVzAC&amp;pg=PA161&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Design of Integrated Circuits for Optical Communications - Page 161</title><description>Loss The loss of microstrips arises from three sources: low-frequency resistance of interconnects, skin effect in interconnects, and dielectric loss.10 The loss due to skin effect in the microstrip of Fig. 5.37 is expressed as [6]: _ 4.34 R, W' 2 11 11 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:47:13">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QHtalNXHKbsC&amp;pg=PA514&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Digital Integrated Circuits: Analysis and Design - Page 514</title><description>h δ FIGURE 14.3 The skin effect in interconnect. w l Solution. Assuming the interconnect takes on the bulk resistivity of aluminum, The magnitude of this value suggests that the interconnect resistance may be neglected only for short wires.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:47:58">http://books.google.nl/books?id=PawQHHpZ6HMC&amp;pg=PA46&amp;dq=interconnects+skin+effect&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=1NxYU5amGejmywOW7YGQDQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Circuit and Interconnect Design for RF and High Bit-rate ... - Page 46</title><description>substrate w h i dm dw i dm t The total effective skin depth δ∗ equals the sum of the skin depths in the x- and y-directions: δ∗ = δx +δ y = δx ( 1+ wt ) (2.55) This empirical correction results in a frequency-independent correction factor. A linear ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>