<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:53:26" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:53:28">http://books.google.nl/books?id=F5gahYoU4_oC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Auto Repair For Dummies</title><description>For anyone who wants to save money on car repairs and maintenance, this book is the place to start.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:54:02">http://books.google.nl/books?id=LhoK_LWk40AC&amp;pg=PA40&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Savvy Guide to Car Maintenance and Repair - Page 40</title><description>Like with motor oil, you should not operate the vehicle with the transmission fluid low and you should not overfill it, either. ... Remove the transmission dipstick from its well and wipe it dry. 3. ... Checking Water/Coolant Levels in the Radiator The radiator usually sits at the very front of the car (as seen in figure 3-4), just behind ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:54:26">http://books.google.nl/books?id=RYWTUDHi0bEC&amp;pg=PT58&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Teach Yourself VISUALLY Car Care &amp; Maintenance</title><description>How to Replace l REPLACE COOLANT To add radiator coolant, follow these steps: 0 Select coolant as recommended by the manufacturer. An auto parts clerk can help you select the appropriate fluid for your car. If in doubt, refer to the owner's ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:54:45">http://books.google.nl/books?id=O4cgtFh_asEC&amp;pg=PA130&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Mustang Restoration Handbook - Page 130</title><description>A small crack can mean gasoline in trunk. place the free end of the hose in the jar so its end is immersed in fluid. You're ready to ... Go under the car and connect the fuel- gage sending-unit wire. Connect the fuel ... After mounting the radiator, install the overflow hose and route it down the left side of the radiator. Attach the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:55:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=dYfbZrla6QQC&amp;pg=PA61&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>How to Plan and Build a Fast Road Car \- Page 61</title><description>The same applies if you do not have an overheating problem, but want to reduce the coolant temperature. ... Changing the pump's gearing by using a smaller pulley may improve water flow at low engine speeds but can have a negative effect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:55:43">http://books.google.nl/books?id=KKj9sX8G_94C&amp;pg=PA42&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>How to Repair Your Car \- Page 42</title><description>Just check and change the oil/filter and coolant periodically. lf there's a transmission fluid dipstick, check this fluid every month or so as well, or at least at every oil change. That's if you can check the transmission fluid. ... A number of newer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:56:27">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XFDO669-RpUC&amp;pg=PA14&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Recipes for Car Care: The Consumer's Guide to Auto Health - Page 14</title><description>Figure 2-9 Most fluids are poisonous, particularly coolant (antifreeze), in tiny amounts. 14 15 Most, if not all, car fluids are ... Most cars now come with a portable combination jack/jackstand for changing a flat tire. They are meant to be used for a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:56:57">http://books.google.nl/books?id=VPSi4dBcGrMC&amp;pg=PA20&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>How to Keep Your Muscle Car Alive - Page 20</title><description>On my car, I change the front disc brake pads and inspect the rotors for thickness, warpage, cracks, and other surface ... motor oil, transmission fluid, radiator fluid, and any other waste fluids you accumulate during maintenance procedures.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:57:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Cc4aCGb6DUQC&amp;pg=PA122&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A Car, Some Cash and a Place to Crash: The Only ... - Page 122</title><description>Not only will replacing a dirty air filter improve your fuel economy, it will protect your engine. I drive a ... Changing the oil regularly will increase the life of your car's engine. Change ... Check oil, transmission fluid, and radiator coolant regularly.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:58:02">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XohzAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA32&amp;dq=car+change+radiator+fluid&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=F99YU86hA7TOyAOenYG4Ag&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>How to Purchase Or Buy A Car with Bad Or No Credit - Page 32</title><description>If the car has a voltmeter, make sure the voltage stays at 13.6 volts when the A/C is on. You may want to bring a portable ... If not, it's been a while since the radiator was maintained and the fluid has turned brown. Is there any windshield fluid?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>