<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:34:41" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:34:43">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SQgyAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA114&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Software Engineer Job Description Handbook and Career ...</title><description>The Complete Knowledge Guide You Need to Start Or Advance Your Career as Software Engineer. Practical Manual for ... This would mean you don't have to work in an office but work at the comfort of your home. You get to ... Planning to become a software consultant as a career move is a good decision. This is because ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:35:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=kxlABcUbI_wC&amp;pg=PA40&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Computerworld - 1 Feb 1999 - Page 40</title><description>Home. Depot. plan. bulk. of. work. in-house. to. best. meet. business. needs. av cnare STEDMAN IG CONSULTING bills are a ... Inc. both have embarked on mostly doit-yourself rollouts of SAP AG's enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:35:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=m2ZWM_UwreQC&amp;q=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Software Programmer - Consultant \- Network Engineer - ... - Page 66</title><description>Instead of enduring an exhausting rush-hour commute from home to the corporate office, people in telecommuting jobs and home-based computer tech jobs are making better use of their time by doing work at alternative worksites-from home, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:35:59">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1z6bAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA30&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Home Networking Annoyances: How to Fix the Most Annoying ...</title><description>How to Fix the Most Annoying Things About Your Home Network Kathy Ivens ... Approach the hiring of a computer consultant the same way you'd approach hiring an electrician or plumber—ask people for ... I've been in many businesses and homes in which my attempts to work on equipment and software were thwarted ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-05"><link>http://books.google.com/books?id=qfzu_YD5pnMC&amp;pg=PA1&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;ved=0CFMQ6AEwBA</link><title>What Your Computer Consultant Doesn't Want You to Know: ... - Page 1</title><description>Paul and Sarah Edwards, Authors of 14 books including Working from Home "I would hope that most reputable tech consultants would handle their clients in such a manner that this book wouldn't be necessary. But I know that's dreaming.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:36:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=_uA0yxXXyBoC&amp;pg=PA379&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Consultant &amp; Independent Contractor Agreements - Page 379</title><description>messengers, couriers, and delivery people, 230 reusable materials, 106, 201 software consultants, 165, 176–177 consumer ... See also assignment and delegation control of methods for accomplishing work accountants and bookkeepers, 154, 158 construction ... of fine art, 193 63, 75 generic agreement for ICs, 77, 84, 93 home child care worker, 110 household services workers, 111, 112–13, 116, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:37:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=NdSurLnMOggC&amp;pg=PT19&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Profitable Consultant: Starting, Growing, and Selling ...</title><description>Having a real office helps separate work from home. ... Many consultants are now taking advantage of one of the most incredible opportunities I think they could have—virtual office ... There are certain software programs that will help save you time as well, so you can spend even more time selling and generating revenue.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:37:48">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Xu__e7mtM8sC&amp;pg=PA120&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Joy of Working from Home: Making a Life While Making a ...</title><description>You can always hire a computer consultant to help you determine your software and hardware needs and specify what you should buy. You can find a consultant by personal referral, through a local computer user group, or in the classified ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:38:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QPSFZAUyh5wC&amp;q=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Working from home: everything you need to know about ... - Page 369</title><description>Here are some of the tasks that people working at home often dislike, can't do alone, or find more cost-effective to have done for ... Jeffery Lant, who trains others in how to establish a consultant practice, ... And fortunately, with a personal computer, learning to type is easy because there are software programs you can use to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:38:47">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1rxrokkmnAEC&amp;pg=PA114&amp;dq=software+consultant+work+at+home&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=wuhYU4kGhOHLA_20gIgL&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>All Moms Work: Short-term Career Strategies for Long-range ...</title><description>consultants. They may be looking for a specific expertise that you can offer. Many stay-at-home career moms opt for ... to do one project at a time, for example, build a website, write a report, write a case study, modify a piece of software, etc.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>