<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:49:42" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:49:43">http://books.google.nl/books?id=OxfN_J74_bMC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cyber Bullying: Protecting Kids and Adults from Online Bullies</title><description>This volume details the extent and types of cyberbullying and offers practical advice for combatting the problem from a variety of approaches.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:50:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=GbLA4lx36QAC&amp;pg=PA11&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Protecting Kids Online Guide - Page 11</title><description>Show your child how to use these settings to limit who can view their online profile, and explain to them why this is important. Explain that kids should post only information that you — and they — are comfortable with others seeing. Even if ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:50:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Ry_WnQEACAAJ&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Safety Monitor: How to Protect Your Kids Online</title><description>Safety Monitor provides hands-on, step-by-step, practical instruction for parents to protect their children from exploitation, sexual predators, adult-only content, pornography, and other harmful content that comes with computer and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:51:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=093Xc6Q67HQC&amp;pg=PA18&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Protecting Kids Online at Schools and Libraries - Page 18</title><description>Adam Walsh Child Protection and Safety Act of 2006 expands the National Sex Offender Registry and ensures law ... COPPA The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) specifically protects the privacy of children under the age of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:51:51">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4j7YPQAACAAJ&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Kids Online: Protecting Your Children in Cyberspace</title><description>Provides step-by-step instructions for keeping children safe while surfing the Internet</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:52:17">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SAN3f596lRAC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Protecting Your Internet Identity: Are You Naked Online?</title><description>"Protecting Your Internet Identity: Are you Naked Online? helps readers, young and old alike, understand the implications of their online personas and reputations.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:52:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=gZ2NGtPWjDsC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>To Catch a Predator: Protecting Your Kids from Online ...</title><description>While the show exposed this epidemic, Chris Hansen’s book, To Catch a Predator, shares the true stories of families who have been targeted by predators, revealing the tactics predators use to manipulate their victims and why even cautious ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:53:08">http://books.google.nl/books?id=OlSeiu6ia-cC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Concussions and Our Kids: America's Leading Expert on How ...</title><description>An expert on the head trauma crisis in sports provides a guide to concussions in youth sports -- what they are, how to treat them and how to protect young athletes. 30,000 first printing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:53:35">http://books.google.nl/books?id=clbiJxUdbiQC&amp;pg=PA29&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Why the government should care about pornography : the ... - Page 29</title><description>President Jerry Herman worked to evaluate the full range of approaches to protecting kids online, and joined the Commission's conclusion that filtering and other user empowerment tools (in the hands of parents) along with education, are the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:53:56">http://books.google.nl/books?id=4_VEc4bJcdkC&amp;pg=PA41&amp;dq=protect+kids+online&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=RuxYU5mED6voywOX2IHwAw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>How to Protect Your Children on the Internet: A Roadmap ... - Page 41</title><description>It is important however, for them to understand the risks of kids going online via a wireless connection that might not be controlled in their own house. This dilemma will only get worse as more powerful and free wireless access points cover a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>