<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:41:38" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:41:39">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SVflYk1Hl0cC&amp;pg=PA439&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>I-mode Developer's Guide - Page 439</title><description>The easiest way to create an original i-mode melody file is to convert one from an existing MIDI sound file. ... You will be happy to know that some inexpensive programs for Windows let you convert existing WAV, MP3, and CD audio files to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:44:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=wMOMjt6FGK0C&amp;pg=PA516&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Mastering Digital Audio Production: The Professional Music ...</title><description>MP3 is a form of data compression that eliminates frequencies that the human ear can't hear. This creates smaller files. ... The iTunes program can easily convert your CDs, AIFF, and WAV files to the AAC format. The main advantage to the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:46:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=jcoKAbcCJKoC&amp;pg=PA70&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Ubuntu: Powerful Hacks and Customizations - Page 70</title><description>Convert WAV to MP3 bash -c “lame %M %d/ `base name %M .wav` .mp3“ Only for files ending in .wav, no multiple selections. This converts file.wav to ... Without the basename program, you would end up with a file named file.wav.mp3.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:47:44">http://books.google.nl/books?id=m2ro0Bf5qoQC&amp;pg=PT279&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Sams Teach Yourself Android Game Programming in 24 Hours</title><description>WAV •OGG • MIDI • MP3 By the Way An easy way to convert audio files from one format to another is with a free audio editor program called Audacity: http://audacity.sourceforge.net. It can convert to and from WAV, MP3, and OGG. Initializing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:48:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=IAPB1IZ5uVMC&amp;pg=PA48&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Practical Computer Literacy - Page 48</title><description>Digital audio is stored in a variety of file types, including WAV, MP3, M4P, and MIDI. Waveform audio ... MP3 software is popular for converting music from CDs into a digital format called MP3 that can be stored on a computer hard disk. Once in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:50:53">http://books.google.nl/books?id=jpFqPhjClv4C&amp;pg=SA10-PA34&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Cutting Edge PowerPoint 2007 For Dummies - Page 10-34</title><description>Rip the CD tracks as WAV, MP3, or WMA files (use MP3 if you're working between both the Mac and Windows versions of ... (See the “Converting CD tracks” section, later in this chapter, to find out how to rip CD audio tracks.) ... You can also use Windows Media Player, an application that's part of Microsoft Windows.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:52:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=XocJtVhhtz8C&amp;pg=PA363&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>PC Recording Studios For Dummies - Page 363</title><description>MP3. Programs. If you want to put your music on the Internet, you need to be able to convert it to MP3 format. Before you get ... WAV files like the other programs, but it also allows you to cut sections from MP3 or WAV files if you want to create ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:54:06">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QpGzt364HpYC&amp;pg=PA116&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Male Voices: Stories of Boys Learning Through Making Music</title><description>Accompaniment Band-in-a-Box (Gannon, 1988) is an excellent program to supplement notational programs in the area of ... Band-in- a-Box song files can be exported as midi files for use in programs such as Windows Media player or iTunes, and converted to .wav files for burning to CD. ... It can import and export .wav, .mp3 and other raw audio files, and it can record from a microphone or line input.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:56:42">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Zz3LwyDCL5MC&amp;pg=PA209&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Sams Teach Yourself HTML5 Mobile Application Development ...</title><description>TABLE 12.2 Browser Support for Audio Codecs Browsers MP3 Vorbis WAV Android version 2.3 version 2.3 Chrome ... Finding commercial programs to convert files to Vorbis can be difficult, but many online converters are available that will do ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7491-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7491_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:00:04">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ygEAAAAAMBAJ&amp;pg=PA1991&amp;dq=convert+wav+mp3+program&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=ggZZU9GUE8TOOemEgOgP&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Maximum PC - Feb 2000 - Page 1991</title><description>Audiograbber was so smooth, Xing made it the cornerstone of AudioCatalyst, its all-in-one MP3 suite. ... to help you clean up, name, and normalize the volume on your ripped WAV files before they're converted to MP3s; in this respect, it bests any of the all-in-one utilities. ... But once you understand the browsing metaphor that Sonique employs, the program becomes quite intuitive, and much more ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>