<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:29" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ZzlNgS70OHAC&amp;pg=PA275&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Weapons of Mass Destruction - Page 275</title><description>SYRIA:CHEMICAL AND BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS PROGRAMS Although constrained by limited resources,Syria re- portedly possesses an active chemical warfare program and a limited biological warfare program. Syria has also acquired a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:46:36">http://books.google.nl/books?id=QvPGAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA167&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Strategic Culture and Weapons of Mass Destruction - Page 167</title><description>Seeing that the Syrian air force is no match for the Israeli air force, Assad decided to acquire long range surface- to-surface missiles.28 It is shortly thereafter that he decided to develop a chemical warfare capability. Hafez Assad's decision to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:47:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Yr_DsC59L3UC&amp;pg=PA201&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Israel and Syria: The Military Balance and Prospects of ... - Page 201</title><description>and suicide bombers still enter Iraq through Syria, albeit at a significantly reduced rate likely owing in part to increasing ... Syrian Chemical Weapons Syria has chemical weapons, and most experts believe it has mustard agents and at least ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:48:09">http://books.google.nl/books?id=MQMGhInCvlgC&amp;pg=PA44&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Chemical and Biological Warfare: A Comprehensive Survey ... - Page 44</title><description>It is difficult to say to what extent Syria relies on foreign expertise for chemical weapons development. Syria has received technical advice from the former Soviet Union and developed its more advanced chemical warheads with assistance also ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:49:06">http://books.google.nl/books?id=ESfIAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA65&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Proliferation of Weapons of Mass Destruction in the Middle ... - Page 65</title><description>minority in March 1988 and against Iran at various times during the Iran– Iraq War, Syria never used chemical weapons, either against its internal opponents (the Muslim Brotherhood in 1982 in Hama) or externally (Israeli forces during their ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:49:36">http://books.google.nl/books?id=6fvZAAAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA188&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Politics and Economics of Defence Industries - Page 188</title><description>This refers mainly to production of chemical weapons (which in the past Syria failed to acquire from the Soviet Union) and development of long range missiles in collaboration with China and North Korea, and to a lesser degree, Iran. Syria ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:50:13">http://books.google.nl/books?id=2wsAAAAAMBAJ&amp;pg=PA37&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists - Sep 1997 - Page 37</title><description>"chemical warfare capability" without indicating whether that state is developing weapons or already has a stockpile of ... Syria. Syria began developing chemical weapons in the 1970s, in response to the Israeli threat, according to a 1993 DIA ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:51:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=H8wwRGrD6V4C&amp;pg=PT89&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Role and Control of Weapons in the 1990s</title><description>It is of interest to note that, while the USA was strongly criticizing Libya for making, or preparing to make, chemical weapons, it was ignoring Iraq's growing chemicalweapon capability. Little is known about Syria's chemicalweapon capability.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:51:59">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Ol-ud-Lj5zEC&amp;pg=PA545&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Peace and War: The Arab-Israeli Military Balance Enters ... - Page 545</title><description>Syrian troops steadily increased their NBC training after 1982, and Syria began to give chemical warfare training a serious priority. More significantly, Syria started a crash effort to produce nerve gas — setting up at least two major chemical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:52:34">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WHXfP25eMq4C&amp;pg=PA220&amp;dq=syria+chemical+weapons&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=eRVZU-GoF6StywPQ6ICoBg&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Atomic Assistance: How “Atoms for Peace” Programs Cause ...</title><description>If safeguards and the NPT had little effect on Syria's nuclear decision making, what explains nuclear restraint prior to 2000? One factor that played a critical role was Syria's possession of chemical weapons. Nuclear weapons and chemical ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>