<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:53:23" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:53:24">http://books.google.nl/books?id=jj4J-AXGDaQC&amp;pg=PA1375&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Africa South of the Sahara 2004 - Page 1375</title><description>there was a strong recovery in the bullion market, owing partly to speculative activity, and in late July and early August the London price exceeded $400 per oz. The gold price declined to $344 (£222) per oz in September, but ended the year at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:01">http://books.google.nl/books?id=hmmBAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA122&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Gold and the Modern World Economy - Page 122</title><description>(1998) found gold mining firms have substantial gold price exposure at around two per cent, confirming Blose and Shieh's (1995) finding. Tufano (1998) developed three models for the valuation of gold companies, namely the fixed production, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:32">http://books.google.nl/books?id=MVhk9a629EUC&amp;pg=PA349&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Taxation: Critical Perspectives on the World Economy</title><description>Gold prices in the 1980s and the Australian gold-mining industry Gold prices in the 1980s In 1979 and 1980, gold price in the world market as well as in Australia registered a sharp rise. For example, in Australian dollars, the 1978 gold price of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:59">http://books.google.nl/books?id=8caeFTHlLLYC&amp;pg=PA11&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Gold: Science and Applications - Page 11</title><description>GOLD PRICE Gold has been used as a medium of exchange for more than 5,000 years. From 1717 to 1931, it was used, for example, within the British monetary system (and maintained a fixed price against the pound sterling) under what was ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:55:54">http://books.google.nl/books?id=SczaAzOdouYC&amp;pg=PA348&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Gold (Routledge Revivals): A World Survey - Page 348</title><description>It is suggested that confirmation that the bull market is over will occur by October 1986 when the moving average line is predicted to cross the gold price line. The variation in cycle length for the two cycles identified and the beginning of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:56:30">http://books.google.nl/books?id=190xVQDRtHAC&amp;pg=PA453&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>A History of the Federal Reserve, Volume 1: 1913-1951</title><description>He anticipated spending $100 million to get the dollar gold price to $33 or $34 before Congress met, and he again warned about the dangers of serious social disorder in the West.73 Markets and the public received Roosevelt's speech ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:57:19">http://books.google.nl/books?id=jyraAgAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA99&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>An Insider's Guide to the Mining Sector: How to Make Money ...</title><description>In the 30s, US investors, unable to own gold, did extremely well in gold shares, which enabled them to legally benefit from the rise in the government supported gold price. Those who bought the US's leading gold miner Homestake for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:58:07">http://books.google.nl/books?id=LNEn45Xfd4kC&amp;pg=PA13&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Monetary Economics in Globalised Financial Markets - Page 13</title><description>Ansgar Belke, Thorsten Polleit. the US government promised to redeem other central banks' holdings of US dollar for gold at a fixed rate of US$35 per ounce. However, persistent US balance of payments deficits steadily reduced US gold ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:59:18">http://books.google.nl/books?id=IdXRAQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA25&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Gold Cartel: Government Intervention on Gold, the Mega ...</title><description>Government Intervention on Gold, the Mega Bubble in Paper, and What This Means for Your Future Dimitri Speck. policy, as it ... For this purpose, the chart of the gold price is shown together with the indicator of rel- ative gold price movements.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:59:49">http://books.google.nl/books?id=da4OxM-AjQcC&amp;pg=PA311&amp;dq=gold+price&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=UxdZU8fqJ-O1yAON7ICoAQ&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Advances in Automation and Robotics, Vol.2: Selected ... - Page 311</title><description>The relationship between Shandong Gold share price and gold price It can be found in the effects of three different gold prices, the domestic gold price is the most significant one. Relatively speaking, the international gold price can be ignored.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>