<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:34" name="Google Books" id="FW14-e029"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:35">http://books.google.nl/books?id=DREC8_uHg20C&amp;pg=PA164&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Retrofitting of Heritage Structures: Design and Evaluation ... - Page 164</title><description>2.4 Roof isolation systems The effectiveness of roof isolation for the aforementioned 13-story building was studied [13]. The building is located in Sherman Oaks, California and designed around 1964. It has 13 stories, 2 basements, a pile ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:01:03">http://books.google.nl/books?id=U329VKjXU1YC&amp;pg=PA2&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Effectiveness and Feasibility of Inter-story Isolation Systems - Page 2</title><description>Experimental research to determine the effectiveness of isolation systems installed at various levels above base is presently underway in China (Zhou et al., 2005). Roof level isolation systems that utilize the tuned mass damper concept, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:01:40">http://books.google.nl/books?id=Ja-PmWe_VFQC&amp;pg=PA343&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Clinical Arrhythmology and Electrophysiology: A Companion ...</title><description>One study suggested that circumferential LA ablation to encircle the PVs is preferable to segmental ostial PV isolation as the ... Ablation strategies may involve the LA roof line, the LA mitral isthmus line, and the RA cavotricuspid isthmus line in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:09">http://books.google.nl/books?id=DxZ4xlvti1sC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Grass Roof, Tin Roof</title><description>In 1975, Tran, a Vietnamese writer facing government persecution, flees her homeland with her two children and seeks refuge in the West, where she marries a Danish-American man with his own memories of another war, in a sensitive debut ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:47">http://books.google.nl/books?id=_3_UAv2HhiAC&amp;pg=PA343&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Clinical Arrhythmology and Electrophysiology: A Companion ...</title><description>One study suggested that circumferential LA ablation to encircle the PVs is preferable to segmental ostial PV isolation as the first ... This finding implicated the LA roof in the substrate maintaining AF after PV isolation.115 Linear ablation was ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:03:35">http://books.google.nl/books?id=GTaWcjpOswYC&amp;pg=PR11&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>The Use of Innovative Base Isolation Systems to Achieve ... - Page xi</title><description>... 3-story building on nonlinear damped isolation system 207 Figure 6-31: Comparison of peak floor acceleration (PFA) at each floor level for 3- story building on nonlinear damped isolation system 208 Figure 6-32: Comparison of median roof ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:04:37">http://books.google.nl/books?id=oOI0z81dzCYC&amp;pg=PA243&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Advances in Visual Computing: 5th International Symposium, ...</title><description>If the buildings are sufficiently distant from each other, each set corresponds to one building. Otherwise, one set represents several buildings. In order to further divide the points into individual roofs, we developed a roof isolation method based ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:46">http://books.google.nl/books?id=WDHu3xWC96QC&amp;pg=PA135&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Seismic Control Systems: Design and Performance Assessment</title><description>Seismic. isolation. for. a. wide. span. glazed. roof. G. C. Giuliani &amp; M. E. Giuliani Redesco Progetti Srl, Milan, Italy Abstract The roofing of the Crowne Plaza Hotel hall, located in Caserta (Italy), took into account the constraints given by the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:06:24">http://books.google.nl/books?id=1EJk33JCCWAC&amp;pg=PA33&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Investments to Improve the Energy Efficiency of Existing ... - Page 33</title><description>But since many buildings have badly deteriorated roofs that urgently need repair, roof insulation is likely to include new roof assemblies that fix immediate problems (such as leaking), ensure a longer period of low maintenance costs, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e029-7500-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e029/7500_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:07:28">http://books.google.nl/books?id=gYsOdXpgkn0C&amp;pg=SA14-PA2&amp;dq=roof+isolation&amp;hl=en&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=AhlZU5n-Daj_ygPZ14GgCw&amp;redir_esc=y</link><title>Seismic Design of Building Structures: A Professional's ... - Page 14-2</title><description>Figure 14.2 One Type of Isolation Bearing holes through outer shims only—to receive studs rubber steel shims cylindrical ... In several recent earthquakes, most buildings experienced maximum accelerations at the roof well in excess of the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>