<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:27:50" name="AOL Video" id="FW14-e175"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:30:12">http://www.ibsfree.net/ibsfree_at_last/fermentation/</link><title>IBS—Free at Last! : Fermentation</title><description>Apr 30, 2013 ... How Long to Stay on Elimination Phase of the IBSFree Diet ... So there is no particular benefit of staying on the restricted phase of the diet for any longer than necessary. .... In this paper, unlike Dr. Pimentels book, there is no discussion of ... If there is a sharp rise in the amount of hydrogen exhaled after the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:31:33">http://ueg.sagepub.com/content/early/2014/01/27/2050640614521124.full</link><title>Symptomatic fructose malabsorption in irritable bowel ...</title><description>Jan 27, 2014 ... IBS characteristics were not predictive even if young (p = 0.031) and ..... C Melchior, G Gourcerol, AM Leroi and P Ducrotté wrote the paper. ... Influence of the oropharyngeal microflora on the measurement of exhaled breath ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_03.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:36:45">http://ueg.sagepub.com/content/early/2014/01/27/2050640614521124.full.pdf</link><title>Symptomatic fructose malabsorption in ir...</title><description>Jan 27, 2014 ... Materials and methods: Ninety Rome III IBS patients (predominant ... of hydrogen (H2) or methane (CH4) levels in the exhaled air led to the ... IBS characteristics were not predictive even if young ..... Ducrotte´ wrote the paper.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:41:58">http://www.health24.com/Medical/Digestive-health/Common-digestive-disorders/Your-complete-guide-to-Irritable-Bowel-Syndrome-20130312</link><title>Your complete guide to Irritable Bowel Syndrome | Health24</title><description>Mar 12, 2013 ... Up to 70% of people suffering from IBS are not receiving medical care for their symptoms. IBS tends to occur .... This can be detected in the exhaled air. .... Toilet paper may irritate the anus, so using baby wipes may be better.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:46:47">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3966170/</link><title>Low-FODMAP Diet for Treatment of Irritable Bowel Syndrome</title><description>This paper will review the pathophysiology of IBS and the role of FODMAPs for the ... that bacteria are the sole producers of intestinal hydrogen, some of which is exhaled. .... Therefore, no definitive conclusions can be made regarding the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:51:01">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1856094/</link><title>Use and abuse of hydrogen breath tests</title><description>“Malabsorption of fructose and/or sorbitol is not more frequent in IBS patients than .... the same authors change their definitions of a positive test in different papers. .... intestinal influences on exhaled breath hydrogen measurements during the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:55:21">http://theceliacmd.com/2013/11/november-2013-sibo-gluten-ibs-connection/</link><title>SIBO, Gluten and IBS: What Is The Connection? | Amy Burkhart ...</title><description>Nov 11, 2013 ... Her doctor told her she had IBS, but she wanted to know if there was something ... the patient drinks a sugar-containing drink and exhaled gases are measured. ... A 2003 paper found there was a high incidence of SIBO in celiac ... There is no definitive test or diagnostic marker at this time (although one is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:59:15">http://www.jnmjournal.org/journal/view.html?uid=202&amp;vmd=Full</link><title>The Hydrogen Breath Test - Journal of Neurogastroenterology ...</title><description>The paper by Ghoshal et al in this issue of the journal reminds us that we can still ... with the irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) were reported to exhale higher basal ... hydrogen excretion after fibre rich meals and lactulose, they had not reported ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:03:23">http://www.patient.co.uk/doctor/lactose-intolerance-pro</link><title>Lactose Intolerance | Doctor | Patient.co.uk</title><description>Dec 10, 2013 ... There is no single agreed diagnostic test, but the following can be ... measuring the exhaled hydrogen concentration after a carbohydrate ... Recurrent abdominal pain of childhood and irritable bowel syndrome can mimic the symptoms .... Are we using antidepressants to paper over the cracks of a fractured ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e175-7002-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e175/7002_10.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:07:06">https://gupea.ub.gu.se/bitstream/2077/4564/1/thesis.pdf</link><title>Peripheral and central factors in the pathophysiol...</title><description>intestinal bacterial overgrowth is not common in IBS, but of uncertain relevance, ... This thesis is based on the following papers, which will be referred to in the text ...... exhaled H2 monitor (GMI Medical Ltd., Inchinistan Estate, Renfrew, UK).</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>