<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:51:51" name="TechRepublic" id="FW14-e171"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:51:52">http://www.techrepublic.com/blog/software-engineer/getting-started-with-the-outsystems-agile-platform/</link><title>Getting started with the OutSystems Agile Platform</title><description>In this series, Justin James chronicles using the OutSystems Agile Platform to write a real-world Web application. Part one covers his initial experiences with the Agile Platform.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:52:54">http://www.techrepublic.com/blog/software-engineer/programming-news-microfocus-acquires-borland-aleri-integrates-coral8-engine-with-windows-hpc-server/</link><title>Programming news: MicroFocus acquires Borland, Aleri integrates Coral8 engine with Windows HPC Server</title><description>Justin James highlights news about MicroFocus' acquisition of Borland and Compuware's testing business, AppStore apps must be iPhone 3.0 compliant, releases of Intentional Domain W...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:54:14">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/control-your-own-destiny-by-using-google-sitemaps-to-drive-traffic-to-your-site/</link><title>Control your own destiny by using Google Sitemaps to drive traffic to your site</title><description>Google Sitemaps endeavors to improve how Google's Web crawlers discover new content on your site to make it more quickly available in Google searches.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:55:28">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/no-training-budget-try-these-five-free-tutorial-sites/</link><title>No training budget? Try these five free tutorial sites</title><description>Keeping your development skills up to date is tough work, especially when you don't have money for books or training. To help you fit more training into your tight budget, check ou...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:57:10">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/regular-expressions-variations-in-support/</link><title>Regular expressions: Variations in support</title><description>RE implementation has been deployed differently, depending on the environment. Here's a look at some of the variations in standards and conventions, along with resources for additi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:58:22">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/book-review-essentially-jython-misses-mark-for-language-novices/</link><title>Book review: Essentially Jython misses mark for language novices</title><description>Jython is the hot new language, combining Python's rapid development capabilities with Java's tremendous resources. This book review of O'Reilly's "Jython Essentials" looks at the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:59:38">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/creating-xml-from-mysql-is-as-easy-as-pi/</link><title>Creating XML from MySQL is as easy as PI</title><description>It's easy to integrate MySQL data into an XML file, but importing XML into MySQL is a bit trickier. Learn how to export and import XML with the popular database MySQL.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:01:15">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/oh-my-mysql/</link><title>Oh, my--MySQL!</title><description>If you are running a host Web site, the chances are good you have MySQL access. Discover when, where, and why you should use MySQL.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:02:35">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/get-your-python-resources-here/</link><title>Get your Python resources here</title><description>Itching to find out more about the powerful, portable language Python? We've got you covered with a list of some of the best Python resources that the Web has to offer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e171-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e171/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:03:28">http://www.techrepublic.com/article/windows-script-host-tutorial-pseudocode-algorithms-and-other-programming-basics/</link><title>Windows Script Host tutorial: Pseudocode algorithms and other programming basics</title><description>Want to script your own Windows solutions? In this Drill Down by Greg Schultz, you'll learn some programming techniques that will help you prepare to script in VBScript or JScript.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>