<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:54:56" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:54:56">http://www.healthline.com/health/circumcision</link><title>Circumcision</title><description>* Circumcision What Is Circumcision? Circumcision is the surgical removal of the foreskin of the penis. It is typically done on a newborn for religious reasons. In adults, several diseases may require circumcision, including balanitis, phimosis and paraphimosis. Circumcision...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:55:27">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/who-says-male-circumcision-should-be-part-hiv-prevention</link><title>WHO says: Male circumcision should be part of HIV prevention</title><description>* WHO says: Male circumcision should be part of HIV prevention Researchers have known for years that circumcision significantly reduces the spread of HIV virus in men, and that uncircumcised men are 3 times more likely to contract HIV. Male circumcision is the surgical removal of the foreskin from the penis. Researchers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:56:14">http://www.healthline.com/health/paraphimosis</link><title>Paraphimosis</title><description>* Paraphimosis In very severe cases, a complete circumcision (removal of the foreskin) may be necessary. If treated at the first sign of a problem, the chances of a full recovery from paraphimosis are very good. As long as the swelling is reduced and the foreskin is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:57:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/you-say-genital-integrity-rules</link><title>YOU Say: Genital Integrity Rules!</title><description>* YOU Say: Genital Integrity Rules! My previous post, WHO says: Male Circumcision Should be Part of HIV Prevention, reporting the World Health Organization's (not my own!) recommendations that male circumcision be part of a comprehensive plan to help prevent HIV transmission hit a nerve....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:58:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/pregnancy/pre-labor-decisions</link><title>Labor &amp; Delivery: Pre-Labor Decisions</title><description>* Labor &amp; Delivery: Pre-Labor Decisions Circumcision is an elective, irreversible, cosmetic procedure that is not done for any specific medical reason. Since it is a surgical procedure, it carries some risk of bleeding, infection, and scarring.Current medical literature has not demonstrated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:59:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/thank-you-dr-keagirl-grand-rounds-328</link><title>Thank You Dr. Keagirl, for Grand Rounds 3.28!</title><description>* Thank You Dr. Keagirl, for Grand Rounds 3.28! She was kind enough to include my recent post:WHO Says: Male circumcision should be part of HIV preventionFor further musings on AIDS, see:AIDS: Why are people of color hit so hard?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:02:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/hiv-aids/prevention</link><title>HIV/AIDS Prevention</title><description>* HIV/AIDS Prevention Studies have also shown that male circumcision reduces the risk of HIV infection among males. Bodily Fluid ExposureExposure to contaminated blood can spread the HIV virus. The use of intravenous drugs poses a great risk for exposure. Recreational drug...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7003-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7003_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:03:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/hiv-facts-you-need-know</link><title>HIV Facts: What You Need to Know</title><description>* HIV Facts: What You Need to Know HIV is a preventable illness. Learn important facts such as how to protect yourself and others, and what the outlook is for HIV-positive people.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>