<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:09:54" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:09:55">http://www.healthline.com/health/stroke/alternative-treatments</link><title>Stroke Alternative Treatments</title><description>* Stroke Alternative Treatments Alternative treatments for stroke can help complement the therapies you doctor will prescribe for you following a stroke. However, you should be aware that none of these treatment options are a direct treatment for a stroke; rather, these should be c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:13:57">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/shyness</link><title>Shyness</title><description>* Shyness What Is Shyness? Shyness is a feeling of fear or discomfort caused by other people, especially in new situations or among strangers. Shyness is an unpleasant feeling of self-consciousness—a fear of what other people are thinking. This fear can inhibi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:17:21">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/super-spice-of-the-week-ginger</link><title>Super Spice of the Week: Ginger</title><description>* Super Spice of the Week: Ginger Ginger has been used since ancient times as a healing medicine in Asian, Arabic, and Indian cultures.Ginger has a spicy and slightly sweet taste with a strong, pungent aroma. Ginger is rich in volatile oils,essential fatty acids, beta-carotene, and a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:21:49">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/asians-and-stigma-mental-illness-national-minority-health-and-hea</link><title>Asians and the Stigma of Mental Illness: National Minority Health and Health Disparities Month</title><description>* Asians and the Stigma of Mental Illness: National Minority Health and Health Disparities Month Asians with mental health problems are very much on our minds this week.Who are Asian Americans? According to the Office of Minority Health (OMC), there are 14.4 million Asian Americans, roughly five percent of the total population. The US states with...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:25:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/fast-food-erases-benefits-of-traditional-asian-diet</link><title>Fast Food Erases the Benefits of a Traditional Asian Diet</title><description>* Fast Food Erases the Benefits of a Traditional Asian Diet Singapore is a remarkably multiethnic society, combining elements of Chinese, British, Indian, and Indonesian cultures. While the cuisine is diverse and not always heart healthy, it has traditionally included plenty of seafood, fruits, and vegetables...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:28:41">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-food-taboos</link><title>Exotic foods</title><description>* Exotic foods Food taboos Amphibians, bee larvae, birds, camels, caribou, casu marzu, cats, cheese fly, chives, cows, crustaceans, culinary aphrodisiacs, delicacy, dogs, donkeys, elephants, feral cats, fish, food taboos, fungi, garlic, grasshoppers, guinea pig , h...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>