<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:22" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:23">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/book-review-tempted-6th-house-night-series</link><title>Book Review: Tempted, 6th in the House of Night Series</title><description>* Book Review: Tempted, 6th in the House of Night Series If you have not finished this book, do not read this book review - it will spoil it for you! Tempted is book six in the House of Night series and begins after Zoey and her friends have banished Kalona and Neferet, Zoey and Stark are both recovering, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:32:54">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/satisfying-breakfast</link><title>Satisfying Breakfast</title><description>* Satisfying Breakfast I know you have heard it before...breakfast is the most important meal of the day. You hear this all the time because it is true! I think all meals are important, but breakfast is extra important to kick start that metabolism from overnight. Eating b...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:34:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/eat-good-form</link><title>Eat With Good Form</title><description>* Eat With Good Form When you watch a diver or figure skater compete, you comment on what good form they have. The slide into the water or across with ice with grace and fluidity. Lifting weights requires you to have proper form to prevent injury.Have you ever thought ab...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:36:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/type-2-life/keep-watching-the-skies</link><title>Keep Watching the Skies!</title><description>* Keep Watching the Skies! In Howard Hawks’ classic 1951 sci-fi thriller, “The Thing from Another World,” a ravenous flesh-eating alien (actually an incredibly grumpy intelligent vegetable) is finally outsmarted and fried to death by a group of U.S. airmen after they find his ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:38:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/foods-fit-goths</link><title>Foods Fit for the Goths</title><description>* Foods Fit for the Goths So, in honor of Halloween, I’m listed the 10 healthiest raven-colored foods, along with some non-threatening suggestions for adding them to your diet: Black beans – delicious in soup, tacos, burritos, salads and even as a secret ingredient in brownies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:41:09">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/health-benefits-turkey</link><title>Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Turkey</title><description>* Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Turkey At last, it's turkey time again! It seems that turkey is ignored 10 months out of the year until the holiday season arrives, but with the nutritional benefits this lean protein provides, people should start thinking about including it more often. Hig...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:43:19">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/the-art-of-keeping-weight-off</link><title>The Art of Keeping Lost Weight off for Good!</title><description>* The Art of Keeping Lost Weight off for Good! One of the biggest struggles people face in terms of dieting and fitness is how to maintain weight after losing it. Whether you have lost 100 lbs or 10 lbs, you want to make sure you keep that weight from creeping back up. Below are some helpful tips...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:46:12">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/protein-keep-you-full</link><title>Protein to Keep You Full</title><description>* Protein to Keep You Full My last post was about how much protein our bodies actually need. I want to follow that information up with some very interesting research and thoughts around what the optimal level of protein is, which may be different than what our body "needs."Ben...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:47:28">http://www.healthline.com/health/afterschool-snacks-start-stocking</link><title>Afterschool Snacks: Start Stocking Up</title><description>* Afterschool Snacks: Start Stocking Up After a long day at school, your kids often arrive home ravenous, craving sugar-filled snacks or high-fat munchies. Research from the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) found that there has been an increase in unhealthy snacking in the last twenty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:49:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/quick-tips-for-cutting-calories</link><title>Quick Tips for Cutting Calories</title><description>* Quick Tips for Cutting Calories Losing weight is not always as easy as it sounds. You have probably tried diet after diet, and while some of them may work in the beginning, the second you straythe pounds start creeping back up. I have seen this same scenario time and again with man...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>