<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:30" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/synovial-biopsy</link><title>Synovial Biopsy</title><description>* Synovial Biopsy What is a Synovial Biopsy? Every joint in the human body contains synovial fluid. This fluid, which is secreted into the joint cavity by the synovium or the synovial membrane, lubricates the joints and allows for ease of movement. The synovial membrane...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:28:15">http://www.healthline.com/health/synovial-fluid-analysis</link><title>Synovial Fluid Analysis</title><description>* Synovial Fluid Analysis Cases of synovial fluid and joint inflammation are more common with increased age. Synovial fluid analysis is also known as joint fluid analysis. When is the Test Done A synovial fluid analysis is performed when there is pain, inflammation, or swelling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:30:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/pain-relief-knee-joint-pain</link><title>Knee and Joint Pain</title><description>* Knee and Joint Pain The knees are the body’s largest and most-used joints, bearing the weight of the body and absorbing the impact of a lifetime of walking, running, and movement. Knee joints are intricate structures with components including bones, cartilage, ligaments...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:33:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/pseudogout</link><title>Pseudogout</title><description>* Pseudogout Your doctor may wish to drain the synovial fluid from the joint to relieve the pressure within the joint and to reduce inflammation. If you are suffering from acute attacks of pseudogout, your doctor may prescribe nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/septic-arthritis</link><title>Infectious (Septic) Arthritis</title><description>* Infectious (Septic) Arthritis What Is Infectious Arthritis? Infectious arthritis is a painful infection in the joint. It may also be referred to as septic arthritis. It occurs when an infection, caused by a bacteria or virus, spreads to a joint or the fluid surrounding the joint ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>