<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:37:21" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:37:22">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/haemophilus-influenzae-type-b-conjugate-vaccine</link><title>Haemophilus influenzae type b Conjugate Vaccine injection</title><description>* Haemophilus influenzae type b Conjugate Vaccine injection Haemophilus influenzae type b Conjugate Vaccine injection What is this medicine? HAEMOPHILUS INFLUENZAE TYPE B CONJUGATE VACCINE (hem OFF fil us in floo En zuh vak SEEN) is used to prevent infections of a Haemophilus bacteria. This medic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:39:46">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/conjugated-estrogens-1</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens injection</title><description>* Conjugated Estrogens injection Conjugated Estrogens injection What is this medicine? CONJUGATED ESTROGENS (CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz) is a mixture of female hormones. It is used to treat abnormal bleeding from the uterus caused by a hormonal imbalance. This medici...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-03"><link>http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/meningococcal-polysaccharide-diphtheria-toxoid-conjugate</link><title>Meningococcal Diphtheria Toxoid Conjugate Vaccine</title><description>* Meningococcal Diphtheria Toxoid Conjugate Vaccine Meningococcal Diphtheria Toxoid Conjugate Vaccine What is this medicine? MENINGOCOCCAL DIPHTHERIA TOXOID CONJUGATE VACCINE (muh ning goh KOK kal dif THEER ee uh TOK soid KON juh geyt vak SEEN) is a vaccine to protect from bacterial me...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:45:16">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/conjugated-estrogens</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens tablets</title><description>* Conjugated Estrogens tablets Conjugated Estrogens tablets What is this medicine? CONJUGATED ESTROGENS (CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz) is an estrogen. It is used as hormone replacement in menopausal women. It helps to treat hot flashes and prevent osteoporosis. It is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:49:35">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/synthetic-conjugated-estrogens</link><title>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (A) oral tablet</title><description>* Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (A) oral tablet Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (A) oral tablet What is this medicine? SYNTHETIC CONJUGATED ESTROGENS (A) (sin THET ic CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz A) is an estrogen. It is mostly used as hormone replacement in menopausal women to treat ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:51:30">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/conjugated-estrogens-2</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Vaginal cream</title><description>* Conjugated Estrogens Vaginal cream Conjugated Estrogens Vaginal cream What is this medicine? CONJUGATED ESTROGENS (CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz) are a mixture of female hormones. This cream can help relieve symptoms associated with menopause.like vaginal dryness and irri...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:55:42">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/synthetic-conjugated-estrogens-1</link><title>Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (B) oral tablet</title><description>* Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (B) oral tablet Synthetic Conjugated Estrogens (B) oral tablet What is this medicine? SYNTHETIC CONJUGATED ESTROGENS (B) (sin THET ic CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz B) is an estrogen. It is mostly used as hormone replacement in menopausal women to treat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7022-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7022_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:57:39">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/conjugated-estrogens-medroxyprogesterone</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens; Medroxyprogesterone tablets</title><description>* Conjugated Estrogens; Medroxyprogesterone tablets Conjugated Estrogens; Medroxyprogesterone tablets What is this medicine? CONJUGATED ESTROGENS; MEDROXYPROGESTERONE (CON ju gate ed ESS troe jenz; me DROX ee proe JES te rone) is used as hormone replacement in menopausal women who still ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>