<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7023">calculate jordan normal form</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:44" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:45">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/watch-hbo-tuesday-baghdad-hospital-inside-red-zone</link><title>Watch HBO Tuesday - Baghdad Hospital: Inside the Red Zone</title><description>* Watch HBO Tuesday - Baghdad Hospital: Inside the Red Zone Fulbright scholar Dr. Omer Salih Mahdi filmed inside the ER where he works at Al-Yarmouk hospital in Baghdad, revealing the terrible wounds suffered by Iraqi civilians in the ongoing fighting. As an ER nurse, I got emotional watching as the staff, wo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:03:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/safe-surgery-saves-lives-endorse-whos-checklist</link><title>Safe Surgery Saves Lives - Endorse WHO's Checklist</title><description>* Safe Surgery Saves Lives - Endorse WHO's Checklist The World Health Organization (WHO) estimates that 234 million major surgical procedures are performed around the world each year. The WHO Surgical Safety Checklist was created to help operating teams reduce poor incidence of poor surgical outcomes. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:04:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/rbc-indices</link><title>RBC Indices</title><description>* RBC Indices What Are Red Blood Cell Indices? The red blood cell indices (RBC indices) are part of a routine blood test called the complete blood count (CBC). The CBC is used as a measure of general health. It measures the quantity and physical characteristics of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:06:51">http://www.healthline.com/health/melanoma-diagnosis</link><title>Melanoma Diagnosis</title><description>* Melanoma Diagnosis Melanoma is the most dangerous form of skin cancer. Found early, most melanomas are curable, however, left undetected, the disease can spread to other parts of the body making it harder to treat, and potentially fatal. Experts advise giving self-exam...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/predicting-your-cardiovascular-risk</link><title>Predicting Your Cardiovascular Risk</title><description>* Predicting Your Cardiovascular Risk Cardiovascular disease kills more women and men than all forms of cancer combined. Although it will ultimately take the life of more than one in every three people, not everyone is at the same risk. Wouldn’t it be nice to know where you stand? There ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:35">http://www.healthline.com/health/fractional-excretion-of-sodium</link><title>Fractional Excretion of Sodium</title><description>* Fractional Excretion of Sodium Fractional Excretion of Sodium Fractional excretion of sodium (FENa) measures the amount of sodium leaving your body relative to the amount of salt filtered through your kidneys and reabsorbed into your body. It is used to determine how well your kid...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7023-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7023_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:15:46">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/atrial-fibrillation-what-you-should-know-about-blood-thinners</link><title>Atrial Fibrillation and What You Should Know About Blood Thinners</title><description>* Atrial Fibrillation and What You Should Know About Blood Thinners Atrial fibrillation is a heart rhythm disturbance that affects upwards of 2.6 million Americans. Although it’s more common after the age of 70, it can happen at any age. In atrial fibrillation the upper chambers of the heart, or atria, quiver erratic...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>