<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:55" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:56">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-targeted-behavior-modification</link><title>Behavior modification</title><description>* Behavior modification Targeted behavior modification Alpha-conditioning, applied behavioral analysis, applied behavioral therapy, assertiveness training, aversion therapy, basic learning techniques, biofeedback, CBT, classical conditioning, cognitive therapy, cognitive-be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:29">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/adhd-myths</link><title>The Four Greatest Myths about ADHD</title><description>* The Four Greatest Myths about ADHD With redirection, positive reinforcement, and proper management, a person with ADHD can successfully complete tasks, even ones that they find boring. 4. People with ADHD Are Irresponsible A person with ADHD may often forget important items. Losing keys,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:23:51">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/bullying-anger-social-issues</link><title>Bullying, Anger, and Other Social Issues for Children with ADHD</title><description>* Bullying, Anger, and Other Social Issues for Children with ADHD Stress the importance of using positive reinforcement in the classroom. If you have an IEP or Section 504 plan, make sure to incorporate strategies for dealing with anger and discipline. Cultivating Healthy Social Skills Friendships can help relieve stress...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:44">http://www.healthline.com/health/eating-disorders-causes-risk-factors</link><title>Eating Disorders Causes and Risk Factors</title><description>* Eating Disorders Causes and Risk Factors Dieting – Weight loss is often met with positive reinforcement. This need for affirmation may drive people to diet more severely, which can lead to an eating disorder.Emotional disorders – People with depression, anxiety, and obsessive-compulsive disorder...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:24">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/think-you-don-t-really-smoke-nicotine</link><title>Think you don’t really smoke for nicotine?</title><description>* Think you don’t really smoke for nicotine? ...reward neurotransmitter” – dopamine, in some of the parts of the brain that are particularly sensitive to reinforcement and emotional regulation. Other effects include a mild stimulant effect, that can be measured as an increase in heart rate, and a speeding...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:33:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/parenting-tips</link><title>Parenting Tips for ADHD: Dos and Don’ts</title><description>* Parenting Tips for ADHD: Dos and Don’ts Repetition and positive reinforcement can help your child to better understand your rules. Define the rules, but allow some flexibility. It is important to consistently reward good behaviors and discourage destructive ones, but you can’t be too strict...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>