<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:50:46" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:50:46">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/how-effective-are-medical-treatments-back-pain</link><title>How Effective Are Medical Treatments For Back Pain?</title><description>* How Effective Are Medical Treatments For Back Pain? Many well-known conventional treatments for injured athletes and military personnel came from ways to keep wounded combatants able to continue fire, not to maximize their long-term survival or later health.Years of my career laboratory research was i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:52:18">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/cancer-treatment-survivorship/how-do-you-prefer-orientationeducation-about-cancer</link><title>How Do You Prefer Orientation/Education about Cancer?</title><description>* How Do You Prefer Orientation/Education about Cancer? The following is a review written by a nurse, Valerie R. Vestal, MSN, FNP, RN, at our institution on a study related to orientation for individuals with cancer and their primary support person.Because of the unfamiliar surroundings and unpredictable ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:52:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/cancer-treatment-survivorship/how-understanding-cancer-patients-internet-design-prefe</link><title>How Understanding Cancer Patient's Internet Design Preferences Affect Patient Education</title><description>* How Understanding Cancer Patient's Internet Design Preferences Affect Patient Education Valerie R. Vestal, MSN, FNP, RN read an article in the Oncology Nursing Forum that was recently written by authors C. Chernecky,D. Macklin, &amp; J. Waller. The authors believe that understanding the computer experience of individuals with cancer and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:55:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/cigarette-brand-preferences-start-young-and-focus-3-brands</link><title>Cigarette Brand Preferences: start young and focus on 3 brands.</title><description>* Cigarette Brand Preferences: start young and focus on 3 brands. When you look at the cigarette counter at a supermarket or even a chain pharmacy you will typically see a wall of cigarettes and advertising placards touting dozens of types of cigarettes. However, although there are actually hundreds of different br...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:57:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/study-finds-smokers-prefer-snus-and-zonnic-over-nicotine-gum</link><title>Study finds smokers prefer Snus and Zonnic over Nicotine Gum</title><description>* Study finds smokers prefer Snus and Zonnic over Nicotine Gum A study was just published comparing the effects of nicotine gum, snus (smokeless tobacco sachets) and Zonnic (new synthetic nicotine replacement sachets) for reducing smoking. The study by Drs Caldwell, Burgess and Crane was conducted with 63 cigare...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:01:04">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/week-medical-technology-news</link><title>This week in medical technology news</title><description>* This week in medical technology news First, a public service announcement:Just a reminder, please submit Grand Rounds entries for Tuesday's host to Blog carnival at: http://blogcarnival.com/bc/cprof_21.html by monday.If you prefer, send the submission letter to drkavokin at yahoo dot co...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>