<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:52" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/bipolar-bites/bipolar-you-need-your-thyroid-checked</link><title>Bipolar? You Need Your Thyroid Checked</title><description>* Bipolar? You Need Your Thyroid Checked When a person is diagnosed with an illness, doctors do something called a differential diagnosis. Basically, this is when a doctor considers all the illnesses that may explain your symptoms and then decides on which one fits best. In the case of bipo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:40:30">http://www.healthline.com/health/ham-test</link><title>Ham Test</title><description>* Ham Test Ham Test Overview The ham test is a blood test designed by Dr. Thomas Ham that is used to determine the condition of the red blood cells in the body and to diagnose certain types of acquired and congenital blood disorders. The test uses a mild acid t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:41:54">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/bagel-sandwich-recipe</link><title>Wasabi Salmon Bagel Sandwiches Lunch Recipe</title><description>* Wasabi Salmon Bagel Sandwiches Lunch Recipe Makes 4 servings Ingredients ¼ cup reduced-fat mayonnaise ½ teaspoon wasabi paste ¼ teaspoon toasted sesame oil 2 (7.5-oz.) cans salmon, packed in water ¼ cup thinly sliced green onions 4 thin whole wheat sandwich bagels* 1 cup cucumber slices 4 butt...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:44:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/wilderness-first-aid</link><title>Wilderness First Aid</title><description>* Wilderness First Aid In a recent issue of Wilderness and Environmental Medicine (Volume 20, Number 2, 2009), Thomas Welch and colleagues have written an article entitled “Wilderness First Aid: Is There an Industry Standard?” The purpose of their inquiry was to determine ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:47:11">http://www.healthline.com/health/restless-leg-syndrome/history</link><title>The History of Restless Leg Syndrome</title><description>* The History of Restless Leg Syndrome Even if you have RLS, you may not be aware that it’s also known as “Ekbom disease” or “Willis-Ekbom disease.” It was identified and described by Professor KarlAxel Ekbom in 1945, but he wasn’t the first. It was initially documented 300 years earlier ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>