<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7039">import .csv excel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:17" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:18">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/top-iphone-android-apps-diabetes</link><title>The 13 Best Diabetes iPhone &amp; Android Apps of 2013</title><description>* The 13 Best Diabetes iPhone &amp; Android Apps of 2013 With rapidly rising diabetes rates, managing this condition is more important than ever. Check out these 13 apps to get a better handle on your blood sugar.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:07:50">http://www.healthline.com/health/important-conversations-have-during-holidays</link><title>Important Conversations to Have During the Holidays</title><description>* Important Conversations to Have During the Holidays The holidays are fast-approaching—and so is your chance to have heart-to-heart conversations with far-flung family members who you may not see often. Though it can be difficult to mention certain topics, this "together time" may make it easier to add...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:08:49">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/importance-fetal-heart-evaluation</link><title>Importance of Fetal Heart Evaluation</title><description>* Importance of Fetal Heart Evaluation Early last week, a 17 year old woman, carrying her first baby, was seen in the office for a routine ultrasound at about 18 weeks’ to confirm gestational age and assess fetal anatomy. During that examination, the baby was found to have a heart abnorma...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:11:46">http://www.healthline.com/health/importance-strength-training-women</link><title>The Importance of Strength Training for Women</title><description>* The Importance of Strength Training for Women What's an activity that can help women stay strong, burn calories, and build healthy bones? Strength training. Before you say "No, thanks," to weights, take some time to debunk the myths and learn the importance of strength training for women. Only a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:15:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/from-womb-to-world/the-importance-of-baby-wearing</link><title>The Importance of Baby Wearing</title><description>* The Importance of Baby Wearing Have you seen the sitcoms lately with all the men wearing their babies? Baby wearing for men and women seems to be more prevalent. Well, it's not just a fad and it's not just for those practicing attachment-parenting. In fact, it has been practiced a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:17:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/importance-education</link><title>The Importance Of Education</title><description>* The Importance Of Education When you think about it, after unconditional love and attention, there may be nothing more powerful a parent can give a child than education. Education brings with it adult mentors who care about kids, knowledge about health, the world, character-bui...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/hold-that-pause/depression-perimenopause-why-exercise-light-important</link><title>Depression in Perimenopause: Why Exercise and Light are So Important</title><description>* Depression in Perimenopause: Why Exercise and Light are So Important Now that March is over, along with the long, dark days of winter, perhaps the topic ofdepression in perimenopausewon’t be so, well, depressing.As one who grew up in the muggy Deep South where actual seasons are an anomaly, I actually love winter. I l...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:22:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/exercise-more-important-calcium-supplements-bones</link><title>Exercise is More Important Than Calcium Supplements for Bones</title><description>* Exercise is More Important Than Calcium Supplements for Bones A study making recent news concluded that taking calcium supplements does not do much to reduce bone fractures in childhood or later life. The study did not cover all reasons, but it does not stand alone. Studies over many years show that bone densit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:25:41">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/importance-touch-and-teens</link><title>The Importance of Touch and Teens</title><description>* The Importance of Touch and Teens Unfortunately, as our teens get older, there is a tendency for them to get less affectionate with us and for us to forget to be affectionate with them. OK - I admit, sometimes affection is the last thing we are feeling toward our teen after a long da...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7039-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7039_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/one-breath-at-a-time/importance-equipment-maintenance</link><title>COPD: The Importance of Equipment Maintenance</title><description>* COPD: The Importance of Equipment Maintenance A patient suffering from COPD has a great deal of equipment and medicine which requires maintenance and proper handling. My mother, a COPD patient, has portable oxygen canisters, a canister holder that rolls, a wheel chair, a rolling walker, air tubi...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>