<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:36:09" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:36:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/surviving-wilderness-emergency-5</link><title>Surviving A Wilderness Emergency 5</title><description>* Surviving A Wilderness Emergency 5 This is the thirteenth post based upon educational sessions and syllabus material presented at the Wilderness Medical Society Annual Meeting &amp; 25th Anniversary held in Snowmass, Colorado from July 25-30. It’s based upon an excellent presentation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:38:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/winter-tragedy</link><title>A Winter Tragedy</title><description>* A Winter Tragedy The practice of wilderness medicine is unfortunately frequently necessitated by tragic events and circumstances. We are all enormously saddened to learn of the death of James Kim, whose recovery was announced today. Mr. Kim succumbed to the cold Paci...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:39:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/ice-it-down</link><title>Ice it Down</title><description>* Ice it Down Athletes know it and do it, and so should you. If you are going to be vigorous on your feet, with your knees, with your shoulders, or any muscle group or joint, inflammation is your nemesis. So, to counteract the irritation, fluid collections, swelli...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:29">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/methamphetamine</link><title>Methamphetamine oral tablet</title><description>* Methamphetamine oral tablet Methamphetamine oral tablet What is this medicine? METHAMPHETAMINE (meth am FET a meen) is used to treat attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). The drug may also be used together with diet and exercise in the short-term treat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:44:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/case-emergency-ice</link><title>In Case of Emergency (ICE)</title><description>* In Case of Emergency (ICE) Here is an important topic I had not given much thought, but I believe parents should put on their "to-do" list. First, the police suggest that you program an "In Case of Emergency" (ICE) number into all the phones in your household. This is a number...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:48:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/shihan-chong-breaks-10-blocks-ice-age-70</link><title>Shihan Chong Breaks 10 Blocks of Ice At Age 70</title><description>* Shihan Chong Breaks 10 Blocks of Ice At Age 70 My friend, teacher, and fellow instructor Shihan (means - high teacher) Peter Chong of Singapore, 8th degree Black Belt (HachiDan), breaks 10 blocks of ice while standing on eggs.Shihan Chong did this for his 70th birthday in front of 200 friends and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:51:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/snow-sledding-safety</link><title>Winter Sports &amp; Sledding Safety</title><description>* Winter Sports &amp; Sledding Safety There are many possibilities for injuries to occur during participation in winter sports (e.g., skiing, snowboarding, snowmobiling, sledding, ice skating and outdoor hockey, backcountry winter camping, ice climbing, mountaineering, ice fishing, etc.)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:52:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/travelers-diarrhea-prevention-treatment</link><title>Guest Post: Prevention &amp; Treatment of Traveler’s Diarrhea</title><description>* Guest Post: Prevention &amp; Treatment of Traveler’s Diarrhea Prevention of traveler’s diarrhea (TD) centers around three methods: dietary safety, immunizations, and chemoprophylaxis (medications taken to prevent diarrhea). Education on safe eating practices should form the basis of protection. Hand washing bef...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:55:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/amphetamine-dependence</link><title>Amphetamine Dependence</title><description>* Amphetamine Dependence Dextroamphetamine and methamphetamine are two other types of amphetamines. Amphetamines are sometimes sold illegally on the street. Both prescribed and street amphetamines can be abused. The most commonly abused amphetamine is methamphetamine. Amphetamine...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:56:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/are-you-always-colder-exercise-cold-water</link><title>Are You Always Colder With Exercise In Cold Water?</title><description>* Are You Always Colder With Exercise In Cold Water? It is winter in the northern hemisphere. Outdoor swimming and boating waters range from chilly to frozen. A widespread assumption is that exercise in cold water always makes you colder. Some scuba diving textbooks assert that cold water will cause he...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>