<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:01:28" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:01:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/hantavirus-yosemite-national-park</link><title>Hantavirus in Yosemite National Park</title><description>* Hantavirus in Yosemite National Park Our National Parks are a treasured heritage, and one of the ways in which we appreciate the outdoors. Millions of visitors flock to the parks in order to camp, hike, climb, swim and most of all, appreciate the wonder and natural beauty of America. As...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:18">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/best-videos-menopause</link><title>8 Best Menopause Videos of 2013</title><description>* 8 Best Menopause Videos of 2013 Prepare to laugh and learn with these menopause videos that share important medical information as well as the lighter side from women going through it.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:09:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/sawyer-water-filter-0</link><title>Sawyer Water Filter</title><description>* Sawyer Water Filter Wilderness and outdoor activities take many of us to the farthest reaches of the globe. Adventures in the mountains, forests, oceans and deserts bring us to countries in Africa, South America, Central America, Asia, and other places, where food, wate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:12:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/cdcs-wants-bloggers-encourage-getting-flu-shots</link><title>CDC's Wants Bloggers to Encourage Getting Flu Shots</title><description>* CDC's Wants Bloggers to Encourage Getting Flu Shots Today, the CDC, America's Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, hosted a webinar for bloggers to ask us to get the word out that people should go get their flu shots.Over the course of 40 minutes, they gave the scientific background supporting ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:16:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/alligator-attack</link><title>Alligator Attack</title><description>* Alligator Attack When I was a 4th year medical student at Duke, I completed an elective rotation in pediatric surgery at Shands Hospital at the University of Florida in Gainesville. It was an outstanding experience, working with some of the most dedicated and innovat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:20:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/adventure-sports-workout</link><title>The Adventure Sports Workout</title><description>* The Adventure Sports Workout Are you tired of the same, old gym routine? Maybe it's time to take your workout to the next level. Adventure awaits you in the great outdoors. Go to the mountains, desert, river, or ocean to get fit, have fun, and explore a new place. You'll have so...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:22:23">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/healthy-places</link><title>Best Places to Visit for a Healthier You</title><description>* Best Places to Visit for a Healthier You Getting away doesn’t mean abandoning all of your healthy habits. These travel destinations make it easy to incorporate health and wellness into your vacation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:24:38">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/28-tips</link><title>28 Healthy Heart Tips</title><description>* 28 Healthy Heart Tips Healthline offers you 28 ways to power up, slow down, have fun, and get fit —all in the name of a healthy heart. Pick your favorites, and work them into your regular routine.1. Stop smoking-no ifs, ands, or (cigarette) butts.People still need to be r...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:26:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/desert-and-desert-survival-1</link><title>The Desert and Desert Survival 1</title><description>* The Desert and Desert Survival 1 This is the third post based upon educational sessions and syllabus material presented at the Wilderness Medical Society Annual Meeting &amp; 25th Anniversary held in Snowmass, Colorado from July 25-30, 2008. This post about the desert and the next t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:27:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/crohns-and-colitis/super-toilet-bowl</link><title>Super [Toilet] Bowl</title><description>* Super [Toilet] Bowl Having watched the Super Bowl recently, seeing the fans in the stands and the crowds gathered outside, I am reminded of the last time I went to an event in a stadium. It was for a concert last summer. I only occasionally go to stadium events anymore—...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>