<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:31:41" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:31:42">http://www.healthline.com/health/rinne-and-weber-tests</link><title>Rinne and Weber Tests</title><description>* Rinne and Weber Tests Rinne Test The doctor strikes a tuning fork and places it near the base of your mastoid bone. The doctor asks you to say when you no longer hear the sound. The doctor notes the time and moves the tuning fork near the ear canal.The doctor asks you to say...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:33:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/evidence-based-management-wilderness-injuries</link><title>Evidence-Based Management of Wilderness Injuries</title><description>* Evidence-Based Management of Wilderness Injuries ...cervical spine (neck) fractures, shoulder dislocations, and detection of fractures (broken bones) using a tuning fork.The Ottawa ankle decision rules for the use of x-rays to determine the presence or absence of an ankle fracture were determined in patients...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:37:05">http://www.healthline.com/health/audiology</link><title>Audiometry</title><description>* Audiometry A tuning fork (a vibrating fork) may be used to determine how well a person hears vibrations through the ear. The doctor may put this metal device against the bone behind the ear (mastoid) or use a bone oscillator to determine how well vibrations pass...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:41:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/improvisation-according-iserson</link><title>Improvisation According to Iserson</title><description>* Improvisation According to Iserson ...transfusions, rehydrating patients without intravenous lines, diagnosing broken bones by auscultation (using a tuning fork and stethoscope) or ultrasound, hypnosis for painful procedures, traction, and more. Of all of the advanced medical information,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:44:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/sensorineural-deafness</link><title>Sudden Sensorineural Hearing Loss (SSHL)</title><description>* Sudden Sensorineural Hearing Loss (SSHL) Tests using a tuning fork can check if there is damage to the parts of the middle ear and eardrum that vibrate. Your hearing can be more thoroughly checked with audiometer tests. An audiologist can conduct thorough testing of your hearing ability using...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:46:57">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-sound-healing</link><title>Sound healing</title><description>* Sound healing Chanting, crystal bowls, didgeridoo, gong, harmonics, metal bowls, music therapy, psycho-acoustics, singing, sonic tools, toning, tuning fork, vibration, vibration healing. Sound healing is the use of chanting, music, and other types of noises to sti...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>