<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:51" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/bells-palsy</link><title>bell's palsy</title><description>* bell's palsy Data Sources The search included MEDLINE, EMBASE, CENTRAL, PsychInfo, CINAHL, Web of Science, PAPERSFIRST, PROCEEDINGSFIRST, and PROQUEST to identify studies up to March 1, 2009. Study Selection and Data Extraction Eligible studies were randomized controlled...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/vote-healthline-people-s-voice-webby-awards</link><title>Vote for Healthline @ The People’s Voice Webby Awards!</title><description>* Vote for Healthline @ The People’s Voice Webby Awards! Healthline has been nominated for the prestigious Webby Award in the category of “Health." The International Academy of Digital Arts and Sciences will choose Webby Award winners, but the People’s Choice Webby lets you decide. It’s easy: Simply log on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/vote-healthline-webby-award</link><title>Vote for Healthline for Webby Award</title><description>* Vote for Healthline for Webby Award Healthline has been nominated for the prestigious Webby Award in the category of “Health."The International Academy of Digital Arts and Sciences will choose Webby Award winners, but the People’s Choice Webby lets you decide. It’s easy:Simply log on t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:38:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/osteoporosis-men-are-risk-too</link><title>Osteoporosis: Men are at Risk, Too</title><description>* Osteoporosis: Men are at Risk, Too Low levels of testosterone and age put millions of men at risk for osteoporosis. Low levels of testosterone can lead to decreased bone mineral density (BMD), putting older men at increased risk for bone fractures.Testosterone replacement therapy (TRT...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:40:14">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/tuberous-sclerosis-alliance</link><title>Tuberous Sclerosis Alliance</title><description>* Tuberous Sclerosis Alliance The Tuberous Sclerosis Alliance asks us to observe Tuberous Sclerosis Month in May. The disease affects about 1 million people worldwide. A genetic disorder characterized by an abnormal growth in the brain that looks like a root or tuber, this diseas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:39">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/notes-technology-entertainment-design-ted-conference</link><title>Notes on the Technology Entertainment Design (TED) Conference</title><description>* Notes on the Technology Entertainment Design (TED) Conference The Technology Entertainment Design Conference -- or TED -- is a 4 day meeting of 50 brilliant speakers from a wide range of fields. In the words of David Pogue, a technology columnist at the New York Times: They are the most compelling, passionate, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>