<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:23:55" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:23:56">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/disorders-of-communication</link><title>Communication Skills and Disorders</title><description>* Communication Skills and Disorders What Are Communication Disorders Communication disorders can affect how a person receives, sends, processes, and understands concepts. They can also weaken speech and language skills, or impair the ability to hear and understand messages. There are m...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:28:33">http://www.healthline.com/health/mixed-receptive-expressive-language-disorder</link><title>Mixed Receptive-Expressive Language Disorder</title><description>* Mixed Receptive-Expressive Language Disorder Mixed Receptive-Expressive Language Disorder People with mixed receptive-expressive language disorder have difficulty expressing themselves and understanding what others are saying. This is unrelated to hearing and speech problems. According to the U...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:31:54">http://www.healthline.com/health/diadochokinetic-rate</link><title>Diadochokinetic Rate</title><description>* Diadochokinetic Rate Diadochokinetic Rate Overview Diadochokinetic (DDK) rate is a test used by speech-language pathologists (SLP) to assess, diagnose, and treat speech malfunctions. It is also known as the Fletcher Time-by-Count Test of Diadochokinetic Syllable Rate. DD...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:35:56">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/developmental-delay</link><title>Developmental Delay</title><description>* Developmental Delay Developmental Delay Overview Children reach developmental milestones at their own pace. Minor, temporary delays are usually no cause for alarm. An ongoing delay or multiple delays in reaching milestones is called developmental delay. Developmental mi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:38:06">http://www.healthline.com/health/developmental-reading-disorder</link><title>Dyslexia (Developmental Reading Disorder)</title><description>* Dyslexia (Developmental Reading Disorder) Overview Developmental reading disorder (DRD), more commonly called dyslexia, occurs when your brain has a hard time processing language. You might misread the letters in a word and/or have difficulty reading irregular or unfamiliar words. Dyslexia i...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>