<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:33" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/straight-talk-stanford-er/whats-your-er-experience</link><title>What's Your ER Experience?</title><description>* What's Your ER Experience? My name is Anil Menon, and I am a first year resident in the Stanford-Kaiser emergency medicine program; however, this winter I found myself playing the role of the patient, which was less than stellar but eye opening at the same time. This experienc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:42:53">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/valerian</link><title>Valerian (Valeriana officinalis L.)</title><description>* Valerian (Valeriana officinalis L.) All-heal, amantilla, balderbrackenwurzel, baldrian, baldrianwurzel, baldrion, Belgian valerian, blessed herb, capon's tail, common valerian, English valerian, fixed valerian-hops extract combination Ze91019, fragrant valerian, garden heliotrope, gard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:44:11">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/dhea</link><title>DHEA</title><description>* DHEA Dehydroepiandrosterone 5-androsten-3 β-ol-17-one, C19 steroid, dehydroepiandrosterone, dehydroepiandrosterone sulfate, DHA, DHAS, DHEA-enanthate, DHEA-FA, DHEA-S, DHEAS, DS, 7-KETO DHE, 7-oxo-DHEA, dehydroepiandrosterone (DHEA), the mother steroid, p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:47:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/floaters-and-flashing-lights</link><title>Floaters and Flashing Lights</title><description>* Floaters and Flashing Lights Medicine for the outdoors is just that – application of the healing arts in outdoor environments, where one must on occasion make do with limited diagnostic capabilities (compared to what is available in a hospital or clinic) and supplies. Often, one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:49:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/meals-in-a-flash</link><title>Meals in a Flash</title><description>* Meals in a Flash photo courtesy of IkescsWith the hectic lifestyles that we all lead, healthy eating can often take a back seat to other obligations, like family, work, hobbies and everyday living. All these can make it hard for individuals to plan healthy and nouris...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:52:28">http://www.healthline.com/health/mens-health/hot-flashes-men</link><title>Hot Flashes in Men</title><description>* Hot Flashes in Men When you think of hot flashes, you probably think of a woman in menopause. But believe it or not, men can also experience the discomfort of flushing and sweating from hot flashes. In fact, according to Harvard Medical School (HMS), although fewer men...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:54:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/let-there-be-light</link><title>Let There Be Light</title><description>* Let There Be Light I'm always grateful for high quality equipment that works under adverse circumstances, when I most need it. If you need to practice outdoor medicine in the shadows or at night, on a mountainside, in a cave, or in another low-light situation, you will...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:59:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-to-heart/heat-fluids-congestive-heart-failure</link><title>Heat, Fluids, and Congestive Heart Failure</title><description>* Heat, Fluids, and Congestive Heart Failure I've a been heart attack survivor for about 4 years now. When I was battling for my life in the critical care unit of the hospital at The University of Pennsylvania, I went into a condition called flash pulmonary edema. This happens when the heart is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:04:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/new-year-ritual</link><title>New Year Ritual</title><description>* New Year Ritual Continuing my theme about the importance of celebration and rituals in our lives, and especially involving teens in holiday rituals, here is a suggestion for a New Years Eve tradition. All you will need is a bowl, preferably metal, a pen, and paper. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:10:09">http://www.healthline.com/health/electroretinography</link><title>Electroretinography</title><description>* Electroretinography What Is Electroretinography? Electroretinography (ERG) is a test that measures the electrical response of the light-sensitive cells in your eyes. These cells are called rods and cones, and form part of the back of the eye known as the retina. There a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>