<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7071">buy LP politics yellowjackets</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:37" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:37">http://www.healthline.com/health/lumbar-puncture</link><title>Lumbar Puncture (Spinal Tap)</title><description>* Lumbar Puncture (Spinal Tap) What Is a Lumbar Puncture? A lumbar puncture is a medical procedure that is usually performed in order to obtain a sample of cerebrospinal fluid. The procedure is sometimes referred to as a spinal tap. Cerebrospinal fluid is the fluid that surrounds the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:17:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/perspectives-in-ms/lumbar-puncture</link><title>Lumbar Puncture</title><description>* Lumbar Puncture ...instill fear and horror in the heart of patients everywhere, he could design no better phrase than “spinal tap” or “lumbar puncture (LP).” Yet, this is a test that I find myself recommending for some terrified soul on an almost weekly basis. As I said...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:22:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/perspectives-in-ms/lumbar-puncture-what-to-expect</link><title>Lumbar Puncture: What to Expect</title><description>* Lumbar Puncture: What to Expect Like a lumbar puncture, this sounds worse than it actually is. In a blood patch, a doctor will inject a patient’s own blood at the same location as the original LP. This procedure is highly effective in almost all patients in permanently eliminating the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:27:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/lumbar-puncture-multiple-sclerosis</link><title>Diagnosing Multiple Sclerosis: How Lumbar Puncture Works</title><description>* Diagnosing Multiple Sclerosis: How Lumbar Puncture Works Doctors use several methods to diagnose multiple sclerosis, including lumbar puncture. Learn what to expect when getting this procedure and what it can reveal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:31:08">http://www.healthline.com/health/neurosyphilis</link><title>Neurosyphilis</title><description>* Neurosyphilis Spinal Tap If your doctor suspects late-stage neurosyphilis, he or she will also order a lumbar puncture, or spinal tap. This procedure will provide a sample of the fluid around your brain and spinal cord. Your doctor will use this sample to find out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:34:18">http://www.healthline.com/health/guillain-barre-syndrome</link><title>Guillain-Barre Syndrome</title><description>* Guillain-Barre Syndrome The following tests are used to help confirm a diagnosis: Spinal Tap This test is also referred to as a lumbar puncture. A spinal tap involves taking a small amount of fluid from the spine in the lower back. The fluid is then tested to detect protein...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:05">http://www.healthline.com/health/meningitis-staphylococcal</link><title>Staphylococcal Meningitis</title><description>* Staphylococcal Meningitis magnetic resonance imaging (MRI): to look for signs of inflammation in the brain lumbar puncture (spinal tap): to look for signs of infection in the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) complete blood count (CBC): to look for signs of infection in your blood Symptoms...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:37">http://www.healthline.com/health/csf-smear</link><title>Cerebrospinal Fluid (CSF) Smear</title><description>* Cerebrospinal Fluid (CSF) Smear The most common method of collecting cerebral spinal fluid is lumbar puncture, sometimes called spinal tap. How CSF Samples Are Taken Lumbar puncture usually takes less than 30 minutes and is performed by a physician specially trained to safely collect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/csf-cell-count</link><title>CSF Cell Count and Differential</title><description>* CSF Cell Count and Differential The most common method of collecting cerebrospinal fluid is a lumbar puncture, sometimes called a spinal tap. Other Test Names Cerebrospinal fluid analysis; spinal fluid analysis; cell count and differential – CSF; CSF Cell Count and Cell Differential...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7071-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7071_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:44:04">http://www.healthline.com/health/csf-analysis</link><title>Cerebral Spinal Fluid (CSF) Analysis</title><description>* Cerebral Spinal Fluid (CSF) Analysis A CSF sample is commonly collected by performing a lumbar puncture (also known as a “spinal tap”). An analysis of the sample involves the measurement of and examination for: fluid pressure proteins glucose red blood cells white blood cells...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>