<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:52:54" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:52:54">http://www.healthline.com/health/menopause/alternative-treatment</link><title>Manage Your Menopause Naturally</title><description>* Manage Your Menopause Naturally ...Ginseng Ginseng is an herb used for its therapeutic health benefits for as many as 5,000 years by Chinese, Koreans, and Native Americans. It may be used to treat menopausal symptoms of fatigue, anxiety, and stress because it’s considered a “normalizer”...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:59:04">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/ginseng</link><title>Ginseng (American ginseng, Asian ginseng, Chinese ginseng, Korean red ginseng, Panax ginseng: Panax spp., including P. ginseng C.C. Meyer and P. quinquefolius L., excluding Eleutherococcus senticosus)</title><description>* Ginseng (American ginseng, Asian ginseng, Chinese ginseng, Korean red ginseng, Panax ginseng: Panax spp., including P. ginseng C.C. Meyer and P. quinquefolius L., excluding Eleutherococcus senticosus) Ginseng Asian ginseng Chinese ginseng Korean red ginseng Panax ginseng General: Acetylenic alcohol, acidid polysaccharides, acupuncture-moxibustion, aglycones, Allheilkraut, American ginseng (AG), American wild ginseng, Araliaceae (family), Asian gin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:59:39">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/shiitake</link><title>Shiitake (Lentinula edodes)</title><description>* Shiitake (Lentinula edodes) Lentinula edodes Lentinan Active hexose correlated compound (AHCC), Agaricus edodes, basidiomycete, beta-glucan, black forest mushroom, C-fraction, C-lipid-fraction, Chinese black mushroom, Coprinopsis ciner, Cortinellus shiitake, D-fraction, d-gluco...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>