<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:40" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:41">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/road-again</link><title>On The Road Again</title><description>* On The Road Again Now that the holiday break has passed, many vacation traveler's are home and business travelers are out in full force again. I travel about every other month for business, but some people live on planes and hotel rooms. If you missed it, be sure to r...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:53:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/travel-safety</link><title>On the Road: Travel Safety</title><description>* On the Road: Travel Safety Healthy and safe traveling, whether to a far off place or just down the road, requires care and preparation. Because visiting a new location puts your body in contact with unfamiliar and different food, water, climate, and air quality, it’s not uncom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:55:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/travel-abroad-watch-road</link><title>Travel Abroad - Watch the Road</title><description>* Travel Abroad - Watch the Road The greatest threat to Americans traveling abroad isn't an exotic tropical disease like malaria. According to US State Department data, the number one cause of death of US citizens traveling internationally is motor vehicle accidents (MVA). Infectiou...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:58:21">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/road-most-travelled</link><title>The Road Most Travelled</title><description>* The Road Most Travelled This is my first post as the CEO of Healthline and the father of 9 week old twin boys (Grant &amp; Cooper). It's been a tremendous ride so far.As quick background, I am a serial entrepreneur and dad... this is my fourth early stage company, working a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:00:49">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/road-not-taken</link><title>"The Road Not Taken..."</title><description>* "The Road Not Taken..." Recently, I was asked to see a very interesting patient in consultation. Although a favorable outcome of her pregnancy is by no means guaranteed at this time, I am fairly sure that the timely request from her physician for a “curbside” consult averte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:02:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/its-a-type-2-life/hitting-the-road-with-type-2</link><title>Hitting the Road with Type 2</title><description>* Hitting the Road with Type 2 My wife and I will soon be driving out from the San Francisco Bay Area to southern Utah. We haven’t visited the glorious red rock country there in years, so we’ve been anticipating this trip for months. Our goal is to shun freeways and interstates as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:04:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/road-trip</link><title>Road Trip</title><description>* Road Trip Hello again! I have not posted in a week because I was on vacation and freed myself from internet and email. I brought my computer along intending to write posts and keep in touch with my email, but my husband convinced me to really actually take a v...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:05:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/on-the-road</link><title>On the Road Again: Eating Healthy While Traveling</title><description>* On the Road Again: Eating Healthy While Traveling I am writing this post on a plane to Las Vegas for a speaking engagement. While healthy eating begins at home, being on the road is not excuse for letting it slip. As a busy professional myself, I know how hard it is to eat healthy while traveling. A...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:07:46">http://www.healthline.com/health/menopause/hot-flashes-travel</link><title>Dealing with Hot Flashes on the Road</title><description>* Dealing with Hot Flashes on the Road Hot flashes are an unavoidable and unpredictable part of menopause. They can come on anytime and anywhere. Since you can’t predict hot flashes, you might be faced with one when traveling – in your car, on an airplane or on the train. If you find your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:09:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/road-again-0</link><title>On the Road Again</title><description>* On the Road Again I’ve been racking up a lot of frequent flyer miles lately. I leave tonight for the Big Apple and will travel to Philly later this week. Healthy eating can be a challenge when traveling, but no matter what my day looks like, I rarely (I’m talking almo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>