<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:10:06" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:10:08">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/eye-burns</link><title>Eye burns | Symptom Search</title><description>* Eye burns | Symptom Search Health Topics Health Topics. Acid Reflux; Alcohol Addiction; Allergies; Alzheimer's &amp; Dementia; Anxiety; Asthma; Bipolar Disorder; Chronic Pain; Cold &amp; Flu; COPD; Crohn's Disease; Depression; Fibromyalgia; Heart Disease; Hypertension; Insomnia &amp; Slee...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:39">http://www.healthline.com/treatments/burns__</link><title>Burns Treatment : Treatment Search</title><description>* Burns Treatment : Treatment Search Learn about treatments, tests, and procedures for burns.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:17:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/diet-reviews</link><title>23 Diet Plans Reviewed: Do They Work?</title><description>* 23 Diet Plans Reviewed: Do They Work? From trendy fads to steady standbys, we've carefully studied and assessed popular diets for effectiveness and safety. Find out which diet is right for you.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:21:24">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/myths-of-dieting</link><title>7 Myths of Dieting</title><description>* 7 Myths of Dieting The 7 Myths of Dieting you need to know about, including the foods that supposedly burn fat, magic diet pills, eating after 8 PM, and more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:23:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/beauty-skin-care-tanning</link><title>5 Tanning Tips You Need to Know</title><description>* 5 Tanning Tips You Need to Know Until the advent of spray tanning and sunless tanning products, the phrase "healthy tan" was a bit of a contradiction in terms. Tanning with ultraviolet (UV) radiation, whether it comes from the sun or from an indoor tanning bed, is dangerous. Period...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:28:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/diet-and-weight-loss</link><title>Healthy Eating for Weight Loss</title><description>* Healthy Eating for Weight Loss With two-thirds of Americans either overweight or obese, weight is a concern for many people. Carrying excess body weight comes with increased risk of diseases such as diabetes, heart disease, some cancers, osteoarthritis, and sleep apnea. Losing wei...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:31:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/serum-ketones-test</link><title>Serum Ketones Test</title><description>* Serum Ketones Test ...Test A serum ketone test is an important test to determine the levels of a byproduct when your body burns fat. Ketones are produced when glucose (a form of sugar) isn’t available to supply the body’s cells with energy. This becomes a problem if your body...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:33:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/does-hyperbaric-treatment-heal-sprains</link><title>Does Hyperbaric Treatment Heal Sprains?</title><description>* Does Hyperbaric Treatment Heal Sprains? ...oxygen speeds healing in certain infections, crush injuries, problem wounds, diabetic ulcers, thermal burns, ionizing radiation injury, refractory osteomyelitis, osteoradionecrosis, and compromised grafts, it has been hoped by some that it would also...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:35:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/no-antibiotics-for-acute-bronchitis</link><title>No Antibiotics for Acute Bronchitis</title><description>* No Antibiotics for Acute Bronchitis ...without antibiotics, copious fluid intake, inhalation of humidified warm air (taking care to avoid steam burns) in order to loosen secretions and ease coughing, a drug to loosen secretions (e.g., guaifenesin [Mucinex] 600 mg by mouth every 12 hours),...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:36:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/exercise</link><title>Can Exercise Reverse or Prevent Heart Disease?</title><description>* Can Exercise Reverse or Prevent Heart Disease? What can you do to prevent or reverse heart disease? Studies indicate that pairing a healthy diet with regular exercise is the best way not only to prevent heart disease, but to reverse some risk factors. Is it necessary to pound the miles at the gym...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>