<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:57" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:58">http://www.healthline.com/treatments/depression__</link><title>Depression Treatment : Treatment Search</title><description>* Depression Treatment : Treatment Search Learn about treatments, tests, and procedures for depression.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:39:20">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-diet-raw-food</link><title>Raw food diet</title><description>* Raw food diet Diet, raw food Ceviche, microgreens, pure foods, raw foodism, raw foodist, raw food veganism, retention factors, vegetarian, wai diet. The raw foods diet is based entirely on the consumption of uncooked foods as a majority of an individual's entire n...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:41:38">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/peppermint</link><title>Peppermint (Mentha x piperita)</title><description>* Peppermint (Mentha x piperita) Mentha x piperita Menthol A-bourbonene, alpha-humulene, alpha-pinene, anisic acid, balm mint, beta-myrcene, beta-pinene, black mitchum, black peppermint, brandy mint, caffeic acid, camphor, carvone, chlorogenic acid, cineol, cobalt, coumarin, curled ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-04"><link>http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/jasmine</link><title>Jasmine (Jasminum spp.)</title><description>* Jasmine (Jasminum spp.) Jasminum spp. Catalonian jasmine, common jasmine, common white jasmine, Italian jasmine, jasmin, jasmine flower, Jasmini Flos, Jasminum, Jasminum grandiflorum, Jasminum officinale, jati, jessamine, mo li hua, pikake (Hawaiian), poet's jasmine, poet's...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:45:30">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/lemon-balm</link><title>Lemon balm (Melissa officinalis L.)</title><description>* Lemon balm (Melissa officinalis L.) Melissa officinalis Balm, balm mint, bee balm, blue balm, Citra, citronellae, citronmelisse, common balm, cure-all, dropsy plant, English balm, folia citronellae, folia melissae citratae, garden balm, gastrovegetalin, hjertensfryd, honey plant, kneip...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:04">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-medical-nutrition-therapy</link><title>Medical nutrition therapy</title><description>* Medical nutrition therapy Diet, dieticians, eating disorders, enteral feedings, MNT, nutritional therapy, parenteral feedings, tube feedings. Medical nutrition therapy (MNT) includes a wide variety of treatments based on the nutritional status of the patient. The intensity of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:55">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-nutrition-questionnaire</link><title>Nutrition questionnaire</title><description>* Nutrition questionnaire Fitness, food pyramid, nutrition worksheet, nutritionist. Nutrition is a concept that examines the relationship between what a person eats and their health. Nutrition is important because the body gets most of its nutrients from the foods that are ea...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:52:46">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/saccharomyces-boulardii</link><title>Saccharomyces boulardii</title><description>* Saccharomyces boulardii S. boulardii Brewer's yeast, Florastor®, Florastor® Kids, Hansen CBS 5926, Lactobacillus, Lactobacillus acidophilus, Lactobacillus bulgaricus, Lactobacillus gasseri, Lactobacillus GG, Lactobacillus plantarum, Perenterol®, probiotic, S. boulardii, Sac...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:54:08">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/rosemary</link><title>Rosemary (Rosmarinus officinalis)</title><description>* Rosemary (Rosmarinus officinalis) Rosmarinus officinalis Albus (cultivar), alecrim (Portuguese), alpha-pinene, Arp (cultivar), Aureus (cultivar), Benenden Blue (cultivar), biberiye (Turkish), Blue Boy (cultivar), borneol, bornyl acetate, caffeic acid, (-)-camphene, camphor, carnosic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:54:51">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/calamus</link><title>Calamus (Acorus calamus L.)</title><description>* Calamus (Acorus calamus L.) Sweetflag Acorus calamus L. Acoraceae (family), acorenone, Acori graminei rhizoma, acorone, Acorus calamus L., Acorus calamus L. essential oils, Acorus calamus Linn. var. angustatus Bess, Acorus calamus var. angustatus Bess, Acorus gramineus Sol. ex ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>