<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:21:05" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:21:06">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/iron</link><title>Iron (Fe)</title><description>* Iron (Fe) Fe Ferrous sulfate Ferrous gluconate Atomic number 26, carbonyl iron, dextran-iron, elemental iron, FE, Fer, ferric ammonium chloride, ferric chloride, ferric citrate, ferric phosphate, ferric pyrophosphate, ferric sodium pyrophosphate, ferric sulfat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:24:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/energy-boosting-foods</link><title>Top 10 Healthy Energy-Boosting Foods</title><description>* Top 10 Healthy Energy-Boosting Foods Nicole Moore, MS, RD, CNSC, LD, clinical dietitian at Georgia Health Sciences Medical Center, recommends these top 10 quick and easy foods that will get you going—and keep you going—all day long.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/superfood-prunes</link><title>Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Prunes</title><description>* Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Prunes Other vitamins and minerals: Prunes also contain iron, copper, calcium, vitamin K, potassium, and magnesium. What makes prunes the perfect snack? When that afternoon sugar low hits, it’s easy to grab something out of the vending machine to deliver that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:30:55">http://www.healthline.com/health/food-nutrition</link><title>Food &amp; Nutrition</title><description>* Food &amp; Nutrition For pregnant women and adults over 50, vitamins such as vitamin D and minerals such as calcium and iron are important to consider when choosing foods to eat, as well as possible dietary supplements. A healthy diet includes a lot of natural foods. A sizeable...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:33:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/grow-edible-gourmet-gardens</link><title>Create Your Own Gourmet Garden</title><description>* Create Your Own Gourmet Garden Transform your garden into a productive patch brimming with fresh, seasonal food. It’s healthy, cost-effective, and you’ll be amazed at how easy your favorite fruit and veggies are to grow. Even the tiniest plot is enough to get started.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:35:54">http://www.healthline.com/health/pregnancy/diet-nutrition</link><title>Healthy Diet During Pregnancy</title><description>* Healthy Diet During Pregnancy Since many women don't get enough iron in their diet, iron is an important part of prenatal supplements. Iron is often poorly absorbed from foods, which is why it is difficult for many people to reach the proper requirement. For example, while many vegetables...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:38:27">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/planning-food-wilderness-expeditions</link><title>Planning Food for Wilderness Expeditions</title><description>* Planning Food for Wilderness Expeditions ...Carbohydrate (g) 440 Fat (g) 160 Vitamin A (RE) 1000 Vitamin C (mg) 60 Vitamin E (mg) 10 Calcium (mg) 800 Iron (mg) 18 Sodium (mg) 5000-7000 Fiber (g) 20-35 Finally, consider the following recipe for energy bars. This is one way to prepare less expensive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:42:14">http://www.healthline.com/health/eye-emergencies</link><title>Eye Emergencies</title><description>* Eye Emergencies What Is an Eye Emergency? An eye emergency occurs anytime you have a foreign object or chemicals in your eye, or when an injury or burn affects your eye area. Remember you should seek medical attention if you ever experience swelling, redness, or pai...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:45:01">http://www.healthline.com/health/lead-poisoning</link><title>Lead Poisoning</title><description>* Lead Poisoning Additional tests could include blood tests to look at the amount of iron storing cells in the blood, X rays and possibly a bone marrow biopsy. How Is Lead Poisoning Treated? The first step of treatment is to locate and remove the source of the lead. Keep...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:46:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/mountain-climbing-safety</link><title>Climbing High</title><description>* Climbing High People who are prone to anemia may want to consider taking an iron supplement before and during travel to high altitudes. Since oxygen is transported in red blood cells, and anemia causes a lowered red blood cell count, persons with anemia are more likely...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>