<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7100">korean bbq san francisco review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:51:47" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7100-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7100_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:51:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/fevers-chills-5-blankets-oh-my</link><title>Fevers, Chills, 5 Blankets, Oh My!</title><description>* Fevers, Chills, 5 Blankets, Oh My! 20 hours on a plane is no fun. 20 hours of fevers &amp; chills on a plane squished into economy class is even less fun. Thank goodness I had a narcotic cough suppressant to keep from hacking on my fellow sufferers, but the fever made me delirious. I ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7100-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7100_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:54:16">http://www.healthline.com/health/medical-board</link><title>Healthline Medical Review and Advisory Board</title><description>* Healthline Medical Review and Advisory Board Medical Review BoardGeorge Krucik, MD, MBAGeorge rejoined Healthline in 2011, and is responsible for reviewing content and clinical applications on Healthline.com and partner websites for medical accuracy and relevance. Also, he works closely with th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7100-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7100_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:57:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/its-a-type-2-life/10-nifty-diabetes-apps</link><title>10 Nifty Diabetes Apps</title><description>* 10 Nifty Diabetes Apps In 1987 I was researching an article about a young man who was making big waves in San Francisco commercial real estate. One day as I was interviewing him he asked me to accompany him on a walk to a client’s office several blocks away. He was one of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7100-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7100_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:59:53">http://www.healthline.com/health/staff</link><title>The Healthline Editorial Team</title><description>* The Healthline Editorial Team George Krucik—Director, Clinical ContentGeorge rejoined Healthline in 2011, and is responsible for reviewing content and clinical applications on Healthline.com and partner websites for medical accuracy and relevance. Also, he works closely with the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7100-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7100_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:02:39">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/sidestream-cigarette-smoke-more-toxic-mainstream-smoke</link><title>Sidestream cigarette smoke more toxic than mainstream smoke</title><description>* Sidestream cigarette smoke more toxic than mainstream smoke In my last post about tobacco smoke pollution I mentioned the puzzling fact that although exposure to tobacco smoke pollution (TSP or ETS or SHS) gives about 1-5% of the smoke dose of active smoking, it gives a proportionately bigger increase in some...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>