<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:32:48" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:32:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/mental-controversial-law-saves-money-by-mandating-care-073013</link><title>Controversial Mental Health Law Saves New York Money</title><description>* Controversial Mental Health Law Saves New York Money A new study shows Kendra’s Law saves the state money by decreasing hospitalizations and increasing outpatient services for the seriously mentally ill.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:36:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/how-have-new-york-and-new-jersey-reduced-smoking</link><title>How have New York and New Jersey reduced smoking?</title><description>* How have New York and New Jersey reduced smoking? From 1992-2002 cigarette smoking prevalence in New York City remained relatively stable, with around 21-22% of adults being smokers. However, in 2002 the city began to implement a comprehensive five-point tobacco control plan, as follows:1. Increased...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:38:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/new-york-soda-tax</link><title>New York City Proposes Soda Tax</title><description>* New York City Proposes Soda Tax I blogged yesterday about how New York City is leading the country by legislating changes in restaurants and food companies to improve the health of it's citizens. They have banned trans fat, required calories to be listed on menus, started advertisi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:42:27">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/links-decoding-your-health-new-york-times</link><title>Links from "Decoding Your Health" from The New York Times</title><description>* Links from "Decoding Your Health" from The New York Times Image by Ethan Bloch via FlickrThe New York Times recently published a special section on "Decoding your Health" focusing on health resources online. The following are selected links from this section as well as other recent health-related articles.Y...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:12">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/cancer-treatment-survivorship/free-set-papers-cancer-new-york-times</link><title>Free Set of Papers On Cancer From New York Times</title><description>* Free Set of Papers On Cancer From New York Times As I was searching for more new information on cancer and resources for us all to share I stumbled on an exciting free piece of information. The New York Times is releasing A free collection of articles about cancer published in The New York Times on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:45:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/conference-aging-dec-2-2006-midtown-new-york</link><title>Conference on Aging Dec 2, 2006 in Midtown New York</title><description>* Conference on Aging Dec 2, 2006 in Midtown New York The Greater New York Chapter of the American College of Sports Medicine (ACSM) will hold a conference on aging on Saturday, December 2nd, 2006 at the Flatotel, 135 W. 52nd Street between 6th &amp; 7th Avenue, in New York City.In one fast moving day, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:46:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/new-york-lower-salt-content</link><title>New York City To Lower Salt Content in Restaurant Foods</title><description>* New York City To Lower Salt Content in Restaurant Foods First Mayor Michael Bloomberg banned smoking in bars and restaurants in New York City (NYC). Then he removed trans fat and required restaurants to post calories on menu boards. He has encouraged the NYC health department to start ad campaigns against...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:48:18">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-battles-over-restaurant-worker-sick-leave-play-out-in-cities-and-states-070113</link><title>More People Falling Ill as Lawmakers Battle Over Paid Sick Leave</title><description>* More People Falling Ill as Lawmakers Battle Over Paid Sick Leave Florida and New York City are the latest battlegrounds in the fight between workers and the food service industry over mandated sick pay.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:49:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/unvaccinated-children-kindling-in-measles-outbreaks-040214</link><title>Study: Unvaccinated Children Are 'Kindling' for Outbreaks</title><description>* Study: Unvaccinated Children Are 'Kindling' for Outbreaks Using disease outbreaks in the wild as a model, researchers show that seasonal birth rates and kids' vaccination schedules could impact outbreaks of measles.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:54:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/pouring-pounds</link><title>Pouring on the Pounds?</title><description>* Pouring on the Pounds? The city of New York is at it again...they were the first to ban trans fat and lead the fight for restaurant labeling of calories on menus. Now they have an ad campaign that is grossing some people out.The picture above is of a glass of soda being po...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>