<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:58:52" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:58:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/summary-health-statistics-us-children-national-health-interview-surve</link><title>Summary Health Statistics for U.S. Children: National Health Interview Survey, 2006</title><description>* Summary Health Statistics for U.S. Children: National Health Interview Survey, 2006 The latest report from the National Health Interview Survey (NHIS) presents selected health measures for children under 18 years of age, by sex, age, race, family structure, parent education, family income, poverty status, health insurance coverage, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:01:07">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/how-your-hair-stylist-can-keep-you-healthy</link><title>How Your Hair Stylist Can Keep You Healthy</title><description>* How Your Hair Stylist Can Keep You Healthy I, for one, love the feel of an expert stylist massaging my scalp. There aren’t many people I’ll let near my head, but at the hands of a pro, I turn to mush. Who doesn’t appreciate some good pampering every now and then? But can my hair stylist help ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:01:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/eating-disorder-support-web</link><title>Eating Disorder Support on the Web</title><description>* Eating Disorder Support on the Web Parents beware! According to researchers who surveyed the Internet viewing habits of 76 patients diagnosed with eating disorders, there are Internet Web sites that promote anorexia and bulimia as acceptable and even desirable life styles. Adolescents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:05:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/teen-marijuana-use</link><title>Teen Marijuana Use</title><description>* Teen Marijuana Use I know that there is a huge disagreement about whether marijuana is harmful or not, but the National Institute on Drug Abuse presents a pretty scary picture, which I thought I should share with parents of teens.Addiction is a disease that usually beg...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:09:14">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd</link><title>ADHD Basics</title><description>* ADHD Basics Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a mental disorder that causes above-normal levels of hyperactive and disruptive behaviors. People with ADHD tend to have difficulty concentrating, sitting still, paying attention, staying organized, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:14:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/snus-use-norway</link><title>Snus use in Norway.</title><description>* Snus use in Norway. Snus is a form of smokeless tobacco that is widely used – primarily by men – in Sweden. It is characterized by being relatively low in toxins but delivers about as much nicotine as a cigarette. It is not harmless (causes gum erosion, and pancreatic c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:17:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/health-benefits-of-owning-a-pet</link><title>7 Ways Your Pets Keep You Healthy</title><description>* 7 Ways Your Pets Keep You Healthy Pets may drive you nuts sometimes, but they do a lot to keep you well. Learn about the health benefits of owning a pet, including improved blood pressure, lower cholesterol, better mood, and higher brain function.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:21:53">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/adhd-symptoms-in-girls-and-boys</link><title>Gender Differences in ADHD Symptoms</title><description>* Gender Differences in ADHD Symptoms ADHD is one of the most common disorders diagnosed in children. Children show signs of this disorder before age seven, though some with ADHD remain undiagnosed until adulthood. There are significant differences in how the condition manifests in boys ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:24:48">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/gay</link><title>Depression and Sexual Orientation</title><description>* Depression and Sexual Orientation Each year, seven percent of Americans suffer from mood disorders such as depression. Depression is the leading cause of disability and the second leading cause of years of life lost due to premature death in the world. Major depressive disorders are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:25:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-sex-tips</link><title>Have Better Sex</title><description>* Have Better Sex Want to improve your sex life? Looking to better understand your (and your partner’s) needs? Here are some easy ways to physically and emotionally enhance your sexual expression. 1. Understand and learn to communicate your sexual needs. Communication...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>