<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:29:46" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:29:49">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/binge-eating</link><title>Binge eating | Symptom Search</title><description>* Binge eating | Symptom Search Health Topics Health Topics. Acid Reflux; Alcohol Addiction; Allergies; Alzheimer's &amp; Dementia; Anxiety; Asthma; Bipolar Disorder; Chronic Pain; Cold &amp; Flu; COPD; Crohn's Disease; Depression; Fibromyalgia; Heart Disease; Hypertension; Insomnia &amp; Slee...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:31:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/eat-light-eat-often</link><title>Eat Light, Eat Often</title><description>* Eat Light, Eat Often Energy and performance are very important in my day-to-day work. In order to be an efficient full-time worker and full-time mom, I need to make sure I’m at the top of my game to provide the best for my family. For many people, the first go-to energy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:32:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/silent-enamel-eating-syndrome-watch-what-you-eat</link><title>Silent Enamel Eating Syndrome: Watch What You Eat</title><description>* Silent Enamel Eating Syndrome: Watch What You Eat If it's eating away your tooth enamel, what is doing to the rest of you? Whatever it is, it can't be good. Dental erosion, the loss of the protective enamel coating on the teeth, is on the rise, according to Professor Amaechi at the University of Tex...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:34:16">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/few-less-bites</link><title>A Few Less Bites</title><description>* A Few Less Bites Could you leave these two bites of sandwich behind?My best friend in college was one of those people who hardly ever finished her plate. She was a cute, petite, blonde, blue-eyed girl (still is!) and she just naturally would stop when she had enough ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:37:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/food-journals</link><title>Want to Lose Twice as Much Weight?</title><description>* Want to Lose Twice as Much Weight? I knew I’d get your attention with that headline. Am I selling a “magic” cream or pill? Nope! Just old fashioned accountability in the form of: a food journal. Simply keeping track of everything you eat within a day can open your eyes to unhealthy ea...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:39:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/pot-luck</link><title>Pot Luck</title><description>* Pot Luck Do you go to Potluck parties? I went to one last night and had a fabulous time! Some people hate pot luck's because they don't know who made what and what is in anything they are eating. I love the mystery and excitement of not knowing if I will love...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-07"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/diabetes-pregnancy-7-self-monitoring-blood-glucose-levels</link><title>Diabetes in Pregnancy - 7 - Self-Monitoring of Blood Glucose Levels</title><description>* Diabetes in Pregnancy - 7 - Self-Monitoring of Blood Glucose Levels After discussing the basics and importance of diet, the next step in counseling for the newly diagnosed woman with gestational diabetes mellitus (GDM) revolves around the means of assessing her ‘diabetic control’. The mainstay of management is freque...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:47:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/pre-and-post-gym-eats</link><title>Pre- and Post-Gym Eats</title><description>* Pre- and Post-Gym Eats A healthy lifestyle combines physical activity with a balanced diet. The effectiveness of a workout doesn't just depend on what you eat, but when you eat it. Make your workout work for you--learn what to eat before and after you hit the gym. Before t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:48:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/eating-speed-weight-gain</link><title>Slow Down: Your Eating Speed Helps Determine Your Weight</title><description>* Slow Down: Your Eating Speed Helps Determine Your Weight I’ve always been a fast eater, but I didn’t find out until college. There I was, sitting in the cafeteria staring at my empty tray of food and all my new friends were just starting in on their food. I guess those 18-minute lunch periods in high schoo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:51:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/night-noshing</link><title>Night Noshing</title><description>* Night Noshing Do you wish you could sleep like Sleeping Beauty? Instead, do you wake up often throughout the night and the only thing that will get you back to sleep is a visit to Ben and Jerry?How often do you eat in the middle of the night? I am not talking abou...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>