<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:57:16" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:57:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/links-interest</link><title>Links of Interest</title><description>* Links of Interest Image via WikipediaThe following posts on the web recently caught my attention.Clinical Cases and Images -- which contains a wealth of resources for technology in medicine -- posted 5 tips to stay up to date with the medical literature (click the lin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:59:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/how-find-your-inner-athlete</link><title>How to Find Your Inner Athlete</title><description>* How to Find Your Inner Athlete Elite athletes thrive on challenge and competition. They approach their training physically prepared and mentally in the zone, and are committed to realizing their full potential. The same principles that guide an athlete’s training can be applied to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:01:08">http://www.healthline.com/health/addiction-incorporated-movie</link><title>The Healthline Interview: Victor DeNoble and Charles Evans Jr.</title><description>* The Healthline Interview: Victor DeNoble and Charles Evans Jr. In 1979 an enthusiastic young scientist named Victor DeNoble was recruited by Phillip Morris to develop a “safer” cigarette, one that would reduce smoking’s harmful effects on the heart. He succeeded. In the process he discovered that cigarettes are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:05:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/aplastic-anemia-and-mds-clinical-trials</link><title>Aplastic Anemia and MDS: Clinical Trials</title><description>* Aplastic Anemia and MDS: Clinical Trials ...to develop effective prevention, treatment and diagnostic protocols for diseases but have difficulty recruiting minorities. Research on this problem itself has revealed that doctors do not discuss the availability of clinical trials with their minority...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:09:49">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/new-study-shows-longer-duration-nicotine-replacement-leads-better-qui</link><title>New study shows that longer duration nicotine replacement leads to better quit rates</title><description>* New study shows that longer duration nicotine replacement leads to better quit rates A new study was published in Annals of Internal Medicine this week, showing that having access to nicotine patches for 24 weeks leads to higher quit rates at 24 weeks (32%) that using the patch for the more typical duration (8 weeks), which led to on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:12:14">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/subjects-invited-immersion-pulmonary-edema-study</link><title>Subjects Invited for Immersion Pulmonary Edema Study</title><description>* Subjects Invited for Immersion Pulmonary Edema Study They are recruiting experimental subjects who have experienced immersion pulmonary edema to participate in studies to investigate causes of this condition. The studies concentrate on effects of cold-water facial and body immersion on pulmonary arterial...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:13:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/obesity-national-security</link><title>Obesity: a Threat to Our National Security?</title><description>* Obesity: a Threat to Our National Security? Linking obesity to our national security may seem like a stretch, but the latest report from the Trust for America’s Health and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation makes it clear that the problem is as serious as a heart attack. The124-page report, “F...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:14:44">http://www.healthline.com/health/staff</link><title>The Healthline Editorial Team</title><description>* The Healthline Editorial Team George Krucik—Director, Clinical ContentGeorge rejoined Healthline in 2011, and is responsible for reviewing content and clinical applications on Healthline.com and partner websites for medical accuracy and relevance. Also, he works closely with the ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>