<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7116">pumpkin pie recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:31:25" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:31:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/oats</link><title>Got Oats?</title><description>* Got Oats? pumpkin pie spiceMakes 2-3 servings *recipe from SHAPE magazine Preparation:Make pancakes on a prepared hot griddle as you would any other pancake recipe! The combination of dietary fiber and protein make this power meal great for breakfast, lunch, or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:34:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/planning-thanksgiving-menu</link><title>Planning Thanksgiving Menu</title><description>* Planning Thanksgiving Menu Many of you will be sitting down and planning your Thanksgiving menu and shopping for those yummy treats. Here are some ideas to make things a bit healthier!Turkey: There are so many options out there. If you aren't into cooking the entire bird, simp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:36:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/pumpkin-power</link><title>Pumpkin Power!</title><description>* Pumpkin Power! Talking about Halloween yesterday put me in the mood for one of my favorite fall flavors - pumpkin. Pumpkins aren't only "gourd-eous" (hee-hee), they're nutrition powerhouses - and they don't even need to be fresh.I call this smoothie "liquid pumpkin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:38:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/recipe-week-pumpkin-pudding</link><title>Recipe of the Week: Pumpkin Pudding</title><description>* Recipe of the Week: Pumpkin Pudding It's still the time of year for pumpkins and you may be surprised how highly nutritious they are. They are loaded with beta-carotene (gives them their bright orange flesh) and are an excellent source of potassium, iron and fiber; key nutrients that w...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:39:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/november-is-peanut-butter-lovers-month</link><title>November is Peanut Butter Lovers Month</title><description>* November is Peanut Butter Lovers Month How do you like your peanut butter? Smeared on a sandwich with jelly, as a topping for apple slices, or plain right out of the jar? I agree, it’s finger licking good. My favorite? A spoonful dunked in a hot bowl of oatmeal. When it melts, it makes th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:43:54">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/a-tribute-to-oatmeal</link><title>A Tribute to Oatmeal</title><description>* A Tribute to Oatmeal This past Monday marked National Oatmeal day, and what’s a better way to celebrate than a warm bowl of oats in the morning? Growing up I’d have instant oatmeal in the car ride to school. My mom wasn’t a huge fan of oatmeal, or so she thought, and the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:47:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies/allergy-free-coffee-cake</link><title>Allergy-Free Apple Spice Coffee Cake</title><description>* Allergy-Free Apple Spice Coffee Cake Chia seeds make a great substitute for eggs in baked goods. When soaked in water they form a “gel” that is similar to eggs in both texture and binding ability. If you don’t have an 8-inch cast iron skillet you can use an 8-inch baking pan but you’ll ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:48:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/underindulging-thanksgiving</link><title>Underindulging on Thanksgiving</title><description>* Underindulging on Thanksgiving I must apologize for not getting any recipes to you for vegetarian entrees but I was plagued with a debilitating migraine Monday and Tuesday and I think I've missed the boat. I promise to post some in time for Christmas feasts.What I want to do today...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:51:36">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/turkey-day</link><title>Turkey Day</title><description>* Turkey Day With such a momentous food-related holiday this week, I feel compelled to write something about Thanksgiving. No one ever likes to have a dietitian around on the one day of the year when it is definite you will overeat. I agree!For Thanksgiving Day, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7116-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7116_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:56:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/happy-thanksgiving</link><title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title><description>* Happy Thanksgiving! Ok, here’s part 2 of how to enjoy a safe holiday meal. These 5 simple tips can make a world of difference in keeping you and your family healthy: -After your meal, don’t leave any perishable foods out on the counter top or table for over 2 hours (pre...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>