<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:59:05" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:59:06">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/worst-cities-for-allergies</link><title>Worst Cities for Allergies in 2013</title><description>* Worst Cities for Allergies in 2013 Here are the results from this year’s top seven worst cities for allergies. Click through the slideshow to learn where not to go if you’re sneezing and wheezing!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:02:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/commute-making-fat</link><title>Your Daily Commute Could Be Making You Fat</title><description>* Your Daily Commute Could Be Making You Fat City life isn’t for everyone, but for many, that’s where the work is. In Dallas, Texas, where I live, it’s not unusual for folks to drive 50 miles or more each morning from their quiet homes out in the country to the frenzied bustle of downtown Dalla...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:06:24">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/early-test-marketing-snus-united-states</link><title>Early test-marketing of snus in the United States.</title><description>* Early test-marketing of snus in the United States. Snus is a relatively new smokeless tobacco product in the United States, and is modeled after the Swedish moist snuff product that is heat-treated rather than fermented, resulting in lower concentrations of certain toxins, (carcinogenic tobacco-speci...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:09:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/healthy-places</link><title>Best Places to Visit for a Healthier You</title><description>* Best Places to Visit for a Healthier You Getting away doesn’t mean abandoning all of your healthy habits. These travel destinations make it easy to incorporate health and wellness into your vacation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:10:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/ill-have-one-everything</link><title>I'll Have One of Everything</title><description>* I'll Have One of Everything Hello from Dallas, Texas!I'm here to speak at a conference, and I read an interesting fact on the plane. Dallas has 4 times more restaurants per person than New York City. Surprised? Me too, especially since I used to live here. I mean, I knew there ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>