<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:13:49" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:13:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/health-chocolate</link><title>Health By Chocolate</title><description>* Health By Chocolate If you are a chocolate lover like me, I am sure you have heard the news about chocolate being good for you. Is it true or is this just another one of those foods that is good for us one day only to be found bad for us another day? Chocolate comes from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:14:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/happy-valentines-day</link><title>Happy Valentine's Day</title><description>* Happy Valentine's Day Valentine's Day! I personally love chocolate (hint, hint to my husband), and just in case you may be getting some chocolate from your sweetheart, I thought I would remind you of the health benefits of chocolate.Have a wonderful day with your sweetie!I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:17:19">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/hug-tree-its-trails-advocacy-week-february-11-14</link><title>Hug a Tree? It's Trails Advocacy Week February 11-14</title><description>* Hug a Tree? It's Trails Advocacy Week February 11-14 Forget chocolates and (blood) diamonds. Take a hike with your loved ones for Valentine's Day. The American Hiking Society celebrates Trails Advocacy Week and if you don't have a favorite trail, this week is good time to discover one. Click on the map...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:19:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/preteen-pms-what-parent-do</link><title>Preteen PMS - What is a Parent To Do?</title><description>* Preteen PMS - What is a Parent To Do? Coping strategies my own daughters liked included chocolate, the one-use heating pads that you wrap around your belly, and you can even try Midol (if there is no contraindication to diuretic use) even if they are not having a period. For the parent, when...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:22:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/go-nuts-gifts-year</link><title>Go Nuts with Gifts This Year</title><description>* Go Nuts with Gifts This Year And last but not least chocolate. Who would have thought chocolate would become a leading health food but it has! Studies have found that dark chocolate contains substances that help relax blood vessels, lowering blood pressure, and it has also been linked...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>