<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:24:30" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:24:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/who-says-male-circumcision-should-be-part-hiv-prevention</link><title>WHO says: Male circumcision should be part of HIV prevention</title><description>* WHO says: Male circumcision should be part of HIV prevention The World Health Organization (WHO) has announced that based on studies in Kenya, Uganda and South Africa, male circumcision reduces the risk of heterosexually transmitted HIV infection in men by 60%. Surprisingly, only 30% of men worldwide are estimated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:27:52">http://www.healthline.com/health/hepatitis-b</link><title>Hepatitis B</title><description>* Hepatitis B The World Health Organization (WHO) states that 25 percent of adults who develop hepatitis B during childhood will later die from complications (WHO). Hepatitis B is the most common form of hepatitis in Asia. Symptoms of Hepatitis B Symptoms of HBV may...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:30:05">http://www.healthline.com/health/menopause/male</link><title>What is Male Menopause?</title><description>* What is Male Menopause? While the World Health Organization (WHO) doesn’t recognize male menopause as a condition, about five million American men don’t produce adequate levels of testosterone. Symptoms of Male Menopause Male menopause can cause physical, sexual, and psychological...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:30:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/tobacco-harm-reduction</link><title>Tobacco Harm Reduction</title><description>* Tobacco Harm Reduction Perhaps the main hope for improving this situation is via implementation of the World Health organization’s Framework Convention on Tobacco Control (FCTC). Details on the FCTC can be found at;http://www.who.int/tobacco/framework/en/There have also been...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:33:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/hold-that-pause/estrogen-new-comeback-kid</link><title>Estrogen: The New Come-Back Kid</title><description>* Estrogen: The New Come-Back Kid I’m not sure if you’ve noticed or not, but there is a shift going on in the field of women’s health. Specifically, in the field of hormone health. The shift is back toward estrogen therapy for the symptoms of perimenopause and menopause. In spite of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:36:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/healthy-food-imposters</link><title>Healthy Food Imposters</title><description>* Healthy Food Imposters Have you ever eaten a food because you thought it was super healthy? Make sure you look carefully at everything you eat and don’t be fooled by deceptive advertising! A few of our favorite foods may have been branded as nourishing, when in reality the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7121-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7121_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:37:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/charles-houston-remembered</link><title>Charles Houston Remembered</title><description>* Charles Houston Remembered In the field of wilderness medicine, I have had many mentors. One of the first, and in many ways the most important to me, was Dr. Charles Houston, who died on Sunday, September 27, 2009 in Burlington, Vermont at the age of 96. Many of us are indebte...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>