<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:01:04" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:01:05">http://www.healthline.com/health/talking-your-child-about-obesity</link><title>Talking to Your Child about Obesity</title><description>* Talking to Your Child about Obesity The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) report that childhood obesity has tripled over the past three decades. Obese children carry a higher risk than children of normal weight for: cardiovascular disease, bone and joint problems, sleep apnea,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:39">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/obesity-rising-among-asian-children</link><title>Obesity Rising Among Asian Children</title><description>* Obesity Rising Among Asian Children Obesity (having a BMI above the 95th percentile) is associated with other health problems including heart disease, strokes and Type 2 Diabetes, making obesity a serious concern for most parents. Until recently, Asian children were the least likely to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:06:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/selling-food-children-why-obesity-problem</link><title>Selling Food to Children: Why is Obesity a Problem?</title><description>* Selling Food to Children: Why is Obesity a Problem? Here is an assignment for you - watch TV with your tween one day and count the food advertisements - a recent study suggests you will see about 21 a day, and 34% of them will be advertising candy or snacks, 28% will be for cereal, and 10% will be for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:10:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/new-research-childrens-obesity-risk</link><title>New Research on Children's Obesity Risk</title><description>* New Research on Children's Obesity Risk Two new studies I saw this week peaked my interest. One study was in the June issue of the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition and showed that women who gained too much weight during pregnancy may increase their children's risk of becoming overwei...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:12:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/bad-news-about-summer-vacation-obese-children</link><title>Bad News about Summer Vacation for Obese Children</title><description>* Bad News about Summer Vacation for Obese Children A recent study published in the Archives of Pediatrics &amp; Adolescent Medicine (June 2007) suggested that for obese middle-school children, school-based fitness interventions are an important part of their overall fitness. In fact, the extended sum...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:14:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/new-slightly-revamped-recs-fight-child-and-youth-obesity</link><title>New Slightly Revamped Recs to Fight Child and Youth Obesity</title><description>* New Slightly Revamped Recs to Fight Child and Youth Obesity More official recommendations to treat and prevent childhood obesity that are pretty much similar to all other official governing bodies' recs. That's not a bad thing. It continues to reinforce the messages to parents, pediatricians and communities in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/severe-childhood-obesity-on-the-rise-040714</link><title>Severe Obesity Is on the Rise in U.S. Children</title><description>* Severe Obesity Is on the Rise in U.S. Children A new study spanning more than 10 years shows that severe childhood obesity is skyrocketing, amid earlier reports to the contrary.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:18:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/child-breastfeeding-longer-does-not-reduce-obesity-risk-031213</link><title>Breastfeeding for Longer Doesn't Reduce a Child's Risk of Obesity</title><description>* Breastfeeding for Longer Doesn't Reduce a Child's Risk of Obesity New research challenges the idea that breastfeeding can reduce a child's risk of obesity later in life.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:22:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/women-weight-gain-during-pregnancy-tied-to-childhood-obesity-100113</link><title>Overeating During Pregnancy Predicts a Lifetime of Obesity for Children</title><description>* Overeating During Pregnancy Predicts a Lifetime of Obesity for Children If a mother puts on too much weight during pregnancy, it increases the chances that her child will be overweight at age 12, new research shows.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:23:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/children-can-appetite-and-satiety-response-predict-obesity-021814</link><title>How Children Respond to Feeling Full May Help Predict Future Obesity</title><description>* How Children Respond to Feeling Full May Help Predict Future Obesity Scientists explore risk factors for childhood obesity to learn what makes some children gain more weight than others.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>