<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7126">alicia keys brand new me lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:25:11" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7126-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7126_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:25:12">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthline-interview-jeanne-tripplehorn</link><title>The Healthline Interview: Jeanne Tripplehorn</title><description>* The Healthline Interview: Jeanne Tripplehorn After actress Jeanne Tripplehorn accepted the role of Pearl, an oncologist treating a series of breast cancer patients in the new Lifetime original movie “Five”—featuring a handful of moving vignettes about breast cancer directed by the likes of Demi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7126-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7126_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:30:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/your-kids-and-investing</link><title>Your Kids and Investing</title><description>* Your Kids and Investing Have them identify a brand or company they are familiar with and buy even one share of that stock, and help your children chart the earnings or loses of that stock, over time. He also suggests family members give stock instead of savings bonds to kids...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7126-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7126_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:34:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/fda-regulation-tobacco-what-does-it-mean</link><title>FDA Regulation of Tobacco: What Does it Mean?</title><description>* FDA Regulation of Tobacco: What Does it Mean? Section 904 mandates that FDA will receive brand-specific information on ingredients, nicotine delivery, and any smoke constituent FDA identifies as harmful or potentially harmful- Companies must also provide FDA with all documents developed after the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7126-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7126_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:36:28">http://www.healthline.com/health/how-make-new-friends-and-get-men-cook-you</link><title>How to Make New Friends (and Get Men to Cook for You)</title><description>* How to Make New Friends (and Get Men to Cook for You) My brand new roommate, who shares my passion for cooking, offered to help me cook down my pumpkins so I could freeze them and use them when I got back from the holiday break. Several hours, mild carpel tunnel syndrome, and massive amounts of pumpkin puree...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7126-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7126_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:38:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/obesity-diabetes-alzheimers</link><title>Obesity, Diabetes, and Alzheimer’s Disease: Is There a Link?</title><description>* Obesity, Diabetes, and Alzheimer’s Disease: Is There a Link? This isn’t a brand new discovery. As far back as 2005, researchers were suggesting that Alzheimer’s was a form of diabetes—that was the year when insulin-like growths were found in the brains of people who died of Alzheimer’s. Another clue into the Alzeheimer’s-insulin...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>