<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:40:50" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:40:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/tar-skin</link><title>Tar on the Skin</title><description>* Tar on the Skin Even though its really cold outside in much of the U.S., it's sunny in northern California and with a hooded sweatshirt, every day is a beach day! So, after a couple of nice days in the snowy mountains, I headed for the coast. On my first step onto t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:44:15">http://www.healthline.com/health/bike-sharing-programs-are-shaking-inner-city-transportation</link><title>Bike Sharing Programs Are Shaking Up Inner City Travel</title><description>* Bike Sharing Programs Are Shaking Up Inner City Travel Whether you are looking to lessen your carbon footprint, drop a few pounds, or avoid rush hour traffic, riding a bicycle is a great way to spice up your daily commute. For those who don’t own a bicycle, bike sharing programs are popping up across the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:45:23">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/lifeguard-situation-california</link><title>Lifeguard Situation in California</title><description>* Lifeguard Situation in California Here's a recent communication that originated with the Orange County (California) Register: Wednesday, April 9, 2008State lifeguard funding gets a reprieve. Public safety mandates staffing.By FRED SWEGLESThe Orange County RegisterLifeguard service at...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:46:45">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/psoriasis-friendly-vacation-spots</link><title>Top 7 Psoriasis-Friendly Vacation Spots</title><description>* Top 7 Psoriasis-Friendly Vacation Spots A vacation can help ease your mind—and symptoms of psoriasis. Learn about skin-soothing vacation spots all around the world, from Florida to France.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:50:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/mermaid-stories</link><title>The Mermaid Stories</title><description>* The Mermaid Stories "Are you a real mermaid?" asked 6-year-old Claire. Readers have been asking about skin and scuba diving, training for triathlon swims and breath hold diving, getting in shape for beach lifeguarding, science of swimming, Navy undersea maneuvers, and m...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:55:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/ozone-and-outdoors</link><title>Ozone and the Outdoors</title><description>* Ozone and the Outdoors Here's an interesting news item (within the quotation marks) that was recently brought to my attention:"Content provided by Reuters on April 22, 2008WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Even breathing in a little ozone at levels found in many areas is likely to ki...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>