<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:02:15" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:02:16">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/home-blood-pressure-monitoring</link><title>Home Blood Pressure Monitoring</title><description>* Home Blood Pressure Monitoring When you visit your doctor, it’s nearly a sure bet that you’ll have your blood pressure measured. A high blood pressure reading usually means that you have hypertension, but sometimes the problem is all in your head. The term “white coat hypertension...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:03:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/caring-for-caregivers</link><title>Caring for the Caregivers</title><description>* Caring for the Caregivers In my practice of cardiology, I take care of many elderly men and women. As they age, the spouse often becomes responsible for his or her partner’s day to day well-being. The strain of this unending, often emotionally wrenching, and physically burden...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:06:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/improvised-medicine-book-review</link><title>Improvised Medicine</title><description>* Improvised Medicine "Improvised Medicine" by Dr. Kenneth IsersonImprovised Medicine, subtitled Providing Care in Extreme Environments, a new book (McGraw Hill Medical; $54 U.S.) by Dr. Kenneth V. Iserson, is intended for health care practitioners who will “ope...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:08:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/cancer-treatment-survivorship/welcome-survivorship-blog</link><title>Welcome to the Survivorship Blog</title><description>* Welcome to the Survivorship Blog Hello, my name is Cyndy. I have been a nurse for almost 3 decades. I love being a nurse. In my years as a nurse I have worked with individuals with cancer and their caregivers/family/friends in various settings (hospitals, clinics, doctors offices, h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:10:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/balanced-breakfast-key-success</link><title>Balanced Breakfasts Are Key to Success</title><description>* Balanced Breakfasts Are Key to Success Do you struggle to get a nutritious breakfast for yourself or your family daily? Too little time? Not hungry? Whatever the reason may be, everyone needs this meal. Breakfast is the most important meal of the day (ever heard that one before?) as it re...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:13:19">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/students-balances-listens-fixes-fathers-back-pain</link><title>Students Balances, Listens, Fixes Father's Back Pain</title><description>* Students Balances, Listens, Fixes Father's Back Pain My student Ginger sent the photo at right taken on her recent camping trip. Don't try this at home. It takes balance training, concentration, and a few changes to standard back bend technique.Ginger is distributing the stretch along the spine so that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:16:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/smoking-breast-cancer-risk</link><title>More Bad News for Smokers: Breast Cancer Risk Rises</title><description>* More Bad News for Smokers: Breast Cancer Risk Rises I am always looking for new angles to use to help my patients to quit smoking. Each year, more than 430,000 Americans die from tobacco-related illness, including heart disease and stroke. Smoking even one cigarette each day raises the heart attack ri...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:20:56">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/childhood-obesity-not-life-sentence</link><title>Childhood Obesity: It Doesn’t Have To Be A Life Sentence</title><description>* Childhood Obesity: It Doesn’t Have To Be A Life Sentence Childhood obesity is an unnatural disaster of literally epic proportions. In years past, it was rare to see an overweight child. Most meals were eaten at home, fast food was considered an occasional treat, and kids were expected to play outdoors when...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:23:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/menopause-corner/picks-best-books-menopause</link><title>My Picks for The Best Books On Menopause</title><description>* My Picks for The Best Books On Menopause My home library is crammed with books, CDs and subscription newsletters about women’s health, from menopause and hormones to exercise, nutrition and natural medicine. I’ve accumulated so much information over the years that I’ve become the go-to pers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:26:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/how-often-should-you-be-healthy</link><title>How Often Should You Be Healthy?</title><description>* How Often Should You Be Healthy? A reader thoughtfully sent in the photos at left to help readers recognize unhealthy bending, and asked, "What is your advice when someone is having to bend to put dishes in the dishwasher? It just seems so uncommon to think to squat while loading th...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>