<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:30:57" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:30:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/10-ways-make-your-golf-game-incredible-workout</link><title>10 Ways to Make Your Golf Game an Incredible Workout</title><description>* 10 Ways to Make Your Golf Game an Incredible Workout Mark Twain once accused golf of being a great way to ruin an otherwise nice walk. Golf aficionados know this isn't true. In fact, a few small tweaks to your golf game can actually turn that nice walk into an effective full-body workout. 1. Leave the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:32:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/phil-mickelson-arthritis</link><title>Celebrities with Arthritis: Phil Mickelson’s Story</title><description>* Celebrities with Arthritis: Phil Mickelson’s Story Learn how legendary golfer Phil Mickelson dealt with his psoriatic arthritis diagnosis, and what enabled him to get back on the course doing what he loves.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:35:21">http://www.healthline.com/health/pre-game-smart-stretches-golf</link><title>Pre-Game Smart Stretches for Golf</title><description>* Pre-Game Smart Stretches for Golf The age-old debate about whether golf is a game or a sport can be fun to debate, but the truth is that it can be either, depending on how you play. For example, warming up for golf as if it were a sport will improve your performance and protect you f...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:36:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/golf</link><title>Is Golf Really Exercise?</title><description>* Is Golf Really Exercise? For many people, the idea of exercise sounds like a chore that they’d rather put off for another day. That’s why I encourage many of my patients to forget about the gym, with its repetitive machines, loud music, and sometimes confusing etiquette, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:39:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/year-round-workout-stay-golf-shape</link><title>Year-Round Workout to Stay in Golf Shape</title><description>* Year-Round Workout to Stay in Golf Shape Many assume that golf is a sport that requires minimal physical fitness. Although it isn't a fast-action sport, golf does require strength and flexibility. According to GolfLink, an 18-hole round, which can require three to five hours of walking and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:41:19">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/video-games-weight-gain</link><title>Video Games and Weight Gain: Truth or Fantasy?</title><description>* Video Games and Weight Gain: Truth or Fantasy? It’s no mystery that a sedentary lifestyle is a major contributor to obesity. Obesity, in turn, plays an important role in the development of heart disease and many other chronic conditions. In my February column for Healthline.com, I told you about ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>