<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:45:45" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:45:46">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/links-interest</link><title>Links of Interest</title><description>* Links of Interest Image via WikipediaThe following posts on the web recently caught my attention.Clinical Cases and Images -- which contains a wealth of resources for technology in medicine -- posted 5 tips to stay up to date with the medical literature (click the lin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:49:39">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/straight-talk-stanford-er/haiti-update-more-they-remain-same</link><title>Haiti Update: The More They Remain the Same...</title><description>* Haiti Update: The More They Remain the Same... Editor's Note: Healthline blogger and Stanford University emergency medicine instructor Dr. Anil Menon is in Haiti to help with the global effort to provide medical care in the wake of the January 12 earthquake. Because communication outlets are limi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:50:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/interview-richard-h-carmona-md-mph-facs-part-i</link><title>Interview with Richard H. Carmona, M.D., M.P.H., FACS: Part I</title><description>* Interview with Richard H. Carmona, M.D., M.P.H., FACS: Part I I had the honor and joy to spend some time speaking with Dr. Richard Carmona, 17th Surgeon General of the United States. This week I will post a series of excerpts from my interview with this warm and remarkable man. Readers of previous posts know th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:52:16">http://www.healthline.com/health/menopause/risk</link><title>Risk Factors for Early Menopause</title><description>* Risk Factors for Early Menopause While women generally enter menopause between the ages of 41 and 55, there are many factors that can interrupt the normal cycle of a woman’s reproductive system and bring about menopause earlier than normal. Premature menopause, also referred to as “...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:55:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/aplastic-anemia-and-mds-ii-iv</link><title>Aplastic Anemia and MDS: II of IV</title><description>* Aplastic Anemia and MDS: II of IV In my previous life as a Nurse Case Manager for a Worker’s Compensation (WC) Third Party Insurance Administrator TPA, I worked with a gentleman who had Aplastic Anemia. His WC claims adjuster accepted his claim as work-related due to an on-the-job ex...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>