<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:59:28" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:59:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/stinging-fishes</link><title>Stinging Fishes</title><description>* Stinging Fishes William Smith and Ward Wheeler, a curator at the American Museum of Natural History, suggest that there are at least 1,200 species of venomous fishes. This was accomplished by comparing DNA sequences from 233 known venomous species and then creating a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:03:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/encyclopedia-life-and-eo-wilson</link><title>The Encyclopedia of Life and E.O. Wilson</title><description>* The Encyclopedia of Life and E.O. Wilson Initial supporters have included the Field Museum of Natural History, Harvard University, the Marine Biological Laboratory, the Smithsonian, and the Biodiversity Heritage Library. Financial support has been provided by the John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:07:36">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/crohns-and-colitis/underwear-history</link><title>Underwear: A Brief History</title><description>* Underwear: A Brief History Having patented a wide variety of fabrics, sewing machines and other equipment, George D. Munsing was an accomplished turn-of-the-century inventor and businessman. But perhaps his best-known contribution to the industrial revolution was his pioneerin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:09:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/diving-japanese-ama-divers</link><title>Diving With the Japanese Ama Divers</title><description>* Diving With the Japanese Ama Divers Last week's story started our travel to several Japanese villages to live and dive with the AmaSan breath-hold divers, the SeaWomen. It continues here.The SeaWomen told me their stories. "I started when I was eight years old," one told me. "I gathere...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:12:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/outdoor-medicine-and-environment</link><title>Outdoor Medicine and the Environment</title><description>* Outdoor Medicine and the Environment I was recently fortunate to have a commentary entitled "Physicians and the Environment" published in the Journal of the American Medical Association. It was an invited piece, and reflected some of my thoughts about current environmental issues and th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:14:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/outdoor-medicine-and-environment-redux</link><title>Outdoor Medicine and the Environment Redux</title><description>* Outdoor Medicine and the Environment Redux Earlier this year, I published a series of three posts based upon a commentary I wrote, entitled "Physicians and the Environment," that was published in the Journal of the American Medical Association. The commentary was an invited piece, and reflect...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>