<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:15:07" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:15:08">http://www.healthline.com/health/copd/yoga</link><title>Yoga for COPD</title><description>* Yoga for COPD Yoga is an excellent form of exercise for almost anyone with COPD. It is relatively low impact, and it can help to improve both emotional and physical health. The National Centre for Complementary and Alternative Medicine describes yoga as a “mind-bo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:19:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/yoga-therapy</link><title>Yoga and Depression</title><description>* Yoga and Depression Yoga therapy involves different yoga poses, techniques, and meditation practices as a means for exercise and mental relief. Yoga may be used as treatment for various mental and emotional problems, such as stress, anxiety, and depression. How Yoga The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:23:44">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-cancer/yoga-breast-cancer</link><title>Yoga for Breast Cancer Patients</title><description>* Yoga for Breast Cancer Patients If you have breast cancer, yoga can help. The energizing combination of movement and meditation can both reinvigorate your body and lift your spirits. While chemotherapy may affect your energy levels and decrease your motivation to exercise, yoga can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:01">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-cancer/yoga-breast-cancer</link><title>Yoga and Breast Cancer Patients</title><description>* Yoga and Breast Cancer Patients If you have breast cancer, yoga can help. Yoga can be practiced gently enough to be adapted to many different skill levels and physical abilities. While chemotherapy may affect your energy levels and decrease your motivation to exercise, yoga's energ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:26:59">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/best-yoga-poses-osteoarthritis</link><title>Best Yoga Poses for Osteoarthritis</title><description>* Best Yoga Poses for Osteoarthritis Osteoarthritis (OA) causes stiffness, pain, and swelling in the joints. Practicing yoga can help ease these symptoms. Learn more about the best yoga poses for OA in this slideshow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:29:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/yoga-seniors</link><title>Yoga for Seniors</title><description>* Yoga for Seniors When you think of a yoga class, you probably picture a room full of thin, vibrant twenty-somethings contorted into a dazzling array of impossible body postures. Some yoga classes do cater to the extraordinarily flexible and fit person. However, moder...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:31:07">http://www.healthline.com/health/everyday-fitness/yoga</link><title>Yoga as a Cross-Training Technique</title><description>* Yoga as a Cross-Training Technique Yoga Overview Yoga is an ancient practice rooted in Indian philosophy. Originally observed as a method of attaining spiritual enlightenment, yoga is a combination of physical postures, breathing exercises, and meditation that aims to bring balance to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:32:57">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/menopause-corner/yoga-for-health-and-hormone-balancing</link><title>Yoga for Health and Hormone Balancing</title><description>* Yoga for Health and Hormone Balancing There is accumulating scientific evidence that yoga offers many well known health benefits, though the yoga enthusiasts I know say they don't need any proof to validate what they already know: Yoga just makes them feel better and they can’t imagine g...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:35:15">http://www.healthline.com/health/yoga-guide-beginners</link><title>Yoga: A Guide for Beginners</title><description>* Yoga: A Guide for Beginners Yoga doesn't have to be complicated and poses aren't usually as intimidating as their names. Here are five basic poses that will help get you acquainted with yoga and its many benefits. You can practice them separately or in-sequence for a ready-made...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:39:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/hold-that-pause/yoga-anxiety-depression-perimenopause</link><title>Yoga for Anxiety and Depression in Perimenopause</title><description>* Yoga for Anxiety and Depression in Perimenopause This past week we had a lively discussion on Facebook on the topic of anxiety and depression in perimenopause. It is a topic I’ve addressed at great length here at Hold that Pause. There’s a reason for that, too. It’s a huge problem for women in peri...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>