<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:20:14" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:20:15">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/2007-medical-weblog-awards</link><title>2007 Medical Weblog Awards</title><description>* 2007 Medical Weblog Awards Voting is now open for the 2007 Medical Weblog Awards, the Academy Awards of the medical blogosphere. (Full disclosure: I'm one of the editors at Medgadget, which sponsors the awards, and I was one of the nominators.) Use the awards as an excuse to v...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:24:12">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/outdoor-medicine-and-environment</link><title>Outdoor Medicine and the Environment</title><description>* Outdoor Medicine and the Environment I was recently fortunate to have a commentary entitled "Physicians and the Environment" published in the Journal of the American Medical Association. It was an invited piece, and reflected some of my thoughts about current environmental issues and th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:28:03">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/narrative-therapy</link><title>Narrative Therapy</title><description>* Narrative Therapy The stories we tell shape our world. That’s the idea behind narrative therapy. Narrative therapy is a form of psychotherapy based on the understanding that people have several narratives they constantly tell themselves. It focuses on how storytelling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:29:50">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/client-centered-therapy</link><title>Client-Centered Therapy</title><description>* Client-Centered Therapy Client-centered therapy, also known as person-centered therapy or the Rogerian style of therapy, was developed more than 70 years ago by Carl Rogers, whom many therapists consider the most influential psychotherapist in history. In client-centered th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:30:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/outdoor-medicine-and-environment-redux</link><title>Outdoor Medicine and the Environment Redux</title><description>* Outdoor Medicine and the Environment Redux Earlier this year, I published a series of three posts based upon a commentary I wrote, entitled "Physicians and the Environment," that was published in the Journal of the American Medical Association. The commentary was an invited piece, and reflect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:30:54">http://www.healthline.com/health/fta-abs-test</link><title>FTA-ABS Blood Test</title><description>* FTA-ABS Blood Test FTA-ABS Blood Test Your body’s immune system produces proteins known as antibodies when harmful substances are detected. These harmful substances, called antigens, take many forms, including parasites, viruses, fungi, and bacteria. The FTA-ABS blood ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:34:08">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/drowning-people-epilepsy</link><title>Drowning in People with Epilepsy</title><description>* Drowning in People with Epilepsy With summer upon us in the northern hemisphere, greater numbers of people are in the water - swimming, boating, diving, etc. Summer camps are booming, and children are being taught to swim, kayak, windsurf, and do all of the other activities that are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:35:58">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/expressive-therapy</link><title>Expressive Therapy</title><description>* Expressive Therapy Art, music, and dance are methods of creative expression, but they can also help a person process and cope with emotional problems, including depression. Expressive therapy goes beyond traditional talk therapy by using creative outlets as a means of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:36:29">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/problem-solving-therapy</link><title>Problem-Solving Therapy</title><description>* Problem-Solving Therapy Problem-solving therapy (PST) is a form of psychotherapy that is centered on developing and improving a patient’s coping skills and enhancing their ability to handle upsetting life experiences. “It’s the notion of focusing on the problem in the momen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:36:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/bipolar-disorder/caregiver-support</link><title>Caregivers: How to Help Someone with Bipolar Disorder</title><description>* Caregivers: How to Help Someone with Bipolar Disorder A person suffering from bipolar disorder has their own obstacles to handle, but caring for someone who is bipolar also has its own challenges. Whether you live together or are on the other side of the planet, there are steps everyone can take to help...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>