<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:41:54" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:41:55">http://www.healthline.com/health/audiology</link><title>Audiometry</title><description>* Audiometry What Is Audiometry? An audiometry exam tests how well a person’s hearing functions. The test covers both intensity and tone of sounds to determine how well a person can hear. It is used to diagnose hearing loss. The test is administered by an audiolo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:43:11">http://www.healthline.com/health/menieres-disease</link><title>Meniere's Disease</title><description>* Meniere's Disease What Is Meniere’s Disease? Meniere’s disease is a disorder that affects the inner ear. The inner ear contains tubes filled with fluid called “labyrinths.” The inner ear is responsible for your balance, as well as hearing. This disorder causes vertigo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:46:26">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/ringing-in-ears</link><title>Tinnitus</title><description>* Tinnitus What Is Tinnitus? Tinnitus is the medical term for noises in the ears. Most people refer to tinnitus as “ringing in the ears.” The feedback you hear, however, is not limited to ringing. You may also hear roaring, buzzing, whistling, or hissing if you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:49:38">http://www.healthline.com/health/swimmers-ear-chronic</link><title>Chronic Swimmer's Ear</title><description>* Chronic Swimmer's Ear What Is Chronic Swimmer’s Ear? Chronic swimmer’s ear is an ear condition in which the outer ear and ear canal become infected, swollen, or irritated. The disorder often results from having water trapped in your ear after swimming. The ear’s structure...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:50:42">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/hearing-impairment</link><title>Hearing Loss</title><description>* Hearing Loss The National Institute on Deafness and Other Communication Disorders (NICDC) reported that, in 2010, 30 percent of those between the ages of 65 and 74 said they had hearing loss (NICDC). Hearing loss is also known as: decreased hearing deafness loss of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:52:17">http://www.healthline.com/health/type-2-diabetes/hearing-loss</link><title>Type 2 Diabetes and Hearing Loss</title><description>* Type 2 Diabetes and Hearing Loss After years of trying and failing to find a distinct relationship between type 2 diabetes and hearing loss, recent studies have confirmed that relationship. In 2008, the National Institute of Health (NIH) found that hearing loss is twice as common in...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>