<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:56:05" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:56:06">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/my-kid-going-college</link><title>My Kid is Going To College!</title><description>* My Kid is Going To College! OMG! WTF? Are you kidding? I am not ready! Those 17 years sure blew by fast - I still remember singing to her while rubbing my pregnant belly! How the heck will we all manage? I take it all back - encouraging independence, providing a great education...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:00:21">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-battles-over-restaurant-worker-sick-leave-play-out-in-cities-and-states-070113</link><title>More People Falling Ill as Lawmakers Battle Over Paid Sick Leave</title><description>* More People Falling Ill as Lawmakers Battle Over Paid Sick Leave Florida and New York City are the latest battlegrounds in the fight between workers and the food service industry over mandated sick pay.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:04:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/allergies</link><title>Common Fall Allergens &amp; How to Fight Them</title><description>* Common Fall Allergens &amp; How to Fight Them Don't let Fall allergies get you down, learn about these 4 common Fall allergens &amp; how to best avoid them.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/five-fall-faves</link><title>Five Fall Faves</title><description>* Five Fall Faves Even though I live in Florida, I can still appreciate the fall. We had our own little cold front come through earlier in the week and it was in the 40's overnight and 60's during the day. That cool air felt so good! I love the "crisp" feel in the air...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:08:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/superfood-pumpkin</link><title>Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Pumpkin</title><description>* Superfood of the Week: Health Benefits of Pumpkin Fall is my absolute favorite time of the year. I love the beautiful colors of the leaves, and of course the food! One particular food that comes to mind is pumpkins! Pumpkins are a true sign that fall has arrived. During the months of September and O...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:13:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/autumn-apples</link><title>Autumn Apples</title><description>* Autumn Apples Fall is definitely here, and we even had a "cold front" come through Florida last week when it got down into the low 60's overnight and high 70's and low 80's during the day. While I love living in Florida, I do miss the change of seasons. My favorit...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>