<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:17:37" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:17:38">http://www.healthline.com/treatments/breast-cancer__</link><title>Breast Cancer Treatment : Treatment Search</title><description>* Breast Cancer Treatment : Treatment Search Learn about treatments, tests, and procedures for breast-cancer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:19:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/breast-cancer-screening</link><title>Breast Cancer Screen Recommendations</title><description>* Breast Cancer Screen Recommendations How does the topic of breast cancer screening relate to outdoor health? In my opinion, it is one of those topics that transcend a single categorization, because it is so important and affects us all. In addition, it can tie in directly to the topic of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:20:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/cancer-treatment-survivorship/enhancing-breast-cancer-screening</link><title>Enhancing Breast Cancer Screening</title><description>* Enhancing Breast Cancer Screening Vestal, MSN, FNP, RN, at our institution on a study related to breast cancer screening.Breast Cancer is the most wide spread cancer affecting women and the second leading cause of cancer deaths in the United States. Survival rates are highly dependent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:23:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-ultrasound</link><title>Breast Ultrasound</title><description>* Breast Ultrasound In addition to determining the nature of a breast abnormality or screening for breast cancer, ultrasounds can also be used to help guide a surgeon while he or she removes a tissue sample from a lump in the breast. This is called an ultrasound-guided core...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:27:06">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-biopsy-ultrasound</link><title>Ultrasound-Guided Core Needle Breast Biopsy</title><description>* Ultrasound-Guided Core Needle Breast Biopsy In addition to determining the nature of a breast abnormality or screening for breast cancer, ultrasounds can also be used to help guide a surgeon while he or she removes a tissue sample from a lump in the breast. This is called an ultrasound-guided core...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:28:33">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-mri-scan</link><title>Breast MRI Scan</title><description>* Breast MRI Scan ...breasts when other imaging tests are inadequate or inconclusive, screen for women with a high risk of breast cancer, or monitor the progression of breast cancer and treatments. Other reasons for getting a breast MRI include: dense breast tissue diagnosing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-07"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-infection</link><title>Breast Infection</title><description>* Breast Infection ...due to breastfeeding or clogged milk ducts, some breast infections are associated with rare kinds of breast cancer. What Causes Breast Infections? Most breast infections are caused by Staphylococcus aureus bacteria. For breastfeeding mothers, a plugged...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:32:26">http://www.healthline.com/health/mammography</link><title>Mammography</title><description>* Mammography A mammography is a screening tool used to detect and diagnose breast cancer. Together with regular clinical exams and monthly breast self-examination, mammograms are a key element in the early diagnosis of breast cancer. According to the National Cancer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:33:14">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-mediterranean-diet</link><title>Mediterranean diet</title><description>* Mediterranean diet Diet, Mediterranean Antioxidants, caffeic acid, diet, fruit and vegetable diet, fatty acids, good fat diet, Greek diet, high fat diet, Italian diet, olive oil, omega-3 fatty acids, tyrosol, vegetarian, vegetarian diet, wine. The Mediterranean diet is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:36:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/lung-cancer</link><title>Lung Cancer</title><description>* Lung Cancer Many people are still surprised to learn that lung cancer kills more women than breast cancer. The risks of lung cancer increase dramatically with age and years of tobacco smoking. Men who continue to smoke are over 20 times more likely to die of lung...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>