<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:42:30" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:42:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/womens-health-urinary-tract-infection</link><title>Urinary Tract Infection (UTI)</title><description>* Urinary Tract Infection (UTI) Other risk factors include: insertion of a catheter diabetes diaphragm contraception Symptoms and Treatment Most people with a UTI experience at least one or more symptoms of the condition. These can include a frequent urge to urinate and a burning feeling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:46:16">http://www.healthline.com/health/emergency-contraception/birth-control-options</link><title>Involve Your Partner</title><description>* Involve Your Partner For some people, talking about sex can be uncomfortable. We remind ourselves about the importance of physical and mental health: limiting alcohol, not smoking, eating a balanced diet, staying active. What about our sexual health? Love and intimacy ar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:46:46">http://www.healthline.com/health/birth-control</link><title>Choosing the Right Birth Control</title><description>* Choosing the Right Birth Control Birth control (also known as contraception) is an age-old concern. Long before the introduction of “The Pill” in the 1960s, men and women were using condoms and other forms of birth control to avoid pregnancy. Today, there are more methods of safe an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:50:07">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-sex-contraceptive-options</link><title>Your Contraceptive Options</title><description>* Your Contraceptive Options Oral Contraceptives (“The Pill”) Most popular method of birth control Pills contain estrogen and progestin and are taken once a day. Require a prescription Work by preventing ovaries from releasing eggs Effectiveness: 99.7%, if used perfectly; with t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:50:41">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/nevirapine</link><title>Nevirapine tablets</title><description>* Nevirapine tablets Nevirapine tablets What is this medicine? NEVIRAPINE (ne VYE ra peen) is an antiretroviral medicine. It is used with other medicines to treat HIV. This medicine is not a cure for HIV. It will not stop the spread of HIV to others. This me...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>