<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7205">turkey leftover recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:04:31" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:04:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/nutritious-ways-re-prepare-leftovers</link><title>Nutritious Ways to Re-Prepare Leftovers</title><description>* Nutritious Ways to Re-Prepare Leftovers Leftovers are a concept that people seem to either love or hate. Whether your fridge is overstocked from a holiday meal or you just cooked a bit too much dinner, your family's taste buds might not appreciate the same meal twice. Get creative to find ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:07:04">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/how-safe-your-thanksgiving-meal</link><title>How Safe is Your Thanksgiving Meal?</title><description>* How Safe is Your Thanksgiving Meal? One of the most important things you can do to stay healthy this Thanksgiving involves how you eat rather than what you eat. Believe it or not, over 200,000 Americans get sick every day from food borne illness (food poisoning) from improper food hand...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:11:39">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/turkey-day-meal-planning-guide</link><title>Turkey Day Meal Planning Guide</title><description>* Turkey Day Meal Planning Guide Whether you’re cooking for two people or 10, these tips will help you navigate through each part of the day to create a memorable holiday feast.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:14:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/10-tips-for-stress-free-thanksgiving</link><title>10 Tips for a Stress-Free Thanksgiving</title><description>* 10 Tips for a Stress-Free Thanksgiving Hosting Thanksgiving dinner at your house? Take these tips for navigating your way around the kitchen and through a successful holiday meal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:16:07">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/top-10-ways-save-money-thanksgiving</link><title>Top 10 Ways to Save Money on Thanksgiving</title><description>* Top 10 Ways to Save Money on Thanksgiving Many of us are feeling the effects of this economy in our bank accounts, yet prices still seem to be going up for many of our commonly purchased items. Let's be thankful that gas prices are down, but Christmas is right around the corner and we need t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:16:56">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/top-5-thanksgiving-tips</link><title>Top 5 Thanksgiving Tips</title><description>* Top 5 Thanksgiving Tips The biggest food holiday of the year for Americans is fast approaching. Are you ready to indulge? What are your favorite treats? People don't want to hear from a dietitian how many calories are in their favorite treats. You just want to enjoy, right?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:20:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/turkey-day</link><title>Turkey Day</title><description>* Turkey Day With such a momentous food-related holiday this week, I feel compelled to write something about Thanksgiving. No one ever likes to have a dietitian around on the one day of the year when it is definite you will overeat. I agree!For Thanksgiving Day, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:21:25">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/holiday-food-safety-tips</link><title>Holiday Food Safety Tips</title><description>* Holiday Food Safety Tips We talked about turkey safety already back in November and now that Christmas is coming up it's time for some additional food safety steps you should take when hosting the 'big meal'. Here are five that'll get you started.1. Stick to the two-hour rul...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:23:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-delicious-holiday-meals</link><title>Healthy Meal for the Holidays</title><description>* Healthy Meal for the Holidays Between turkey, vegetable sides and hearty winter flavors — there’s no reason your holiday feast needs to be a diet disaster to be delicious and satisfying. Williams-Sonoma has created a holiday menu of recipes that are low in fat, high in nutrients,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7205-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7205_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:24:36">http://www.healthline.com/health/jillian-michaels-the-doctors</link><title>The Healthline Interview: Jillian Michaels from TV's 'The Doctors'</title><description>* The Healthline Interview: Jillian Michaels from TV's 'The Doctors' Health and fitness guru Jillian Michaels took time away from her busy schedule to give Healthline.com readers advice on how to eat healthy this holiday season without packing on pounds.Health and fitness guru Jillian Michaels took time away from her ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>