<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:33:26" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:33:27">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/earthquake-tsunami-japan</link><title>Earthquake and Tsunami in Japan</title><description>* Earthquake and Tsunami in Japan Sendai Earthquake 2011Our thoughts and prayers go out to everyone in harm’s way related to the earthquake and tsunami that just struck Japan, as they did for persons in New Zealand, Haiti, and every other country recently affected by a natural disaster....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:36:15">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/earthquake-tsunami-japan-update</link><title>The Japan Earthquake, Tsunami, and Nuclear Reactor Complication</title><description>* The Japan Earthquake, Tsunami, and Nuclear Reactor Complication Ofunato, Japan After the Earthquake and TsunamiI have just received word that my good friend N. Stuart Harris, MD, who is Chief of the Division of Wilderness Medicine in the Department of Emergency Medicine at Massachusetts General Hospital, is in Japan...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:37:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/haiti-relief-from-the-ground</link><title>Haiti Earthquake Relief</title><description>* Haiti Earthquake Relief ...today with a link to a list of some of the ways to donate to disaster relief for the victims of the earthquake in Haiti.Here is the link: http://www.astmh.org/Content/NavigationMenu/Advocacy/HaitianEarthquakeRelief/default.htmIf you are able to make a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:39:50">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/images-test</link><title>images test</title><description>* images test Our thoughts and prayers go out to everyone in harm’s way related to the earthquake and tsunami that just struck Japan, as they did for persons in New Zealand, Haiti, and every other country recently affected by a natural disaster. These natural catastrophes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:42:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/world-rushes-haiti</link><title>The World Rushes to Haiti</title><description>* The World Rushes to Haiti After many logistical hurdles in the days immediately following the earthquake, international aid groups began arriving in Haiti over the weekend – ranging from search-and-rescue teams with large equipment for digging through the rubble to health organizations...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:45:15">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/haitian-health-concerns-grow-due-devastating-quake</link><title>Haitian Health Concerns Grow Due to Devastating Quake</title><description>* Haitian Health Concerns Grow Due to Devastating Quake ...all the hospitals and health care facilities in Port-Au-Prince, capital of Haiti and epicenter of the earthquake, have been severely damaged or destroyed completely. In any case such structural damage would be detrimental to relief efforts, but in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:46:04">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/straight-talk-stanford-er/my-journey-haiti</link><title>My Journey to Haiti</title><description>* My Journey to Haiti ...Menon is in Haiti to help with the global effort to provide medical care in the wake of the January 12 earthquake. Because communication outlets are limited, he has been sending updates to his mother via text message. She has been transcribing those messages...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:47:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/what-to-expect-after-a-natural-disaster</link><title>What to Expect After a Natural Disaster</title><description>* What to Expect After a Natural Disaster Sichuan earthquake rescue workers carrying an injured person. In light of the widespread media coverage of natural disasters, such as the earthquake in Haiti and the tsunami in Japan, the public and medical professionals are aware of the anticipated immediate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:48:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/straight-talk-stanford-er/first-days-haiti</link><title>The First Days in Haiti</title><description>* The First Days in Haiti The decision to travel to Haiti to assist with medical relief following the earthquake was at the same time easy and difficult. It was easy, because how could anyone know of such misery and suffering and not volunteer to help, but difficult because it...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:51:10">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/haiti-relief-from-the-ground</link><title>Haiti: The First Days</title><description>* Haiti: The First Days The decision to travel to Haiti to assist with medical relief following the earthquake was at the same time easy and difficult. It was easy, because how could anyone know of such misery and suffering and not volunteer to help, but difficult because it...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>