<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:04:56" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:04:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/guide-dealing-stress-caring-child-special-needs</link><title>A Guide to Dealing with the Stress of Caring for a Child with Special Needs</title><description>* A Guide to Dealing with the Stress of Caring for a Child with Special Needs Parents of children with special needs have their own special needs--for exceptional stress-management skills. While raising a child can be tough for any parent, a child with special needs poses additional challenges to navigate on a daily basis. The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:06:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/dan-guide-dive-medical-frequently-asked-questions-faq</link><title>The DAN Guide to Dive Medical Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)</title><description>* The DAN Guide to Dive Medical Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) The DAN Guide to Dive Medical Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) is a book to which I and other dive medicine authorities have contributed. This compilation of questions and answers by the Divers Alert Network (DAN) is available through DAN or from Be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:09:38">http://www.healthline.com/health/age-guide-developmental-milestones</link><title>By-Age Guide of Developmental Milestones</title><description>* By-Age Guide of Developmental Milestones Although each child's development is slightly different, there are some milestones you should expect your child to reach by certain ages. Keeping track of your baby's progress could thwart or reveal potential problems. 2 Months By two months old, you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:10:30">http://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/treatment-options</link><title>IBS: Your Guide to Tailoring Treatment</title><description>* IBS: Your Guide to Tailoring Treatment Just because there isn't a single definitive way to treat IBS, doesn't mean it can’t be treated. Lifestyle changes can make a difference and your doctor can help you work through other options. Diet Certain foods can trigger symptoms, so keep a food ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:14:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/beginners-guide-mountain-biking</link><title>A Beginner's Guide to Mountain Biking</title><description>* A Beginner's Guide to Mountain Biking Mountain biking combines a great cardio workout with a challenging outdoor adventure. If you enjoy biking on the road but are looking for a new twist--or if you've never been much of a biker but crave a new adventure--mountain biking may be the sport...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:18:53">http://www.healthline.com/health/lice-parents-guide-to-outbreaks</link><title>Lice Emergency? A Parent’s Guide to Lice Outbreaks</title><description>* Lice Emergency? A Parent’s Guide to Lice Outbreaks Have you ever had this experience—your child pulls out of their backpack a notice from the school nurse, informing you that there has been a lice outbreak in your child’s class or school? Have you had that sinking feeling? Did your scalp start itchin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:22:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/menopause-corner/does-your-doctor-have-the-expertise-to-guide-you-through-the-menopause-years</link><title>Does Your Doctor Have the Expertise to Guide You Through the Menopause Years?</title><description>* Does Your Doctor Have the Expertise to Guide You Through the Menopause Years? I recently attended the annual conference of the North American Menopause Society (NAMS)--whose membership is comprised of clinical and science experts, including physicians, researchers, and nurses -- who focus almost exclusively on women’s health i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:23:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/book-review-when-your-kid-goes-college-parents-survival-guide</link><title>Book Review: When Your Kid Goes to College: A Parents Survival Guide</title><description>* Book Review: When Your Kid Goes to College: A Parents Survival Guide As promised, here is the first book I can recommend for parents struggling with an empty nest. When Your Kid Goes to College: A Parents Survival Guide (1998), by Carol Barkin is a "support group with a binding" for parents preparing to let their kids...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:24:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/guide-to-healthy-vacation</link><title>Guide to a Healthy Vacation</title><description>* Guide to a Healthy Vacation Where are you going on vacation? I love summer because it’s a chance to spend time with family and friends, and, with kids on summer break, it’s a perfect excuse to go on a summer vacation! Unfortunately, we also tend to get off schedule, including o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7211-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7211_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:27:29">http://www.healthline.com/health/hiv-aids/patient-guide-to-living-with-hiv</link><title>A Patient’s Guide to Living with HIV</title><description>* A Patient’s Guide to Living with HIV In the United States, more than one million people are currently living with human immunodeficiency virus (HIV). Over the past 30 years, much of the stigma and misconceptions around the disease have disappeared. Better information and education have ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>