<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:04:59" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:05:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/squamous-cell-carcinoma-pictures</link><title>Pictures of Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>* Pictures of Squamous Cell Carcinoma Squamous cell carcinoma is more likely to develop on body parts exposed to sunlight. See pictures of this cancer type and learn about symptoms.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:06:33">http://www.healthline.com/health/squamous-cell-skin-cancer</link><title>Squamous Cell Cancer</title><description>* Squamous Cell Cancer There are three main types of skin cancer: squamous cell carcinoma, basal cell carcinoma, and melanoma. Your skin has multiple layers: the upper, protective layer of the skin is known as the epidermis. The epidermis is comprised of three types of cells...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:07:17">http://www.healthline.com/health/skin-cancer</link><title>What is Skin Cancer?</title><description>* What is Skin Cancer? Most actinic keratoses are benign, but some studies show that up to 10 percent may progress to squamous cell carcinoma. Actinic keratosis affects more than 58 million Americans. About 65 percent of all squamous cell carcinomas come from lesions that previously...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:11:54">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/types-of-skin-cancer</link><title>What Does Skin Cancer Look Like?</title><description>* What Does Skin Cancer Look Like? Skin cancer is the uncontrolled growth of cancer cells in the skin Learn about basal cell carcinoma, squamos cell carcinoma, melanoma and kaposi's sarcoma.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:12:57">http://www.healthline.com/health/gerd/esophageal-cancer</link><title>Esophageal Cancer and Acid Reflux</title><description>* Esophageal Cancer and Acid Reflux There are two common types of esophageal cancer: squamous cell carcinoma and adenocarcinoma. Squamous cell carcinoma usually occurs in the upper and middle parts of the esophagus. Adenocarcinoma affects the cells in the lower portion of the esophagus,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:15:50">http://www.healthline.com/health/keratoacanthoma</link><title>Keratoacanthoma</title><description>* Keratoacanthoma Keratoacanthoma (KA) is a low-grade skin cancer tumor that is similar to squamous cell carcinoma (SCC). It originates in the skin’s pilosebaceous glands, or hair follicles. This skin cancer tumor grows rapidly, in just a few weeks to a few months. It...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:19:30">http://www.healthline.com/health/lung-cancer-non-small-cell</link><title>Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</title><description>* Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer Non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) is also called lung adenocarcinoma or squamous cell carcinoma. According to the American Cancer Society (ACS), this is the most common kind of lung cancer, comprising 85 to 90 percent of lung cancer diagnoses (ACS, 2012)....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:20:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/skin-cancer</link><title>Skin Cancer Overview</title><description>* Skin Cancer Overview ...carcinoma: the most common form; develops from abnormal cell growth in lowest layer of the epidermis Squamous cell carcinoma: develops in the middle layer of the epidermis Melanoma: the least common but the most dangerous type; it forms in the melanocytes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:22:36">http://www.healthline.com/health/skin-cancer/complications</link><title>Skin Cancer Complications</title><description>* Skin Cancer Complications For example, squamous cell carcinoma is likely to recur within two years of having surgery to remove the cancer, according to the Skin Cancer Foundation. People who are diagnosed with skin cancer are also at a greater risk for a developing another skin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:24:25">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/sunscreen</link><title>sunscreen</title><description>* sunscreen Are Sunscreens Cost-Effective for the Prevention of Skin Cancer?A modest investment in prevention produced substantial savings in illness-related costs. Dermatologists routinely recommend regular application of sunscreens to people at risk for develo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>