<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:25:44" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:25:45">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/bacterial-diarrhea</link><title>Bacterial Diarrhea</title><description>* Bacterial Diarrhea Campylobacter, nontyphoid Salmonella, Shiga toxin-producing E. coli, and Shigella bacteria are common causal agents of bacteria-induced diarrhea in the U.S. Other bacteria are more frequently associated with particular environments, such as Aeromonas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:28:41">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/foodborne-bacterial-diarrhea</link><title>Foodborne Bacterial Diarrhea</title><description>* Foodborne Bacterial Diarrhea Causes of Bacterial Diarrhea Salmonella, Shiga toxin-producing E. coli, and Shigella bacteria are common causal agents of bacteria-induced diarrhea in the U.S. Other bacteria are more frequently associated with particular environments, such as Aeromonas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:32:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/food-contaminated-spices-found-amid-food-imports-082813</link><title>Could What’s in Your Spice Rack Be Making You Sick?</title><description>* Could What’s in Your Spice Rack Be Making You Sick? Salmonella-laced spices could already be in your home. Learn what to do to keep your family safe.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:36:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/women-breast-milk-bought-online-often-contaminated-102113</link><title>Breast Milk Bought Online Often Contaminated With Harmful Bacteria</title><description>* Breast Milk Bought Online Often Contaminated With Harmful Bacteria Researchers find bacteria and fecal matter in breast milk purchased online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:39:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/crohns-scientists-map-crohns-gut-bacteria-031214</link><title>Study Reveals Specific Gut Bacteria Involved in Crohn's Disease</title><description>* Study Reveals Specific Gut Bacteria Involved in Crohn's Disease The balance of microbes in the intestines is thrown off in people with Crohn’s disease, a finding that might lead to new, targeted treatments.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:43:18">http://www.healthline.com/health/salmonella-enterocolitis</link><title>Salmonella Food Poisoning (Salmonella Enterocolitis)</title><description>* Salmonella Food Poisoning (Salmonella Enterocolitis) Salmonella Food Poisoning Salmonella food poisoning is an infection in the small intestine. It is also called salmonella enterocolitis or salmonellosis. It is one of the most common types of food poisoning, and is caused by the bacteria group Salmonella....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:45:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/tomatoes-and-salmonella</link><title>Tomatoes and Salmonella</title><description>* Tomatoes and Salmonella outbreak of infections caused by Salmonella serotype Saintpaul, attributed to consumption of raw tomatoes, and in particular, red plum, red Roma, or round red tomatoes. Thirty-two states and the District of Columbia were said to have reported infections...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:47:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/more-tomatoes-salmonella-outbreak</link><title>More Than Tomatoes in Salmonella Outbreak</title><description>* More Than Tomatoes in Salmonella Outbreak A few new foods have been added to the investigation around the salmonella outbreak in the US. Since April there have been 943 cases in 40 states of the same salmonella strain (salmonella saintpaul). While tomatoes were the original suspect, officials...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:49:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/salmonella-sickens-people-across-us</link><title>Salmonella Sickens People Across U.S.</title><description>* Salmonella Sickens People Across U.S. UPDATE Friday 11/3/06:Restaurant tomatoes have been identified as the culprit in the Salmonella outbreak that has sickened 183 people across 21 U.S. states and Canada, with 22 hospitalizations. "We identified tomatoes eaten in restaurants as the cause...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:51:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/food-safety-dairy-products</link><title>Safe Eggs and Dairy Products: Store Well and Prevent Salmonella</title><description>* Safe Eggs and Dairy Products: Store Well and Prevent Salmonella ...the federal government and voluntarily recalled by egg manufacturers as a preemptive measure against salmonella contamination. It is important to know the most common problems associated with egg and dairy production, and how to avoid contaminated eggs...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>