<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7217">who was lincolns vice president</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:54:25" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:54:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/update-swine-influenza</link><title>Update on Swine Influenza</title><description>* Update on Swine Influenza or World Health Organization (WHO) authorities. President Felipe Calderón published an order today that would give his government powers to address a deadly flu epidemic, including isolation of persons affected by the rare virus, inspection of their homes,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:55:44">http://www.healthline.com/health/fda-approves-new-treatment-of-allergic-rhinitis</link><title>The FDA Approves New Treatment of Allergic Rhinitis</title><description>* The FDA Approves New Treatment of Allergic Rhinitis Teva Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd. recently announced the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) approval of their new “dry” nasal aerosol, QNASLTM. The corticosteroid spray is intended to treat year-round and seasonal allergic rhinitis in individu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:57:21">http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-healthcare-guide/eligible-participate-insurance-exchanges</link><title>Who will be eligible to participate in the health insurance exchanges?</title><description>* Who will be eligible to participate in the health insurance exchanges? Healthline &gt; Health Insurance &gt; Questions and Answers &gt; Will the new healthcare law lower my premiums?--&gt; Q: Who will be eligible to participate in the health insurance exchanges? Answer: The health insurance marketplace is open to U.S. residents or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:59:42">http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-healthcare-guide/standards-insurance-companies</link><title>Are there any standards that health insurance companies in exchanges will have to follow, or will they be able to cover only what they want to?</title><description>* Are there any standards that health insurance companies in exchanges will have to follow, or will they be able to cover only what they want to? Healthline &gt; Health Insurance &gt; Questions and Answers &gt; Will the new healthcare law lower my premiums?--&gt; Q: Are there any standards that health insurance companies in exchanges will have to follow, or will they be able to cover only what they want t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:00:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/getsmart-eye-smart</link><title>GetSmart: Eye Smart!</title><description>* GetSmart: Eye Smart! H. Dunbar Hoskins, Jr. MD FACS, Executive Vice President of the American Academy of Opthalmology (AAO), was kind enough to spend some time with me today talking about Eye Health. AAO has two important programs Dr. Hoskins wants Healthline readers to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7217-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7217_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:01:49">http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-healthcare-guide/reform-increase-taxes</link><title>Will healthcare reform increase taxes?</title><description>* Will healthcare reform increase taxes? Healthline &gt; Health Insurance &gt; Questions and Answers &gt; Will the new healthcare law lower my premiums?--&gt; Q: Will healthcare reform increase taxes? Answer: Most Americans are required to buy health insurance or pay a penalty for failing to do so. Peo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>