<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7234">347 ford engines</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:14:22" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:14:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/mens-health/obesity-story</link><title>Personal Obesity Stories: Mike (54, Building Supervisor &amp; Engineer) and Matt (18, Student) Cianciullo</title><description>* Personal Obesity Stories: Mike (54, Building Supervisor &amp; Engineer) and Matt (18, Student) Cianciullo Matt Cianciullo, 18, StudentHealthline: Mike, can you give us a little background about your experience with obesity? Mike: I always remember being “pleasantly plump” (as I said to people in my childhood). As I got older, when people commented about ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:17:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/visual-medical-dictionary-and-curehunter-engine</link><title>A Visual Medical Dictionary and the CureHunter Engine</title><description>* A Visual Medical Dictionary and the CureHunter Engine Curehunter.com offers a free "visual medical dictionary" at https://www.curehunter.com/public/dictionary.do. The idea is similar to Healthlines' HealthMaps -- an interrelated web of complex terms is displayed as a simple map or diagram to enhance und...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:21:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/genetically-engineered-t-cells-block-hiv-without-drugs-030514</link><title>Genetically Engineered T-Cells Block HIV Without Drugs</title><description>* Genetically Engineered T-Cells Block HIV Without Drugs It sounds like science fiction, but gene editing could be a powerful new weapon against HIV.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:23:36">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/tech-oxitec-mosquitoes-dengue-fever-032213</link><title>Scientists Genetically Engineer 'Dead End' Mosquitos to Fight Dengue</title><description>* Scientists Genetically Engineer 'Dead End' Mosquitos to Fight Dengue Oxitec has created a breed of mosquito whose offspring don’t survive to adulthood in an effort to eradicate mosquito-borne illness.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:25:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/winter-tragedy</link><title>A Winter Tragedy</title><description>* A Winter Tragedy The practice of wilderness medicine is unfortunately frequently necessitated by tragic events and circumstances. We are all enormously saddened to learn of the death of James Kim, whose recovery was announced today. Mr. Kim succumbed to the cold Paci...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:27:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/thyroid-expert-q-and-a</link><title>Expert Q&amp;A: Thyroid Health</title><description>* Expert Q&amp;A: Thyroid Health The thyroid is a tiny gland with a big job. Located in the neck, it secretes hormones that are responsible for the body's energy supply and for ensuring that organ systems run properly. The thyroid plays such a vital function in our health, January h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:28:24">http://www.healthline.com/health/gasoline</link><title>Gasoline and Health</title><description>* Gasoline and Health What Does Gasoline Have to Do With Your Health? Gasoline is considered dangerous for your health because it is poisonous. Exposure to gas—either through physical contact or inhalation—can cause health problems. The effects of gasoline poisoning can h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:29:23">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/thank-you-paul-s-auerbach-md</link><title>Thank you Paul S. Auerbach, MD</title><description>* Thank you Paul S. Auerbach, MD On Thanksgiving Day, I always try to reflect on the things I have been grateful for in my life. It dawned on me as I awoke yesterday morning that one of the people I have been most thankful for, and never told, is an old friend, and fellow Healthline...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:32:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/some-symptoms-functional-thyroid-disease</link><title>Some Symptoms of Functional Thyroid Disease</title><description>* Some Symptoms of Functional Thyroid Disease Thyroid disease is an everyday reality for over 27 million people in the United States. Within this enormous group, it is estimated that more than half remain undiagnosed and untreated. Iodine deficiency causes significant thyroid problems for many m...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7234-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7234_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:34:05">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/where-did-your-labels-go</link><title>Where Did Your Labels Go?</title><description>* Where Did Your Labels Go? How do you keep a search engine happy? Programmers, marketers - do you have ideas how we can write the blogs to better feed the search engines? They seem hungry.Healthline wrote,"In part of our ongoing testing, we've discovered that the addition of l...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>