<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:40:30" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:40:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/bambino-anyone</link><title>Bambino Anyone?</title><description>* Bambino Anyone? How can something that tastes so great be so good for you? I bought this “baby” watermelon at a Farmer’s Market over the weekend and it was delicious (fun fact: Florida is one of that nation’s top growers of watermelon). Watermelon’s got a lot going ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:42:58">http://www.healthline.com/health/personal-health-record</link><title>Building a Personal Health Record</title><description>* Building a Personal Health Record Where Are Your Health Records? What's the first thing that comes to your mind when you think of a visit to the doctor's office? If it's filling out forms, you're not alone; it's a common frustration for patients nationwide. Detailed questions about y...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:44:14">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/uk-national-smoking-cessation-conference</link><title>UK National Smoking Cessation Conference</title><description>* UK National Smoking Cessation Conference Probably the best conference on smoking cessation over recent years has been the UK National Smoking Cessation Conference. The UK is probably the only country to have a national and fairly comprehensive smoking cessation service involving widespread ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:48:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/most-disruptive-changes-healthcare-according-sermo</link><title>Most Disruptive Changes in Healthcare (According to Sermo)</title><description>* Most Disruptive Changes in Healthcare (According to Sermo) Last month I gave a talk on Health 2.0: Disruptive Changes in Healthcare. I spoke about online communities of physicians and patients, and one of the communities I discussed was Sermo:Sermo was founded on the idea of information arbitrage, that there...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:52:24">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/worlds-largest-quit-smoking-program</link><title>The World's Largest Quit Smoking Program</title><description>* The World's Largest Quit Smoking Program What do you think about quitting with 100,000 people from 89 different countries? If you are not quite ready to quit, this course (https://www.stopsmoking.ucsf.edu/en/Intro/Home.aspx)probably isn't for you. But if you are ready to give quitting a try...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>