<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:55:44" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:55:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/collagen-vascular-disease</link><title>Collagen Vascular Disease</title><description>* Collagen Vascular Disease Collagen Vascular Disease Collagen vascular disease refers to a group of diseases that affect your connective tissue. Collagen is a protein-based connective tissue that forms a support system for your skin. The connective tissue holds bones, ligaments,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:58:12">http://www.healthline.com/health/antithyroglobulin-antibody</link><title>Antithyroglobulin Antibody Test</title><description>* Antithyroglobulin Antibody Test What Is an Anti-thyroglobulin Antibody Test? Your thyroid is an endocrine gland located in your neck. It is responsible for releasing hormones that control your metabolism. The thyroid gland produces a number of different proteins, including thyroglo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:59:01">http://www.healthline.com/health/antinuclear-antibody-panel</link><title>Antinuclear Antibody Panel</title><description>* Antinuclear Antibody Panel These include: systemic lupus erythematosus chronic liver disease rheumatoid arthritis collagen vascular disease Sjögren syndrome scleroderma thyroid disease If your test comes back positive, your doctor will likely do a complete physical exam and blood...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:02:15">http://www.healthline.com/health/complement-component</link><title>Complement Component 4 Test</title><description>* Complement Component 4 Test What Is a Complement Component 4 Test? Your complement system is made up of a group of protein molecules in your bloodstream that helps your immune system remove harmful pathogens (viruses, bacteria, and other germs) and other foreign substances from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:06:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/thoracentesis</link><title>Thoracentesis</title><description>* Thoracentesis ...different possible causes for the effusion, including the presence of lung cancer, mesothelioma, tumors, collagen vascular disease, viral or fungal diseases, or parasitic disease. Preparing for a Thoracentesis There is no special preparation for thoracentesis....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:08:19">http://www.healthline.com/health/blood-differential</link><title>Blood Differential Test</title><description>* Blood Differential Test inflammatory bowel disease) a parasitic or viral infection a bacterial infection in your heart a collagen vascular disease (e.g. lupus, vasculitis, or rheumatoid arthritis) certain types of leukemia You may have too high a percentage of eosinophils in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:09:39">http://www.healthline.com/health/multiple-sclerosis/prognosis</link><title>Multiple Sclerosis (MS) Diagnosis and Progression</title><description>* Multiple Sclerosis (MS) Diagnosis and Progression It’s crucial to understand how doctors assess MS symptoms and how the severity of the disease increases over time. MS is caused by the body’s defense system attacking myelin, the fatty substance surrounding and protecting nerve fibers in the central ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:12:11">http://www.healthline.com/health/pregnancy/hypertension-eclampsia</link><title>Overview of Eclampsia</title><description>* Overview of Eclampsia ...hydatidiform mole (an abnormal pregnancy resulting in a mass of cysts that resemble a bunch of grapes), collagen vascular disease, or antiphospholipid syndrome.How Does Eclampsia Differ From Epilepsy? Generally, eclampsia occurs within 4 weeks of giving...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:15:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/cervical-incomptence-and-cerclage-4-diagnosis</link><title>Cervical Incomptence and Cerclage - 4 - Diagnosis</title><description>* Cervical Incomptence and Cerclage - 4 - Diagnosis As pointed out in our previous posts on this subject, one of the greatest frustrations of cervical incompetence has been to establish its diagnosis in a timely and reliable fashion. Since multiple factors can contribute to cervical incompetence, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:17:37">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/trandolapril-verapamil</link><title>Trandolapril; Verapamil sustained-release tablets</title><description>* Trandolapril; Verapamil sustained-release tablets Trandolapril; Verapamil sustained-release tablets What is this medicine? TRANDOLAPRIL; VERAPAMIL (tran DOLE a pril; ver AP a mil) is a combination of two drugs. It is used to treat high blood pressure. This medicine may be used for other...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>