<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:20:57" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:20:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/men-teens-who-play-sports-more-likely-to-abuse-032614</link><title>Study: Boys Who Play High School Sports More Likely to Be Abusive in Relationships</title><description>* Study: Boys Who Play High School Sports More Likely to Be Abusive in Relationships Why are young football and basketball players more likely to be aggressive toward their partners off the field?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:21:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/sports-related-injuries-among-high-school-athletes-united-states</link><title>Sports-related injuries among high school athletes in the United States</title><description>* Sports-related injuries among high school athletes in the United States A report recently published by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) encourages teens to participate in high school sports to promote a healthy lifestyle and documents a huge increase in high school sports participation in the last thi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:23:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/girls-and-sports-results-seventeen-and-wnba</link><title>Girls and Sports - Results from Seventeen and WNBA</title><description>* Girls and Sports - Results from Seventeen and WNBA Seventeen Magazine and the Women's National Basketball Association (WNBA) recently conducted a survey about how sports impact the lives of teen girls. The results may surprise you - they did me. According to this survey (of only about 1,000 young wom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:24:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/national-girls-and-women-sports-day-support-title-ix</link><title>National Girls and Women in Sports Day: Support Title IX</title><description>* National Girls and Women in Sports Day: Support Title IX February 6, 2008 is National Girls and Women in Sports Day, celebrated to honor the achievement of and encourage the participation of female athletes. Besides the obvious health and fitness benefits of participating in sports, adolescent athletes hav...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:25:15">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/newsbites-march-9</link><title>Newsbites: March 9</title><description>* Newsbites: March 9 Recall last week when Prince Charles bad mouthed McDonald's. As I'm sure you had predicted there's been some backlash against Chuck. But not from McDonald's so much as from the British media. Various British newspapers told the Prince to "Burger Off"...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>