<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:29:45" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:29:46">http://www.healthline.com/health/hospital-acquired-nosocomial-infections</link><title>Hospital-Acquired (Nosocomial) Infections</title><description>* Hospital-Acquired (Nosocomial) Infections What Are Nosocomial Infections? Nosocomial infections are infections are acquired in hospitals and other healthcare facilities. To be classified as a nosocomial infection, the patient must have been admitted for reasons other than the infection. He o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:33:15">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-probiotics-1</link><title>Probiotics</title><description>* Probiotics AB-yogurt, acidophilus, acidophilus milk, antibiophilus, bacillus, Bifidobacteria, Bifidobacterium animalis ssp. lactis (BB-12), Bifidobacterium DN-173 010, Enterococcus, Enterococcus faecium M-74, escherichia, fermented soymilk, flora, fructo-oligos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:36:14">http://www.healthline.com/health/pseudomonas-infections</link><title>Pseudomonas Infections</title><description>* Pseudomonas Infections What Are Pseudomonas Infections? Pseudomonas infections are diseases caused by a bacterium from the genus Pseudomonas. The bacteria are found widely in the environment, such as in soil, water, and plants. They usually do not cause infection in health...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:37:45">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/aging-healthcare-acquired-infections-kill-nearly-a-hundred-thousand-a-year-072713</link><title>99,000 Americans Die of Healthcare-Aquired Infections Every Year</title><description>* 99,000 Americans Die of Healthcare-Aquired Infections Every Year More work needs to be done to combat the problem of infections acquired in hospitals and doctors' offices, which the CDC director calls a 'winnable battle.'...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:38:59">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/doctors-stethoscopes-source-of-contamination-022814</link><title>Germ-Covered Stethoscopes Cause Hospital-Acquired Infections, Study Finds</title><description>* Germ-Covered Stethoscopes Cause Hospital-Acquired Infections, Study Finds A new study shows that stethoscopes need to be disinfected between patients to prevent contamination inside the healthcare system.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:41:34">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/selenium</link><title>Selenium (Se)</title><description>* Selenium (Se) Se 5-methylselenocysteine MSC, adrusen zinco, atomic number 34, DL-selenomethionine, benzisoselenazol, ebselen, gamma-glutamyl-selenomethyl-SeCys, high-selenium yeast, L-selenomethionine, methylseleninic acid, methyl selenol, monomethylated Se, Na2Se...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:42:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-antibiotic-resistant-bacteria-a-national-threat-091613</link><title>CDC: We're Buying Time with Antibiotic-Resistant Infections</title><description>* CDC: We're Buying Time with Antibiotic-Resistant Infections Despite a decrease in MRSA infection rates, the CDC director says we need to preserve antibiotic effectiveness for the future.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:46:10">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/arginine</link><title>Arginine</title><description>* Arginine L-arginine 2-Amino-5-guanidinopentanoic acid, agmatine, Arg, arginine, arginine hydrochloride (intravenous formulation), Ark1, decarboxylated arginine, dipeptide arginyl aspartate, HeartBar®, L-arg, L-arginine, L-arginine aspartate, NG-monomethyl-L-a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:47:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/cdc-reports-small-reduction-in-hospital-infections-032614</link><title>One in 25 Patients Infected at U.S. Hospitals</title><description>* One in 25 Patients Infected at U.S. Hospitals The CDC has reported some improvement in preventing deadly infections, though there's still work to be done.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:48:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/antibacterial-soaps-encourage-mrsa-in-nose-041014</link><title>Antibacterial Soaps Encourage MRSA Bacteria to Colonize Your Nose</title><description>* Antibacterial Soaps Encourage MRSA Bacteria to Colonize Your Nose Could you be helping a superbug take hold in your nasal secretions?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>