<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7299">row row row your boat lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:03:49" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7299-01"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/prevent-knee-pain-when-rowing</link><title>Prevent Knee Pain When Rowing</title><description>* Prevent Knee Pain When Rowing Rowing can be fun, and good functional exercise.To prevent knee pain when rowing any craft or machine that uses foot bracing, foot wells, or other foot counter-force, do not push off the ball of the foot, pictured above.Keep your heels down. Push off...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7299-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7299_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:05:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/fast-fitness-handstand-rows</link><title>Fast Fitness - Handstand Rows</title><description>* Fast Fitness - Handstand Rows Here is Friday Fast Fitness - rows to strengthen the upper body, practice balance and neutral spine, and avoid lower disc injury from bad forward bending.Readers have been writing in, excited about doing handstands for the first time or improving the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7299-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7299_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:08:25">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/fast-fitness-prevent-back-pain-when-rowing</link><title>Fast Fitness - Prevent Back Pain When Rowing</title><description>* Fast Fitness - Prevent Back Pain When Rowing Here is Friday Fast Fitness - make rowing good exercise, not bad sitting:Don't round your spine forward (left). Rounding pushes discs outward. Left drawing shows disc pushing outward by bending the vertebrae to that they open in back. Rounded sitting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7299-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7299_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:10:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/fast-friday-incline-rowing-pull-ups</link><title>Fast Friday - Incline Rowing Pull Ups</title><description>* Fast Friday - Incline Rowing Pull Ups Here is Fast Friday Fitness - Fun rows to strengthen your back, chest, arms, grip, and torso muscles, without bending over or forward, using commonly available objects, no gym needed:To start, leave both feet on the ground. Hold a low study pipe, bra...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7299-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7299_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/diver-down-flags-boating-swimming-scuba-safer-and-smarter</link><title>Diver Down Flags - Boating, Swimming, SCUBA Safer and Smarter</title><description>* Diver Down Flags - Boating, Swimming, SCUBA Safer and Smarter My father, some of my brothers, and I loved swimming together in a cold river in the northern United States. We enjoyed fun discussions treading water at the turn-around points. One day, a speedboat left the boating lanes and came at us. I stared dum...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>