<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:16:04" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-01"><link>http://symptom.healthline.com/symptomsearch?addterm=Feet%20Itching</link><title>Feet itching | Symptom Search</title><description>* Feet itching | Symptom Search Health Topics Health Topics. Acid Reflux; Alcohol Addiction; Allergies; Alzheimer's &amp; Dementia; Anxiety; Asthma; Bipolar Disorder; Chronic Pain; Cold &amp; Flu; COPD; Crohn's Disease; Depression; Fibromyalgia; Heart Disease; Hypertension; Insomnia &amp; Slee...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-02"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/eczema</link><title>Eczema</title><description>* Eczema What Is Eczema? Eczema is a common skin condition marked itchy and inflamed patches of skin. It is also known as atopic dermatitis. It is more common in babies and young children. It occurs on the faces of infants, as well as inside the elbows and be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-03"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/food-allergy-symptoms</link><title>Food Allergy Symptoms</title><description>* Food Allergy Symptoms Food allergies can cause a wide range of symptoms, which usually begin immediately or within two hours of eating and include, among others: Rash or hives Red or itchy skin Stuffy or itchy nose Sneezing Itchy and teary eyes Vomiting, stomach cramps, g...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:25:40">http://www.healthline.com/health/dyshidrotic-eczema</link><title>Dyshidrotic Eczema</title><description>* Dyshidrotic Eczema Overview Dyshidrotic eczema, or dyshidrosis, is a skin condition in which blisters develop on the soles of your feet and/or the palms of your hands. The blisters are usually itchy and may be filled with fluid. Blisters normally last for about three w...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:26:30">http://www.healthline.com/health/eczema</link><title>Eczema Symptoms</title><description>* Eczema Symptoms Eczema is characterized by itchy, dry, rough, flakey, inflamed, and irritated skin that can flare-up, subside, and then flare again. It looks like a rash on the skin. The skin condition usually affects the arms (particularly the inner elbow), behind ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:28:18">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-ways-treat-your-feet</link><title>Healthy Ways to Treat Your Feet</title><description>* Healthy Ways to Treat Your Feet You can see the evidence on your hands: Dry wrinkles, overgrown cuticles, chapped knuckles and itchy skin. The winter months, with their low humidity, sharp winds, and indoor heating, can strip skin of its moisture and leave hands unsightly and uncom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:32:01">http://www.healthline.com/health/type-2-diabetes/skin-problems</link><title>Type 2 Diabetes and Skin Health</title><description>* Type 2 Diabetes and Skin Health Skin problems of all types, including bacterial infections like boils and carbuncles, are worsened by type 2 diabetes. According to the American Diabetes Association, more than one-third of all diabetics experience skin-related complications. Besides...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-08"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies/hay-fever-rash-video–test2</link><title>Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever?</title><description>* Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever? Hay fever symptoms are fairly well-known. Sneezing, watery eyes, and congestion are all allergic reactions to airborne particles, but skin irritation is one of the symptoms of hay fever that gets little attention. Said to affect more than one in five...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-09"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies/hay-fever-rash-video–test4</link><title>Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever?</title><description>* Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever? Hay fever symptoms are fairly well-known. Sneezing, watery eyes, and congestion are all allergic reactions to airborne particles, but skin irritation is one of the symptoms of hay fever that gets little attention. Said to affect more than one in five...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7303-10"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies/hay-fever-rash-video–test1</link><title>Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever?</title><description>* Do You Have a Rash from Hay Fever? Hay fever symptoms are fairly well-known. Sneezing, watery eyes, and congestion are all allergic reactions to airborne particles, but skin irritation is one of the symptoms of hay fever that gets little attention. Said to affect more than one in five...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>