<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:49:21" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:49:21">http://www.healthline.com/health/common-cold-causes</link><title>Common Cold Causes</title><description>* Common Cold Causes The cold is a common infection of the upper respiratory tract. Although many people think you can catch a cold by not dressing warmly enough in the winter, it is a myth that you can catch the common cold from exposure to chilly weather. The real culp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:52:24">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/japanese-ama-divers-cold-clothing-and-children</link><title>Japanese Ama Divers - Cold, Clothing, and Children</title><description>* Japanese Ama Divers - Cold, Clothing, and Children The multi-part story of diving with the Japanese Diving Women continues here:In villages along the Japanese coasts, diving by the AmaSan for sea plants and other harvests goes on without tourist fanfare. We dived in the cool, dim waters, rubbing leav...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:54:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/three-common-swimming-and-scuba-myths-news-again</link><title>Three Common Swimming and SCUBA Myths in the News Again</title><description>* Three Common Swimming and SCUBA Myths in the News Again On Monday July 7, a news show Troubled Waters featured a story of two scuba divers who floated 19 hours overnight after they and their dive boat did not connect after a dive on the Great Barrier Reef in Australia.In their television interview, the tw...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:55:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/jellyfish-florida</link><title>Jellyfish in Florida</title><description>* Jellyfish in Florida This time of year, Portuguese man-of-war jellyfish wash up on the beaches in South Florida. When they are in the area, strong breezes directed toward shore drive them into the surf. As the lifeguards and residents in the area know, they can pack quit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:56:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/thank-you-laikaspoetnik-grand-rounds-netherlands</link><title>Thank You LaikaSpoetnik Grand Rounds From The Netherlands</title><description>* Thank You LaikaSpoetnik Grand Rounds From The Netherlands Thank you Jacqueline for hosting Grand Rounds Vol. 6 No. 2 this week on the LaikaSpoetnik MedLibLog and including my article Fast Fitness - Stretch For Menstrual Cramps - a quick stretching technique to ease symptoms of menstrual and other uterine cr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:00:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/extremes-survival-injuries-faster-higher-stronger-fitness-fixer</link><title>Extremes, Survival, Injuries, Faster Higher Stronger - Fitness Fixer</title><description>* Extremes, Survival, Injuries, Faster Higher Stronger - Fitness Fixer My professional and life work is understanding and studyMy professional and life work is understanding and studying the fastest, highest, quickest, coldest, hottest, bravest, strongest in human physiology. I study the body in extremes. I study what m...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:02:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/immune-system-boosters</link><title>Foods That Boost the Immune System</title><description>* Foods That Boost the Immune System Include the following 10 immune system boosters in your recipes and meal planning, and you'll increase your family's chances of fighting off those winter bugs before they get you sick.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:04:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/meat-tenderizer-jellyfish-sting</link><title>Meat Tenderizer for a Jellyfish Sting</title><description>* Meat Tenderizer for a Jellyfish Sting Anonymous has left a new comment on your post "Myths to Debunk": "What about meat tenderizer for a jellyfish sting? I know that hot water works well as it causes the venom proteins to refold, but the usual folk treatment for Man 'o War stings here in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:05:56">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/jellyfish-tale</link><title>A Jellyfish Tale</title><description>* A Jellyfish Tale In May, I enjoyed a few days' diving in the Baja at La Paz, Mexico. At that time of year, the water is relatively cool and the visibility isn't perfect, but there is still much to see underwater as the nutrients arrive in the currents prior to the re...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:08:57">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/hot-water-jellyfish-stings</link><title>Hot Water for Jellyfish Stings</title><description>* Hot Water for Jellyfish Stings There are multiple therapies recommended for field therapy (first aid) for jellyfish stings. These include topical decontaminants, such as vinegar (acetic acid), rubbing alcohol, papain, citrus juice, ammonia, and others; rapid decontamination combin...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>