<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7320">cayenne pepper plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:58:21" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:58:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/skin-blushing-flushing</link><title>Skin Flushing/Blushing</title><description>* Skin Flushing/Blushing These include cayenne pepper, paprika, chili peppers, and red peppers. Eating these foods may raise your body temperature and cause facial redness. Also, handling these types of foods can cause skin redness and irritation. Emotional Triggers Extreme emotions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:01:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/anti-acne-diet</link><title>Anti-Acne Diet</title><description>* Anti-Acne Diet Spicy foods such as Indian foods that are rich in curry or foods with cayenne or hot peppers are triggers for rosacea and should be avoided," says Taylor.More from AOL Health:How to Be HappyWhat Your Skin is Telling YouCooler Cleanse Review...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:03:04">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/black-pepper</link><title>Black pepper (Piper nigrum)</title><description>* Black pepper (Piper nigrum) Piper nigrum Bai hu jiao (Chinese), beta-caryophyllene, Bioperine®, bisalkaloids, black pepper essential oil, black pepper oil, Brazilian black pepper, dipiperamide D, dipiperamide E, golmirch (Hindi), green pepper, guineensine, kaalii mirch (Hindi),...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:05:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/put-little-spice-your-life</link><title>Put a Little Spice in Your Life!</title><description>* Put a Little Spice in Your Life! My husband can eat raw Habaneros, the hottest pepper on the planet. Sometimes I think he actually has an iron stomach. I on the other hand whimper if the slightest hint of a jalapeno (5 times milder) crosses my lips. But honestly, I wish I wasn’t so ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:08:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diabetes/spring-cleaning-from-inside-out</link><title>Spring Cleaning: From the Inside Out</title><description>* Spring Cleaning: From the Inside Out The temperature is warming up and the flowers are blooming, which only means one thing - spring is in the air! With spring, comes spring cleaning. Not just cleaning up your home, but also cleaning up your eating habits and overall lifestyle. After a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:11:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/oh-crumbs/byo-cookout-tips-for-celiacs</link><title>BYO: Cookout Tips for Celiacs</title><description>* BYO: Cookout Tips for Celiacs I am having one of those weeks where I just feel icky. From a constant, mild headache to a slightly irritated digestive system, I cannot seem to go more than a few hours before heading off to the nearest restroom. Unfortunately, this is not that unco...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:14:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/recipe-week-california-chicken-wrap</link><title>Recipe of the Week: California Chicken Wrap</title><description>* Recipe of the Week: California Chicken Wrap cayenne pepper (optional)4 10-inch flour tortillas (try to find whole wheat.. they are much more common now)2 cups shredded romaineDirections:1. Mince half of the roasted peppers; set aside the other half. 2. Combine the minced red and green bell peppers,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:16:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/high-sodium-dishes</link><title>High Sodium Dishes</title><description>* High Sodium Dishes I love salt. I love the taste of salt and I love salty food. Salt simply tastes good. Unfortunately, too much salt isn't good for us. It can lead to high blood pressure which can lead to stroke.Salt is listed as sodium on a food label, and the US Die...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:20:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/simple-summer-eating</link><title>Simple Summer Eating</title><description>* Simple Summer Eating The best part of the year and my favorite time of the year is finally here! That’s right …it’s summer time. Warmer temperatures mean more days spent outdoors, more pool days with the kids, backyard BBQ’s, vacations, and many other social events that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7320-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7320_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:22:19">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/children-lead-found-in-imported-hot-sauces-081313</link><title>Mexican Hot Sauces Contain Unsafe Levels of Lead</title><description>* Mexican Hot Sauces Contain Unsafe Levels of Lead Which hot sauce brands should you avoid, and which are safe to eat?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>