<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7344">pampered chef</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:52:07" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-01"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/iron-chef-heart-healthy-recipe-challenge</link><title>Iron Chef Heart-Healthy Recipe Challenge</title><description>* Iron Chef Heart-Healthy Recipe Challenge High cholesterol doesn’t mean you can’t eat anything—it just means you should eat differently. Get new menu ideas and a better perspective on healthy eating with these tasty recipes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:53:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/straight-talk-stanford-er/too-many-chefs</link><title>Too Many Chefs</title><description>* Too Many Chefs I am now in Los Angeles visiting my sister and her newly born daughter. Immediately after work I drove straight for San Jose and Southwest Airlines to see the first new member in our small family. The stark transition of my last two hours in the emer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:56:21">http://www.healthline.com/health/mens-health/stomach-cancer-story</link><title>Personal Stomach Cancer Story: Bryan Au, Chef, L.A., CA</title><description>* Personal Stomach Cancer Story: Bryan Au, Chef, L.A., CA Bryan Au, Chef, LA, CAHealthline: Can you give us a little background about your father’s experience with stomach cancer? Bryan: Basically, he ate too much meat—especially the kind that has sodium nitrate, which is a leading cause of stomach cancer.W...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:57:27">http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies/questions-for-your-server</link><title>Dining Out: Questions for Your Server</title><description>* Dining Out: Questions for Your Server If you have an allergy or other condition that affects how your body handles food, it can make a simple joy like eating out more complicated, but it doesn’t make it impossible. One of the keys to eating out when you have food restrictions is communic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:59:37">http://www.healthline.com/health/high-cholesterol/pinterest-contest</link><title>Pinterest Contest</title><description>* Pinterest Contest var switchTo5x=true; stLight.options({publisher: "384b89f4-cd27-4ec8-9727-b7619b079b00", onhover: false}); .stButton .stFb, .stButton .stTwbutton, .stButton .stMainServices { background-image:none !important; } .stButton .stBubble { background-image:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:02:18">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/cooking-tips-for-crohns-disease</link><title>Tips for Stress-Free Cooking</title><description>* Tips for Stress-Free Cooking Use these simple tips to take some of the work out of planning and preparing meals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:05:09">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/the-acid-reflux-solution/cooking-for-charity-and-finding-inspiration-in-unlikely-places</link><title>Cooking For Charity and Finding Inspiration in Unlikely Places</title><description>* Cooking For Charity and Finding Inspiration in Unlikely Places About a month ago I was approached to participate in a charity raffle. I agreed, seeing as I am not the sort of person to say no to a good cause. I offered to cook meals out of my book, The Acid Reflux Solution,as my auction item. I thought it would ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-08"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/x-treme-eating-tips-avoid</link><title>X-Treme Eating: Tips to Avoid</title><description>* X-Treme Eating: Tips to Avoid Center for Science in the Public Interest (CSPI) is at it again. (If you remember I've referred to them a couple times in recent posts Soda Not So Lucrative for Schools and Weight Loss Claims Under Fire) The consumer watchdog group has coined the phr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:08:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/smart-phone-apps-health-conscious-traveler</link><title>Smart Phone Apps for the Health Conscious Traveler</title><description>* Smart Phone Apps for the Health Conscious Traveler It’s vacation season – time to venture out to an unknown city and seek new experiences. At home, you may be comforted by your routine, but a new city can offer endless opportunities to explore a side of yourself you didn’t know existed. Health and we...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7344-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7344_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:11:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/its-food-revolution</link><title>It's a Food Revolution!</title><description>* It's a Food Revolution! Did you see Jamie Oliver's Food Revolution last Friday on ABC? If you missed it, you can watch the first two episodes here.The gist of the show is that Jamie, a trained chef from England who single handedly changed school food in England, goes in to ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>