<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:41" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-01"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-healthcare-guide/state-map</link><title>Map State</title><description>* Map State function state_hover(s_id) { for(var i = 0; i Health Insurance Exchanges by State Find the state that you live in on the interactive map below for information on where you can shop for and compare health insurance plans. Some states have created thei...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-02"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/surviving-wilderness-emergency-2</link><title>Surviving A Wilderness Emergency 2</title><description>* Surviving A Wilderness Emergency 2 This is the tenth post based upon educational sessions and syllabus material presented at the Wilderness Medical Society Annual Meeting &amp; 25th Anniversary held in Snowmass, Colorado from July 25-30. It’s based upon an excellent presentation given...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-03"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/healthmap-maps-epidemic-text-alerts-graphical-map-world</link><title>HEALTHmap Maps Epidemic Text Alerts to a Graphical Map of the World</title><description>* HEALTHmap Maps Epidemic Text Alerts to a Graphical Map of the World HEALTHmap provides a jumping-off point for real-time information on emerging infectious diseases and has particular interest for public health officials and international travelers.It "brings together disparate data sources to achieve a unified and c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-04"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/plain-talk-about-adolescent-reproductive-health</link><title>Plain Talk About Adolescent Reproductive Health</title><description>* Plain Talk About Adolescent Reproductive Health In the United States, 4 out of 10 young women become pregnant at least once before they are 20, giving us the highest rates of teen pregnancy and births in the Western industrialized world (AMCHP). The majority of these pregnancies are unintended, an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:37:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/tobacco-atlas-3rd-edition</link><title>The Tobacco Atlas (3rd Edition)</title><description>* The Tobacco Atlas (3rd Edition) Today I received my 2009 copy of The Tobacco Atlas (3rd edition). This an excellent and comprehensive report that maps the history, documents the current situation, and predicts the future of the tobacco epidemic.For tobacco geeks like myself it is p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:40:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/visual-medical-dictionary-and-curehunter-engine</link><title>A Visual Medical Dictionary and the CureHunter Engine</title><description>* A Visual Medical Dictionary and the CureHunter Engine Curehunter.com offers a free "visual medical dictionary" at https://www.curehunter.com/public/dictionary.do. The idea is similar to Healthlines' HealthMaps -- an interrelated web of complex terms is displayed as a simple map or diagram to enhance und...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:42:19">http://www.healthline.com/health/bike-sharing-programs-are-shaking-inner-city-transportation</link><title>Bike Sharing Programs Are Shaking Up Inner City Travel</title><description>* Bike Sharing Programs Are Shaking Up Inner City Travel Whether you are looking to lessen your carbon footprint, drop a few pounds, or avoid rush hour traffic, riding a bicycle is a great way to spice up your daily commute. For those who don’t own a bicycle, bike sharing programs are popping up across the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:44:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/crohns-disease/restroom-legislation</link><title>The Restroom Access Act: A Major Victory for Crohn’s Patients</title><description>* The Restroom Access Act: A Major Victory for Crohn’s Patients Some of the best ideas occur to people while they are in the bathroom. In the case of Allyson Bain, it was a lack of restroom accessibility that helped launch critical legislation, websites, and several iPhone apps. It all started a decade ago, when ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:46:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-healthcare-guide/new-york-health-exchange</link><title>NY State of Health</title><description>* NY State of Health New York Overview of New York’s Health Insurance Exchange When the Affordable Care Act was passed in 2010, states gained the opportunity to build health insurance marketplaces called exchanges. The state of New York's exchange is called NY State of H...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7348-10"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/thyroid-questions-our-readers-communicating-your-doctor</link><title>Thyroid Questions from Our Readers: Communicating with Your Doctor</title><description>* Thyroid Questions from Our Readers: Communicating with Your Doctor None of our blog posts have generated as much interest or as many comments as Some Symptoms of Functional Thyroid Disease. Let's start out by stating that I am not a thyroid disease expert and that blog posts are not exactly the right forum for getti...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>