<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7401">yo mama jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:33:12" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7401-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7401_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:33:13">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/yohimbine</link><title>Yohimbine tablets</title><description>* Yohimbine tablets Yohimbine tablets What is this medicine? YOHIMBINE (yoh HIM been) is used to treat erectile dysfunction (ED) in men. This medicine may be used for other purposes; ask your health care provider or pharmacist if you have questions. What sho...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7401-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7401_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:35:29">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/yohimbe-bark-extract</link><title>Yohimbe bark extract (Pausinystalia yohimbe Pierre ex Beille Rubiaceae)</title><description>* Yohimbe bark extract (Pausinystalia yohimbe Pierre ex Beille Rubiaceae) Pausinystalia yohimbe Corynanthe yohimbi Aphrodien, Corynanthe johimbi, Corynanthe yohimbi, corynine, iohimbina (Brazilian Portuguese), johimbe (Danish, Dutch, English, Hungarian), johimbi, kiima-johimbepuu (Estonian), P. yohimbe (CCD-X), Pausinystal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7401-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7401_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:37:56">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-sports-supplements</link><title>Sports supplements</title><description>* Sports supplements Amphetamines, anabolic steroids, androstenediol, androstenedione, athlete nutrition, athletic performance, blood doping, caffeine, carbohydrate loading, carnitine, chromium, creatine, DHEA, dehydroepiandrosterone, ephedrine, ergogenic aids, exercise,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7401-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7401_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:39:46">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/arginine</link><title>Arginine</title><description>* Arginine L-arginine 2-Amino-5-guanidinopentanoic acid, agmatine, Arg, arginine, arginine hydrochloride (intravenous formulation), Ark1, decarboxylated arginine, dipeptide arginyl aspartate, HeartBar®, L-arg, L-arginine, L-arginine aspartate, NG-monomethyl-L-a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7401-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7401_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:41:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/boost-your-libido-10-natural-tips</link><title>Boost Your Libido with These 10 Natural Tips</title><description>* Boost Your Libido with These 10 Natural Tips If your libido needs a boost and you’re not ready to try prescription medications, one or more of these 10 natural tips could help you and your partner become happier between the sheets.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>