<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:42:54" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:42:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/nit-pickers-should-get-their-head-examined</link><title>Nit Pickers Should Get Their Head Examined</title><description>* Nit Pickers Should Get Their Head Examined Dear parent, the school nurse has determined that little Johnny has a small ecosystem growing in his hair and he is being excluded from school until every nit is nixed." In observance of Head Lice Prevention Month the National Pediculosis Association...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:44:17">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/chocolate-amore</link><title>Chocolate Amore!</title><description>* Chocolate Amore! I love, love, love chocolate! Are you with me? If you read this blog, you know I'm a big movie buff and the film Chocolat (with the amazing Johnny Depp) is one of my very favorites. Like the main character Vianne Rocher, I believe chocolate is enchan...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:45:44">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/aids-why-are-people-color-hit-so-hard</link><title>AIDS: Why are people of color hit so hard?</title><description>* AIDS: Why are people of color hit so hard? Last summer I finally got around to reading Edward Hooper's fascinating work, The River: A Journey to the Source of HIV and AIDS. First published in 1999, investigative journalist Hooper goes where scientists feared to tread, proposing alternative th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:47:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/pre-op-dr-t</link><title>Pre-op Dr T!</title><description>* Pre-op Dr T! Well, in about one hour and forty-five minutes I will become a ‘patient’ myself. That’s because at midnight, I can no longer eat or drink anything until after I have had my left shoulder operated on in the morning. I am NOT looking forward to that, b...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:48:33">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-gardening/extra-sensory-gardening</link><title>Gardening for the Senses</title><description>* Gardening for the Senses Experience a breath-taking perennial border, a container billowing with tropical color, or the air filled with an illusive perfume; a smile emerges, both inwardly and outwardly. While some of a garden’s allure is based on horticulture, for most of us...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>