<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:53:08" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:53:08">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-phototherapy</link><title>Light therapy</title><description>* Light therapy Bioptron Phototherapy Acne, bili blanket, BIOPTRON, delayed sleep phase syndrome, DSPS, light therapy, neonatal jaundice, photomedicine, phototherapy, psoriasis, SAD, seasonal affective disorder. Light therapy, also known as phototherapy, is the use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:54:27">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/light-therapy</link><title>Light Therapy and Depression</title><description>* Light Therapy and Depression Light therapy, also known as phototherapy, is a treatment in which the patient is exposed to an artificial light source. The therapy primarily treats seasonal affective disorder (SAD). Seasonal affective disorder is the formal name of a type of depression...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:56:54">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/guttate-psoriasis-pictures</link><title>Guttate Psoriasis Pictures</title><description>* Guttate Psoriasis Pictures Guttate is a type of psoriasis in which the affected patches of skin appear as small, separated teardrops. Click through to see pictures of guttate psoriasis.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:58:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/inverse-psoriasis</link><title>What Does Inverse Psoriasis Look Like?</title><description>* What Does Inverse Psoriasis Look Like? Inverse psoriasis is a form of the disease that affects skin folds and is usually indicated by a red, shiny, smooth rash. Learn how to spot and treat it.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:00:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/psoriasis-diet</link><title>Psoriasis Diet: Fact or Fiction?</title><description>* Psoriasis Diet: Fact or Fiction? Some research suggests that making certain diet choices may help with psoriasis treatment. Learn more in this slideshow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:03:02">http://www.healthline.com/health/seasonal-affective-disorder</link><title>Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>* Seasonal Affective Disorder Treatment for Seasonal Affective Disorder Light therapy is the primary treatment for SAD. A portable light box provides you with a bright light that mimics sunlight. Light therapy, also called phototherapy, is a daily treatment that you will undergo throughout...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:04:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/psoriasis/benefits-and-risks-of-sunlight</link><title>Sun &amp; Psoriasis: The Benefits &amp; Risks</title><description>* Sun &amp; Psoriasis: The Benefits &amp; Risks Phototherapy Phototherapy is the term used to describe natural or synthetic light treatment for psoriasis. Your skin absorbs the ultraviolet rays as you sunbathe or expose your skin to a special light box. The sun’s ultraviolet rays are categorized as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:06:02">http://www.healthline.com/health/psoriasis/drugs</link><title>Psoriasis Drugs</title><description>* Psoriasis Drugs ...normalize DNA activity in your skin cells and remove scales, and is sometimes used in combination with phototherapy. Doctors recommend that this cream stay on your skin for a brief time since it can irritate skin if left too long, and cause staining....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:07:41">http://www.healthline.com/health/crigler-najjar-syndrome</link><title>Crigler's-Najjar Syndrome</title><description>* Crigler's-Najjar Syndrome Phototherapy The most common treatment for babies with CNS is light therapy, also known as phototherapy. This noninvasive procedure exposes the child’s skin to blue light to prevent or treat yellowing of the skin. This treatment is more successful...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:08:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/what-seasonal-affective-disorder</link><title>What is Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>* What is Seasonal Affective Disorder ...energyIrritability and sluggishnessWithdrawal from others Treating SAD There are two main treatments for SAD: light therapy and home management. Light therapy. Light therapy involves the use of a special lamp that contains very bright light that mimics...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>