<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:12:13" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:12:14">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/adhd-children-whats-latest</link><title>ADHD in Children: What’s the Latest?</title><description>* ADHD in Children: What’s the Latest? ADHD in children seems to be rising. Is that because doctors are more aware of it today? Learn about the gender gap, treatments, and outlook for kids with ADHD.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:12:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/being-parent-adhd-child</link><title>Being the Parent of a Child with ADHD</title><description>* Being the Parent of a Child with ADHD As the parent of a child with ADHD, no doubt you may feel overwhelmed at times. Follow our tips for keeping your child on track while keeping yourself intact.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:14:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/bullying-anger-social-issues</link><title>Bullying, Anger, and Other Social Issues for Children with ADHD</title><description>* Bullying, Anger, and Other Social Issues for Children with ADHD Bullying 101: Signs and What You Can Do About It Bullying is defined as repeated, aggressive behavior by one child to another. There are three types of bullying: verbal bullying: name calling, teasing, threateningphysical bullying: pushing, hitting, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:14:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/mental-adhd-medications-dont-affect-substance-abuse-risk-052913</link><title>ADHD Medication in Childhood Doesn’t Affect Later Substance Abuse Risk</title><description>* ADHD Medication in Childhood Doesn’t Affect Later Substance Abuse Risk UCLA research shows that ADHD medications have no impact on future substance abuse, contradicting decade-old research that says stimulants have a protective effect.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:17:15">http://www.healthline.com/health/consumer-reports-adhd</link><title>ConsumerReports.org: Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)</title><description>* ConsumerReports.org: Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) ...help parents, and sometimes teachers, build the skills to cope with, and respond appropriately to, a child's ADHD behaviors. The use of drugs to treat ADHD has been more thoroughly evaluated over the years than other forms of treatment. But there is some...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:20:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/adhd-medication-children</link><title>ADHD Medication for Children: Is It Safe?</title><description>* ADHD Medication for Children: Is It Safe? Medication is a common treatment for ADHD symptoms. There are several medications prescribed to treat symptoms, but they do come with some risks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:21:16">http://www.healthline.com/health/attention-deficit-hyperactivity-disorder-adhd-facts-and-statistics</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD): Facts and Statistics</title><description>* Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD): Facts and Statistics What Is ADHD? Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a condition characterized by difficulty paying attention, impulsive actions, and excess amounts of energy. It frequently appears in childhood. ADHD is a neuro-developmental disorder tha...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:22:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/aspergers-adhd</link><title>Asperger’s or ADHD? Symptoms, Diagnosis, and Treatments</title><description>* Asperger’s or ADHD? Symptoms, Diagnosis, and Treatments ADHD and Asperger's syndrome share common symptoms, but they differ in many important ways. Here is how to tell if your child has either and how to treat it.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:24:30">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd</link><title>ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder)</title><description>* ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder) Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a mental disorder that causes high levels of hyper and disruptive behaviors. ADHD can lead to difficulties.

ADHD Basics \- Assess Your Symptoms \- Complications \- Adult ADHD \- Treatment &amp; Support</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:27:18">http://www.healthline.com/health/adhd/iq-adhd</link><title>Why Being Smart Doesn't Help People With ADHD</title><description>* Why Being Smart Doesn't Help People With ADHD Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a condition that impacts the lives of people young and old, across the country and around the world. Afflicting more than seven percent of school-aged children and as much as five percent of adults, ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>