<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:39" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/mental-risk-factors-for-young-onset-dementia-identified-081213</link><title>Alcohol Use and 8 Other Risk Factors for Early Dementia Identified</title><description>* Alcohol Use and 8 Other Risk Factors for Early Dementia Identified New research shows nine risk factors trigger early onset dementia, many of which can be prevented beginning in adolescence.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:34:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/fantastically-freeze-dried</link><title>Fantastically Freeze Dried</title><description>* Fantastically Freeze Dried ...Research, it’s time for at least one category, freeze dried fruits, to get an image overhaul (pay attention Tom Cruise –– just kidding!). Scientists say these crunchy, light weight goodies retain almost all of the disease fighting phytochemicals found...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:37:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/menopause-celebrities</link><title>Famous Faces of Menopause</title><description>* Famous Faces of Menopause Healthline offers inspiration to menopausal women via five famous faces of menopause and how they’ve tackled menopause in their own unique ways.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:40:12">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/obstetrical-ultrasound-sinister-cause-concern</link><title>Obstetrical Ultrasound - A Sinister Cause for Concern?</title><description>* Obstetrical Ultrasound - A Sinister Cause for Concern? Ultrasound is so widely considered completely ‘safe’ that if you have enough money, like Tom Cruise, you can buy your own machine and use it every day; and “Fetal Foto” shops, employing 3-D and 4-D ultrasound imaging are springing up in strip malls all...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>