<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:48:29" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:48:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/cruise-2-lesson-group-therapy</link><title>Cruise - 2 - A Lesson in Group Therapy</title><description>* Cruise - 2 - A Lesson in Group Therapy The last day of the cruise was overcast, rainy, and cold. For those who had gotten too much sun already, that was probably a blessing! We were not in sight of land and the open water was rougher than it had been – out came the Dramamine. Anyway, not ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:49:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/watch-your-eyes</link><title>Watch Your Eyes!</title><description>* Watch Your Eyes! August is Eye Injury Prevention Month as well as Children's Eye Health and Safety Month.Prevent Blindness America has a great website with UV Learning Center chock full of helpful hints on ways to protect ourselves and our children from an everyday e...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:51:38">http://www.healthline.com/health/quit-smoking-teens</link><title>Help Your Teen Quit Smoking</title><description>* Help Your Teen Quit Smoking Teens who smoke become adults who smoke, and 90 percent of adults who are regular smokers started smoking before the age of 18. Most teens don’t fully understand the risks associated with smoking or the time it takes to quit. The average person who s...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:54:25">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/concept-of-risk</link><title>The Concept of Risk</title><description>* The Concept of Risk Dr. Robert “Brownie” Schoene, an enormously talented, accomplished, and insightful physician who resides within the bedrock of wilderness medicine, gave a wonderful presentation about the concept of risk at the 2010 annual summer meeting of the Wilde...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:55:25">http://www.healthline.com/health/multiple-sclerosis/depression-stress-anger</link><title>Advancing MS: Coping with Depression, Stress, and Anger</title><description>* Advancing MS: Coping with Depression, Stress, and Anger While MS can profoundly affect your physical health, it can also take a serious toll on your mental health. Although depression, stress, anxiety, and frustration are all common in people dealing with advancing MS, you don’t have to suffer silently. H...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>