<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:57:31" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:57:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/cms-releases-list-nursing-homes-which-fail-improve</link><title>CMS releases list of Nursing Homes which Fail to Improve</title><description>* CMS releases list of Nursing Homes which Fail to Improve Special Focus Facilities Not Showing Significant Improvement Most Recent Months as Region Facility Name Address City State Zip Phone Number Survey an SFF 04 Eastview Health Care Center 7755 Fourth Avenue South Birmingham AL 35206 (205) 833-0146 9/27/...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:59:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/medicare-agency-releases-list-chronically-underperforming-snfs</link><title>Medicare Agency Releases List of Chronically Underperforming SNF's</title><description>* Medicare Agency Releases List of Chronically Underperforming SNF's Skilled nursing facilities that receive federal funding - at a cost of over $72 billion to taxpayers- are inspected annually. Criteria for review are:medication errorspreventing accidents and infectionsassisting residents with activities of daily liv...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:01:18">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/procainamide-1</link><title>Procainamide tablets, extended-release or sustained-release</title><description>* Procainamide tablets, extended-release or sustained-release Procainamide tablets, extended-release or sustained-release What is this medicine? PROCAINAMIDE (proe kane A mide) is an antiarrhythmic drug. It helps make your heart beat regularly. This medicine also helps to slow rapid heartbeats. Thi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:01:52">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/acetaminophen-chlorpheniramine-phenylephrine</link><title>Acetaminophen; Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release</title><description>* Acetaminophen; Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release Acetaminophen; Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release What is this medicine? ACETAMINOPHEN; CHLORPHENIRAMINE; PHENYLEPHRINE; PHENYLTOLOXAMINE (a set a MEE noe fen; klor fen IR a meen; fen il E...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:03:46">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/chlorpheniramine-phenylephrine-4</link><title>Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine oral capsule or tablet, extended release</title><description>* Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine oral capsule or tablet, extended release Chlorpheniramine; Phenylephrine oral capsule or tablet, extended release What is this medicine? CHLORPHENIRAMINE; PHENYLEPHRINE (klor fen IR a meen; fen il EF rin) is a combination of an antihistamine and a decongestant. It is used to t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:05:50">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/carbetapentane-guaifenesin-phenylephrine-2</link><title>Carbetapentane; Guaifenesin; Phenylephrine oral tablet, extended release</title><description>* Carbetapentane; Guaifenesin; Phenylephrine oral tablet, extended release Carbetapentane; Guaifenesin; Phenylephrine oral tablet, extended release What is this medicine? CARBETAPENTANE; GUAIFENESIN; PHENYLEPHRINE (kar bay ta PEN tane; gwye FEN e sin; fen il EF rin) is a combination of a cough suppressant an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:06:47">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/ascorbic-acid-3</link><title>Ascorbic Acid, Vitamin C capsules and tablets, extended release</title><description>* Ascorbic Acid, Vitamin C capsules and tablets, extended release Ascorbic Acid, Vitamin C capsules and tablets, extended release What is this medicine? ASCORBIC ACID (a SKOR bik AS id) is a naturally occurring form of vitamin C. It is used to treat or prevent low levels of vitamin C and to treat scur...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:08:41">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/link-all-iphone-applications-app-store-sorted-release-date</link><title>A Link to All iPhone Applications in the App Store Sorted by Release Date</title><description>* A Link to All iPhone Applications in the App Store Sorted by Release Date ...be great if there was a link to the iTunes store which showed all new iPhone applications, sorted by release date?Here it is: tinyurl.com/newiphoneappsDrag the link to your browser bar, and you have one-click access to all the new iPhone apps.On days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:10:26">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/acetaminophen-phenyltoloxamine-1</link><title>Acetaminophen; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release</title><description>* Acetaminophen; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release Acetaminophen; Phenyltoloxamine oral tablets, extended release What is this medicine? ACETAMINOPHEN; PHENYLTOLOXAMINE (a set a MEE noe fen; fen ill toe LOX a meen) is a combination of a pain reliever and an antihistamine. It is used to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:11:02">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/erythromycin-6</link><title>Erythromycin tablets or capsules, delayed release</title><description>* Erythromycin tablets or capsules, delayed release Erythromycin tablets or capsules, delayed release What is this medicine? ERYTHROMYCIN (er ith roe MYE sin) is a macrolide antibiotic. It is used to treat certain kinds of bacterial infections. It will not work for colds, flu, or other ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>