<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:32:35" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:32:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/market-mcveggie</link><title>From Market to McVeggie</title><description>* From Market to McVeggie ...the Acropolis on foot (did I mention that physical activity forms the foundation of the Mediterranean Food Pyramid?). I included two photos of me in front of it so you could see just how many steps it took to reach the very top of the hill (re: the photo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:35:01">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/diabetes-cookbook-reviews</link><title>Reviews of the Top Diabetes Cookbooks</title><description>* Reviews of the Top Diabetes Cookbooks Discover 7 top diabetes cookbooks, which prove that it’s possible to prepare healthy and delicious meals that keep blood glucose levels in a safe range.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:35:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/why-i-love-garlic</link><title>Why I Love Garlic</title><description>* Why I Love Garlic It’s hard to imagine Italian, Spanish, Asian, or Middle Eastern food without the bite of garlic. Just about any food can be enhanced with the “stinking rose,” even ice cream, if the folks in Gilroy, California (billed as “The Garlic Capital of the World”)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:36:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/fuel-your-fitness-goals</link><title>Fuel Your Fitness Goals</title><description>* Fuel Your Fitness Goals Some people may think that getting into great shape means to only work out regularly, however if getting in shape is one of your New Year’s Resolutions, exercise is only half the equation. What you eat can make or break your fitness goals so that’s w...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:38:57">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/4th-july-where-grilling-easy</link><title>4th of July Where the Grilling is Easy</title><description>* 4th of July Where the Grilling is Easy ...yummy!According to The Association for Dressings and Sauces (a trade company) use 1/2 cup of marinade per pound of food. Grilled veggies can be delicious with a little olive oil, herbs and a dash of sea salt. Wrap them in tinfoil to keep them moist and...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>