<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:47:46" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7428-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7428_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:47:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/summer-health/summer-activities-for-kids</link><title>Keep Your Kids Occupied During the Summertime</title><description>* Keep Your Kids Occupied During the Summertime While most children can’t wait for summer vacation, the reality of long, lazy days turns into long hours of boredom for many. And left to their own devices, most kids are more than happy to hunker down in front of the computer, TV, or video game system....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7428-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7428_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:50:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/from-womb-to-world/do-i-get-to-be-sick-as-a-mom</link><title>Do I Get to Be Sick as a Mom?</title><description>* Do I Get to Be Sick as a Mom? Having sick children to care for is already a bummer and a challenge. The poor babies can't really convey what's wrong. Of course, when they are sick they are in need of more one on one attention. With my head throbbing and feeling completely exhausted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7428-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7428_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:51:43">http://www.healthline.com/health/reliving-childhood-summer</link><title>Reliving the Childhood Summer</title><description>* Reliving the Childhood Summer Take time to rekindle your youthful nature and rediscover child-like wonder this summer. Here are some summer break-inspired lessons to reduce your grown-up anxiety. 1. Reconnect with nature. Nature holds endless possibilities for children. Rediscover...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7428-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7428_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:53:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/avoid-vacation-relapse</link><title>Avoid the vacation relapse</title><description>* Avoid the vacation relapse As we have discussed many times on this forum, quitting smoking can be difficult, but staying quit can be even harder. Part of the reason that relapse is so common among smokers who initially quit successfully (e.g. for a month) is that whereas durin...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>