<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:34:24" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:34:25">http://www.healthline.com/symptom/tooth-decay</link><title>Dental Cavities</title><description>* Dental Cavities What Are Dental Cavities? Dental cavities are permanently damaged areas that often develop into holes in the enamel, or hard outer surface, of your teeth. Cavities are also known as tooth decay or caries. Anyone with teeth can get a cavity, but they ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:36:54">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/when-you-break-or-lose-a-tooth</link><title>When You Break or Lose A Tooth</title><description>* When You Break or Lose A Tooth Sometimes when a person falls or is struck in the mouth, a tooth is broken or knocked out. If a tooth is cracked (with the root still present and in place), there is little for the victim to do other than keep his mouth clean and avoid contact with e...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:39:27">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/first-trimester-screening-aneuploidy</link><title>First Trimester Screening for Aneuploidy</title><description>* First Trimester Screening for Aneuploidy In my November 29, 2006 post, I promised that my “next post” would focus on a discussion of first trimester screening for aneuploidy. It has taken awhile to get back to this, having had a few distractions along the way, but blogging does offer some d...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:41:03">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/how-heart-works</link><title>How Your Heart Works</title><description>* How Your Heart Works The human heart is one of the hardest working organs in the body, beating on average 72 times a minute (though 60-100 beats per minute is normal for an adult). As the heart beats, it provides pressure so blood can deliver oxygen and important nutrien...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:41:55">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/aging-male-pattern-baldness-may-indicate-increased-chd-risk-040413</link><title>Male Pattern Baldness May Foreshadow Heart Disease</title><description>* Male Pattern Baldness May Foreshadow Heart Disease New research is drawing attention away from the head and toward the heart for men with balding crowns.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>