<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:01:22" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:01:23">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/running-a-marathon</link><title>Work Your Way up to a Marathon</title><description>* Work Your Way up to a Marathon Pursuing marathon training should not be taken lightly—particularly if you have risk factors for heart disease or have been diagnosed with high blood pressure or a pulmonary condition. The Cleveland Clinic emphasizes that, in these cases, it’s especially...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:02:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/crohns-and-colitis/get-up-get-out-part-two</link><title>Couch Your Doubt: Get Up &amp; Get Out Part 2</title><description>* Couch Your Doubt: Get Up &amp; Get Out Part 2 Last time we talked about Team Challenge, a half-marathon training and fund-raising program put on by the Crohn’s and Colitis Foundation of America. This time we’ll look at another goal that might be a bit more manageable—either on its own, or as a starting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:03:35">http://www.healthline.com/health/gurus-guide-triathlon-training</link><title>Guru's Guide to Triathlon Training</title><description>* Guru's Guide to Triathlon Training Though marathon training certainly gobbles up its share of hours, the most time-consuming training can often be saved for the weekend, with speedwork sessions and shorter maintenance runs filling in the rest of the week. This is not the case with triathlon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:05:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/sample-day-when-training</link><title>Sample Day When Training</title><description>* Sample Day When Training As promised, here is a sample day of what I would eat when marathon training:Snack before run: 3/4 cup Total or Wheaties either dry handfuls or with ½ cup soy or skim milk OR a bananaDuring run: Gatorade or water, depending on distance. If more than 10...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:07:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/fueling-runners</link><title>Fueling Runners</title><description>* Fueling Runners I was a lacto-ovo vegetarian (no meat but ate eggs and dairy) for 12 years before I started marathon training. The most important lesson I learned was that, as a vegetarian especially, I was getting plenty of carbs, but I actually needed more protein...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>