<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:08:50" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:08:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/nutrition-made-easy</link><title>Nutrition Made Easy</title><description>* Nutrition Made Easy com and enter in the code on the container and you can save on things to keep the family active like running shoes or trips to the zoo.Need to reduce saturated fat? Make a simple substitution of soft spread margarines like Promise or I Can't Believe It's...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:10:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/workplace-health/if-you-work-on-your-feet</link><title>If You Work on Your Feet</title><description>* If You Work on Your Feet Wear the Right Shoe “Contrary to popular belief, running shoes aren’t the best for prolonged standing,” says Lucille B. Andersen, MD, a foot and ankle surgeon with Webster Orthopedics in San Ramon, California. “They are good for impact, but running shoes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:11:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diabetes-still-isnt-easy/its-never-too-late-to-try-something-new</link><title>It's Never Too Late to Try Something New</title><description>* It's Never Too Late to Try Something New Running has been part of my life since middle school. I enjoy mapping out new running routes when I travel, listening to music when I run, and observing how different my neighborhood looks when I run my usual route during the four seasons. I always encourage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:12:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/walking-softly-benefits-olympic-wrestler</link><title>Walking Softly Benefits Olympic Wrestler</title><description>* Walking Softly Benefits Olympic Wrestler Not long after, I saw Dennis running by at a fast clip, with beautiful neutral spine, good leg and foot alignment, and a light landing with each foot-fall. I asked him why he had asked about running lightly when his running was great. He said he had changed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:13:59">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/hold-that-pause/vitamin-d-good-medicine-for-uterine-fibroids</link><title>Vitamin D: Good Medicine for Uterine Fibroids?</title><description>* Vitamin D: Good Medicine for Uterine Fibroids? We now have another reason why it’s a good idea to lace up those walking and running shoes ladies, and get thee outside into the sunshine! Magnolia Miller is a certified healthcare consumer advocate in women's health and a women's freelance health writer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:16:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/hold-that-pause/beating-depression-perimenopause-exercise-light</link><title>Beating Depression in Perimenopause with Exercise and Light</title><description>* Beating Depression in Perimenopause with Exercise and Light ...consistently shown that a mere 30 minutes per day of some form of aerobic exercise – walking, biking, running, hiking, or swimming – combined with moderate exposure to sunlight, is enough to substantially lift your mood. As a former long distance runner...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:18:56">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthymagination-mental-fitness-101</link><title>Mental Fitness 101</title><description>* Mental Fitness 101 More motivation to lace up your running shoes and get your muscles pumping: Exercise is a great way to keep cholesterol in the healthy range. A study found that high cholesterol is linked to increased risk for memory loss. Play PacMan. Play video, online,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:21:46">http://www.healthline.com/health/triathlon-training-tips-take-your-fitness-next-level</link><title>Triathlon Training Tips: Take Your Fitness to the Next Level</title><description>* Triathlon Training Tips: Take Your Fitness to the Next Level ...Triathlon is an exciting, multidisciplinary sport that combines racing segments of swimming, biking, and running. While you may worry that long, intense races like triathlons and marathons are only for veteran athletes, think again. According to Indian...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:24:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/arch-support-not-shoes</link><title>Arch Support Is Not From Shoes</title><description>* Arch Support Is Not From Shoes Engineered running shoes are not necessary to prevent lower leg pain. Some even add to knee and ankle pain - more in other articles. Support your own feet by holding position using your own muscles, not a shoe 'straight jacket' that lets ankles atrophy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:26:07">http://www.healthline.com/health/are-you-cross-country-runner-heart</link><title>Are You a Cross Country Runner at Heart?</title><description>* Are You a Cross Country Runner at Heart? Like track, cross country involves running over a predetermined course. Unlike track, however, it's much more than simply running from point A to point B. Cross country can take you over dirt trails, grassy fields, steep hills, rocky areas, and muddy...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>