<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:31:36" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:31:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/organic-supply-shortages</link><title>Organic Supply Shortages</title><description>* Organic Supply Shortages I am a fan of organic foods, but I don't buy everything organic. The reason is mainly price. We all know that the organic label comes at a premium. With food costs rising, we need to consider how we want to spend our food dollars a bit more closely.I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:32:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-smart-living/eat-like-cardiologist</link><title>Eat Like a Cardiologist: A Few of My Favorite Things</title><description>* Eat Like a Cardiologist: A Few of My Favorite Things My patients often fret that eating a heart smart diet will be too expensive, too time consuming, too complicated, too confusing, or too dull. The truth is that eating a healthy diet, like almost everything else, can be as simple or as complex as you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:33:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/soy-heart-health</link><title>Soy for Heart Health</title><description>* Soy for Heart Health This is the third of three posts on heart health because it is National Heart Month and heart disease is the #1 killer of men and women in this country! Check out the first post on risk factors for heart disease and the second post on how to decrease...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:35:44">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-organic-food</link><title>Organic food</title><description>* Organic food Agro-toxins, antibiotics, biodynamic, bioengineered, community supported agriculture, CSA, food additives, food coloring, food labeling, free-range, genetically modified food, genetically modified organism, GMO, grass-fed, green labels, growth hormon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:36:36">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-diet-raw-food</link><title>Raw food diet</title><description>* Raw food diet Diet, raw food Ceviche, microgreens, pure foods, raw foodism, raw foodist, raw food veganism, retention factors, vegetarian, wai diet. The raw foods diet is based entirely on the consumption of uncooked foods as a majority of an individual's entire n...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>