<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:39:02" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:39:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/its-a-type-2-life/10-nifty-diabetes-apps</link><title>10 Nifty Diabetes Apps</title><description>* 10 Nifty Diabetes Apps In 1987 I was researching an article about a young man who was making big waves in San Francisco commercial real estate. One day as I was interviewing him he asked me to accompany him on a walk to a client’s office several blocks away. He was one of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:40:30">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/alzheimers-brain-games</link><title>Brain Games: Stay Mentally Active to Prevent Alzheimer’s</title><description>* Brain Games: Stay Mentally Active to Prevent Alzheimer’s Learn how to stay mentally fit and possibly ward off Alzheimer’s by learning something new, speaking more than one language, reading, playing chess, and more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:41:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/weeks-interesting-medical-posts</link><title>This Week's Interesting Medical Posts</title><description>* This Week's Interesting Medical Posts Here's a collection of interesting posts and links from the last week.From Science Roll: ambulance rides in different parts of the world. This is Budapest:[youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PJovb1myOpc&amp;rel=0&amp;border=0]Slate is one of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:42:21">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/pc-spes</link><title>PC-SPES®</title><description>* PC-SPES® PC-SPES Baicalein, baicalin, Chrysanthemum morifolium (chrysanthemum, mum, Chu-hua), Ganoderma lucidum (Reishi mushroom, Ling Zhi), Glycyrrhiza glabra (licorice), Isatis indigotica Fortune (dyer's wood, Da Qing Ye), oridonin, Panax pseudo-ginseng (Sa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:43:52">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/happy-3rd-anniversary-teen-health-411-readers</link><title>Happy 3rd Anniversary Teen Health 411 Readers</title><description>* Happy 3rd Anniversary Teen Health 411 Readers Teen Health 411 has now been around for three years and to celebrate, as is the tradition, here is an index of articles, by topic! Thank you for being a reader!Abortion (6)When Denial is Not the Best ChoiceUnwanted and Teen Pregnancy in the MediaSupr...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>