<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:26:33" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:26:34">http://www.healthline.com/health/new-orleans-brown-rice-cala-recipe</link><title>New Orleans Brown-Rice Calas Recipe</title><description>* New Orleans Brown-Rice Calas Recipe Calas—or rice fritters—are classic New Orleans street food. This holiday time-saving recipe allows you to make the batter day before to finish quickly on the day of your gathering. Our healthier version uses brown rice, whole-wheat and almond flours,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:27:33">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/recipe-week-mexican-rice</link><title>Recipe of the Week: Mexican Rice</title><description>* Recipe of the Week: Mexican Rice This recipe is from the California Nutrition Network Harvest of the Month program, delivering nutrition education, messages and recipe to California children, parents and teachers all over the State. They do great work and because they are funded by ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:28:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/family-fork/recipe-week-wild-rice-orange-salad</link><title>Recipe of the Week: Wild Rice &amp; Orange Salad</title><description>* Recipe of the Week: Wild Rice &amp; Orange Salad I often make this rice salad for parties as it is always a hit and I never have to throw any away. The candied pecans and mandarin oranges lend some sweetness making it more appealing to the 18 and under crowd. It is a nice change from the same-o sam...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:30:06">http://www.healthline.com/health/heart-disease/rice-pilaf-recipe</link><title>Brown Rice Pilaf Dinner Recipe</title><description>* Brown Rice Pilaf Dinner Recipe Makes 8 servings Ingredients Vegetable cooking spray 1 onion, chopped 1 teaspoon minced garlic 1 cup long grain brown rice 1 cup dry white wine 2½ cups vegetable stock, heated Instructions Preheat oven to 350 degrees. Spray a large oven-proof saucepa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:31:41">http://www.healthline.com/health/type-2-diabetes/italian-beef-rice-stuffed-pepper-recipe</link><title>Italian Beef and Rice Stuffed Peppers Recipe</title><description>* Italian Beef and Rice Stuffed Peppers Recipe Makes 4 servings Ingredients 4 medium-size red bell peppers Cooking spray3/4 pound extra-lean ground beef 1 cup chopped onion1/2 cup chopped Italian (flat leaf) parsley 1 teaspoon smoked paprika1/4 teaspoon kosher salt1/4 teaspoon garlic powder 1/2 (...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>