<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:35:05" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:35:06">http://www.healthline.com/health/breast-cancer/clinical-trials-offering-hope</link><title>Clinical Trials: Offering Hope for Breast Cancer Patients</title><description>* Clinical Trials: Offering Hope for Breast Cancer Patients In this article, “clinical trials” refers to research into the effects of experimental drugs or procedures designed to treat stage 4 breast cancer. These may include new drugs or new combinations of drugs, new approaches to surgery, or experimental radiation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:36:09">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/television-social-aggression-bullying</link><title>Study Roundup: Is TV Making Our Kids "Mean Girls"?</title><description>* Study Roundup: Is TV Making Our Kids "Mean Girls"? The Gist We’ve all heard the adage: “sticks and stones may break my bones, but words will never hurt me.” But is it true? Over the years, considerable attention has been paid to combating the “sticks and stones”—namely, nose-bloodying schoolyard bull...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:36:51">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/bpa-miscarriage-birth-defect</link><title>Study Links BPA to Miscarriages, Birth Defects in Primates</title><description>* Study Links BPA to Miscarriages, Birth Defects in Primates The Gist BPA (bisphenol A) is an industrial chemical used in a variety of common food containers, such as water bottles, heat-activated register receipts, cups, linings for metal food cans, bottle tops, and more. It is a synthetic form of estrogen. I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:38:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/classic-study-lung-health-study</link><title>A Classic Study: The lung Health Study</title><description>* A Classic Study: The lung Health Study Every now and again I like to pick one of the classic research studies on smoking cessation in order to highlight some of the key findings. Today I’m going to focus on the part of the Lung Health Study.The Lung Health Study is certainly one of the be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:39:03">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/anxiety-medications-dementia-seniors</link><title>Study Roundup: Can Anti-anxiety Medications Cause Dementia in Older People?</title><description>* Study Roundup: Can Anti-anxiety Medications Cause Dementia in Older People? The GistBenzodiazepines are a class of drugs frequently prescribed to treat anxiety, panic attacks, insomnia, and other conditions including alcohol dependence and seizures. Introduced in the 1960s, they offered a relatively safe replacement for barb...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-06"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/gut-bacteria-imbalance-type-2-diabetes</link><title>Study Roundup: Can Gut Bacteria Imbalances Lead to Type 2 Diabetes?</title><description>* Study Roundup: Can Gut Bacteria Imbalances Lead to Type 2 Diabetes? The Gist The bacteria residing in a person’s intestines—often referred to as gut bacteria or microflora—is much more like an environmental ecosystem than previously realized. As many as 100 trillion different bacteria may reside there, affecting ever...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-07"><link>http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/study-roundup/knee-replacement-increasing</link><title>Study Roundup: Are Total Knee Replacements Being Performed Too Often or Too Little?</title><description>* Study Roundup: Are Total Knee Replacements Being Performed Too Often or Too Little? The Gist Total knee replacement, also known as total knee arthroplasty, is one of the most common and most expensive surgical procedures carried out in the United States. It is a common treatment for knee pain associated with osteoarthritis and simil...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:44:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/new-study-shows-longer-duration-nicotine-replacement-leads-better-qui</link><title>New study shows that longer duration nicotine replacement leads to better quit rates</title><description>* New study shows that longer duration nicotine replacement leads to better quit rates A new study was published in Annals of Internal Medicine this week, showing that having access to nicotine patches for 24 weeks leads to higher quit rates at 24 weeks (32%) that using the patch for the more typical duration (8 weeks), which led to on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:46:28">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/combination-nrt-gets-higher-quit-rates-new-study</link><title>Combination NRT gets higher quit rates: new study</title><description>* Combination NRT gets higher quit rates: new study A new study published this month in the journal “Archives of General Psychiatry” aimed to compare the effectiveness of some of the main medicines for stopping smoking and their combinations. The study, by Dr Megan Piper and colleagues at University o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:48:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/varenicline-chantix-does-not-produce-depression-or-suicide-new-study</link><title>Varenicline ( Chantix ) does not produce depression or suicide: new study</title><description>* Varenicline ( Chantix ) does not produce depression or suicide: new study The smoking cessation medicine, varenicline, has proven safe and effective in numerous placebo-controlled trials, but in the post-marketing phase there were numerous reports of patients experiencing “neuropsychiatric effects” ranging from poor concen...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>