<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:13:16" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:13:24">http://www.healthline.com/health/cardiac-tamponade</link><title>Cardiac Tamponade</title><description>* Cardiac Tamponade Overview Cardiac tamponade is a serious medical condition in which blood or fluids fill the space between the sac that encases the heart and the heart muscle, placing extreme pressure on the heart. The resulting pressure prevents the heart's ventricl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:14:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/tips-help-you-quit-smoking</link><title>Tips to help you quit smoking</title><description>* Tips to help you quit smoking Patients I’ve seen who succeeded in quitting, sometimes tell me what it was that enabled them to quit this time when they had been unsuccessful many times before. Sometimes it was a change in personal circumstances, sometimes an aspect of the treatme...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:15:53">http://www.healthline.com/health/outdoor-health/winter-safety</link><title>Winter Safety Guide</title><description>* Winter Safety Guide It's often said that the only things predictable in this world are death and taxes. But what's left out of this idiom is the very thing it suggests — that what we can expect to expect is the unpredictable. And in the wintertime, this becomes an unavo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:17:12">http://www.healthline.com/health/safety-and-transition-outdoor-activity</link><title>Safety and the Transition to Outdoor Activity</title><description>* Safety and the Transition to Outdoor Activity It's summer at last - time to get off that treadmill and go outside! But as you dust off your outdoor gear and prepare to transition to working out in the fresh air, it's important to remember how to stay safe while exercising outside. While there's ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:18:52">http://www.healthline.com/health/pancreatic-pseudocyst</link><title>Pancreatic Pseudocyst</title><description>* Pancreatic Pseudocyst What Is A Pancreatic Psuedocyst? A pancreatic pseudocyst is a collection of tissue and fluids that forms on your pancreas, an organ located behind your stomach. It is usually the result of pancreatitis (inflammation of the pancreas) or a hard blow to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:20:04">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/vitamin-c-and-gout</link><title>Vitamin C and Gout</title><description>* Vitamin C and Gout This past month, I saw a couple of patients in the emergency department who suffered from gout. When I was a medical student at Duke in the early 1970s, we commonly encountered patients with this disease, because of epidemiological factors that clust...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:21:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/winter-tragedy</link><title>A Winter Tragedy</title><description>* A Winter Tragedy The practice of wilderness medicine is unfortunately frequently necessitated by tragic events and circumstances. We are all enormously saddened to learn of the death of James Kim, whose recovery was announced today. Mr. Kim succumbed to the cold Paci...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>