<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7470">is sugar poison</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:23:11" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7470_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:23:12">http://www.healthline.com/health/basic-metabolic-panel</link><title>Basic Metabolic Panel</title><description>* Basic Metabolic Panel What Is a Basic Metabolic Panel? Whether you’re going to see your doctor for a routine checkup or are admitted to the hospital, your doctor needs information about how your body is functioning. A basic metabolic panel is a combination of tests that h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7470_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:24:50">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/witch-hazel</link><title>Witch hazel (Hamamelis virginiana)</title><description>* Witch hazel (Hamamelis virginiana) Hamamelis virginiana Aldehydes, aliphatic alcohols, catechins, epicatechin, epigallocatechin, flavone aglycones, gallate, gallic acid, gallocatechin, galloylhamameloses, Hamamelidaceae (family), Hamamelis japonica, Hamamelis mollis, hamamelis ointmen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7470_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:26:41">http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/bromocriptine</link><title>Bromocriptine tablets or capsules</title><description>* Bromocriptine tablets or capsules Bromocriptine tablets or capsules What is this medicine? BROMOCRIPTINE (broe moe KRIP teen) is used to treat type 2 diabetes. It helps to control blood sugar. Treatment is combined with diet and exercise. This medicine may be used for oth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-04"><link>http://www.healthline.com/goldcontent/saxagliptin</link><title>Saxagliptin oral tablets</title><description>* Saxagliptin oral tablets Saxagliptin oral tablets What is this medicine? SAXAGLIPTIN (SAX a glip tin) helps to treat type 2 diabetes. It helps to control blood sugar. Treatment is combined with diet and exercise. This medicine may be used for other purposes; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7470_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:31:27">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/ginkgo</link><title>Ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba)</title><description>* Ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba) Adiantifolia, AKL1, arbre aux quarante écus (French), ArginMax®, bai guo ye, baiguo, BioGinkgo®, Blackmores Ginkgo Brahmi (Bacopa monniera), BN-52063, duck foot tree, EGb, EGb 761, Elefantenohr (German), eun-haeng (Korean), Fächerblattbaum, fossil tr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7470-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7470_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:32:55">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/aconite</link><title>Aconite (Aconitum napellus)</title><description>* Aconite (Aconitum napellus) Aconitum napellus Acetylbenzoylaconin, aconite root, aconiti frus, Aconiti Herba, aconiti lateralis preparata, aconiti tuber, aconitine, aconitknollen, aconito, Aconitum angustius, Aconitum anthoroideum, Aconitum artemisiifolium, Aconitum austroyunna...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>