<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:57:00" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:57:01">http://www.healthline.com/health/halloween-pet-safety</link><title>Keeping Your Pet Safe on Halloween</title><description>* Keeping Your Pet Safe on Halloween Protect Your Pets On Halloween and on Mischief Night, pets—especially black cats—are vulnerable to pranks and sheer cruelty. It's wise to keep pets indoors or ensure they are properly restrained.On Halloween and on Mischief Night, pets—especially bla...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:57:29">http://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-travel</link><title>Before You Go Checklist</title><description>* Before You Go Checklist For most of us, vacation planning revolves around the exciting stuff: plane tickets, hotel reservations, and creating an itinerary of exciting or relaxing activities. The less exciting pre-trip details tend to get overlooked. A travel checklist can p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:57:59">http://www.healthline.com/health/remembering-tips</link><title>Memory Aids Training</title><description>* Memory Aids Training Memory Loss and Techniques to Improve Your Memory Many health conditions can lead to memory loss, particularly in older adults. Alzheimer’s disease and other forms of dementia are among the most common causes of poor memory. However, your memory can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:58:25">http://www.healthline.com/health/sensorineural-deafness</link><title>Sudden Sensorineural Hearing Loss (SSHL)</title><description>* Sudden Sensorineural Hearing Loss (SSHL) What Is Sensorineural Hearing Loss? When you lose your hearing very quickly, it is called sudden sensorineural hearing loss (SSHL). It can happen instantly or over a span of several days, during which sound is gradually muffled or reduced. This type ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:59:05">http://www.healthline.com/health/hike-your-way-better-health</link><title>Hike Your Way to Better Health</title><description>* Hike Your Way to Better Health You're long overdue for some exercise, but you need something more interesting than regular trips to the gym. You want to unwind, unplug, and relax. It's time to pack a water bottle and trail mix, put on some good shoes, and get outdoors. Get out of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>