<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:49:55" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:49:56">http://www.healthline.com/health/staff</link><title>The Healthline Editorial Team</title><description>* The Healthline Editorial Team George Krucik—Director, Clinical ContentGeorge rejoined Healthline in 2011, and is responsible for reviewing content and clinical applications on Healthline.com and partner websites for medical accuracy and relevance. Also, he works closely with the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:51:29">http://www.healthline.com/health/medical-board</link><title>Healthline Medical Review and Advisory Board</title><description>* Healthline Medical Review and Advisory Board Medical Review BoardGeorge Krucik, MD, MBAGeorge rejoined Healthline in 2011, and is responsible for reviewing content and clinical applications on Healthline.com and partner websites for medical accuracy and relevance. Also, he works closely with th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:53:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/physician-success-strategies-conference-what-can-doctors-learn-consulta</link><title>The Physician Success Strategies Conference: What Can Doctors Learn From Consultants?</title><description>* The Physician Success Strategies Conference: What Can Doctors Learn From Consultants? Many doctors, in their daily practice, have the nagging suspicion that there must be a better way to do things.The blog focuses on strategies and ideas that doctors can use to stay organized, increase productivity, and take better care of patients. M...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:54:29">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/medical-apps-iphone-diagnosaurus-icd9-consult-and-welladult</link><title>Medical Apps for the iPhone: Diagnosaurus, ICD9 Consult, and WellAdult</title><description>* Medical Apps for the iPhone: Diagnosaurus, ICD9 Consult, and WellAdult As of this writing, there are over 400 medical applications in the iTunes App Store. Whether you're a health care provider or patient, and whether you have an iPhone or iPod Touch or not, it's worth exploring the impressive range of applications avai...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:55:47">http://www.healthline.com/health/jenny-craig-diet</link><title>The Jenny Craig Diet</title><description>* The Jenny Craig Diet What is it? Jenny Craig is a diet program that is nearly 30 years old. It's a three-tiered personalized weight loss program that focuses on food, body, and mind. The core of the diet is portion control that begins with pre-packaged meals, which are u...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:57:02">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fruit-womb/road-not-taken</link><title>"The Road Not Taken..."</title><description>* "The Road Not Taken..." Recently, I was asked to see a very interesting patient in consultation. Although a favorable outcome of her pregnancy is by no means guaranteed at this time, I am fairly sure that the timely request from her physician for a “curbside” consult averte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:58:49">http://www.healthline.com/health/bipolar-disorder/live-expert-q-and-a</link><title>Free Live Expert Q&amp;A: Bipolar Disorder</title><description>* Free Live Expert Q&amp;A: Bipolar Disorder Hi, everybody. Welcome to a live Q&amp;A session about bipolar disorder. This broadcast is brought to you by the good people at Healthline.com. My name is Dr. Rob Dobrenski and I'm a licensed psychologist here in New York City. I'm a consultant for H...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:01:05">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-diet-jenny-craig</link><title>Jenny Craig diet</title><description>* Jenny Craig diet Diet, Jenny Craig Group weight loss, Jenny Craig, prepackaged diet plans, weight loss, weight loss support. The Jenny Craig diet combines elements of social support, pre-packaged meals, food and nutrition counseling, as well as exercise to assist cli...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:01:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/bio/tara-gidus</link><title>Tara Gidus, MS, RD, CSSD, LD/N</title><description>* Tara Gidus, MS, RD, CSSD, LD/N

Tara Gidus is a nationally recognized expert and spokesperson on nutrition, fitness, and health promotion. Tara is quoted in a variety of media including television, radio, newspapers, magazines, and websites and is a past National Media Spokesper...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:03:07">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/freedom-smoking/doctors-under-influence-real-story</link><title>Doctors Under the Influence? The Real Story</title><description>* Doctors Under the Influence? The Real Story About a month ago, my colleague, Dr Michael Steinberg, and I were contacted by a journalist for BusinessWeek magazine, who said she was interested in discussing “smoking cessation” with us, focusing on a paper we had recently published in Annals of I...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>