<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:20:47" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:20:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-should-we-worry-about-the-new-bird-flu-040513</link><title>The New Bird Flu: Should You Be Worried?</title><description>* The New Bird Flu: Should You Be Worried? The latest virus infecting people in China has only caused deaths in people with prior illnesses, many of whom had direct contact with infected birds.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:21:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-genetic-experiments-on-bird-flu-stir-controversy-080713</link><title>Proposed Experiments on Deadly Flu Virus Stir Controversy</title><description>* Proposed Experiments on Deadly Flu Virus Stir Controversy Two researchers are proposing genetic experiments on the H7N9 flu virus to see what would happen if it could spread from person to person.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:23:22">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/types-flu</link><title>A-B-C, 1-2-3: Type of Flu and Me</title><description>* A-B-C, 1-2-3: Type of Flu and Me Types of flu are categorized as A, B, and C. Learn about seasonal flu viruses, swine and avian flu, and how to protect yourself during flu season and pandemics.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:24:31">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/10-worst-disease-outbreaks</link><title>10 Worst Outbreaks in U.S. History</title><description>* 10 Worst Outbreaks in U.S. History Learn about the 10 worst disease outbreaks and epidemics in U.S. history, including the smallpox epidemic, cholera outbreaks, yellow fever, Spanish flu and more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:25:14">http://www.healthline.com/health/avian-influenza</link><title>Bird Flu</title><description>* Bird Flu Overview Bird flu, also called avian influenza, is a viral infection that can also infect humans and other animals. However, most forms of the virus are restricted to birds. H5N1 is also the most common form of bird flu. Not only is it deadly to birds,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:26:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/fluchip-shows-promise-diagnosing-ah5n1-avian-flu-and-others-including-p</link><title>FluChip shows promise in diagnosing A(H5N1) avian flu, and others including pandemic flu</title><description>* FluChip shows promise in diagnosing A(H5N1) avian flu, and others including pandemic flu The New York Times reports on a new test for A(H5N1) avian influenza (commonly called bird flu) which is undergoing further research. The FluChip was designed by Robert D. Kuchta and Kathy L. Rowlen, a University of Colorado chemistry professor who led...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:28:02">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/alt-antiviral-herbs</link><title>Antiviral herbs</title><description>* Antiviral herbs Allium sativum, apple juice, Andrographis paniculata, arabinoxylan, astragalus, avian flu, bird flu, cat's claw, cloves, coenzyme Q10, cranberry, echinacea, Echinacea purpura, elderberry, forsythia, Forsythia suspense, honeysuckle, garlic, ginger, gi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:29:57">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/policy-six-deadly-bioterror-threats-102613</link><title>Deadly Bioterror Threats: Six Real Risks</title><description>* Deadly Bioterror Threats: Six Real Risks Healthline asks the experts about today's biggest bioterror threats.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:31:28">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/tech-internet-speeds-up-vaccine-development-process-051613</link><title>Internet Helps Researchers Create Bird Flu Vaccine in Record Time</title><description>* Internet Helps Researchers Create Bird Flu Vaccine in Record Time The rapid flow of genetic information over the Internet has revolutionized how scientists create vaccines for emerging flu virus strains.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:32:28">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/cold-new-compounds-to-prevent-cytokine-storms-030414</link><title>New Compounds Might Prevent Swine Flu Deaths</title><description>* New Compounds Might Prevent Swine Flu Deaths Some strains of the flu are more deadly than others. But a new treatment might block the chemical pathway that some strains use to kill their hosts.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>