<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:33:45" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:33:46">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/immunize-school-aged-children-flu-and-protect-us-all</link><title>Immunize School Aged Children for Flu and Protect Us All</title><description>* Immunize School Aged Children for Flu and Protect Us All What ages to immunize to reduce the spread of infectious disease is an important public health topic of research. Recent evidence from a study published in PLoS and covered by the WSJ, suggests that for influenza the answer changes with the varying t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:34:31">http://www.healthline.com/health/allergies-managing-your-childs-at-school</link><title>Managing Your Child’s Anaphylaxis at School</title><description>* Managing Your Child’s Anaphylaxis at School Whether by accident or from medical testing, thousands of children and their parents learn of a potentially life-threatening allergy each year. The number of children receiving these diagnoses is growing: According to The Centers for Disease Control ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:36:43">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/its-whole-new-world-relationships-and-sex-21st-century</link><title>It's a Whole New World: Relationships and Sex in the 21st Century</title><description>* It's a Whole New World: Relationships and Sex in the 21st Century Information about Teen Sexual Behavior Let me first say, that although we were all teenagers once, our experience was so different than what our teens are experiencing today, that we cannot assume to know anything – and applying the way our parents p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:37:49">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/potassium-iodide-nuclear-radiation</link><title>Using Potassium Idodide After a Nuclear Radiation Emergency</title><description>* Using Potassium Idodide After a Nuclear Radiation Emergency Potassium IodideHere in more detail is information from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)about the use of potassium iodide after a nuclear radiation emergency:How Potassium Iodide Works Potassium iodide (also called KI) is a s...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:38:16">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/environmental-microbes-childhood-asthma</link><title>Environmental Microorganisms and Childhood Asthma</title><description>* Environmental Microorganisms and Childhood Asthma This past week, there was discussion on the internet about an article entitled “Exposure to Environmental Microorganisms and Childhood Asthma” that was written by Markus Ege, MD and colleagues (New England Journal of Medicine 2011;364:701-709). The g...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:38:53">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/brain-cooling-brain-injury</link><title>Brain Cooling for Brain Injury</title><description>* Brain Cooling for Brain Injury Research suggests hypothermia therapy may not benefit children with brain injuries. In June, Reuters reported that "chilling the body to well below its normal temperature does little to protect children from further damage after an accidental brain i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:41:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/summer-berries</link><title>Summer Berries</title><description>* Summer Berries Now that summer is here, so are some of the best fruits. Berries are such a great treat in these summer months. And, they are loaded in antioxidants! They are low in calories and have virtually no fat or sodium. A cup of many berries are less than 10...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:43:08">http://www.healthline.com/health/cold-flu</link><title>Cold and Flu</title><description>* Cold and Flu Cold and flu are two conditions that have similar symptoms. Cases of each increase in colder months. Neither are curable but both can be prevented and treated.

Learn the Basics \- Prevent Getting Sick \- Find Your Remedy \- Treating Your Kids</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:45:25">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/you-are-what-mom-eats</link><title>You Are What Mom Eats</title><description>* You Are What Mom Eats Since I am still nursing Basil, I read every study on breastfeeding I can find. It is well documented that breastfeeding has benefits of stronger immune systems, reduced risk of obesity, protects against diabetes, gastrointestinal problems, respirato...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:46:40">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthy-vision/a-j-burnett-eye-injury</link><title>When Does An Eye Injury Require Medical Attention?</title><description>* When Does An Eye Injury Require Medical Attention? Pittsburgh pitcher A.J. BurnettPittsburgh Pirate pitcher, A.J. Burnett, recently suffered an orbital fracture after being hit in the temple during a bunting drill. Although Burnett was wearing a batting helmet, it did not protect him from the ball as...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>