<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:47:24" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:47:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/teens-privacy-online-social-networks</link><title>Teens, Privacy &amp; Online Social Networks</title><description>* Teens, Privacy &amp; Online Social Networks Social networking sites appeal to teens because they provide instant communication, blogging, photos, music and video sharing, and a chance to post original creations. Currently, 93% of teens between 12 and 17 years old use the Internet, 61% of those...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:48:38">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/medicine-20-congress</link><title>The Medicine 2.0 Congress</title><description>* The Medicine 2.0 Congress Image via Wikipedia The first "Medicine 2.0" Congress happened on September 4 - 5 in Toronto, Canada. You're justified in being confused by — or even skeptical of — any concept released under the version number "2.0" (or, even God help us, "3.0"). Bu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:49:58">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/be-nice-to-your-coworker</link><title>Be Nice to Your Coworkers. You’ll Live Longer.</title><description>* Be Nice to Your Coworkers. You’ll Live Longer. Here’s a sad number: 100,000. 0 0 1 8 40 Healthline Networks 1 1 47 14.0 Normal 0 false false false EN-US JA X-NONE That’s the number of hours you will probably work in the course of your life. And that’s if you’re like most people and get your first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:52:34">http://www.healthline.com/health/bipolar-disorder</link><title>Support 2.0</title><description>* Support 2.0 Sources of Support In times of doubt and despair, knowing you're not alone can help. So can the comforting words, "It's going to be okay," even if they come from a stranger who is going through the same ordeal. Support groups for those living with me...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:53:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/tech-medicine/eavesdrop-doctors-and-medical-students-twitter</link><title>Eavesdrop on Doctors and Medical Students on Twitter</title><description>* Eavesdrop on Doctors and Medical Students on Twitter Here's a feed containing the conversations of all known doctors and medical students who use Twitter: http://feeds.feedburner.com/doctorsontwitter. (If that doesn't work, you can try the original feed from Yahoo Pipes instead.)Technical details, for ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>