<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:59:47" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:59:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/making-your-own-gummy-worms</link><title>Making Your Own Gummy Worms</title><description>* Making Your Own Gummy Worms OK, so this is not a medically brilliant post, but I thought I would share! For a low sugar snack, you can try making your own gummy worms! Thank you to whomever developed this fun treat!Ingredients2 packages sugar free Jell-O2 packages plain gelatin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:02:00">http://www.healthline.com/health-news/pumps-and-worms-grossest-weight-loss-treatments-011413</link><title>Worms &amp; Pumps: the Newest, Grossest Ways to Fight Obesity</title><description>* Worms &amp; Pumps: the Newest, Grossest Ways to Fight Obesity If you eat too much, you may be able to pump it straight out of your body. That is, of course, if the worms don’t get it first.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:03:58">http://www.healthline.com/health/strongyloidiasis</link><title>The Nasty Truth About Strongyloidiasis</title><description>* The Nasty Truth About Strongyloidiasis What is Strongyloidiasis? Strongyloidiasis is infection by a roundworm calledStrongyloides stercoralis (S. stercoralis). The S. stercoralis roundworm is a parasite. A parasite is an organism that lives in the body of a different species from which it...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:05:37">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/oh-crumbs/helminthic-therapy</link><title>Helminthic Therapy</title><description>* Helminthic Therapy Helminthic therapy is a type of immunotherapy that is quite trendy right now in the treatment of autoimmune diseases. "Helminthic" refers to the helminths that the person receiving the therapy is inoculated with. Helminths, for those who don't know, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:07:49">http://www.healthline.com/health/pinworms</link><title>Pinworm Infection</title><description>* Pinworm Infection Understanding Pinworms and Pinworm Infections A pinworm infection is a type of human intestinal worm infection. Pinworms are tiny, narrow worms that are white and less than half an inch long. A pinworm infection, also known as enterobiasis or oxyuria...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:08:32">http://www.healthline.com/health/echinococcus</link><title>Echinococcus</title><description>* Echinococcus What Is Echinococcus? Echinococcus is an infection caused by the echinococcus multilocularis worm, which is a parasitic tapeworm. The infection is rare in the United States. It occurs more often in the Middle East, Africa, Central Asia, and the Medit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:09:27">http://www.healthline.com/health/ascariasis</link><title>Ascariasis</title><description>* Ascariasis Overview Ascariasis is an infection caused by Ascaris lumbricoides, which is one species of roundworm. Infections caused by roundworms—which are a type of parasitic worm that can be as small as one millimeter or as long as a one meter—are relatively ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:12:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/trichinosis</link><title>Trichinosis</title><description>* Trichinosis What Is Trichinosis? Trichinosis is a disease caused by a roundworm that is found in animals that eat meat. Humans can be infected when they eat undercooked pig, horse, bear, fox, and walrus meat. The roundworm begins its life cycle in the intestines...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:12:34">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/halloween-healthy-eating</link><title>Halloween Candy Facts: What’s in the Bag?</title><description>* Halloween Candy Facts: What’s in the Bag? As trick-or-treating draws to an end Halloween night, the reality sets in: it’s time to play tug-of-war with your little one over their giant sack of sugar.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7481-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7481_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:15:25">http://www.healthline.com/health/crohns-disease/hook-worms</link><title>Hook Worms as a Treatment for Crohn’s Disease</title><description>* Hook Worms as a Treatment for Crohn’s Disease A hook worm grows in the small intestine of humans, cats, and dogs, growing and putting its host at risk for infection. Why would someone volunteer to be infected with hook worms? Patients undergo helminthic therapy to cure or control certain disease...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>