<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:08:34" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:08:35">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/diet-diva/support-the-farmers-buy-local</link><title>Support the Farmers -- Buy Local</title><description>* Support the Farmers -- Buy Local ...on the edge about visiting your local farmer’s market, here are 8 reasons/benefits you should start shopping there weekly! Fresh Produce: You can smell the freshness of the fruits and vegetables in the air! The fruits and vegetables you see on display...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:10:16">http://www.healthline.com/health/make-most-your-weekend</link><title>Make the Most of Your Weekend</title><description>* Make the Most of Your Weekend ...gym or doing a group workoutTaking a trip to the mall or drugstore for needed itemsGetting the grocery shopping doneHandling car maintenanceFueling up the carDoing your ATM banking Note that the ideas above are just suggestions for how you might use your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:12:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/fitness-fixer/healthy-mothers-day</link><title>Healthy Mother's Day</title><description>* Healthy Mother's Day Do some cooking, shopping, vacuuming, and cleaning for Mom (or a Mom). Water their plants. It's good exercise for you and a nice thing for them.Be good to each other - all the children of Earth. Follow the advice of the unknown who said, "The most important...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:13:09">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/heart-to-heart/the-whole-story</link><title>The Whole Story</title><description>* The Whole Story It was Sunday, June 8th, 2008, and I wasnine months into my fifth pregnancy. I was relaxing at home, watching some television, when it happened.As I rolled over to get up, I felt a pain stronger than I had ever felt before. This was my fifth pregnanc...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>