<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:15:44" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:15:45">http://www.healthline.com/health/coccidioidomycosis-disseminated</link><title>Disseminated Coccidioidomycosis</title><description>* Disseminated Coccidioidomycosis ...include: ulcers, skin lesions, or nodules that are more serious than a rash lesions in bones including the skull or spine painful and swollen joints, especially in the knees or ankles meningitis, the most deadly complication Let a doctor know if you have...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:17:39">http://www.healthline.com/health/nasal-trauma</link><title>Nasal Trauma</title><description>* Nasal Trauma In some cases, a nasal fracture can damage the bones that attach your nose to your skull. This injury can allow cerebrospinal fluid to leak. It also presents an opportunity for bacteria from your nose to reach your brain and spinal cord. This can cause...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:19:11">http://www.healthline.com/health/cold-flu/mask</link><title>Does Wearing a Mask Prevent the Flu?</title><description>* Does Wearing a Mask Prevent the Flu? When the Unites States experienced an outbreak of swine flu in 2009, everyone was talking about how to reduce the spread of the infection. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), vaccinations were limited that year because ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:20:26">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/mouth-to-mouth-mask-assisted-cpr</link><title>Mouth-to-Mouth Breathing Versus Mask-Assisted Breathing</title><description>* Mouth-to-Mouth Breathing Versus Mask-Assisted Breathing When a person performs cardiopulmonary (heart and lung) resuscitation (CPR), it is sometimes recommended to provide rescue breathing. This is certainly the case when the primary cause of the victim’s difficulty relates to failure to breathe adequatel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:22:21">http://www.healthline.com/health/nasal-cpap</link><title>Nasal CPAP</title><description>* Nasal CPAP What is Nasal CPAP Therapy? Nasal continuous positive airway pressure (CPAP) therapy is a non-surgical treatment that provides a steady flow of air to the lungs through the nose. Nasal CPAP is often prescribed for those with obstructive sleep apnea, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:24:04">http://www.healthline.com/health/halloween-kid-safety</link><title>Halloween Safety: Trick-or-Treating</title><description>* Halloween Safety: Trick-or-Treating Who among us hasn't heard the urban legends about the perils of Halloween? According to popular lore, flashers in trench coats and psychopaths in Jason masks are lurking behind every shrub. Our trick-or-treat buckets are packed with cyanide-filled Pi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:24:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/outdoor-medicine/numask</link><title>NuMask</title><description>* NuMask In the critical moment when you need to administer rescue breathing, there is not a second to spare. In every first aid kit, there needs to be a clearly marked, easily available rescue breathing kit, consisting of at least an intraoral "mask" to allo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:26:32">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/allergies</link><title>Common Fall Allergens &amp; How to Fight Them</title><description>* Common Fall Allergens &amp; How to Fight Them Don't let Fall allergies get you down, learn about these 4 common Fall allergens &amp; how to best avoid them.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:28:47">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/fathers-day-gifts</link><title>Healthy Gift Ideas for Father’s Day</title><description>* Healthy Gift Ideas for Father’s Day This Father's Day, give him something he can actually use—the gift of good health. Check out these great gift ideas that will keep dad healthy and smiling.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:30:22">http://www.healthline.com/health/pregnancy/newborn-evaluation-physician</link><title>Premature Baby: Evaluation by Doctor</title><description>* Premature Baby: Evaluation by Doctor Although a baby is occasionally born sick without prior warning, most of the time, physicians know when a baby will be born prematurely or at risk for problems. A neonatal team (made up of physicians, nurses, and respiratory therapists who are specia...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>