<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:35:24" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:35:26">http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/facebook-depression</link><title>Is Facebook Depression Real?</title><description>* Is Facebook Depression Real? Though the term “Facebook depression” was coined in an April 2011 edition of Pediatrics, little research shows an association between time spent on social media and depression. Also importantly, none of the sources Pediatrics cited drew a direct conn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:36:00">http://www.healthline.com/health/bipolar-disorder</link><title>Support 2.0</title><description>* Support 2.0 Sources of Support In times of doubt and despair, knowing you're not alone can help. So can the comforting words, "It's going to be okay," even if they come from a stranger who is going through the same ordeal. Support groups for those living with me...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:36:42">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/surviving-teen-suicide-attempt-subject-novel-and-web-site</link><title>Surviving Teen Suicide Attempt the Subject of Novel and Web Site</title><description>* Surviving Teen Suicide Attempt the Subject of Novel and Web Site According to Dr. Susan Vaught 98% of the teens that attempt to kill themselves actually survive. Many are left with serious disabilities and a long struggle to reintegrate themselves back into their family, school, and community. Dr. Vaught has just ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:37:48">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/healthline-connects/celebrities-and-schoolkids-money-haiti-coming-all-directions</link><title>Celebrities and Schoolkids: Money for Haiti Coming from All Directions</title><description>* Celebrities and Schoolkids: Money for Haiti Coming from All Directions The citizens of the world are responding en masse to the January 12 disaster in Haiti, mainly in the form of money. The Chronicle of Philanthropy has been tracking the overwhelming response to fund-raising efforts across the US. In a January 18 repor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:40:11">http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/best-diabetes-blogs</link><title>The 17 Best Diabetes Health Blogs of 2013</title><description>* The 17 Best Diabetes Health Blogs of 2013 Looking for a list of the best diabetes blogs? Healthline scoured the web to hand select the top 17 diabetes blogs &amp; websites of 2013.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>