<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:08:46" name="HealthLine" id="FW14-e067"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e067-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:08:47">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/american-hellebore</link><title>American hellebore (Veratrum viride)</title><description>* American hellebore (Veratrum viride) Veratrum viride Jervine alkaloids American false hellebore, American white hellebore, cevadine, corn lily, cryptenamine, cyclopamine, false hellebore, germidine, germitrine, green corn lily, green false hellebore, green hellebore, green veratrum, hel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:10:55">http://www.healthline.com/natstandardcontent/coleus</link><title>Coleus (Coleus forskohlii)</title><description>* Coleus (Coleus forskohlii) Coleus forskohlii Coleon U-quinone coleus, coleonol, Coleus amboinicus Lour (CA), Coleus barbatus Benth, Coleus blumei, Coleus blumei Benth, Coleus carnosifolius, Coleus galeatus, Coleus kilimandschari, Coleus parvifolius, Coleus scutellarioides, col...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:13:13">http://www.healthline.com/health-blogs/teen-health-411/coming-age</link><title>Coming of Age</title><description>* Coming of Age ...usually a celebration, and may include a tattoo, a trial, the piercing of a body part, or a period of isolation. Native Americans have many variations of the coming of age ritual, depending on the tribe. For the most part, girls have their rite of passage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e067-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e067/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:15:03">http://www.healthline.com/health/personality-disorders</link><title>Personality Disorder</title><description>* Personality Disorder This combination of difficulties leads to a sense of loneliness and isolation. Antisocial Personality Disorder People with antisocial personality disorder: do not obey rules show no regard for the feelings of others can be aggressive and violent are at...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>