<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:07:27" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/108038985259359575981/albums/6003726124754950321/6003726120753620130</link><title>Does the reduced risk of disease from male circumcision outweigh the risks of the procedure? Why or why not? Record a video comment: http://ow.ly/vS5Xi and/or leave your thoughts in the comments section below. Read more: http://ow.ly/vW21l 

Monday, April 21 at 19:30 GMT: 

Roughly 1.1 million people in Zimbabwe live with HIV. Studies show circumcision could reduce the risk of infection by 60 per cent. Since 2011, Zimbabwean men and infants have been undergoing voluntary non-surgical circumcision. Opponents of circumcision argue the risks don’t outweigh the benefits and claim messaging is giving men a false sense of hope regarding HIV prevention. To cut or not to cut? Join the conversation at 19:30 GMT.﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-bekc-UrhbJg/U1GFGQRA5KI/AAAAAAAAT58/zv2vA_1vTBU/s426/5i847.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/114120029640091673775/albums/5945546554962710561/5945546557062926530</link><title>Male Circumcision Leads to Worsened Sex Life (Study) 
http://karmajello.com/lifestyle/dating-sex/male-circumcision-worsened-sex.html 
Circumcised men have more difficulties reaching orgasm, and their female partners experience more vaginal pains and an inferior sex life, based on a new study. 
#circumcision #sexualhealth﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-J1DyGunmEIk/UoLTF8FIUMI/AAAAAAAAUiw/IxoHjRpTJ_0/w426-h283/3b7b8ab9-6aca-4198-998c-91a407ae6205</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/101068850358271508284/albums/5779024728164896273/5779024735865824818</link><title>The Health Benefits Of Male Circumcision Are Now Reconfirmed - http://www.businessinsider.com/the-health-benefits-of-male-circumcision-are-now-reconfirmed-2012-8 

falling infant circumcision rates could end up costing billions of U.S. health care dollars when men and their female partners develop AIDS and other sexually transmitted infections and cancers that could have been prevented. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-D0jBvgX_GyM/UDM4YPF6ZjI/AAAAAAAADdo/8NqIbNQVoII/w426-h320/baby-icu-hospital-medical-debt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/112905910114385373167/albums/5807924901684903313/5807924906436201122</link><title>Mixed Progress in #Uganda Male Circumcision Campaign - Just &gt; 1/4 Circumcised http://ht.ly/f5aoj RT @irinnews#HIV﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-k7AbFENVK-Y/UJnk7kJGCqI/AAAAAAAALwc/XyINhrR4Oro/w426-h601/More%2Bthan%2B380%252C000%2BUgandan%2Bmen%2Bhave%2Bbeen%2Bcircumcised.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/112160690802536563874/albums/5828748222113861345/5828748227981485874?authkey=COyuoNvN8oPY3AE</link><title>ideas in action.... Male Circumcision community mobilization at Geita District in Tanzania. 01.01.2013... Happy new year!!!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Fz1OJAAAr6A/UOPfoZ4GJzI/AAAAAAAAABQ/fnVQkAx5-xk/w426-h320/Photo0068.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/110595293603194342020/albums/5808767069694874801/5808767070745716242</link><title>From the training of safe male Circumcision﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-x07Jc4AQb_w/UJzi3-rI5hI/AAAAAAAAAEw/ltzdl18OV9I/w426-h320/RHSP%2BWorkshop.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/111695556012531831912/albums/5779025737962417681/5779025738702639586</link><title>Right to Care's Medical Male Circumcision video...We did it, what about you?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/--drNjVwWZPw/UDM5Sm810eI/AAAAAAAAAC8/kZ1z08KQi_Q/w426-h320/Final%2BVersion.m4v</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/117820303228397254916/albums/5779448007777951521/5779448011440427138</link><title>Decline In Circumcision Leads To Increased Healthcare Costs 

Declining Rates of U.S. Infant Male Circumcision Could Add Billions to Health Care Costs 
A team of disease experts and health economists at Johns Hopkins warns that steadily declining rates of U.S. infant male circumcision could add more than $4.4 billion in avoidable health care costs if rates over the next decade drop to levels now seen in Europe. 

In a report to be published in the Archives of Pediatrics &amp; Adolescent Medicine online Aug. 20, the Johns Hopkins experts say the added expense stems from new cases and higher rates of sexually transmitted infections and related cancers among uncircumcised men and their female partners.  They say the study is believed to be the first cost analysis to account for increased rates of multiple infectious diseases associated with lower rates of male circumcision, including HIV/AIDS, herpes and genital warts, as well as cervical and penile cancers. 

Read more at http://scienceblog.com/56188/declining-rates-of-u-s-infant-male-circumcision-could-add-billions-to-health-care-costs/#xdhoxx47fbilRt0C.99 

#AIDS   #circumcision   #Healthcare  #penile #cancers﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-yPM_rJyYAyw/UDS5WHe-kII/AAAAAAAADqM/yvz2QL5afzQ/w426-h287/shutterstock_106897790-617x416.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/109095038400758757625/albums/5782361745594604481/5782361750154373442</link><title>CIRCUMCISION BENEFITS OUTWEIGH RISKS 
AMERICA'S MOST INFLUENTIAL PEDIATRIC GROUP 

CHICAGO — America’s most influential pediatricians group says the health benefits of circumcision in newborn boys outweigh any risks and insurance companies should pay for it. 

In its latest policy statement on circumcision, a procedure that has been declining nationwide, the American Academy of Pediatrics moves closer to an endorsement but says the decision should be up to parents. 

“It’s not a verdict from on high,” said policy co-author Dr. Andrew Freedman. “There’s not a one-size-fits-all-answer.” But from a medical standpoint, circumcision’s benefits in reducing risk of disease outweigh its small risks, said Freedman, a pediatric urologist in Los Angeles. 

Recent research bolstering evidence that circumcision reduces chances of infection with HIV and other sexually spread diseases, urinary tract infections and penis cancer influenced the academy to update their 13-year-old policy. 
http://news.nationalpost.com/2012/08/27/circumcision-benefits-outweigh-risks-and-insurers-should-pay-for-it-pediatricians/ 

WHO AND UNAIDS CONFIRM CIRCUMCISION REDUCES RISK OF HIV BY 60% 

There is compelling evidence that male circumcision reduces the risk of heterosexually acquired HIV infection in men by approximately 60%. Three randomized controlled trials have shown that male circumcision provided by well trained health professionals in properly equipped settings is safe. WHO/UNAIDS recommendations emphasize that male circumcision should be considered an efficacious intervention for HIV prevention in countries and regions with heterosexual epidemics, high HIV and low male circumcision prevalence. 
http://www.who.int/hiv/topics/malecircumcision/en/ 

CDC (CENTRE FOR DISEASE CONTROL USA LISTS CIRCUMCISION AS A PREVENTIVE MEASURE 

Prevention with HIV (-) Persons 
Condom distribution 
Behavioral risk reduction interventions and condoms 
Pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) 
Post-exposure prophylaxis 
Syringe services 
Male circumcision 
Microbicides 
STD screening and treatment 
http://www.cdc.gov/about/grand-rounds/archives/2012/pdfs/GR-HIV%208-21.pdf 

JOURNAL OF AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION 

"Other important interventions include medical male circumcision, which offers a highly effective and durable way to protect heterosexual men from HIV infection; and potentially, pre-exposure prophylaxis with antiretroviral medications, which have shown promise in reducing an individual's risk of acquiring HIV infection." 
JAMA July 25 issue.﻿

Meer lezen (58 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-r1SLIZqgo6o/UD8TYCDB6UI/AAAAAAAAABw/9mtD5g9t6dY/w426-h320/circumcision.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7003-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Male%20circumcision/photos/106836423571789897378/albums/6001118404240870049/6001118407569670578?sqi=106821025608931269290&amp;sqsi=f7de3bd4-4d86-4994-a7e4-07e0de2aa97b</link><title>How The PrePex device enables safe non-surgical adult male #circumcision in resource limited settings as a means to prevent the spread of HIV. 

#HIV has taken the lives of 25 million people at a rate of 2 million per year, with 2/3 of these deaths in Sub-Saharan Africa. In 2007, the World Health Organization and UNAIDS cited that voluntary medical male circumcision (VMMC) can reduce the risk of HIV infection by approximately 60% in high risk areas such as Sub Saharan Africa. The “ABCs” – Abstinence, Be Faithful and Condoms are crucial elements, but are not enough. The much anticipated HIV vaccines have been under development for nearly 20 years but are nowhere near market readiness. 

The US Government (USAID) underscores the impact of male circumcision if conducted rapidly in target countries. However, surgical male circumcision requires highly trained medical professionals and sterile surgery-type settings. While genuine attempts have been made by target countries to scale up surgery in the past years, the procedure is not geared for the volume required in Africa, especially in rural and resource limited areas. 

In December 2011, UNAIDS, in partnership with the US Government (PEPFAR) World Health Organization, Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation and the World Bank launched an accelerated action plan to reach 20M VMMC by 2015. Achieving this goal will save nearly 3.4M lives and 16.5 Billion USD in long term healthcare costs. 

The PrePex device (learn more) offers a safe, simple and scalable solution for scale up of adult male circumcision in resource limited settings for HIV prevention. 

Read more: http://www.prepex.com/﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7003_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9e52m2zHg30/U0hBZXo_gbI/AAAAAAAAOcw/7_VYvyrU1kY/w426-h237/prepex.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>