<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:59:21" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/114730057913327763827/albums/5768346463316701297/5768346464915433986</link><title>Manchester United Back in News for Various Transfers 

The popular football club, Manchester United is again in news for its various transfer windows, which includes sale, purchase and elimination of players. Feel the live action and thrill of Manchester United FC with online advance Manchester United FC Tickets! 

Arsenal striker Robin Van Persie is one of the most controversial names of this season, as Manchester City, Juventus and Manchester United are willing to sign this Dutch International. 

In the transfer window, Lucas Moura is certainly the topmost priority with Red Devils who are desperate to sign this teenager from Sao Paulo. The latest update about him is that two clubs have agreed to sign a hefty amount of deal. 

Moussa Dembele from fulham is another name which is gaining popularity in Manchester United FC. It seems that Cottagers are not interested in selling Dembele, but the presence of star striker Clint Dempsey who is most probably on his way out of the club. This might lead to the acceptance of offer worth £15 million for this must sought after Belgian International. 

Everton defender, Leighton Baines is another desirable candidate for Manchester United, as Sir Alex Ferguson made confirmation regarding the vacant left back position. He is certainly the finest left-back in the country and considered as a natural replacement of Patrice Evra. 

For more interesting facts and information about Manchester United Football Club, just log on to us. We are one of the leading secondary market providers of premium Manutd FC Tickets at competitive rates! So, hurry, book your online advance Manchester United Football Tickets at world class services! 
(www.manutdfootballtickets.com)﻿

Meer lezen (32 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-NGuPUev3A-I/UA1IjD6qKgI/AAAAAAAAAGs/LuS8LX5or1c/w426-h448/Lucas_Moura.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/110996309696799464189/albums/5829199349663662833/5829199353774442834?authkey=CLWvzevUn_rXpwE</link><title>Manchester United FC is an English master football club, founded in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester that plays in the Premier League. In 1878 the football club known as Newton Heath LYR; the club simplified to Manchester United in 1902. Ticket4Football is the best place to buy Football Tickets of all popular events especially Premiership Football Tickets. Here fans can also sell their spare tickets. Soccer fans can get Manchester United Tickets at the best price. 

http://www.ticket4football.com/blog/football-tickets/manchester-united-tickets/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-pdAY-O5lHFc/UOV57YapiVI/AAAAAAAAAQg/vP1GI8mSI0U/w426-h667/Manchester%2BUnited%2BTickets.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/108992007110283236440/albums/5781599055441785457/5781599054905916082</link><title>Manchester United Shares Fall below IPO Price. 

Shares in Manchester United football club closed below their initial public offering (IPO) price for the first time on August 16, AFP said. During the session the price fluctuated around $14 
per share, which is its IPO price, before dropping to $13.77. The daily fall was 1.99 percent. Manchester United registered in the Cayman Islands priced its IPO last week in the USA. Before, the date of placing shares was moved several times. The club’s American owners, the Glazer family, expected IPO to value Man Utd at $3bn, but it was only $2.3bn. As a result, 10 percent of the club was sold, raising $234 million. More than a half the Glazers picked up, 101.7 million were spent on reducing the club’s heavy debt of more than $660 million. The Financial Times said that the reason of such considerable fall was the news that the club had signed star Dutch striker Robin van Persie from Arsenal for £24million ($37.5 million). Though fans were glad to hear this news, investors considered it to be unprofitable as the high-paid player is not quite young and prone to injuries.﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-5gWpZGTWcrA/UDxdtU1murI/AAAAAAAAGso/W0OgZ7Qfdmw/w426-h314/555471_358289887578381_102609121_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/103670217713714253118/albums/5796286518449624113/5796287252137447154</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldo of Manchester United Football Club arrives without his tie, the team flew out of Manchester airport for a Champions League match, Manchester, England.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AGG8trIjjgQ/UHCMi7fHDvI/AAAAAAAAAD8/nxNA10y-B78/w426-h639/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/112958959242861184512/albums/5774941924776385089/5774941926650866050</link><title>Cheap Manchester United FC 2011/12 Away Team Football Shirt 
£29.99 
http://authenticsoccerjersey.org/cheap-manchester-united-fc-201112-away-team-football-shirt-p-287.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-GmVwlE7Hyd8/UCS3FdiI6YI/AAAAAAAAAKM/9oWgkR0XPGc/s426/287pro.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/104926349145648791912/albums/5915187410599397425/5915187417587954050?authkey=CM-D-oO5upTEZQ</link><title>Apollo Tyres collaborates with Manchester United Football Club to expand its presence in the global market. Here's the full grab: http://bit.ly/1d7wTCV﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ahYdF0dQrG0/Uhb3ncUwsYI/AAAAAAAAX3E/50DkVt2EuLA/s426/Zigwheels_Apollo_Tyres_11am.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/104756561608847708699/albums/5942232892563092417/5942232893322372306</link><title>+Barclays Premier League Matchday 10 Results: 
+Newcastle United  2-0 +Chelsea Football Club \- http://bit.ly/1e8D7TV 
+Fulham Football Club 1-3 +Manchester United \- http://bit.ly/1e8D8ax 
+Hull City 1-0 +Sunderland AFC \- http://bit.ly/1e8D6zn 
+Manchester City FC 7-0 Norwich City - http://bit.ly/1e8D9eq 
+Stoke City FC  1-1 +Southampton FC \- http://bit.ly/1e8DaiA 
West Bromwich Albion 2-0 Crystal Palace - http://bit.ly/1e8Db6d 
+West Ham United 0-0 +Aston Villa FC \- http://bit.ly/1e8DduT 
+Arsenal 2-0 +Liverpool FC \- http://bit.ly/1e8DihY 
Everton 0-0 +Tottenham Hotspur \- http://bit.ly/1e8DiyJ 
+Cardiff City FC 1-0 Swansea City - http://bit.ly/1e8DkGA﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-rRU0weU4C1o/UncNVUsfJNI/AAAAAAAAAZ4/IwvswJl5tjQ/w426-h265/335902hp2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/103175550943790765275/albums/6004113787702143233/6004113794615042994</link><title>Roberto Martinez' side are dreaming of Champions League football, but first they have to take on Manchester United! 

Everton-Man Utd        2,40     3,45      2,75 

Enjoy in good sport, bet with meridianbet.com we guarantee the best deal and betting odds on all sporting events.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-W6tuzfH33DM/U1Llr18NY7I/AAAAAAAAIyo/zmfl15wwnu0/w426-h318/everton%2B-%2Bman%2Butd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/114798960478398207095/albums/5999981869572405409/5999981875085664114</link><title>DETROIT – Chevrolet today announced Manchester United will play the L.A. Galaxy of Major League Soccer in the Chevrolet FC Cup, July 23 at the Rose Bowl in Pasadena, Calif. 

The match is part of Manchester United’s 2014 pre-season schedule and will be the first time the club plays in Chevrolet-branded shirts. Chevrolet, which kicks off its seven-year shirt sponsorship with Manchester United on July 1, will stream the match free online at www.chevroletfc.com. 

“It will be an incredible moment for Chevrolet. Not only will we have our brand on Manchester United’s shirts for the first time in a world-class match in a historic venue, but we’ll give Manchester United fans around the world a chance to watch their favorite football club,” said Paul Edwards, U.S. vice president, Chevrolet Marketing. “Our ‘What Do You #PlayFor?’ campaign is all about bringing fans closer to this great sport than ever before.”﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-jjC1I_26Ajw/U0Q3ueNDX3I/AAAAAAAAXms/5m9-J2fycGU/w426-h281/cq5dam.web.1280.1280%2B%25286%2529.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7010-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/manchester%20united%20FC%20football/photos/114730057913327763827/albums/5766064192049487617/5766064195289940018</link><title>Berbatov to Bid Adieu to Manchester United FC 

Dimitar Berbatov is quite particular about his exit from Manchester United, as he feels it would be, “better for everyone”. On the other hand, he wants to stay and be the part of English Premier League giants. 

The four year old stay at Old Trafford of the striker comes to an end, as he managed 12 league appearances last term and scored seven goals. An year ago, he was the equal top scorer of Premier league. 

Manchester United signed the Bulgarian at a cost of Â£30 million from rivals Tottenham. He vent out his feelings on his social networking page, as he said, “The truth is, I love this club, but I am not going to be useful to anyone if I am not playing. And I want to play, I want to help. But for unknown reasons it's not going to happen, or my chances will be limited, so it's better for everyone if we say goodbye.” 

He further added, “If not, I am professional and I will keep doing everything I can to help my team and my team-mates, whenever I have opportunity to do so.” 

According to reports, price tag of Â£10 million have been placed on Berbatov. The forward also said the manager Sir Alex Ferguson stated that figure was just half of the amount. 

Berbatov also stated, “Because I am tired of speculation, I am telling you this. I read the papers and I see they say 10 million pounds is my price. I go and talk with Sir Alex, and he says to me 5 million. So who is telling the truth, what do you think??” 

48 league goals have been scored by Berbatov at United which helps them to won two Premier league titles. His future in Old Trafford is doubtful, as made exit from the squad for 2010-11 Champions League final while playing against Barcelona at Wembley. 

Feel the magic of your favorite football club Manchester United with online advance Manchester United Football Tickets at best prices! Book online advance Manchester United Football Tickets at competitive rates! So, what are you waiting for? Call our executives now and order Manchester United Football Tickets!﻿

Meer lezen (39 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7010_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-pRY9CU6VRKw/UAUs1fBbADI/AAAAAAAAAFA/lW2e8OLr0HY/w426-h241/brtbatov_quit_man_utd.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>