<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:04:00" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/117806851859198394402/albums/5846601204193322257/5846601209653799986?authkey=CJGXture-cXUAQ</link><title>The sacroiliac joint is a planar (sliding) synovial joint in the bony pelvis, formed by the meeting of the sacrum (at the base of the spine) and upper part of the hip (ilium). Two such joints are found in the human body on either side of the sacrum and they move as a unit, such that movement on one side will produce movement on the other side. The bones connect at their respective auricular surfaces on the outside of the sacrum and inside of the ilium, with a raised area of bone known as the sacral tzygoteuberosity that is connected to the hip bones. http://bit.ly/Zon2Tt﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_01_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-AoSVumeGTpA/USNM0tTIrDI/AAAAAAAAAGE/ist0Axcjz50/w426-h548/Gray319.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/105071588889838378531/albums/5992488338811020145/5992488341504935634</link><title>Exercises Can Ease Arthritis Pain 

"If you've got aching joints and arthritis, exercise can help. It may be hard to believe, but experts agree -- moving your joints helps relieve joint pain." 

""When you exercise, you strengthen the muscles around the joints, which helps take stress off joints," says Richard Weil, MEd, CDE, WebMD's fitness expert. "It also reduces joint stiffness and builds flexibility and endurance." Exercise can improve your mood and self-esteem. It helps you sleep better, keeps weight under control, and gives you more energy. 

There's also a certain sense of accomplishment that comes from exercise. After all, pushing yourself to exercise - when your body hurts - isn't easy. In addition to arthritis pain relief, exercise can offset other health problems, like osteoporosis, diabetes, and heart disease. 
If you're new at this, just remember - start slow, Weil advises. 
Warm Up for Arthritis 
Whether you have arthritis or not, a warm-up is a smart place to start. Going into an exercise activity with cold muscles can only cause pain and possibly injury. If you have arthritis, you may want to do something extra. "A lot of people like to take a warm bath or apply heat packs to joints before they do any exercise, to get the synovial [joint] fluid flowing ... it lubricates the joint," Weil tells WebMD." 

"""" 

Learn more about low intensity muscle training:http://arthritis.andpainrelief.com/sanjose-california/ 

Source:http://goo.gl/dn7i4r 

#exercise #easepain #healthandmind #arthritis #sanjoseca #california #superslowzone﻿

Meer lezen (33 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-kHoEpdiC8fw/UymYZaQSRtI/AAAAAAAAArU/vdm8Dc4AC-M/w426-h320/4WXj8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/103381990515958346974/albums/6003319389942171457/6003319387704605810</link><title>Not all joints in your body move. Joints are the place where two bones meet or connect, so the joints in your skull are some of those that do not move. Joints that do move are call synovial joints.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-YSyeRcN94bk/U1ATLRlZPHI/AAAAAAAAAYM/EK5AdYSI9d4/w426-h568/602cf231-3e24-4792-a629-72fccd91b651</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/117143121104529675276/albums/5705537076923578129/5842862975505318802?authkey=CIfmpuqo252_Hg</link><title>Cracking your knuckles does not actually hurt your bones or cause arthritis. The sound you hear is just gas bubbles bursting. 
Cracking your knuckles (or any of your joints) can have therapeutic benefits. When you crack one of your joints you are pulling the bones that are connected at the joint apart from each other. This process stimulates your tendons, relaxes your muscles, and loosens your joints. Chiropractors do this for spinal joints when your back is sore and stiff, but you can do this on your own for your knuckles, toes, knees, neck, etc. 

Unfortunately, there can be too much of a good thing. Cracking your knuckles will never lead to arthritis (despite what your mom keeps telling you), but scientists have discovered that it can cause tissue damage in the affected joints. Knuckle-cracking pulls your finger bones apart which stretches your ligaments. Too much stretching of your ligaments will cause damage to your fingers akin to the arm injuries sustained by a baseball pitcher who throws too many pitches. In addition to making your hand really sore, this ligament damage can also result in reduced grip strength. 

How does this work? Your joints, the places in your body where you can bend, are where your bones intersect and are held together by ligaments. These joints are surrounded by a liquid called synovial fluid. When you stretch your ligaments by pulling the bones apart to crack your knuckles a gas in the synovial fluid escapes and turns into a bubble. This process is called cavitation. Cavitation ends when the bubble eventually bursts, producing that popping sound we know and love. After that, your joints won't be able to crack for another 25-30 minutes while the gas gets reabsorbed into the synovial fluid.﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-JwVooFkaiss/URYE615Gw5I/AAAAAAACcsY/wqUzxoRbJ8U/w426-h259/1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/114223966178278613536/albums/5840062314484329745/5840062319846569058?authkey=CPzw_bO56IH7Tw</link><title>Turmeric Extract Puts Drugs For Knee Osteoarthritis To Shame 
By: Sayer Ji 

Millions take non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) daily for arthritis and related inflammatory conditions, but are completely unaware that far safer, and at least as effective, natural alternatives already exist -- and are as easily accessible and inexpensive as the spices found in your kitchen cupboard. 

Human research on the health benefits of turmeric is sparse, mainly due to the lack of capital available to fund expensive clinical trials.[i] Despite many decades of investigation as a lead drug compound, and the availability of thousands (http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed?term=curcumin) of preclinical studies indicating turmeric's therapeutic value, few yet realize that this common kitchen spice may provide a suitable drug alternative for common health conditions. 

The latest human study to clinically confirm turmeric's medicinal value was published in the Indonesian Journal of Internal Medicine in April, 2012 (http://www.inaactamedica.org/archives/2012/22745140.pdf) and found the curcuminoid extract of turmeric was able to reduce inflammation in patients suffering from knee osteoarthritis. 

Researchers compared the effect of a curcuminoid extract to the NSAID drug diclofenac sodium in reducing cycloxygenase -2  (COX-2) secretion by synovial fluid's monocytes in two, randomly divided, groups suffering with knee osteoarthritis. 

The synovial fluid is an egg yolk-like liquid within the cavities of the synovial joints, which serves to reduce friction between articular cartilage during movement.  In knee osteoarthritis, a condition that afflicts 1 in 2 people by the age of 85 years, the immune cells known as monocytes express increased inflammatory COX-2 enzyme activity within the synovial fluid. 

In the study, subjects were given either 30 mg 3 times daily of turmeric extract (curcuminoid) or 25 mg 3 times daily of diclofenac sodium for 4 weeks. After the treatment period, aspiration of the joint as performed and the secretion of cycloxygenase-2 enzyme by synovial fluid's monocytes was evaluated. 

Results were reported as follows: 

In curcuminoid group the average scores were 1.84±0.37 and 1.15±0.28 respectively (p&lt;0.001). In diclofenac group the average scores were 1.79±0.38 and 1.12±0.27 respectively (p&lt;0.001). In curcuminoid group the decreasing score of cycloxygenase-2 secretion was 0.70±0.51 while in diclofenac group was 0.67±0.45. There was no significant difference in decreasing the score of cycloxygenase enzyme secretion between both treatment groups (p=0.89). 

In summary, both curcuminoid and diclofenac sodium were capable of significantly decreasing the secretion of the inflammatory COX-2 enzyme, with nearly identical potency. 

Discussion 
This is not the first human study to confirm turmeric is at least as effective as an NSAID drug in reducing the symptoms associated with knee osteoarthritis. A 2010 study published in the Journal of Alternative and Complementary Medicine found 2,000 mg of turmeric extract was as effective as 800 mg of ibuprofen in reducing symptoms of pain and inflammation.[ii] 

What is most remarkable about the more recent study is not that turmeric curcuminoids have potent anti-inflammatory properties – there are already hundreds of studies confirming its COX-2 (http://www.greenmedinfo.com/greenmed/topic/18768/focus/5278/page) reducing and otherwise anti-inflammary effects (http://www.greenmedinfo.com/greenmed/topic/18768/focus/5167/page)  -- but rather how much safer they are relative to NSAID drugs like diclofenac, which like most pharmaceutical anti-inflammatory drugs have been linked to adverse health effects such as increased cardiac mortality, miscarriage and seizure. (http://www.greenmedinfo.com/toxic-ingredient/diclofenac) 

One way to assess the relative toxicity of these two compounds is to compare the primary polyphenol in turmeric, curcumin, with diclofenac sodium through their respective Material Safety Data Sheets, which contain detailed information on the toxicity of these substances. 

Diclofenac Sodium: The LD50 for mice is 95 mg/kg, meaning that it only takes 95 mg/kg of mouse to acutely kill 50% of an exposed group.  http://www.nsf-rs.org/media/downloadable/files/msds/diclofenac_sodium_msds.pdf 

Curcumin: The LD50 for mice is &gt;2,000 mg/kg, meaning that it would take more than 2,000  mg/kg of mouse to acutely kill 50% of an exposed group.  http://www.sciencelab.com/msds.php?msdsId=9923607 

In order to get perspective on how toxic an LD50 of 95 mg/kg is, let's first calculate how much of this chemical it would take in milligrams to kill an average sized mouse. Mice are between 15-27 grams, depending on their age, strain and diet. If we take the average between the two, at 21 grams, our mouse would weigh 0.021 kilograms. This means that it only takes 1.9 milligrams to acutely kill 50% of the mice given such a dose. 

Extrapolating to humans, an average 150 lb adult weighs 68.03 kilograms, it would only take 6462 milligrams, or 6.46 grams to kill 50% of the humans given the dose. This is less than the weight of three pennies (7.5 grams).  Compare this to the LD50 of curcumin (2,000 mg/kg), where it would take more than 136,000 mgs (4.86 ounces) to kill 50% of the humans given it – and even this estimation is doubtful, since it is likely that it would simply be vomited up, or expelled through the gastrointestinal tract, and other organs of elimination, before reaching lethal levels in the body.  Also, remember that it only took 90 mg a day in the aforementioned study to reduce inflammation as effectively as diclofenac sodium.  The difference between the 90 mg required to produce an effective response, and a (theoretical) 136,000 mg threshold for lethal toxicity, is four orders of magnitude. 

In practical terms, the chance of you hurting yourself with a drug like diclofenac sodium -- ironically, in an attempt to reduce pain -- as compared to a simple kitchen spice like turmeric, is infinitely higher. Consider too, that there are over 100 known adverse health effects (http://www.greenmedinfo.com/toxic-ingredient/non-steroidal-anti-inflammatory-drugs-nsaids) associated with this chemical class of drugs, whereas turmeric (and curcumin) has been linked to over 600 beneficial ones (http://www.greenmedinfo.com/substance/turmeric) -- not exactly a hard choice to make, when it comes to risk-benefit analysis. 

For additional research on natural alternatives to common NSAID drugs like aspirin and ibuprofen, read the following articles: 

Is There A Natural Alternative To Aspirin? 
http://www.greenmedinfo.com/blog/aspirin-dangers-and-natural-evidence-based-alternatives 

Ibuprofen Kills More Than Pain, So What Is The Alternative? 
http://www.greenmedinfo.com/blog/ibuprofen-kills-more-pain-so-what-alternatives 

\--------------------- 

Resources: 

[i] GreenMedInfo.com, Why The Law Forbids The Medicinal Use of Natural Substances, Feb. 26th, 2012 
http://www.greenmedinfo.com/blog/why-law-forbids-medicinal-use-natural-substances 

[ii] Vilai Kuptniratsaikul, Sunee Thanakhumtorn, Pornsiri Chinswangwatanakul, Luksamee Wattanamongkonsil, Visanu Thamlikitkul. Efficacy and safety of Curcuma domestica extracts in patients with knee osteoarthritis. Int J Mol Med. 2010 May;25(5):729-34. PMID: 19678780 
http://www.greenmedinfo.com/article/turmeric-extract-appears-be-safe-and-effective-ibuprofen-treatment-knee-osteoarthritis 
\-------------------- 

Sayer Ji is the founder and director of GreenMedInfo.com and co-author of the book The Cancer Killers: The Cause Is The Cure. His writings and research have been published in the Wellbeing Journal, the Journal of Gluten Sensitivity, and have been featured on Mercola.com, NaturalNews.com, Reuters.com, GaryNull.com, and Care2.com. Check out his newest project with co-author Tania Melkonian: EATomology: An Edible Philosophy of Food﻿

Meer lezen (161 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YDYmM2875JU/UQwRvOiZNGI/AAAAAAAABl8/LF9fs9IFV_U/w426-h283/turmeric_inflammation.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/106161459436262804764/albums/5752344743877836177/5752344745628084802</link><title>Joint Failures Potentially Linked to Oral Bacteria: 
\----------------------------------------------------------------------- 
The culprit behind a failed hip or knee replacements might be found in the mouth. DNA testing of bacteria from the fluid that lubricates hip and knee joints had bacteria with the same DNA as the plaque from patients with gum disease and in need of a joint replacement. 

This study is one of many coming from the Case Western Reserve University School of Dental Medicine that have linked oral bacteria to health problems when they escape from the mouth and enter the blood. 

Working with University Hospitals Case Medical Center researchers, the dental, orthopedic and arthritis researchers suggest it might be the reason why aseptic loosening or prosthetic wear of the artificial joints fail within 10 years when no infection appears to be present. The pilot study's findings were reported in the April issue of the Journal of Clinical Rheumatology. 

Dr. Nabil Bissada, chair of the Department of Periodontics at the dental school, said the objective of the study, "Identification of Oral Bacterial DNA in Synovial Fluid of Patients with Arthritis with Native and Failed Prosthetic Joints," was to see if bacteria like Fusobacterium nucleatum and Serratia proteamaculans found in patients with gum disease were present in the fluid. 

"For a long time, we've suspected that these bacteria were causing problems in arthritis patients, but never had the scientific evidence to support it," Bissada says. 
The researchers recruited and studied 36 patients seeking care at the University Hospitals Case Medical Center for osteoarthritis (the wearing of the joints) and rheumatoid arthritis (an autoimmune disease). 
These study participants had both natural and artificial joints. Researcher extracted samples of their synovial fluid, which is much like oil that keeps a door from squeaking. These patients also had signs of periodontitis or gum disease and undergone exams where dental plaque was obtained for the study. 
Plaque build-up from the bacteria, associated with gum disease, breaks down the walls of the pockets around the teeth. The inflammation process from the bacteria acts like a gate that gives bacteria access to the blood stream. Once in the blood, the oral bacteria have induced inflammation in remote sites where the bacteria has been linked to heart, kidney and cancer diseases and premature births and fetal deaths. 

Because these bacteria cannot be found with routine lab tests, detection of bacteria in the plaque and fluid was done through a process called polymerase chain reactions and DNA sequence analysis of specific genes (16S-23S rRNA). This is a sophisticated DNA tracking procedure. 

Five of the 36 patients (14%) showed direct DNA links between the bacteria in the fluid and plaque from the mouth. The breakdown in patients was: one from a rheumatoid arthritis (RA) patient with a failed natural joint and one RA patient with a failed replacement joint; two osteoarthritis (OA) patients with failed artificial joints and one OA patient with a failed natural joint. 

Bissada said researchers will continue exploring the oral health link in a larger study. "We have a link now and want to see just how much of a trend this is. We also will be able to see if treating the periodontal disease, can reduce the number of future costly joint replacements." 

Collaborating with Bissada on the National Institutes of Health and Department of Periodontics-funded research were: Stephanie Temoin, Alia Chakaki, Ahmed El-Halaby, Yiping Han from the Case Western Reserve dental school, and Ali Askari, Steven Fitzgerald and Randall E. Marcus from University Hospitals Case Medical Center.﻿

Meer lezen (67 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-dbXjIQVW1F0/T9RvEaS_KkI/AAAAAAAAATA/KT1x_Hv95UA/w426-h341/527146_249717551795083_8352620_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/108217645267372137616/albums/5857397769122929601/5857397770169818498?authkey=CLXP7fPW8tjSVw</link><title>Eat These 10 Anti-Inflammatory Foods for Pain Free Joints 

If you suffer from occasional joint inflammation and decide to pay a visit to the doctor's office it's not very likely you'll start talking about food. In fact they'll probably ask you when knee or other joints hurt the most, tell you to stop the activity and recommend some kind of pain killer. 

The article below courtesy of Injury Specialist and Exercise Physiologist Rick Kaselj, MS provides a food based alternative that you should find  helpful. He is the guy who teaches the other fitness professionals the newest 
techniques to help their own clients.  He has given over 315 live presentations to over 6065 health and fitness professionals across Canada and the USA. After reading the insightful article below be sure to check out his brand new Fix My Knee Pain Program that made its debut this week: http://tinyurl.com/FixMyKnee 

============= 
Eat These 10 Anti-Inflammatory Foods for Pain Free Joints 
by Rick Kaselj 

Inflammation in the joints can limit mobility and be very painful.  When the 
pain is severe, it can bring strength training or weightlifting to a screeching halt. Sometimes, occasional joint inflammation--such as the kind brought on by an injury--can't be avoided. 

There are however, steps you can take today to speed up the recovery process should you injure yourself and more important, reduce the likelihood that you'll suffer from other types of joint inflammation and pain. One thing you can do is start incorporating these ten anti-inflammatory foods into your diet. Let's take a look. 

In the human body, a joint is the point at which two or more bones come together. Us humans have about 230 of them. They have different ranges of mobility (from no mobility, limited movement and full range of movement) and are classified by type such as ball and socket, elbow, gliding, hinge, hip and saddle joints. 

Joints can also be classified by structure, function, biomechanical properties 
and more--it really gets very technical. Regardless of the type or classification, joints wouldn't function very well if they were just 'bone meeting bone,' because there would be too much friction. Just like a ball bearing sealed with oil, to allow for ease of movement, human joints have either cartilage or synovial fluid--or both--between the bones. 

Cartilage is a smooth connective tissue while synovial fluid is a yolk-like viscous fluid that serves as a lubricant. Ligaments connect bone to bone and stabilize the joints. There are two key points to this anatomy lesson: 

1) joints are very complex; and 
2) we have a lot of them in our bodies. 

For the most part we don't give any thoughts to our joints unless we're having 
problems with them.  And when we do have problems with them, it can be not just painful, but downright debilitating.  Inflammation is the most commonly-cited problem or difficulty with joints. Inflammation in joints is swelling that is actually part of the body's self-protection mechanism as it tries to remove harmful stimuli such as damaged cells or irritants. And when joint inflammation occurs, it inhibits mobility and causes pain. 

Sometimes joint inflammation can bring about severe pain that can last for days, weeks or longer, sometimes becoming a chronic condition that lasts a lifetime. In some cases, inflammation in the joints is the result of a sudden event like lifting a weight improperly, tearing a ligament or a similar type injury. Recovery from this type of joint inflammation can take anywhere from just a couple days up to several months, depending on the nature and scope of the injury. 

Other times, joint inflammation is not caused by a single event but rather, is a condition that builds up over time, eventually reaching the point where it limits mobility and results in intermittent--or sometimes constant--pain. 
Your metabolism plays a central role in determining whether or not you develop joint inflammation that occurs over time and how quickly it recovers from the type that is brought on by a sudden injury.  And fortunately, scientists have discovered that eating certain foods can boost the body's ability to fight joint inflammation. Not surprisingly, these are foods that are rich in vitamins, antioxidants, minerals, proteins, healthy fats or complex carbs--you won't see any processed foods, artificial ingredients, saturated fats or trans fats on the list below.  In fact, many highly processed, refined foods have been shown to actually decrease the body's ability to fight inflammation.  Here is the list: 

1\.    Alaskan Salmon (wild is best) 
2\.    Fresh whole fruits and vegetables 
3\.    Bright multi-colored vegetables 
4\.    Green tea 
5\.    Olive oil 
6\.    Lean poultry 
7\.    Nuts, legumes and seeds 
8\.    Dark green leafy vegetables 
9\.    Old fashioned oatmeal 
10\.  Spices, especially Turmeric and Ginger 

It's no coincidence that these are foods that help the body to build muscle and maintain a healthy weight. Strong muscles help keep joints stable and a healthy weight reduces pressure on joints, helping to minimize--or in some cases prevent--joint inflammation.  Eat these foods and while you might not completely eliminate joint inflammation, you'll certainly increase your body's ability to fight joint inflammation and even prevent it from occurring in the first place. 

You can learn more about this in Component 2 of "Fix My Knee Pain" Here: http://tinyurl.com/FixMyKnee 

In selecting foods from the list, be sure to choose so you get a well-rounded variety of healthy, wholesome, unprocessed, inflammation-fighting foods in your daily diet. And while I didn't put it on the list, you should also be sure 
to drink plenty of water every day. This helps flush toxins from your body and keeps your joints lubricated. 

\------end of article 

If you have any kind of knee pain or soreness I want to urge you to grab a 
copy of "Fix My Knee Pain" while it's being offered for less than the cost of 
a co-pay..  Learn just one technique that gives you some relief and it pays 
for itself...but you'll learn more than that. 

If you feel like you've been going in circles with the doctors and rehab places 
and don't want to waste any more time or money on temporary solutions check out Fix My Knee Pain right now -- http://tinyurl.com/FixMyKnee  ﻿

Meer lezen (132 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-6XD4uRgSnds/UUmoPPcjHYI/AAAAAAAACAU/NjaRj3ziwh8/w426-h404/knee-article.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/113695691862261895911/albums/5688537705148068657/5688537708069402562</link><title>Glucosamine 
PRODUCT DESCRIPTION: 
* All-natural supplement aids in relieving joint stiffness and pain. 
* Can help improve joint function and mobility. 
* A prescription arthritis product in Europe. 
* Highly absorbable form of Glucosamine. 
* Basic building block for cartilage, synovial fluid, and other connective tissues. 
$4.99 
Retail Price: $8.95 
You Save: $3.96 (44%) 
OR just $8.14 with a Standing Order 
You save $0.81 (9%) 
www.tripleclicks.com/11302792/pbwin﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-7Pry5_c70eM/TvG-6ATkN8I/AAAAAAAAAI8/jo0f7AMkV-0/w426-h575/3315.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/100032413120776787331/albums/5985722270430452513/5985722273204670386</link><title>Describe the types of joints in the human Skeleton ? 
Joints have been classified into three major structural forms, namely, fibrous,cartilaginous and synovial : 
(a)  Fibrous Joints: Fibrous joints do not allow any movement.  This type of joint is shown by the flat skull bones which fuse end-to-end with the help of dense fibrous connective tissues in the form of sutures, to form the cranium. 
(b)  Cartilaginous Joints: In cartilaginous joints, the bones involved are joined together with the help of cartilages. The joint between the adjacent vertebrae in the vertebral column is of this pattern and it permits limited movements. 
(c)  Synovial Joints: Synovial joints are characterised by the presence of a fluid filled synovial cavity between the articulating surfaces of the two bones.  Such an arrangement allows considerable movement.  These joints help in locomotion and many other movements. 
Ball and socket joint (between humerus and pectoral girdle), 
Hinge joint (knee joint) 
Pivot joint (between atlas and axis), 
Gliding joint (between the carpals) and 
Saddle joint (between carpal and metacarpal of thumb). 

For further details visit www.microlifeindia.org﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_09_thumb.gif">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-v1i82xNsghE/UxGOsZqCD7I/AAAAAAAAB7A/g0wFNknwN7Q/w426-h320/Skeleton.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7020-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/synovial%20joint/photos/102613566924630472516/albums/5907168203123574545/5907168200507724018?authkey=CNiuisihsvLZOA</link><title>Lubricin: New Promise for Joint-Preserving Therapy 

The boundary mode of the synovial joint is lubricated during periods of low sliding speed (less than 0.3 mm/sec) and high physiologic loads (approaching 5 mPa) by hyaluronic acid and  lubricin, which prevents the pressurized joint surfaces from adhering to each other. 

http://www.musculoskeletalnetwork.com/osteoarthritis/content/article/1145622/2152309?cid=G+ 

#lubricin﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7020_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-xalMSss-9k4/Ufp6Lku_EPI/AAAAAAAAAtU/qX-BE1ttfBE/w426-h314/image_galleryCA1NNP6W.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>