<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:23:44" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7022-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hermitian%20conjugate/photos/116991816840985675138/albums/5918519822252903697/5918519823540253346?authkey=CO3s3PS8i9GgPA</link><title>After I have listened to the Harvard OpenCourse online, The Abstract Algebra, I feel a little bit disappointed. The elderly lecturer did not show students the essence and methodology of Modern Algebra, and de facto did not enable the students to employ self study in future. 

This weekend, I’d like to show my insights about the Abstract Algebra, making a brief introductory note and enlightening my readers interested in this wonderland. 

First of all, I’d love to define what “Abstract” means to us. In the recent century, human races come to a holly alliance of general unification, not merely in astronomical and microscope physics. This is a glory way to the “Abstract” term. To unify two fields of study, or to unify two heterogeneous concepts, you have to put both into a general term and ignore the difference, then you will find the common ground. 

Generally speaking, “Abstract” means confusion, generality, vagueness. For example, how could we make analogy between electronic current and ocean current? We try the abstract way; say they could be regarded as a same thing, the current. 

The more abstract a computer codes is, the wider scope the codes would be applied. For instance, “Derek is a boy” can only apply to the boy whose name is Derek. If we put that expression into a more abstract term, “He is a boy”, it would then be applied to more male young human beings. If we put it into a general term, “Something is a thing”, it would be applied to a set with a wide scope. 

In a nutshell, “Abstract” per se means to ignore the differences but to focus the similar parts. However, this generalization method may not be necessarily correct. But Mathematics is not a specific science. Instead, it’s a language, a language of expressing the time, space and their nature. Thus it is not necessary to be truth. But is ought to be solid logically in itself. That is to say, mathematicians can and only can employ the methodology of deduction rather than induction, where deduction means from the general to the specific while induction means from the specific to the general. 

Based on this, we can understand the first lesson about two calculations, addition (+) and multiplication (*). They are the same thing definitely. Therefore, modern algebra researchers and teachers prefer to use “·”, “⊙”, “◎”, or “○”, to proxy either addition or multiplication. 

Thus, why is that? Alright, second of all, calculation or algebra can be regarded as paper folding. Let’s think about geometric transformation, axial symmetry like doubling over, or centro symmetry like rotating around. 

In fact, almost all the rules of addition can be applied to multiplication. In another vision, geometric vision upon equations and matrices, we would observe that both addition and multiplication are symmetric transformation. Then we could call them "symmetry" for short, or more generally they are called as "group", which is one of the simplest algebra. 

Recently, I have seen some kids were asked to produce nine different solutions to a "magic square" problem. It really sounds horrible. But if those little minds are enlightened after they have got the first solution, it would be far easier. That is to regard this resolved square as a piece of paper. How could we transfer all values of each column into each row respectively; and vice versa (to transfer all values of each column into each row respectively)? This is particularly the same as folding along the diagonal of the paper. Then they will find four different solutions as they double over. When they rotate around, they will find another four different squares. Aha! 

These paper folding tricks can be put into a way of algebra, which is called matrix. Each transformation refers to a matrix. And this is an abstract way, combining equations with dynamics. 

Some friends may feel frustrated and confused about the Hermitian matrix, the transpose of conjugated matrix. This concept is often strange to a new face for its complex format. But this is a reasonable innovation similar to the standard deviation or variance. In the complex field, we always meet up with the " i ",the square root of -1. If we want to calculate the "length" or"module" or whatever measurement, you will find the method of simple squaring is no longer effective. Because the squared " i " is -1, which might offset positive values. And we cannot measure this matrix. Hence we invent the concept of conjugate value, and then the Hermitian matrix. 

Many students learn this course online, but only find the confused bricks and stones, never see what the framework of the architecture would be. Those bricks and stones are well known to everybody,"group", "domain", "field". You do not need to know Galois, the young man cut off in his prime. In modern days, all mathematicians can be put into an abstract term, Nicolas Bourbaki, which is not a real person but is the collective pseudonym for 20th-century mathematicians.﻿

Meer lezen (88 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7022_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-EX9-6kwAGbQ/UiLOa_45cqI/AAAAAAAAAEU/8cE-cE6LGBY/w426-h482/2012%C2%B7Preston+S.+Fan.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7022-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hermitian%20conjugate/photos/113064514537405769519/albums/5842692957245684865/5842692957062233058?authkey=CO3c6YXrjv6z4AE</link><title>Lazyplus, what's the name for this style of closure? 

I wanted to buy some jars of this kind yesterday and ended up practically giving an engineering spec in text to someone as a description.  Probably would have been more efficient to draw a blueprint.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7022_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-c-XPuwsuNkk/URVqSd1e--I/AAAAAAAAHH4/Tv-iOW77be0/w426-h320/IMG_20130208_124317.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>