<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:36:15" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/115417572242464286437/albums/5947724356454736241/5947724363988906354</link><title>50,000 Ultimate Rewards sign up offer – Chase Sapphire Prefered Card http://www.mightytravels.com/13232755/50000_ultimate_rewards_sign_up_offer_chase_sapphire_prefered_card.php﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-2FSxS4juyE8/UoqPy_F-sXI/AAAAAAAAL78/x_Bm7XhxaMc/w426-h237/chase_50000.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/105706178492556563330/albums/5707973490334836801/5766259370053783666</link><title>Preferred Hangout Language For This Session 

Wow, I just noticed this new option under "Hangout options" when starting a hangout. Perhaps this will help with the language barrier problems experienced in public hangouts. I'm going to play around with it to see if I notice anything different. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-F-CvakgFw2Y/UAXeWJrS0HI/AAAAAAAB-FQ/WCO1P3lt_bw/w426-h237/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/115677423527955102124/albums/5912106340323794657/5912106342596320866?authkey=CLXH2OaWx76cfg</link><title>Owens Corning Architectural Shingles, As PREFERRED CONTRACTOR We represent the Best, And share our discount with our customers, Best Prices on Roofing "FRASER RROFING LLC"﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-HVTPpbx2LQ8/UgwFZRjJnmI/AAAAAAAAAGM/RyktOzxtkrU/w426-h237/Fraser+Roofing+Owens+Corning+prefered+contractors.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/102141977003090560589/albums/5892028578870778513/5892028582579209074?authkey=CIXs9eSFib3ucg&amp;sqi=113711991701122962234&amp;sqsi=0b21f5ef-10eb-4c33-9fce-cb8cc734d1ab</link><title>+Dat Chu , your Azrael blob has me wondering about my own IG/SW version. I was thinking that Wolf Priest could supply Fearless, Prefered Enemy, Outflank, 5+ Psychic protection and Stealth for a relatively low cost. (Could also stick a Rune Priest in there to give them Cover 5+ save which Wolf Priest improves to 4+ cover.) Worth trying out, you think? About the same total cost as Azreal. Anybody have thoughts about it?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_o26jYwMjwc/UcSwx08VA3I/AAAAAAAAEYo/V48ECy6DI5s/w426-h609/blob.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/111582328174252160142/albums/5987044847568075249/5987044848484638770?sqi=106531613159130328605&amp;sqsi=7d479f95-ef5b-4225-bf3a-616183ad2cf7</link><title>Yep. Just arrived. Missing my xtra charger. But got two tshirts and three key chains that i didnt back. Would have prefered the xtra charger. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-X0lOpRy9wgI/UxZBkahCYDI/AAAAAAAAJ1I/wMZbmjhQixY/w426-h757/2014%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/100035762233109552669/albums/5940313918755972497/5940313921597031602?sqi=115758385206378551362&amp;sqsi=ae0d29d1-e1b2-4ef6-a0f0-63e9c2eebb4e&amp;sqi=115758385206378551362&amp;sqsi=ae0d29d1-e1b2-4ef6-a0f0-63e9c2eebb4e&amp;sqi=115758385206378551362&amp;sqsi=ae0d29d1-e1b2-4ef6-a0f0-63e9c2eebb4e&amp;sqi=115758385206378551362&amp;sqsi=ae0d29d1-e1b2-4ef6-a0f0-63e9c2eebb4e</link><title>Custom URL Issues 

Your highly motivated and truly dedicated team of of Google+ Top Contributors hear you loud and clear - there are some problems with the custom URL options that many of you are getting as apart of today's rollout.  We don't have any answers for you yet, but we need your help so that we can properly escalate this issue. 

If you're having problems with your vanity URL (not just not having received one yet, but an issue with the one you did receive), please leave the following information in a comment below. 

1)  A link to the Page/Profile in question 
2)  The name of the Vanity URL offered to you. 
3)  The name you would prefer. 

We're collecting this information for the specific purposes of passing it onto our Community Managers and through them the Product Teams.  Help us to help you!  Thanks, everyone. 

Edit (10/30/13 - 9:05am PDT): Okay, the way we got it figured, issues are pretty much falling into one of three categories. 

1) You have a Custom URL that consists of your first name and last name and a nickname if you have one on your profile and you want to change it to something else. If that applies to you, then we can't help you here - that's exactly the way it's supposed to work.  Your best bet is to send feedback via the option at the bottom of the dropdown menu on the lefthand side of the desktop site and request a feature involving changing Custom URLs; the more people do so, the higher priority it is to get it sorted. 

2) You have a Custom URL with a Top Level Domain issue, like 'net' or 'blogspot' or 'CoUk' or something appearing in your Custom URL and you don't want it there. If that's you, then keep letting us know here in this post so we add it to our escalation report because that's actually a problem. 

3) 1 and 2 don't apply to you, but there's still a weird issue with your Custom URL. If that applies to you, same rules as number two - keep letting us know here.  Be sure to include details on your particular issue. 

Thanks to all of you, and we hope we can continue helping you get the most out of your Google+ experience!﻿ 

Edit (10/30/13 - 10:26pm PDT): Thanks everyone!  We now have all the examples we need for our report.  For any further requests regarding Custom URLs, please use the Feedback tool located at the bottom of the dropdown menu on the left (desktop). 

Closing comments on this post now so that all further feedback can go there﻿

Meer lezen (49 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-lEqaLgARtEc/UnA8Cd8ZRLI/AAAAAAAA3lA/4JH8pIfjdgs/w426-h237/10-Brands-with-Great-Google%252B-Pages.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/111348027847411245504/albums/5778583394286558273/5778583400806025554</link><title>vmware有点不解的地方，prefered mod里面有 vt-x和vtx-ept的设置， 
然后下面又有个可以勾选的 virtuallize vt-x，有啥不同？ #Vmware  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_08_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-RoQwMAx7Bbk/UDGm_J4DCVI/AAAAAAAAgcs/bhWlJGY394I/w426-h237/vmwarexxxx.PNG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/101707061863693895408/albums/5964951226020678833/5964951231732979442</link><title>تقدم الآن لشغل #وظيفة "Research Assistant in Polymers and/or Nanomaterials" بجامعة العلوم والتكنولوجيا بـ #مدينة_زويل #مصر 

Apply now for "Research Assistant in Polymers and/or Nanomaterials" vacancy at University of Science and Technology at #ZewailCity #Egypt #Jobs 

Languages: Excellent level of spoken and written English 
Job Category: Research 
Job Type: Part time/ Full Time 
:Description 
The selected candidate will chemically modify polymers, develop new nanostructures (nanoparticles, nanofibers, nano-scaffolds, etc…) for various biomedical (mainly drug delivery and tissue engineering), biotechnological and environmental applications.The responsibilities of the selected candidate will include, but not limited to:1. Doing intensive literature survey2. Conducting experiments 
3\. Writing research papers, review articles and assisting in proposals writing. 

4\. Database management 

5\. Ordering equipment and supplies 

:Qualifications 
The candidate should have a B.Sc. (with a grade of very good at least) or M.Sc. (PREFERED) in Polymer Chemistry, pharmacy, or related area 
Laboratory experience of more than one or two years in polymer synthesis, polymer modification, and nanofabrication 
It is preferred to have prior publications or conference presentations 
Gender: Any 
Education major: Polymer Chemistry, Pharmacy or related fields. 
Experience: 1 – 2 Years in research 
:Other Skills 
Strong writing and presentation skills 
Experience with spectroscopic and other analysis tools (FTIR, UV-vis, NMR, EA, Thermal analysis, etc) and ability to interpret the results 
Experience with the use of electrospinner is preferred 
Experience with endnote, web design, SPSS is preferred 
Can work in a team and must be able to follow instructions and protocols 
Problem solving and analytical thinking 
Planning and organizing 
Innovative 
Initiative 
Job Contact Person: Human Resources 
Job Contact E-mail: recruitment@zewailcity.edu.eg 
Job Contact Info: To ensure full consideration, please send your application letter, curriculum vitae including the names and contact details for at least two references and a brief statement of a research career plan (not more than 1 page) to recruitment@zewailcity.edu.eg by no later than 13 January 2014.Please use the job code ‘Nanomaterials-RA-2014’ in the subject line of your e-mail.﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-YU4D-vAB2F8/UsfDiqX5FvI/AAAAAAAAB1Y/aW095Cz7xrM/w426-h237/f.b-04.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/113380154862525616342/albums/5995364393483192897/5995364393889062834</link><title>What is your preferred haircut or style? 

#Haircut #Hairstyle #MensStyle﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-CmR39cD5l_A/UzPQJsTIX7I/AAAAAAAAFno/IoT9-pKBWKM/w426-h320/52jTH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7027-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/prefered%20or%20preferred/photos/109531051302578874151/albums/5917873342141065313/5917873342459445106?authkey=CIKcuOzzivX-qQE</link><title>Email marketing is dead? No, Email marketing is evolving 

People say that email is losing its efficiency. The fact is that email is still a prefered method of communication. 

See some details and the infographic here → http://goo.gl/KElJbx﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7027_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DHniSQPjmIg/UiCCc2MMf3I/AAAAAAAABKA/7k5dtvKL1Ek/w426-h237/email-marketing-620x206.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>