<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7030">Lyrics Bangarang</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:47:45" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/110500989111244502729/albums/5827648666626692497/5827648670483937554?authkey=CK6gy4DY84CE8wE</link><title>TOP 10 SONGS OF 2012 

1\. Usher, “Climax” 

It never gets to a climax itself: Usher’s magnificent performance here, which is justifiably much louder than anything else on the recording, is all tension building and no release (it starts with his 800-thread satin falsetto), and pulls back every time it seems like it’s building toward a lunge forward. You could say the same for the song itself, with its lyrics that are phrased like a seduction but are actually about a dead-end relationship. It denies its listeners the pleasure of a destination; instead, we get to focus on the thrill of where it is at every moment. 

2\. PSY, “Gangnam Style” 

Roll your eyes if you must. The fact is that 20 years from now, you’re going to remember this as the song of 2012. The YouTube meme, a good-natured, mind-bendingly catchy lampoon (in Korean!) directed at a particular neighborhood of Seoul, turned into a global obsession. Now, how many curious listeners are going to track down more K-pop and Korean hip-hop? Probably not many — but if you’re one of them, you might want to start with G-Dragon’s “Crayon” video. 

Lyrics: 
Oppa is Gangnam style 
Gangnam style 

A girl who is warm and humanle during the day 
A classy girl who know how to enjoy the freedom of a cup of coffee 
A girl whose heart gets hotter when night comes 
A girl with that kind of twist 

I'm a guy 
A guy who is as warm as you during the day 
A guy who one-shots his coffee before it even cools down 
A guy whose heart bursts when night comes 
That kind of guy 

Beautiful, loveable 
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey 
Beautiful, loveable 
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey 
Now let's go until the end (= let's dance and go crazy 'till there's nothing more left) 

Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style 
Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style 
Oppa is Gangnam style 

Eh- Sexy Lady, Oppa is Gangnam style 
Eh- Sexy Lady oh oh oh oh 

A girl who looks quiet but play (have fun) when she plays 
A girl who puts her hair down when the right time comes 
A girl who covers herself but is more sexy than a girl who bares it all 
A sensable girl like that 

I'm a guy 
A guy who seems calm but plays (have fun) when he plays 
A guy who goes completely crazy when the right time comes 
A guy who has bulging ideas rather than muscles 
That kind of guy 

Beautiful, loveable 
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey 
Beautiful, loveable 
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey 
Now let's go until the end (= let's dance and go crazy 'till there's nothing more left) 

Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style 
Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style 
Oppa is Gangnam style 

Eh- Sexy Lady, Oppa is Gangnam style 
Eh- Sexy Lady oh oh oh oh 

On top of the running man is the flying man (*), baby baby 
I'm a man who knows a thing or two 
On top of the running man is the flying man (*), baby baby 
I'm a man who knows a thing or two 

3\. Carly Rae Jepsen, “Call Me Maybe” 

Like “Gangnam Style,” the way everybody was hyping this song, quoting it and parodying it for a couple of months made it seem a little oppressive. (Cookie Monster’s “Share It Maybe” on Sesame Street might have been the last straw.) The arrangement is incredible, though, with synthesized orchestral strings playing a tense pizzicato loop through the verses and stabbing around Carly Rae Jepsen’s voice like fireworks on the chorus. Jepsen is a subtly fantastic vocalist too: check out the way she spins every phoneme in the line “And all the other boys/ Try to chase me.” 

4\. Taylor Swift, “We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together” 

5\. Parquet Courts, “Master of My Craft” 

6\. Skrillex, “Bangarang” 

7\. Nicki Minaj, “Roman in Moscow” 

8\. Pussy Riot, “Putin Lights Up the Fires” 

9\. The Belle Brigade, “No Time to Think” 

10\. Can, “Graublau” 

entertainment.time.com﻿

Meer lezen (109 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-8vObNwjgmdA/UN_3lu_4-RI/AAAAAAAAMos/DQqI_A5Ya6A/w426-h257/psy-gangnam-style-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/103225232336735040063/albums/5843271491580645889/5843271490509017314?authkey=CO2Um5nk_4-kmQE</link><title>TODAY﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4QXYEVZOe3M/URd4di31EOI/AAAAAAAABUI/XYutF3NNxV0/s426/gra.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/116726325327075260175/albums/5785392389892313505/5785392392210731890</link><title>QUESTION OF THE DAY: If you had to choose a theme song for yourself that played every time you walked into a room, what would it be? 

#questionoftheday 

Let me know if you would like to be added to the QotD notification circle﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-zua2XmlkJwY/UEnXunf303I/AAAAAAAAaPc/P-QYaQ0wYJo/w426-h237/09.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/114116601160642008127/albums/5964520993693449969/5964520998218711634</link><title>I think it's time for me to do another rockin cover. What do you guys wanna hear? It can be from a movie, game or from the pop charts.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-8yHUTwYbyNs/UsY8PxovQlI/AAAAAAAASeg/sbqkkhhkiJs/w426-h421/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-01-02%2Bat%2B9.39.10%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/112546833633391090642/albums/5634894696214831905/5769258517690918130</link><title>The Amazeballs Music Player. 

In recent light of +Georgi Karavasilev's mission to design an "idiot proof" music player UI, I figured I would weigh in here with what my dream music player would look like. 

I call it Amazeballs Music™ (patents have already been applied for). 

You can play around with play button positioning, menu button/menubar and whatnot if you like... but I want to see is that search box. And it should be voice enabled. 

Oh sure, there should definitely be a First Boot Assistant, helping you to setup the player so that it knows where your local music is and also asks if you want to add web-based music services too; I'm thinking Spotify, last.fm, Grooveshark, Pandora, YouTube and more. 

Think of this as like the +Ubuntu Unity Dash but in a music app. It asks the simple question "What do you want to listen to?" 

Type it in, whether it's an artist, a genre, an album or a single track. The app will be smart to recognise the query and prioritise results. It will favour local results (if you search "Nirvana", you obviously want to play the high-quality mp3s you have already have, rather than a 128kps YouTube video). 

Results are displayed not in lists but grids and preferrably using visuals of album art and artist photography to aid in recognition. A list of text does not scale well; grids do and have done for centuries. 

Musical preferences are remembered, possibly with some +The Zeitgeist Project love in there. 

Most importantly, the app learns your preferences, not the other way round. 

Essentially, imagine a music app that had the speedy and useful searching power of Google but with the beauty and preference-remembering abilities of the Unity Dash. 

The only app I can currently think of that comes close to this is Tomahawk but it appears to have no solid Linux desktop integration yet and weirdly only plays a single track then never moves onto the next track. 

I've deliberately left out browsing views for the app, largely because browsing in music apps _is already prevalent in hundreds of current Linux music apps._ 

But search is often relegated to a tiny little searchbox in the corner of the app. 

Let search take a greater role and allow the app to learn who you are. 

#hex_ui-design﻿

Meer lezen (53 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_05_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-RyGKIYE-CQg/UBCGDhRdJPI/AAAAAAAANAs/ktmHb0jSv5Q/w426-h302/amazeballs-music.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/117163332633490191376/albums/5843139723440088817/5843139720773553362?authkey=CJ6N-qHy7urI8gE</link><title>I'm going sane ~ what a shame!!! :'(﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-2kfX7XxdwIA/URcAniWuzNI/AAAAAAAAAsE/ISefWLLrvuc/w426-h320/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/103004643235588316768/albums/5772769490589985201/5772769493473193778</link><title>Lil Wayne Quits Rapping . YAYY !!!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-m5_6yg0M-jM/UBz_RNSubzI/AAAAAAABXb8/C0sTs5kjffo/w426-h338/images.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/109558936176395349609/albums/5856658675490779217/5856658679384026530?authkey=CM-VpOHnq9eoTQ</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-77NAtSpyklU/UUcICftkraI/AAAAAAAAw6Q/5zVKnRovTx8/w426-h303/115.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7030-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Lyrics%20Bangarang/photos/107577785796696065138/albums/5857817679789795473/5857817680150064178?authkey=CMaFuKeOnfLaCw</link><title>the Raring Ringtail (13.04) - Part3 

Amarok now with initial desktop search integration﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7030_09_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Zhn0RDggk5E/UUsmJOBY7DI/AAAAAAAABaM/hEjt3ps8Xis/w426-h266/amamuk.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>