<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:12:36" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/101636881032878340378/albums/5659773896928457057/5659773898992748754</link><title>Journalism 101: do not write your headlines too early 

Oops - iPhone only made it to 4+annex :) 

(Australian Financial Review 5th Oct 2011)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-leFxEYDsc7Y/TouOX9Z9iNI/AAAAAAAACGw/uaPPzMZKz9s/w426-h568/11%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/113117251731252114390/albums/5821879042540492913/5821879040941714178?authkey=CI3kzIDJmcK7lwE</link><title>Why I don't do access journalism. 

Even within the insular world of the technology press, there are many kinds of journalism. Reports about science, technology, business, finance, culture and how-to information are all lumped together under "tech." 

And there are many ways to go about approaching the subject. 

The two extremes of technology journalism are what you might call "user journalism," and "access journalism." 

On the one extreme, the journalist becomes a user -- they get the products, try them out and write their stories based on their personal experience as a user. 

On the other extreme, the journalist becomes a member of the industry. They attend parties, accept junkets, and try to spend all their time with people in the industry, then write their stories based on their experience as an industry figure. 

In the past, I've done both. Nowadays, I do neither. 

I don't do "user journalism" because there's plenty of great user journalism out there. Both product reviews and how-to information are examples of user journalism. There's a glut on the market of "user journalism." 

And I don't do "access journalism" because I'm a little old-fashioned about my craft. I started out in newspaper journalism, and reporters are always warned as a matter of professional ethics about getting too close to sources. Ultimately, journalists are supposed to represent the readers, not the industries (or governments) they cover. So I've become increasingly resistent to "access journalism," and all its many trappings. 

Note that I have nothing against either "user journalism" or "access journalism." We're all describing different parts of the elephant. And, admittedly, I am a user, and I do have access, so I do veer into the extremes. 

I prefer to view myself as neither user nor industry figure, but instead an observer who watches the industry and tries to make sense of what's really going on. I try to take a Big Picture view of technology, which is ultimately about how tech affects culture and how culture affects tech. 

Anyway, I was inspired to write this post after reading +Dave Winer's post on access journalism. 

http://threads2.scripting.com/2012/december/cynicismAmongReporters 

_(Pic props: http://lejournaldelaphotographie.com/fullscreen/391 )_﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_02_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Gji2tjyj4Mo/UMt4JGCfawI/AAAAAAAE5Co/J9ZP88_9m_E/w426-h267/Screen%2BShot%2B2012-12-14%2Bat%2B10.01.16%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/103158907747936316985/albums/5804746036649515425/5804746040884644210</link><title>RECYCLING CONSENT 
Manufacturing Consent: Noam Chomsky and the Media revisited by Peter Strempel, with some mixed feelings 

[For ease of reading this essay is also available at my blog: http://peterstrempel.zxq.net/omnium/tv/manufacturing-consent/mc-29-10-2012-1.php] 

Manufacturing Consent: Noam Chomsky and the Media (1992), 167 minutes.  Zeitgeist Films, Canada.  Produced and directed by by Mark Achbar and Peter Wintonick. 

The project 
Quite apart from the pleasure of revisiting old stomping grounds, a review in a contemporary context if this seminal documentary serves as an arguably arbitrary but convenient starting point for a broader project: a review of documentary films in the 1990s and 2000s as an often underrated vehicle for presenting unorthodox perspectives and interpretations of defining contemporary events and developments, offering a tantalising glimpse at what might be the lacunae in mass media news coverage. 

I intend to intersect this territory in three essays.  The present review considers the relevance, then and now, of the documentary's exposition of Chomsky's theory on mass media as mechanisms to represent the interests of corporations by persuading people to support those aims, while diverting their attention away from unpalatable truths. 

A second study will survey a selection of documentaries that followed Manufacturing Consent, examining in particular what new dimensions have been added to contemporary news discourses by them.  The third essay will focus on a personal reconciliation of these voices with Fourth Estate ideals and contemporary 'reporting' practices. 

To begin, it strikes me as appropriate to reorient us to the environment which gave rise to both the book, Manufacturing Consent: The Political Economy of the Mass Media (1988) by Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky, and the film, which premiered on 18 June 1992 at the Sydney Film Festival in Australia. 

A different time 
Achbar and Wintonick followed Chomsky for five years to make their documentary,(1) implying that they began their project in 1986 or 1987.  A very different time that some readers here might not remember too well, or not at all. 

To offer a glimpse into that era, imagine Miami Vice entering its fourth season, the Simpsons first appearing as short film clips, Star Trek: The Next Generation premiering on network TV, the Bangles walking like Egyptians, Bon Jovi prancing on a prayer, U2 still hadn't quite found that pot of gold at the end of the rainbow they were looking for, fully grown men wearing big hair and pastel baby blue and pink clothes, women wearing shoulder pads as big as those sported by gridiron players, fluoro coloured neon lights in nightclubs and restaurants, and greed was definitely good all around. 

In 1987, US President Ronald Reagan challenged Mikhail Gorbachev to tear down the Berlin Wall, and was censured by the Tower Commission for not being in control of his National Security Council's 'involvement' in the Iran-Contra conspiracy.  But all was well, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average surpassing 2000 points for the first time, rising to 2510 in July. 

Microsoft, which had listed publicly the previous year, released Windows 2.0, and the Knoll brothers began developing the prototype for Photoshop, which was initially distributed exclusively with a brand of slide scanners, a couple of years before Apple acquired the licence for distributing version 1.0. 

The Single European Act was passed by the European Community while the Walt Disney Company and France signed an agreement to construct Euro Disney.  Margaret Thatcher's Conservative Party was re-elected to a third term in the UK, while British Airways was privatised in line with her policies, and listed on the London stock exchange. 

Rudolf Hess, the last surviving Nazi war crimes prisoner, hanged himself in his cell in Spandau Prison, aged 93, and the First Intifada began in the Gaza Strip and the West Bank. 

In Australia, Prime Minister Bob Hawke's Labor Party was re-elected for a third term, and the 19-year reign of Queensland Premier Johannes Bjelke-Petersen came to an end. 

Born that year were Lyndsy Fonseca, Robert Kardashian Jr, Hayley Westenra, Rosie Huntington-Whiteley, Maria Sharapova, Hilary Duff, Zac Efron, and ... Snooki.  The departed that year included Alistair MacLean, Liberace, David Susskind, Andy Warhol, Randolph Scott, Danny Kaye, CL Moore, Erskine Caldwell, Rita Hayworth, James Tiptree Jr, Fred Astaire, Jackie Gleason, John Huston, Lee Marvin, Lorne Greene, Peter Tosh, Mary Astor, and Henry Ford II. 

By the time the documentary was finished in 1992, the first Gulf War had come and gone, George HW Bush was the outgoing President with Bill Clinton waiting to be sworn in.  The Soviet Union and the Berlin Wall were gone, and Boris Yeltsin was President of a new Russian Federation.  The Maastricht Treaty signed into existence the European Union and South Africans voted to end Apartheid.  There was civil war in the former Yugoslavia and Afghanistan, riots in Los Angeles following the acquittal of police who beat Rodney King, and Queensland introduced Freedom of Information laws. 

The long 1980s boom had become only marginally unstuck with the British currency crisis in 1992, and the whole idea of a never ending, American-led prosperity, based on unlimited growth, made it seem unnecessary to challenge orthodoxy.  In such an environment, Achbar and Wintonick's film, presenting a significantly dissenting view about corporate motives and morality, and doing so in a non-fiction film lasting almost three hours, necessitating an intermission, might have seemed a big risk, perhaps explaining why it was premiered in far-away Australia. 

It appears the gamble paid off.  The documentary became highly successful, winning 22 awards globally, being screened in cinemas in 300 cities world-wide, including 50 film festivals, and being broadcast on TV in 30 markets.  Whatever may be thought of the subject of the film, it must be accepted today as globally influential. 

The central thesis 
The film presents Chomsky as the narrator of the central thesis in Herman and Chomsky?s book: that American news media are manipulative in creating consent for corporate interests by skewing perceptions with propaganda, while avoiding negative reportage of corporate activities, or dissent from the hegemony of orthodox capitalism. 

We are told the news media do this by interposing filters between what occurs and what and how it is reported.  The filters include promoting the interests of corporate advertisers; focusing on a limited group of news 'makers' and 'experts'; relegating dissenting opinions to little or no coverage at all; limiting the length of TV or print explanations of ideas, events, opinions and analysis to fit into short 'grabs', thus limiting the breadth and depth of debate overall; repeating orthodox interpretations and opinions, particularly those initiated by 'elite' or big media outlets, as 'necessary illusions' and so often that they take on the appearance of objective factuality just by uncritical repetition; promoting this skewed coverage as an institutional and self-referential memory in media archives that are then regurgitated as actual history; and diverting people's attention away from their own self-interests or issues that might concern them, and towards meaningless distractions like sports, entertainment, and other contemporary analogues of 'bread and circuses'. 

By pursuing these strategies, corporations gain the support for their activities of the educated and politically active 20 per cent of the population that matters to them, while the opinions of the remaining 80 per cent of the population are effectively neutralised. 

It was and remains quite telling that politicians hardly feature in Chomsky's scheme of things, except, perhaps, as the lackeys of corporations.  In a different but apposite context, Chomsky is shown arguing that any kind of social or political action has to be animated by a clear vision for a better future society.  It is my own conclusion, not Chomsky's, that politicians clearly lack any such vision. 

He does, however, warn that a hegemonic system seeking to maintain private control over public resources, and which subverts human needs to function creatively rather than as wage slaves, does so by undermining the US First Amendment ideal of not limiting public access to free ideas and opinions.  As such it must have the support of politicians in deliberate actions that are corrosive of a healthy democracy as intended by the American founders and their constitution. 

This thesis was a significant challenge to orthodox views on how capitalism worked in America.  It was also a major attack on the notion that there is a 'free press' pursuing Fourth Estate ideals.  Yet these ideas were hardly new. 

The title 'manufacturing consent' was actually coined by Walter Lippman in his 1920 book, Liberty and the News, in which he opposed the old elite orthodoxy about liberal democracy: that most people are not intellectually equipped to make sound judgements about issues affecting national interests.  Consequently the decision-making function was to be reserved for an educated, intellectual elite. Lippman argued that the 'press' was a threat to democracy when it adopted objectives other than a 'free flow' of ideas, and that it did so partly because journalists themselves interposed their own subjectivities and practices between truth and reportage.(2) 

The concept of 'necessary illusions' comes from theologian Reinhold Niebuhr, who suggested in the 1920s and '30s that the inspiration for the mass of people to play an unquestioning role assigned to them by an elite is not rationality, but faith in the illusions necessary to make faith itself an animating replacement for rational analysis.(3) 

The caution that repetition of an orthodoxy gives it an apparent respectability or unassailable truthfulness dates back at least to Thomas Paine's Common Sense in 1776, in which he said that 'a long habit of not thinking a thing WRONG, gives it a superficial appearance of being RIGHT, and raises at first a formidable outcry in defense of custom.' 

That these ideas are not new does not make them less (or more) credible, but it does establish for them a kind of orthodoxy in themselves that might help to explain their public appeal. 

Chomsky's thesis oddly lacks an emphasis on concentration of ownership, which was one of the major concerns about news media elsewhere in the West in the 1980s, when orthodox capitalist theory saw takeovers and mergers as efficiencies, but fewer owners of news media raised apprehensions about the potential for fewer sources of independent analysis and opinion. 

It must also be acknowledged that while the film expurgates a thesis developed and published as the book Manufacturing Consent: The Political Economy of the Mass Media (1988) by Edward S Herman and Noam Chomsky, Herman himself, a professor of finance and a specialist in institutional analysis, corporatism, and modern terrorism, is invisible in the film despite the fact that he contributed the media propaganda model and did most of the writing,(4) an assertion uncritically confirmed by Chomsky himself.(5)  Whatever the reasons, however, the film focuses on Chomsky, not Herman, and this review follows suit. 

Also, while Herman and Chomsky acknowledge an intellectual debt to Alex Carey in the preface of their book, the subject of that debt is as opaque as Herman.  The Australian social psychologist Alexander Edward Carey is credited in some circles with pioneering the study of corporate propaganda, and he was a prominent anti-Vietnam War figure in Australia during the 1960s and '70s, but he was largely unpublished and little known outside his home country.(6)  I assume that his influence is most evident in Herman's work. 

Cambodia and East Timor - them and us 
To prove the Chomsky media thesis, the film presented an interpretation of the role of the New York Times (NYT), regarded with some justification as the most influential newspaper on the planet, in reporting news about Cambodia and East Timor between 1975 and 1979.  Without regurgitating the history of the appalling events in both places, Chomsky's argument was that the 'elite' media pointed to the horrors of Cambodia because these were perpetrated by 'them' (communists), while the horrors in East Timor were profitably supported by 'us' (Henry Kissinger, Gerald Ford, and American corporations investing in Indonesia, selling it the arms for its genocidal colonial venture).  His empirical evidence that the NYT published 70 column inches of reportage on East Timor, but 1,175 column inches about Cambodia, stands undisputed, and no matter how much NYT spokesman Karl Meyers wriggled around, trying to discredit Chomsky as naive about media practices, ignorant of journalistic professionalism, or motivated by conspiracy theories, he came across just as unconvincingly today as he did back in the 1990s. 

To be fair, there is evidence to suggest that Chomsky was ideologically blind to the intentions of the Khmer Rouge and the Cambodian genocide for much of the 1970s, probably because of the American bombing of Cambodia, and did not change his opinions significantly until the 1980s.  British anarchist Paul Bogdanor suggested that this was because Chomsky and Herman were in the thrall of 'Trotskyite style anti-Westernism, which can often result in what can seem like efforts to defend inhuman, irrational regimes.'(7)  In the context of Chomsky's argument about media focus and filtering, however, such a bias is irrelevant, even if proven incontrovertibly. 

Dissent as conspiracy theory ? 
I confess that I was moved, back in the early 1990s, by Tom Wolfe's on-screen rejection of Chomsky's adherence to conspiracy theories, but only long enough to discover two things: as a pretty recent graduate(8) who had admired Wolfe as an exemplar of alternative journalism, I had fallen precisely into the trap of being defined by my professional prejudices as a journalist - the very ones that Chomsky had indicated as a potential cause of self-censorship, and of unquestioning faith in recognised authority figures; and Chomsky had nowhere actually advocated a conspiracy theory, instead explicitly rejecting such an approach.  Wolfe had simply asserted it, and I had uncritically accepted that fabrication.  This realisation made me change my mind not only about the film, but also about Chomsky?s work more generally. 

A good part of the documentary is in fact devoted to Chomsky dealing with some grotesquely irrational accusations made against him on the basis of positions he had never adopted, but that were ascribed to him by shallow reporting and discussion of his theses. 

There was, for example, the ridiculous moment when Dutch Defense Minister Frits Bolkestein, debating Chomsky in a public forum, realised that his prepared arguments against Chomsky were based on fantastical distortions of Chomsky's actual positions, and then excused himself from the debate on the limpid pretext he had to be somewhere else, but a little too late to save face.  There were also some bizarrely incomprehensible exchanges between Chomsky and interlocutors who charged him with supporting holocaust-denial simply because he had supported freedom of speech - the freedom for French academic and author Robert Faurisson to deny this piece of history.  It was direct evidence of the power of the media to propose interpretations which are then uncritically accepted by a great many people without any effort to analyse and come to independent conclusions. 

In sharp contrast with his interlocutors, Chomsky is shown as calmly rational, pointing patiently at facts rather than assumptions, and is at his most convincing when he repeatedly states that people shouldn't just believe what he says either, but that, instead, they should form their own independent conclusions by engaging with issues themselves, based on an outlook, and information, broader than that offered by mass media. 

The cult of Chomsky 
Although Avram Noam Chomsky was already pretty well known in the US as a notable linguist and part of the anti-Vietnam War literati, it may be that the documentary established him as an international superstar among the global intelligentsia, partly because of the film's reach, and partly because Chomsky was so easily characterised as a stereotype of what an intellectual should be: mildly spoken, bespectacled, modestly presented, impeccably correct, and only ever approaching passionate loss of composure in the heat of discussion, but even then only approaching that state. 
Born in 1928 into a moderately affluent household of Russian Jewish emigre parents who had met and married in the USA, and who were both teachers, Chomsky earned Bachelor, Master and PhD degrees from the University of Pennsylvania before joining the faculty of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology in 1955, where he has worked ever since, becoming a full professor in 1961, and an Institute Professor in 1976, placing him at the pinnacle of formal academic titles, and giving him an almost unbounded remit to pursue whatever field of enquiry and publication he might choose. 

The film presents a Chomskian vision for a better society, albeit in truncated form.  He is revealed as favouring an anarcho-syndicalist economy based on libertarian notions of individual liberty, or freedom, from the need for wage slavery (his terminology) and embracing what he sees as the innately creative tendencies of human beings.  While not being specific about details, when pushed for examples of what he had in mind, Chomsky mentioned instances of pre-war revolutionary Spanish collectives and the Israeli Kibbutzim.(9) 

To rid society of being deluded by necessary illusions or contrived consent for corporate machinations, Chomsky suggests for individuals a greater eclecticism about sources of news, and attentive analysis of events rather than reliance on expert interpretations, though he concedes that the pressure of working routines makes this difficult to pursue with the effort it deserves. 

What is not made directly visible in the film is an apparent dichotomy between Chomsky's academic status, rooted in all the methodology and structure of the academy, and his apparent disdain for the academic culture of expertise, methodology, and the application of theoretical models.  He favoured instead an approach to institutional analysis via a comparison of stated aims to actions and outcomes, mostly on the basis of empirical evidence, and an almost systematic aversion to ascribing significance to individual human agency.(10) 

By way of a mea maximum culpa, as a fresh graduate in the early 1990s, and still today, I adhered to the latter principles, except the exclusion of considering individual agency, as a guide to what I perceive journalism should aspire to, albeit that I derived this ideal not from Chomsky, but from my interpretation of Enlightenment era conceptions of the Fourth Estate as a fearless collegium that should function to analyse and question the uses and abuses of public and private power. 

What bothered me in the 1990s was what I saw as a rigid determinism in Chomsky, made most explicit in his early linguistic theory, which proposed that human beings are predisposed to language abilities via 'hard-coded' genetic instructions.  This always implied to me that human beings are therefore also predisposed to specific cognitive limitations and approaches to social formation, since I saw both flowing directly as objects and constructs of language.  Today I am less inclined to make such a judgement, not least because it is deterministic in its own right, but also because I have found nothing in Chomsky's extended oeuvre that excludes the possibility of more than one valid approach to the subjects on which he writes. 

Nevertheless, I think his distinctive eschewal of theory and focus on individual human agency is what his staunchest critics seize on instinctively to make their attacks about his ivory tower isolation from the minutiae of, for example, news media methodologies and professional journalistic practices.  These are areas in which my interpretation of Chomsky has altered significantly. 

Distorted Fourth Estate principles 
In the 1990s I was much more inclined to be suspicious of Chomsky's dismissal of individuality in the practice of journalism than I am today.  Back then I believed individual integrity could always overcome institutional mediocrity, censoriousness, or hierarchy. Today I know this to have been misplaced idealism. 

My perception of journalism today includes analysis with the kind of social theory Chomsky eschews, which suggests to me that journalists tend to be dramatically influenced by their own social self-identification as educated, middle class professionals, and by the pragmatic exigencies of forming unhealthily close relationships with the subjects of their inquiry, which is particularly the case in financial and political journalism, where journalists area loath to offend their sources, thus risking being cut off from the flow of what passes as 'inside information'.  Additionally, it seems that quite often the social lives of such journalists are subsumed by contacts exclusive to their profession, making them as isolated from different social and political perspectives as professional politicians and wealthy residents of gated communities.  Arising out of this increasing isolation of journalists from reality is the particularly loathsome feature of contemporary news media that elevates notional journalists to the status of media personalities in their own right.  The spectacle of journalists interviewing other journalists is almost farcical, with palpable arrogance and conspicuously extravagant presumption evident in many of such contrivances.  This is nowhere more powerfully illustrated than in American TV news broadcasts. 

I must acknowledge, though, that my personal opinions and insights in this regard do not contradict Chomsky's overall analysis of journalists, as a faceless group, acting as the propagators of corporate propaganda by repeating uncritically the nonsense they are told by their contacts and pretending that this parroting is 'objective' journalism citing 'credible' sources. 

In my contemporary reassessment, then, Chomsky's uncomplicated and relatively Spartan approach to hypothesis does not seem to adversely affect his reasoning or theses, and might actually be quite ingenious in pursuing a formula that is both accessible for mass consumption, and the profitability of publishing for a mass market, without undermining the potential for the altruistic purpose of bringing alternative and challenging points of view to the 80 per cent of people Chomsky suggests are irrelevant to corporate interests and machinations. 

There is, however, another aspect to Chomsky's 1980s analysis that is purely contemporary in its ambit: does his thesis stand up to the changed dynamics of the new media that arose after he developed his views? 

Chomsky's withering gaze into the future 
Last year Chomsky commented that neither computers nor the internet had created as big a change in society or communications as the telegraph in the 19th century, and that online communication through gadgets 'erodes normal human relations', making 'them more superficial, shallow, evanescent', and causing people to be far less well read, even among his own students,(11) than they used to be. 

For these comments he was taken to task by PJ Rey(12), who suggested Chomsky as an example of affluent white academics reinforcing their privileged positions by rejecting media accessible to non-experts, and that 'Chomsky is seemingly ignorant to the use of Twitter and other networks in shaping the Arab Spring and the #Occupy movement; or the fact that young people are voraciously sharing and consuming important news stories through these same networks; or that Blacks and Hispanics were early adopters of smartphones; or that gay men have been pioneers in geo-locative communication. In many cases, historically-disadvantaged groups have used social media technology to find opportunities previously foreclosed to them.  For these folks, social media is hardly trivial.' 

Rey further claims that 'Chomsky's mistake is in his failure to recognize that social media marks a significant shift away from the passivity of mass consumption and towards a paradigm of mass participation.  Social media's characteristic rapidity - which Chomsky ties to shallowness - is also what facilitates its interactivity.  And it is, in fact, the participation and interaction engendered by social media that differentiates it from broadcast media.  The old media-manipulation frame is simply inadequate to capture all the activity occurring through these new means of communication.'(13) 

What does all of this actually mean?  Let's step through it point by point. 

Chomsky does not appear to need to promote or preserve any status.  He already has a reputation unequalled by more than a handful of people on the planet, and he arrived at it without the use or need of social media, or the gadget culture, neither of which appear to be serious threat to his status at this stage (he's in his 80s). 

It is unclear to me whether Rey was suggesting that 'Twitter and other networks' caused the Arab Spring and Occupy movements, or that they would have embodied entirely different ideas without social media and gadgets, or that there was some kind of positive outcome attributable to social media and gadgets. 

There is a concept known as 'weasel word' that proposes the combination of two words sometimes sucks the meaning out of one of those words, like a weasel sucks the yolk from an eggshell.  This is probably precisely what happened in labelling Arab social and political unrest a kind of spring without acknowledging the bitter irony of borrowing that unfortunate conjugation from the Hungarian and Czech uprisings against Soviet tyranny in the 1950s and 1960s.  I say bitter irony because both of these uprisings were brutally suppressed, and even more draconian controls were imposed as a consequence.  It is too early to say what will be the case in Arab countries because the bloodshed and brutality of the initial foment has not yet subsided.  Arab re-freezing may yet be a more accurate description than spring. 

In terms of the Occupy movement, it might be said that social media and gadgets were used to spread awareness of various sit-ins, but to what effect?  Has the Occupy movement a legitimate claim to have changed a single feature of American politics or capitalism? 

Is it not just as plausible to argue that both kinds of movements occurred for reasons well beyond mere communications technology, and that both actually serve as good examples of media orthodoxy that works to divert attention from seriously analysing root causes for these phenomena, directly attributable to corporate machinations in both cases, by focusing instead on the trivia of technology accessories and fetishes?  Can it not also be argued that the endless mention of these examples is in itself an example of media repetition to establish as truth an inconsequential support by the news media for 'alternative' points of view?  Finally, is the repetition of these examples without any analysis not just effective, free advertising for the corporations that control the networks and gadgets spoken of?  And not a word by Rey about the potential for networks and gadgets in both cases to have been used to track, arrest, torture, and even kill the dissidents. 

Voracious sharing of important news stories appears a deliberately disingenuous re-framing of the reality that young people are drowned in tsunamis of information without any means to determine the accuracy, context or value of that data, let alone its importance to them personally.  How significant are celebrity gossip, pictures of cats or landscapes, or re-shared TED video clips?  I suggest that the sheer volume of unsorted, unclassified and unvetted information flowing through the internet makes it unnecessary to censor or suppress dissidence since the inconsequential and inane will always drown out the truthful or significant. 

Rey's mention of gadget uptake by blacks, Hispanics and gays implies that these methods of communication have somehow substantially altered the behaviour or social and political prospects of those groups.  I don't see much evidence for that suggestion.  Instead, I see evidence for the success of corporate advertising for gadget accessorising, and support for Chomsky's argument that gadgets have not promoted a depth of analysis that might be required to understand and change the barriers to black, Hispanic and gay marginalisation in their own societies.  LOL, ROFL, and CUL8R type messages don't count for anything in that context.  Again, no mention of the potential for these gadgets to also function as tools of criminal organisation, and for legal and illegal persecution of the groups mentioned. 

Taken together, the points Chomsky and Rey made about social media in particular, but also gadgets as access ramps by implication, are strongly reminiscent of a comment made by commercial Google Plus user, +Steve Faktor, that the only apparently sound reasons for using this platform are the pursuit of profit (self promotion, advertising), and 'fun'.  No mention of social agitation, fomenting revolution, or even just serious analysis and debate.  In that formula we might recognise Chomsky's cautions about the 'manufactured consent' for the notion that the pursuit of profit is not only necessary, but transcends all critique of it.  Likewise, we might recognise as a Chomskian 'necessary illusion' that immaterial labour(14) to populate social networks, thus making them profitable for their owners (corporations), is 'fun', and, perhaps more importantly, that this 'fun' is a diversion from understanding how such behaviour exploits the people performing the immaterial labour. 

In this light, Chomsky's thesis appears to stand up pretty well in the era of new media, gadgets, social networking, and all its mantras. 

Exit stage left ... 
It seems appropriate to me to return to an earlier critique I made of Chomsky, as a parting observation.  There is an absence in his conception of the role and power of media: the concept of interpellation as developed after Althusser and Foucault to describe a process of objectifying media audiences as both consumers of, and objects within media discourses.  That can be taken to mean in some contexts that apparently external, objective observers are interpellated into the media discourse by being positioned as members of groups such as consumers, or law abiding citizens, or patriotic Americans, and pre-emptively laden with fabricated values that the observers uncritically accept as their own.  Thus, for example, good 'law abiding American consumers' includes you as the consumer of the message, and also as the 'patriotic' American who supports whatever war your president has initiated, while also sharing in the community of consumptive interest of your fellow Americans in the shiny new products on offer from patriotically American corporations.  And so it goes.  But not in Chomsky's conception. 

Perhaps I see this as a failure in Chomsky's thesis because the notion of interpellation proposes that all dissenting ideas are portrayed as pre-existing components of even the media discourses that first mention them, and that are already accommodated in orthodox perspectives without challenging them or the media discourses themselves. 

I'm pretty certain a smart, switched on guy like Chomsky would have been aware of this concept, but chose not to adopt it, and therefore also not to speculate on whether his own dissenting opinions would be interpellated into the very mainstream media discourses he criticised as propaganda extrusions. 

I propose here that over a relatively short period of time Chomsky has become part of the orthodoxy of discussion about the media and corporate elites, and may in fact have been a significant influence on the emergence of a whole range of dissenting opinions, almost as a genre of mainstream media, particularly in the area of documentary films. 

That last area, of a genre of dissident documentary examinations of contemporary issues, is the subject of a coming survey, the second of my three essays about my experience of documentary films in my era. 

NOTES: 
(1) Burns, Alex (2001), 'operation mindcrime: the selling of noam chomsky.'  disinformation, 15 November, reproduced at http://www.chomsky.info/onchomsky/20011115.htm, accessed on 18 October 2012. 
(2) See http://archive.org/details/libertyandnews01lippgoog for the digitised book. 
(3) Chomsky, Noam (1989). Necessary Illusions.  http://books.zcommunications.org/chomsky/ni/ ni-c01-s06.html, accessed 18 October 2012. 
(4) Burns, Alex (2001). 'operation mindcrime: the selling of noam chomsky'.  disinformation, 15 November, http://old.disinfo.com/archive/pages/article/id589/pg5/index.html, accessed 20 October 2012. 
(5) 'I can begin with the very title of the film. The title of the film is Manufacturing Consent. The title is taken from a book, a book written by Edward Herman and me. And if you look at the book, you'll find his name comes first. Well, his name came first at my insistence . . . for the simple reason that he did most of the book. And in fact, most of the things people write about in the reviews of the film are his work. Here we already begin to see what's wrong. These are all cooperative activities and they shouldn't be personalized and associated with one individual. . . . And if the impression is given that there's some leader or spokesman or something like that organizing, galvanizing things, that's absolutely the wrong lesson. The lesson there is follow your leader. The lesson ought to be: take your life into your own hands.'  Source: http://www.chomsky.info/books/power02.htm, accessed 20 October 2012. 
(6) Sources: State Library of NSW: http://acms.sl.nsw.gov.au/item/itemDetailPaged.aspx?itemID=888148, accessed 26 October 2012; Pilger, John (2005).  The Propaganda War On Democracy.? Znet, 16 May.  http://www.zcommunications.org/the-propaganda-war-on-democracy-by-john-pilger, accessed 24 October 2012; Carey, Alex (1987). 'Managing Public Opinion: The Corporate Offensive,' Aotearoa Independent Media Centre,  http://www.indymedia.org.nz/sites/default/files/usermedia/application/3/Carey.pdf, accessed 25 October 2012. 
(7) Bogdanor, Paul (undated). 'Noam Chomsky on Cambodia', http://www.paulbogdanor.com/chomsky/wma.html, accessed 18 October 2012. 
(8) My undergraduate degree is a BA English with double majors in journalism and 'literature, language and culture', and a politics minor. 
(9) Chomsky spent some months in 1953 living in the northern Israeli kibbutz of HaZore'a, which he described to Shira Hadad in 2005 as a mixed experience, enjoying the social aspects but not the nationalist intellectual climate in which he said excessive optimism was displayed about Stalinism.  The interview, apparently conducted for Israeli newspaper Haaretz, cannot be found on that paper's web site using a simple search, but is reproduced on Chomsky's web site at http://www.chomsky.info/interviews/20051110.htm. 
(10) Abele, Robert P (2011a). 'Conspiracy Theory,' Spotlight on Freedom, http://spotlightonfreedom.com/conspiracy-theory, accessed 25 October 2012; and Abele Robert P (2011b). [Unpublished draft] 'Noam Chomsky's Theory of Justice,' Encyclopedia of Social Justice.  The Hague: Springer Publishing.  Source: http://www.chomsky.info/onchomsky/2011----.htm, accessed 25 October 2012. 
(11) Jetton, Jeff, (2011). 'The Secret of Noam: A Chomsky Interview'.  Brightest Young Things, 9 March.  http://www.brightestyoungthings.com/articles/the-secret-of-noam-a-chomsky-interview.htm, accessed 24 October 2012. 
(12) Rey is a sociology PhD student at the University of Maryland. 
(13) Rey, PJ (2011). 'Followup: Chomsky on Social Media', The Society Pages, 19 October, http://thesocietypages.org/cyborgology/2011/10/19/followup-chomsky-on-social-media/, accessed 24 October 2012. 
(14) Unpaid but nevertheless time and resource consuming labour typical of social networking activities.  I have written about this on Google Plus at https://plus.google.com/110695872689494369839/posts/d74CF9tLLVV. 

Note on the image: detail from the cover design of the video cassette of the documentary.  That's right - video cassette.  Remember those?﻿

Meer lezen (682 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-u6inqjF6778/UI6ZxPJIyXI/AAAAAAAAAqI/j38I7svhCNw/w426-h320/manufacturing-consent.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/103636214904400746295/albums/5792107212270913153/5792107216093911394</link><title>Happy Birthday, William Faulkner, born 25 September 1897, died 6 July 1962 
The 10 Best William Faulkner Quotes On Writing 
1\. The best fiction is far more true than any journalism. 
2\. If a story is in you, it has to come out. 
3\. Facts and truth really don’t have much to do with each other. 
4\. In writing, you must kill all your darlings. 
5\. Always dream and shoot higher than you know you can do. Don’t bother just to be better than your contemporaries or predecessors. Try to be better than yourself. 
6\. The artist doesn’t have time to listen to the critics. The ones who want to be writers read the reviews, the ones who want to write don’t have the time to read reviews. 
7\. A writer needs three things, experience, observation, and imagination, any two of which, at times any one of which, can supply the lack of the others. 
8\. The writer’s only responsibility is to his art. He will be completely ruthless if he is a good one. He has a dream. Everything goes by the board: honor, pride, decency, security, happiness, all, to get the book written. If a writer has to rob his mother, he will not hesitate; the Ode on a Grecian Urn is worth any number of old ladies. 
9\. My own experience has been that the tools I need for my trade are paper, tobacco, food, and a little whisky. 
10\. Read, read, read. Read everything— trash, classics, good and bad, and see how they do it. Just like a carpenter who works as an apprentice and studies the master. Read! You’ll absorb it. Then write. If it is good, you’ll find out. If it’s not, throw it out the window. 
http://post.ly/9QIFb﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DZVyMtshZPA/UGGy0zxBGWI/AAAAAAAAnKY/u48fvB6Tifs/w426-h256/WilliamFaulkner_WritersWrite.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/112574195622556976547/albums/5951069225849236353/5951069230284960370</link><title>I really question the future of anime and game journalism, sites like Kotaku and ANN seem to be letting anyone with a blog writers grip on English write for them.  I saw one writer using a Doge meme in their PS4 Vs XBox1custom sticker review, another giving KLK a poor review after watching episode 1 citing references to Nazis. 

If you're going to sell yourself as a reputable news site you should at least have someone proofreading this stuff before hand. I don't ever go out of my way to check these sites so maybe I'm only seeing the bottom of the barrel but every time someone links me an article it only reinforces my fear that Game/Anime Journalism is dead.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_05_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-3vXGKIt27IU/UpZx71DkcnI/AAAAAAAA0xw/oJhJIGQgkn4/w426-h241/1385428732778.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/105263975143467297874/albums/5716316152282478577/5716316152621308354</link><title>How To Get a Job At A Magazine 

Getting a job at any magazine company is really tough. They receive hundreds of submissions. Assistant jobs are more often than not being no more than a �go for� type job. Internships are available but less than a handful of interns are lucky enough to receive an offer of employment afterwards. So how can you avoid the pitfalls of the magazine industry? You have to plan and be prepared. 

The first step to any career is career research and planning. In the case of the magazine industry even more research and planning is required. The first step to starting a career that will land you a job at a magazine company is to make the choice of what you want to do. Companies that sell magazines (in print &amp; online) are just like any other business. They utilize various departments such as 

Accounting 

Advertising 

Marketing 

Inventory 

Shipping 

Sales 

However, magazine companies also employ 

Journalism 

Editorial Staffing 

Publicists 

Editorial: Must be original, creative, analytical and absolutely must understand the audience that the magazine targets. 

Journalism: Magazine journalists research and write news and article features that will most interest a magazine's audience. 

Publicist: Get publicity for the magazine�s next issue prior to it being distributed. When you read reviews or news articles about a story that runs in magazine, it is the department and responsibility of a Publicist that makes sure that would be readers know that particular story will be published. 

Be sure to read the magazine from front to back and read several issues before even applying to the magazine. Know what the magazine is about, have an understanding of whom they are targeting and form solid opinions about some of the issues or subjects that the magazine publishes. Be prepared to discuss (but not defend) your opinions in an interview. 

Other characteristics every company looks for are 

Hard working 
Dedication 
Passion about the services / products the company sells 
Self-motivated 
Have multiple skills - in this day and age everyone should have multiple skills 
Experience and or knowledge with a desire to continue learning the company�s desired style of work. 
High school prepares you for the real world of being an adult but college teaches you the fundamental foundation to begin a career. So yes, both educational steps are needed. If you are still in high school the extracurricular activities that are so down graded will definitely help you land a quality job during college. However the same is true for college, choose the extracurricular activities that you genuinely believe you would like doing. High school is a time for experimenting, if you don�t like something and you genuinely believe you don�t like it because you don�t like it and not because it�s too hard than try something else. 

Great classes and clubs to take as suggested by Wired Magazine 

Courses You Should Take 

Introduction to Programming - lays the foundation for you to learn on your own 
Creative Writing 
Literature 
Shop Class - tinkering is fun 
Journalism 
Humanities 
History 
Politics 
Business 
Activities and clubs 

Debate Club 
School Newspaper 
Chess Club 
Your Blog (you have to have a blog and a personal web page that has nothing to do with a social networking site) 
Internships at any magazine or newspaper company are an absolute must for a sold and stable career. As soon as you have decided that you most definitely want to have a career working for a magazine company, start getting work experience that will be most benefit you. Working inside a magazine and or newspaper company will introduce you to the key players in the industry and where they work. A working knowledge of the following terms is most favorable: 

Web 2.0: A term often applied to a perceived ongoing transition of the World Wide Web � 2020 Systems 

Wiki: This is a website that includes the collaboration of work from many different authors. A wiki site allows anyone to edit, delete, or modify the content on the web. - The Technology Initiative Grant 

IPO: A company's first sale of stock to the public. - The Schaeffer's Edge 

Newsreader: A program designed for organizing the threads received from a mailing list or newsgroup. - Vikont Solutions Dek: Is a Data Encryption Key � OASIS Management 

Learn to network and develop a great networking circle 

But the best way to get a job at any magazine is to actually know someone at any magazine. While college is the best way to learn, meet and develop contacts it is just as important to get out in the world and meet people. This is anther place where extracurricular activities can help you. It�s a perfect place to network. Other places include online social networking sites such as LinkedIn. 

Lastly, have a great resume, develop an e-portfolio and practice interviewing, volunteer, go after internships, practice interviewing again and network. 

Soweto Magazine﻿

Meer lezen (131 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-yOjtg0KnJks/T1RvQSTSGcI/AAAAAAAAAC0/iOj4o-hz5KM/w426-h491/images.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/100844393588789487035/albums/5766710398887312977/5766710397871402546</link><title>O is for OZ 

AMOS OZ is the highly regarded Israeli author of numerous works of fiction, journalism, and essays. He has received several international awards. Oz writes in Hebrew, his native tongue, and has been translated into more than thirty languages. He is Professor of Hebrew literature at Ben Gurion University in the Negev. 

“If I had to tell you in one word what my work is about, I would say family.” 
                                                    – Amos Oz, “The Art of Fiction No. 148,” The Paris Review, 2009 

Sometimes the family Oz writes about is his own family; in these autobiographical works such as A Panther in the Basement (1995) and A Tale of Love and Darkness (2004), he explores ‘a perpetual rotation of love and hatred, jealousy and solidarity’ within a small family more loving than it is riven by tensions between passionate rivals. Sometimes the family Oz writes about is the archetypal dysfunctional family that appears in The Same Sea (1999): riven by loss, tempted by incestuous longings, exalted by echoes of Biblical poetry in their daily lives, and connected by the same sea, the novel’s characters are as real and contemporary as they are timeless. 

In A Tale of Love and Darkness, Oz tells the tale of his family by beginning at the beginning. 

Amos Oz was born in Jerusalem in 1939, descendant of renowned kabbalist Rabbi Alexander Ziskind of Grodno, Lithuania (b.1793), Oz’s great-great-great-great-great grandfather, and ultimately descendant of Yehuda Arieh Klausner of Jerusalem: scholar, librarian, writer, and father of Amos Oz. In between the famous mystic and the seventh succeeding generation that produced the internationally acclaimed writer, the paternal line brought forth a second Lithuanian scholar of Torah; an enlightened trader who allowed his daughter to study; the daughter, who settled in Odessa along with the family of her atheist brother, a factory owner; and Amos Oz’s grandfather, a petty trader and secular hedonist who ultimately settled in Palestine. 

As a teen-ager, reacting to the trauma of his mother’s suicide when he was age twelve, Oz broke with his paternal heritage and moved to a kibbutz, where he lived with another family; when he began to publish his own writing, he changed his name to Oz, meaning “strength.” By the time he emerged as a writer, Oz thus appeared to be an independent agent. Working outside the imperatives of his particular of family history, the author seemed identified with the existential crisis of the Jewish people (Unto Death, 1971), and preoccupied with the current reality, and politics, of Jews living in Israel (A Perfect Peace, 1982; Black Box, 1987). Yet it was his father, the student of literature, combining as he did the scholarship of the ancestral rabbis with the enlightened outlook of the secular businessmen, who must have served Oz as a role model. Oz had likely internalized the history of his paternal ancestors, from their intense confrontation with the divine to their embrace of secular ideals and business success. As a contemporary scholar puts it: 

“So there you have it. The entire recent history of our spiritual and intellectual journey as Jews encapsulated in just four paragraphs [of Oz’s A Tale of Love and Darkness] covering eighty years from 1805 when Oz’s great great great great grandfather was seventeen and living in Lithuania, to 1885 when his great grandfather was living in Odessa. From faith stronger than the agonies of self-imposed deprivation and affliction, to faith fragmented into a hundred irreparable shards.” 
(‘God has Survived the Enlightenment, but Whose God?’ Rabbi Dr. Tony Bayfield, 2009) 

Oz also writes of his maternal ancestry in A Tale of Love and Darkness.  His mother, Fania Mussman, was the granddaughter of a simple miller in Ukraine; Herz Mussman, the miller’s son and eventual father of Fania, became successful as the steward of a large estate; Herz Mussman was ruined in the 1930s, but reinvented himself as a carter after emigrating to Palestine. Oz’s mother grew up in Ukraine, where she was harshly treated by her own mother, Itta Schuster. Fania studied philosophy and history in Prague, and later at Hebrew University in Jerusalem, where she met fellow scholar Yehuda Klausner. They married in 1938. 

Why should a writer’s genealogy matter? Isn’t it an author’s literary pedigree that counts? No doubt, but in the case of Oz, a great deal of the spiritual and intellectual history that informs his writing has been transmitted precisely through the author’s personal ancestry. Part of what gives this author his authority is the way in which he has come to terms with the history of European Jews, as represented by the trajectory of his forebears: from religious preoccupation to disavowal and rebellion to accommodation. If Oz’s reckoning with the vast cultural inheritance of prior generations, and by extension with the Jewish past in Europe, is a more recent development, his novels have centered upon childhood and the nuclear family (A Panther in the Basement), or its precursor, the couple in love, (My Michael, 1968) or have pondered life in Israel amidst struggle and loss (The Same Sea, 1999) from the beginning of his career. 

Who is this family whose tale Oz tells? 

You can begin to know this family by getting to know the father. 

You can get to know Oz’s father, the librarian, in A Panther in the Basement, and enjoy his contradictory character: that of an Anglophile who hated the occupying British. Such contradictions are part of the story of the survival of the Jewish people. Indeed, Oz’s father hid a terrorist’s explosives behind his library books, where the British failed to find them during a search. A man divided against himself, Yehuda Klausner could not appreciate the irony of his contradictions. But that irony was clear to his son. Yehuda Klausner was, as Oz remarked, a man who wrote “fiery illicit pamphlets against perfidious Albion, calling the British every name in the book, quoting Shelley and Keats and Byron to prove how hypocritical and unjust they were.” (‘The Art of Fiction No. 148,’ Paris Review, 1994). 

Or you can get to know the archetypal, conflicted father of Oz’s experimental novel The Same Sea. Recently widowed, the father longs for his ghostly wife and his son, missing in the Himalayas, and in a different way he longs for his daughter-in-law, who may or may not be pregnant with his grandchild. 

Reading The Same Sea is a dreamlike experience. Full of the sensory detail of Mediterranean life, the novel is nevertheless vague, almost tenuous, in its evocation of character. Reading The Same Sea is more like reading a cycle of poems than becoming absorbed in a novel. Each chapter is like a prose poem: advancing the story, yet readable on its own, for its own delights. 

Following are a few passages from The Same Sea, translated by Nicholas de Lange. 

Through us both 

Before excuse me is this seat taken, 
before the color of your eyes, before can I get you a drink, 
before I’m Rico, I’m Dita, before the fleeting touch, 
of a hand on a shoulder, it passed through us both 
like a door opening a crack in your sleep. 

He isn’t lost even if he is 

Crystalline silence, transparent and blue. 
The wind has died. Over deserted plains 
a veil of glassy frost descends. 

Cold and empty. Vast. Just over the horizon 
according to the map there is a little village. 
There is no sign of the village. Perhaps he is lost. 

He will press on a little further. If he is lost 
never mind: he will give up and go back 
silently. The way he came. 

The road is level. The frost is fine and bright. 
Beside the sea his father is waiting 
and beyond, in the depths, his mother. 

But Albert stops her 

Her hand so light in the hay of my chest. On the back 
of her hand my shriveled hand. She’s on my own. I’m on her own. 
On my veranda. We are alone. The sea has taken, the sea 
has given. A slim silhouette and a little shadow. A timid 
shadow. That turns. Escapes. The sea gives and the sea 
takes. 

Never far from the tree 

The apple never falls far from the tree. The tree stands 
at the apple’s bedside. The tree turns yellow and the apple turns brown 
the tree sheds damp leaves. The leaves shroud 
the apple. The cold wind leafs through them. 
Winter comes autumn is over the tree is eaten the apple 
rots. Very soon it will come. It will come it will hurt. 

O is for Oz﻿

Meer lezen (179 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DlTvu4ZddxA/UAd4jbOtLjI/AAAAAAAAALI/Nqr3ZyJWhVI/w426-h256/0z.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/106875990476951662693/albums/5912107733743164913/5912107735947585522?authkey=COC067nbu9CiSA</link><title>The unfortunate death of the sidebar, and other things I miss from writing for print publications 

I am the first person to tell you about the glories of writing for online publications rather than print magazines. The benefits are wondrous, including but not limited to: 

* No arbitrary word count. I never will forget writing about a complex topic and struggling to make the explanation fit into 750 words, because that was all that would fit on a Sm@rt Reseller magazine page. And then the Art department told me I had to cut another 50 words "because the art came in big." (Not that I hold a grudge or anything, but that was the ugliest damned drawing I ever saw.) 

Now the article can be exactly as long as it needs to be, whether that's 500 words or 2,500. As long as you want to read every one of them, we're good. And I don't have to spend extra time cutting information that readers truly ought to know. 

* Speed to publication. When we published weekly or daily, a "scoop" was measured in hours. Now it's measured in minutes. 

* Linking to relevant information. Some things never get old, and one of those joys is the splendid ability to help a reader dive deeper into a topic by giving her a URL to a relevant news story, background documentation, or other articles on our site on the same topic. 

However, I miss some things from my Print Days with an almost physical pain. I've never found a publication that fills the void of these publishing/journalistic practices. 

* Primarily I miss print packages, wherein you might have five "entry points" to an article, with sidebars and infographics and case studies. 

For example, in print I might have a "mainbar" -- the primary feature article -- about how a Texas hat company implemented their e-commerce system including integrating the company minicomputer with partners' supply chain systems using XML. I would accompany it with separate charts (perhaps, oh, sales numbers or transaction speed), and with a Tech Sidebar (a glossary of the tools or technologies used, since at the time not everyone knew what XML was), and another sidebar with a bulleted list of "What the company learned" and perhaps another of a tangent about where XML is headed (but not quite related enough to include in the main feature). Not to mention related artwork and charts, put together by a professional art staff. 

That example would have been unremarkable at the time; I can think of other "packages" with far more elements. It's a different kind of story construction, and it is totally gone today. 

Oh, sure, the mainbar is still there. But the sidebars are gone. Few of them stand alone well enough to be mini-articles of their own, and even if you do take the time to do that, only a tiny percentage of readers looking at the main feature click through to read the "click here for more about the tech the company used" link. These were written to be something you saw out of the corner of your eye. 

Which means that you ought to look at them in the same way today. Except I have never never seen a website publication that did even an "adequate" job of displaying a sidebar, much less a good one. It's an unsolved mystery of web design. 

End result? These packages are gone. (Which doesn't stop some of my experienced writers from submitting sidebars with their features. All I can do is cry.) 

* Speaking of case studies, some sorts of stories have gone away completely. In print we used to write case studies regularly, such as "how a company solved a business problem" or "the steps this business took to implement this technology, and the pain that ensued." It's still possible to write a case study these days but (unless the who-did-it subject is a big name such as Disney or Bank of America or Johnny Depp) the hook is always about the technology or business problem. 

I think this is a victim of the SEO-driven article; nobody says to himself, "Gosh I wonder how a random ice-cream company deployed cloud computing tools" and heads to Google. But in print, you'd turn the page and... there it was. If the headline and art grabbed you, you'd glance at the text and perhaps you would be hooked. 

The other category that disappeared with print was big product review roundups. These had their problems -- many of my friends still bear the scars from comparing 25 video cards or 40 printers -- but review roundups helped readers wrap their heads around what to look for in a product category, what they got for the money, and so on... not just the "editor's choice." A few publications still do real reviews (a hat tip here to +Computerworld) but so few pay for them anymore. 

Arguably that void is provided by plenty of sites where people offer "real" reviews for free, from yelp to Amazon to tripadvisor. Those have a lot of value, but there is even more value in someone doing a dispassionate comparison of several options and telling you what really matters in your choice, not theirs. 

Note that I love writing reviews so much that I turned my own reviewing into a serious hobby at Amazon. I guess my professional reviewing skill with computing is why I earn so many Helpful votes, even though I mostly write about fiction, food, and crafts.  (If you are tempted to see how it's done, visit my list of nearly 800 reviews... and I am not shy about suggesting that more Helpful votes are always appreciated. http://ow.ly/nWf58 ) 

I probably could categorize this type of stuff as "articles you didn't know you wanted to read," what +Abbie Lundberg once called, "Eat-your-vegetables articles." Sometimes you need information landing in front of you, not the pull of reading only the information you searched for. To some degree social media answers this serendipity ("Oh look what my friend shared!") but that works mostly for topics that tug at us emotionally ("code review lessons I learned from my cat") rather than the "dull" things you need to pick up somewhere ("How many of these disaster recovery mistakes is your company making?"). 

* With a little less intensity, I miss a table of contents where you can see everything in an issue, and visually understand an article's category. People understood that a column was an opinion and that a news story was a reported and researched article. Nowadays everything looks the same, and readers can be confused about the authority of the speaker. 

In print, too, readers understood that the cover story was the one that we editors believed was the most important. That didn't mean the rest was _un_important, but it helped them recognize the priority of the information in their lives. 

* And even less intensity, but still some sadness: I do miss photography and imagery that were designed for an article, not chosen from a stock art site or grabbed from a casual photo done by the writer. This particular problem is getting a bit less-yucky because we have more visualization tools for the graphically-challenged (/me holds up her hand); a screen shot can replace a thousand words; and the stock art sites have gotten pretty good. Besides, all you want is a picture of my cat anyway. 

* A few years ago I might have said that I miss clever headlines with puns and such because SEO demanded we write the same text that someone types into a search engine. I'm happy to say that the clever headline is back with social media. Even if the article has an SEO-friendly "just the facts ma'am" headline, I can tell you about it on social media with any damned wording I like (such as "This proves we killed English," which just netted me my most-ever Twitter retweets). 

Whew, that's plenty -- but I bet that with some thought I could add more. Or you could. What do you miss from print publications that's gone online? 

#blogsofaugust #writing 

Earlier in this series: 
Several Tiny Tips for Improving Your Prose (a few words at a time) 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/106875990476951662693/posts/iumJ78UADX4 

The Three Reasons to Write 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/106875990476951662693/posts/f1KBrGXBtat 

Advice for Writers: Coming up with sell-able ideas 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/106875990476951662693/posts/ak8bp2XhNmf﻿

Meer lezen (162 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-mg_jsHsFNqg/UgwGqYL-p_I/AAAAAAAABLw/JDvQ0FGo1Go/w426-h567/ink_dreamstimefree_4723847.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/106875990476951662693/albums/5916263298591687713/5916263300860210434?authkey=CLvVsdu0n9vzWQ</link><title>My recommended books on writing 

Somehow, I managed to become a full-time writer and editor without a college degree. I've never taken a class in journalism (though I keep thinking I should), and my writing classes were back in school when a term paper was considered huge at 8 pages. 

I became a writer by writing, and I did it because I loved it. 
(See my earlier post about motivations, "The Three Reasons to Write" 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/106875990476951662693/posts/f1KBrGXBtat ) I began writing professionally when opportunity knocked on the door... or really, when it knocked down the door and came to get me out of bed. 

"Write without pay until somebody offers pay. If nobody offers within three years, the candidate may look upon this circumstance with the most implicit confidence as the sign that sawing wood is what he was intended for." -- Mark Twain 

So it wasn't until after I was earning a decent living as a full-time writer that I began to read books about how to do it. My interest has never been academic or pie-in-the-sky; it's always been pragmatic, even when my primary consideration is, "How can I improve my skills? What can I do to make myself more creative?" Of equal importance is my ability to make a living as a writer and editor. And by "make a living" I do not mean "scraping by;" my cats have expensive taste in kibble. 

Is that enough context? Okay, let's take a look at some of the books I find most useful to me as a writer. Maybe they'll help you, too. In no particular order: 

I read The Well-Fed Writer: Financial Self-Sufficiency As a Freelance Writer in Six Months or Less several years ago, and I quibbled with several of his points (such as a lack of discussion of cash flow). Nonetheless it's a decent guidebook if you're considering the freelance lifestyle. The author, Peter Bowerman, has updated the book since then; perhaps he's addressed some of these issues. 
http://ow.ly/ofYGK 

Lynne Truss' Eats, Shoots &amp; Leaves: The Zero Tolerance Approach to Punctuation is a wonderful book to make you appreciate using punctuation correctly. And it's truly funny, besides. I've given copies of this book as gifts to several of my regular authors because it's a pain-free way to improve one's skills. 
http://ow.ly/ofZ1W 

Bird by Bird: Some Instructions on Writing and Life, by Anne Lamott, taught me several important lessons. One of them is her mantra to write shitty first drafts; that is, don't worry about editing anything until later, just write it all down right now. It gave me permission to be bad at the beginning because that let me improve it before anyone else saw it. Plus she talks about procrastination. Also, it's funny. (Do you see a theme here?) 
http://ow.ly/ofZaa 

A former (cherished) boss gave me a copy of The Art and Craft of Feature Writing by William E. Blundell about 13 years ago, and that one book really helped me get my head screwed on straight. Blundell taught me how to tell the difference between a topic ("I could write something about data centers, maybe?") and a feature idea ("How to prepare your data for the zombie apocalypse"). And he vastly improved the structure of my articles. 
http://ow.ly/ofZWi 

There are some who embrace Julia Cameron's The Artist's Way as a lifestyle change. I'm not among them, but I got a lot out of her book at one time and I do suggest giving her suggestions a try. Cameron's suggestions helped me find new ways to be creative, helped me resolve problems by "talking them out" with myself (not just writing related), and helped me recognize my own constructive processes, so I could get out of my own way. 
http://ow.ly/og0MG 

Most of these recommendations are common ones, but I dare say that nobody has suggested, before, that as a writer you pick up a copy of Audition: Everything an Actor Needs to Know to Get the Part. As I wrote in a review several years ago, it has a surprising amount of value to given even a non-fiction writer: His second guidepost: "What are you fighting for?" helps actors look for the conflict in the scene. But it absolutely resonates with me as a writer and even more so as an editor. I'm so often surprised at how much writers shy away from conflict in their writing. Yes, even non-news non-fiction. Readers respond to conflict because they have choices in their own lives and it's your job to help them make good choices. If you're writing about two products that promise to solve a technical problem, there's an inherent conflict ("Which one is worth the money and time? Which will make me happy? I want to make the right decision!") and it's appropriate to identify that conflict. If you're quoting people on two sides of an issue, it's far more interesting to read how and why each side believes his viewpoint is right; but I see so many writers cover the story as if only one side is credible. It's far more interesting the other way. 
http://ow.ly/ofZGB 

I've read plenty of other books on writing, and it would not take a lot of effort for me to add more to the list. But these should get you started. And, of course, you can add your own suggestions in the comments! 

#writing #blogsofaugust﻿

Meer lezen (99 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ymXtW-w9j2c/UhrKIF1z7QI/AAAAAAAABPI/iGgWh3E4nnw/w426-h274/carousel_most-ridiculous-eula-clauses-560x360.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7037-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/how%20to%20write%20journalistic%20review/photos/116874863662598950951/albums/5950401109307557153/5950401109049519058</link><title>Layman's writing: The importance of a good intro 

I don't have any formal training on writing, I didn't go to journalism school, in college I studied earth sciences and writing classes weren't a highlight of the curriculum. 

I enjoy writing and there aren't many things in life that brings me joy as much as getting my ideas across to people. I'm also a bit of a perfectionist so in the past, the self consciousness that I'm lacking training and experience on writing had always made me a bit shy to show my writing to others. 

So what did I do? 

I decided to learn from other people's experiences. Hoping that I'd be able to gain insights of what makes their writing good and hopefully borrow some of their tricks. 

One book that I found incredibly valuable is Robert M. Knight's "Writing public prose: How to Write Clearly, Crisply, and Concisely" 

http://www.amazon.com/Writing-Public-Prose-Clearly-Concisely/dp/1936863014 

The book told me to ditch high school level organization and spend my time crafting a good intro instead, for it provides a frame work in which authors can tell their stories the same way they would to their spouse or friends. 

Jeremy Clarkson quite often demonstrates how to do this properly. 

Check out how he crafted the intro of his review on the new Maserati Quattroporte: 

Another day. Another squadron of messages from members of the Twitter army asking whether they should buy a BMW X3 or an Audi Q5. Or for my opinion on the Hyundai Veloster. Or if a secondhand Jaguar XK is a good buy. And the simple answer to all these questions is: I absolutely don't have a clue. 

Mainly, this is because it's not 1932 any more. Back then, there were hundreds of different car manufacturers, all trying something new and interesting. Valves were being mounted sideways, axles were fitted to the roof. Gearboxes were upside down, and thick-cut marmalade was being used instead of petrol. 

So the job of the car journalist was valuable. He - I was going to say "or she" at this point, but I don't think it's necessary - would puff on his pipe, listen to the engineer explaining why he'd mounted the propshaft to the steering column, and then write a long review of whether or not the solution had worked. These were the days before oversteer became the be-all and end-all of motoring journalism. 

Today, the differences between an Audi Q5 and a BMW X3 are infinitesimal. Picking a favourite in terms of engineering is like picking your favourite from two sardines. Or two milk bottles. Or deciding which is your favourite ear. 

You can check out his full review below and see how his intro helped him to organize his review and eventually tell it like one would tell a friend at a dinner party. 

http://www.topgear.com/uk/jeremy-clarkson/jeremy-clarkson-october-top-gear-magazine-column-maserati-quattroporte-2013-10-14 

As always, this post was entirely composed on my phone, Samsung's Galaxy Note 8.0﻿

Meer lezen (69 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7037_10_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/--xsNLHOLWgI/UpQSSDf8q9I/AAAAAAAAPdU/X8TdPzu7Yt8/w426-h266/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>