<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:29:28" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/101292786949171118245/albums/5810025322714341425/5810025326519667714</link><title>This science attacks something I care deeply about: tuning fork diagnosis of stress fractures. Yeah, you read that right. 

Supposedly a humming tuning fork applied to a stress fracture will make it ache. This analysis of studies since the 1950’s tried to determine if either ultrasound or tuning forks are actually useful in finding lower-limb stress fractures. Neither technique was found to be accurate; “it is recommended that radiological imagining should continue to be used” instead. 

Sigh. I really loved the tuning fork thing. However, thank goodness, they aren’t saying that a tuning fork actually can’t work … just that’s it not reliable for confirmation, which kind of a “well, duh” conclusion. I don’t suppose I ever thought it was a slam dunk diagnosis, just an easy and quirky clue generator. 

http://SaveYourself.ca/bibliography.php?sch8 

Lovely tuning fork photo by Shaylor: 
http://www.flickr.com/photos/shaylor/﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-bJazB9yqSGE/UKFbQGs6TAI/AAAAAAAAAIw/ocag1rAbgO4/w426-h284/tuning%2Bfork.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/110206169594070357955/albums/5634061481668563521/5634061481890391890</link><title>This is a photo of a tuning fork. I had this idea of using an extremely shallow depth of field to defocus the prongs and make them look like they're vibrating -- a visual representation of sound, if you will, done without any postprocessing (other than making the photo black and white). 

In case you're wondering: the tuning fork was in fact vibrating and sounding when I took the shot. Though it made no difference for the photo, that just felt like the right thing to do. 

Incidentally, this was my entry for a friendly photo club contest. The theme was titled "Atonality", and it asked for photos suggesting a lack of center, independent parts, chromaticism, abstraction, and other elements often associated with atonal music. I didn't win, but I mention this because some of you may have noticed that shot is in fact a play on the title of that contest. You see, this is an A-440 tuning fork, so it makes a sound that's "A"-tonal. :D 

&lt;insert groans here&gt;﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Rv1Ta4SmY6o/TjA1ETbJp1I/AAAAAAACCGs/mcPHJuN62Ho/w426-h284/IMG_1573.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/109007802493662296517/albums/5674152866535140801/5674152866935933746</link><title>Demonic Portal Tuning Fork (Via the Janas and Cardea Window) - by Tribal Gothic (Click to Activate)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_03_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-kCrqSlFF_RU/Tr6j-DL7CzI/AAAAAAAAFJg/YR3Uh89yNyE/w426-h524/Demon_Cross_Animated.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/118159989747072814756/albums/5882834552506865569/5882834558772406146?authkey=COuoy9GZ2MaqtgE</link><title>Featured Item of the Day: Crystal Tuning Fork 

http://www.healingcrystals.com/Crystal_Tuning_Fork.html 

The Crystal Tuner is tuned to a frequency of 4096 cycles per second (cps). This frequency is generated from an 8cps fundamental tone raised nine octaves (i.e. 8 cps, 32 cps, 64 cps, 128 cps, 256 cps, 512 cps, 1024 cps, 2048 cps, 4096 cps.) The 8 cps fundamental resonates with the pulsation of the Earth. 

With a frequency tuned to the pulsation of the Earth, the Crystal Tuner amplifies the healing power of crystals through sonic vibration. Enhancing a crystal's ability for light conduction and powerful sound healing, when tapped on a crystal, this tuning fork forms a bridge between Heaven and Earth. 
Use discount code HCGGLE10 for 10% off your purchase.﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-BKX2P_BWH0o/UaQG3NQFZ4I/AAAAAAAACvE/eAC2FtdHFt4/s426/crystal-tuning-fork.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/101529457429929085369/albums/5712019528730601537/5711232690072345794</link><title>Tuning Fork, taken from my new Galaxy Note﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-tzN3bL8qbjs/T0Jf30lcXMI/AAAAAAAAAj8/yAiU7HdX-xM/w426-h320/20120220_145847.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/111751668601879136609/albums/5992900609665180913/5992900610258613234</link><title>A tuning fork placed in water filmed in slow motion.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_06_thumb.gif">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9hGFIfXdx-Y/UysPWnCvs_I/AAAAAAAAEms/GZv0dxiRdKs/w426-h239/ca8aadff-8d3c-448f-a490-8988a894f65f</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/106807901091951091505/albums/5832176449295425265/5832176448909113602?authkey=CJS-57yrxvPjPw</link><title>Our first Tuning Fork Training this year is coming up - Feb 22-24, details on our website or email sheila@inner-sound.co.uk for a course brochure. Deeply relaxing, benefits both physical and emotional well-being! 
Booking required http://ow.ly/gJ9Q3﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-AHtmn03Om3A/UPANlICgeQI/AAAAAAAAAHg/xStGbWYYDQo/w426-h433/1merH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/113959903678083812636/albums/5791633564370673265/5791633464316306802</link><title>Music is our foundation while the tuning fork symbolizes the potential to "Tune UP" to harmony when we truly collaborate to achieve our collective goals.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_08_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZIFT8tzQYzc/UGAD803WpXI/AAAAAAAAAGw/-BZlop76Qz0/s426/Screen%2BShot%2B2012-09-23%2Bat%2B11.55.27%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/113912467031290944426/albums/5818788789979922337/5818788794255451730</link><title>Antike Stimmgabel auf dem Mars? 
Ancient tuning fork on Mars? 
See: http://mars.jpl.nasa.gov/msl/multimedia/raw/?rawid=NLA_407975326EDR_D0050432NCAM00343M_&amp;s=118﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_09_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Iov6UcH3PgU/UMB9lECeplI/AAAAAAAAAGE/qmewuRTcRG4/s426/NLA_407975326EDR_D0050432NCAM00343M_-br.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7046-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/tuning%20fork/photos/115754371967324227307/albums/5683744593064244785/5683744592434283858</link><title>For #HistoryThursday curated by Matt Shalvatis 
Another Bulova Accutron Tuning fork timed timepiece from my collection. This one was called their "D" series day &amp; date, for obvious reasons and had an integrated band. They seem to have been manufactured only for the 1971 production run. 
When Bulova moved the set stem in their Accutrons from the back of the watch to the side of the case they placed it at the 4 o'clock position on all of them, rather then the conventional 3 o'clock position most of us are familiar with. Probably to differentiate it, along with it's noticeable hum when held close to the ear, from the rest of the pack. 
This particular model's short duration in their lineup has made it rather rare and hard to come by. I must admit, it does feel a bit strange when worn, but not at all uncomfortable. As with the rest of their tuning fork timed watches the tuning fork oscillates at 360HZ per second and was guaranteed accurate to within 1 minute a month.﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7046_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-D4CJyRBWoi8/TuC3l9IXxVI/AAAAAAAAFho/uIlkt3pMLNE/w426-h562/%255BUNSET%255D</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>