<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 15:25:49" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/101750834029362155012/albums/5974321807835389457/5974321804078326450</link><title>We’ve just provided a #10Gig Optical Point to Point #NetworkConnection in just 3 working days. Visit http://www.vtesse.com to get connected to our ROADM network﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1o3_JftxAOY/UukOBwn1orI/AAAAAAAAAXg/uG6_3SMAm94/s426/Network_Connection.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/109220060006128553211/albums/5682904025077716497/5682904022701103842</link><title>My Taxi Fetish Continues... 

Two-and-a-bit years after shooting a magazine feature about Tokyo's taxis and drivers, I still can't shake the obsession. This is not a bad thing, as obsessions can often pay their way in the photographer's life and I have made money from selling photos and series about not just taxis but umbrellas, too: another of my obsessions. 

With the taxis and their drivers the root of my obsession is part vehicular, part fauna, part scenic: I like the cars and their many different colours and liveries but the drivers add in that spice with their expressions and the mystery factor of us, the voyeur, being able to imagine what they may have seen in the course of their work. Then there is the fact that the taxi contributes so much to the mobile scenery of Tokyo with, at various times of the day, perhaps eight out of every ten cars being for hire in the city. 

This was shot yesterday whilst out with some of the folk I'd been with over the weekend, teaching and shooting at +Eric Kim's Tokyo street photography workshop. It was taken in a part of town - Okachimachi - and in an exact spot -sat on the railing by the side of the roadm under the bridge - which has become a regular haunt for me. Great light, always plenty of action and lots of wonderful vantage points for shooting. 

The tech stuff: 

Nikon D700 
Nikkor 50mm f/1.2 Ai lens [shot at f/1.2] 
In-camera monochrome using my MonoHC-01 picture control.﻿

Meer lezen (27 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-6E-oOeEDTbw/Tt27GW282uI/AAAAAAAAHKs/irSByPw0EEQ/w426-h283/okachimachi_taxi_ALF_0185.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/102491032674185146466/albums/5793930293611213345/5946550151675201442?sqi=107447406412854645080&amp;sqsi=6071378f-bcfc-4592-9a37-9c4658990129</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Z4sMIp_q7WU/UoZj21WlR6I/AAAAAAAABX8/kJ2MPUmthgA/s426/25920_10151543385452963_1584665002_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/111953967143729787078/albums/5920442008710101217/5920442009306971426?authkey=COu5lZy7gO-DGg</link><title>Get Sophisticated IP Connectivity Services From Cogeco Data Service Inc. 

Cogeco Data's IP Connectivity Services allows your business operations communicate through the Internet Protocol solutions. Cogeco is a genuine data service provider which helps your enterprise to have the quality IP connectivity services that can reduce your entire IT solutions. You can have Connectivity Services delivered through Cogeco's one of the most up to date and sophisticated all-optical standards-based networks. 

These company provides various types of Sophisticated IP Connectivity Services that will save your money, time and most importantly efforts to concentrate on your core business. 

Managed Wave 

Cogeco's Managed Wave services endow businesses to cost efficiently converge network services, together with WAN, SAN and Internet access, via a unified, scalable construction. It offers: 

All optical transport platform 
Next generation optical network 
Minimize network overbuilds 
End-to-end management 
OTN standards 
Carrier class network 
Wavelength Selective Switching (WSS) 
Reconfigurable Optical ADD Drop multiplexing (ROADM) 

Metro LAN 

Metro LAN from Cogeco Data Services improves your business efficiency with quicker, more dominant interoffice network connections. Now you can simply enlarge your local area network with genuine provider’s Ethernet Metro LAN service - cost-effective, the seamless, flexible and scalable service designed to increase your effectiveness. 

Internet Services 

Ethernet-based Internet Services stand for the apex of throughput and suppleness for Internet applications. With speeds varying from 2 Mbps to 1 Gbps and beyond from Internet services endow the ability is essential to run advanced applications such as voice, video streaming, and off-site data backup and recovery. You can have superior internet services from Cogeco. 

Managed Ethernet 

Cogeco offers Managed Ethernet cost-reducing operation services that assist you save the time and cost of network administration. It contains: 

Layer 2 Access 
Bandwidth 
Industry Leading Performance Management Package (Pro-active monitoring, pro-active notification, web-based performance reporting) 
Industry Leading Service Level Agreement 

Managed IP VPN 
Managed IP VPN is a fully supported service that has real recompenses for an enterprise - flexible, easy to administer and cost-effective. The Managed IP VPN Service contains: 

Layer 3 Access 
Bandwidth and Class of Service (CoS) 
Industry Leading Performance Management Package (Pro-active monitoring, pro-active notification, web-based performance reporting) 
Remote Access Services (RAS) 
Industry Leading Service Level Agreement 

For further details regarding IP Connectivity Services, one may visit - http://www.cogecodata.com/connectivity﻿

Meer lezen (71 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-7Qh_OVu174Q/Uimio74KvSI/AAAAAAAAACk/tYiZlBTIgBw/w426-h625/cogeco.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/101750834029362155012/albums/5933158258896660753/5933158258086452418?sqi=100394819192755577992&amp;sqsi=98f06b76-43d4-4199-a36d-7d333fab8cf4</link><title>Take a look at our super-fast, reliable, 100GbE #Network using the latest #ROADM technology, secured with DDoS technology? Visit our website  http://www.vtesse.com/networks/our-network/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_06_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DRXcSS0vNKk/UlbQACFrHMI/AAAAAAAAAM8/HsPgdcnPCiE/w426-h420/ROADM-Network-map.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7056-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ROADM/photos/117164005201677467840/albums/5952263897332423537/5952263899448480642</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7056_07_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_FdegX62zwU/UpqweugCE4I/AAAAAAAAJRA/2zf5cTG1y54/s426/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>