<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:13:31" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/110278003536476194286/albums/5830797378626825073/5830797383087536866?authkey=CNu2l5rSxYjXVA</link><title>Treehouse Friends with Jonathan Ozeran 

In this episode Amit Bijlani interviews Jonathan Ozeran, VP of Product and Mobile at RECSOLU (http://trhou.se/UC3xos) and advisor and mentor to several Chicago-based startups. Jonathan shares his experience and insights into mobile design, analytics and managing a team: http://trhou.se/11914na 

Treehouse Friends is part of the Bonus Content available to Gold Members. Check out other episodes in the series, including interviews with Josh Elman and Jessica Hische: http://trhou.se/V9Rxtw﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-EDgLgGhQ77Q/UOsnU7g1uuI/AAAAAAAABkk/TwD2vl1hMAg/w426-h271/THF.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/100107434573379707581/albums/5856923913461276065/5856923911752135474?authkey=COuQxYnM4JzE1AE</link><title>We are pleased to announce Securly as a sponsor for the Google Apps for Education Illinois Summit that will take place next week outside Chicago! http://il.gafesummit.com/ 

About Securly 
Securly is a web filter that has been designed from the ground up for schools. It is completely cloud based, takes five minutes to set up per district and costs a fraction of the enterprise solutions that schools are forced to pay for today. Securly is the only web-filter to integrate with Google Apps for Education. http://www.securly.com/ 

#gafesummit 
 ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-aIkbpyc1kdI/UUf5RDR6MzI/AAAAAAAAZYM/2_4zuQNKKt8/w426-h237/securly_logo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/112312310009074382791/albums/5901932409859601041/5901932410796693426?authkey=CIDK08zPvZqV-gE</link><title>The World's Fastest Business Jet? 
Thursday, July 18, 2013 8:15:11 AM America/New_York 
Despite enormous odds, a small aircraft startup hopes to sell the world’s fastest business plane, one styled after a military fighter jet. Saker Aircraft is pitching its two-seat S-1 as the only airplane able to fly business executives and playboys at just under the speed of sound. The plane will have a maximum speed of Mach 0.99 but will cruise at 0.95, or about 720 miles per hour, a good deal faster than most commercial flights. Why not Mach 1? Federal authorities prohibit supersonic flight over the U.S., because sonic booms are annoying. The $5 million jet is supposed to appeal to executives who want to zip from Los Angeles to Chicago, or New York to Florida, in about two hours. ”That’s what we’re selling: the fastest aircraft available,” says Saker CEO Sean Gillette, a 25-year-old ex-Air Force pilot from Santa Monica, Calif., who says he has spent about $100,000 of his own savings to design the S-1. The jet’s development is estimated to cost roughly $350 million, with a delivery target date set for sometime in 2019. The plane’s speed could prove critical for passengers in another important way: There’s no toilet on board. Nor is there a desk, table, or sofa—common amenities on business aircraft, many of which hit speeds only marginally slower than the S-1. (Cessna Aircraft’s (TXT) Citation X cruises at Mach 0.93 and carries nine passengers, although at $23 million, it’s about 4.5 times the price of the Saker.) The S-1′s lack of comforts for a gazillionaire could hinder sales, although Gillette says the airplane represents a new niche in aviation–quick flights under 1,600 nautical miles. “We know our jet is not going to be for everybody,” he said. External fuel pods will increase the plane’s range to about 2,200 miles, just under the distance for a transcontinental flight. The S-1, which will also come with an ejection seat option, is counting on the fact that half of all business jet trips are made with one or two passengers, even with planes that can carry 10 or more people. “It’s like one person riding a bus,” says John Narraway, Saker’s marketing director. Charlie Johnson, the former president and chief operating officer of Cessna, and a former U.S. fighter pilot, has been working with Saker as an advisor. Johnson is also the former president of Aviation Technology Group, which designed a similar aircraft called the Javelin in the early 2000s and collected 120 preorders before financing dried up; the company dissolved in 2008. He predicts that the S-1 will field at least enough orders for the company to produce 50 planes each year for a decade — provided it can find the money to proceed. Gillette says he and Johnson are talking with an investment bank, name undisclosed. Still, if you have gobs of spare cash and want to fly fast, why not just buy an old fighter jet? That’s what the Google (GOOG) founders,Larry Page and Sergey Brin did in 2008, getting a Dornier Alpha Jet from Europe. Microsoft (MSFT) co-founder Paul Allen acquired a Russian MiG 29 two years ago. Oracle (ORCL) CEO Larry Ellison, an avid fan of airplanes and boats, has also purchased fighter jets, according to the New York Times. Fighter jets are relatively cheap, too: A 1980s era L-39 Albatros jet from the former Czechoslovakia can be had for under $200,000, while aged Russian MiGs are sold online for as little as $79,000, less than a high-end Audi. But Johnson says a speed demon with a fat bank account cannot buy current military hardware to fly fast, and he contends that an old fighter jet is far from safe. “The old airplanes require a lot of care and feeding. Nothing in the world is nicer than something that’s brand-new and high-performance,” he says. “When you talk to these guys who want to buy [a fighter], the wives are the ones who roll their eyes.” http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-07-15/the-worlds-fastest-business-jet#r=hpt-tout 

http://www.mach3composites.com/news/businessjet-update﻿

Meer lezen (59 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-r7vrvmFzpeE/UefgQgHm17I/AAAAAAAAAII/7cakGGj8lwA/w426-h384/76031_166524126702155_4244828_n.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/113006222763238310666/albums/5978784689192264897/5978784689677485298</link><title>#Chicago Business Update 
Unstoppable. This is how Chicago business is doing even at the first month of the year with many new companies moving or expanding in the area. 
Here are some updates on Chicago’s business going full speed in 2014. 
Billionaire Sam Zell, equity group buys Lake Forest property. According to Crain’s Business, “For the first time in seven years, real estate billionaire Sam Zell is a suburban Chicago landlord. A joint venture between Mr. Zell's Equity Group Investments LLC and Chicago-based Fulcrum Asset Advisors LLC paid $13.1 million Jan. 16 for a 105,000-square-foot office building in north suburban Lake Forest that's about one-quarter vacant, according to Lake County records.” 
The state of Illinois plans to invest $3.5 million in a second business incubator for downtown Chicago, Crain's Chicago Business reported. The state-sponsored business incubator, which will house biotech and pharmaceutical startups, will be modeled on the highly successful 1871 incubator, www.1871.com, which has served as a base for dozens of emerging digital firms, Crain's reported. Illinois Gov. Pat Quinn is expected to announce in his State of the State speech Wednesday that the state's is making a $2.5 million grant and a $1 million loan to the center, which will occupy 25,000 square feet downtown, possibly at the Merchandise Mart. 
Shopping centres construction to rise in 2014. As Crain’s Business reported, “Developers and retailers are expected to complete more than 2.6 million square feet of new shopping centre space in the Chicago area this year, up 16 percent from 2.2 million square feet in 2013, according to a forecast from Mid-America Real Estate Corp., an Oakbrook Terrace-based retail brokerage.” 
Marriott's AC Hotels brand is set to open in the popular River North neighborhood. The AC will open in the existing Four Points by Sheraton hotel at 630 N. Rush Street. The hotel will have 217 rooms and all the design elements of an AC hotel such as numerous design-forward, public spaces for the millennial guests to socialize in. 
A Neiman Marcus Last Call Studio is coming to The Shops at North Bridge. Construction will begin in April, and the project is scheduled to wrap up around August 2014. The 15,000-square-foot store—the first of its kind in Chicago—will be adjacent to Eataly. It will offer in-season, designer apparel and accessories for 30 to 60 percent off regular retail price. 
For more business updates and investment opportunities in Chicago, contact: info@temple-rock.com.﻿

Meer lezen (40 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-WYi3mctPlTI/Uvjo_5DFRPI/AAAAAAAAAGk/6n4rIU7iHIc/w426-h284/chicago2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/112374836634096795698/albums/5849697798886702113/5849697798532321970?authkey=COnQzqWwsb6ZIw</link><title>I'm advising Motorola 

I love mobile devices, Android, and Google, and Motorola is at the nexus (no pun intended) of these three passions. So I've accepted a position as an advisor to Motorola. My focus is on product design, user interface, marketing, and social media. 

Motorola reminds me of the Apple of 1998: a pioneer in its market segment, engineering-driven, and ripe for innovation. I believe that great products can change everything. For example, the creation of the iMac G3 (the Macs that came in colors such as Bondi, Strawberry, Blueberry, Lime, and Grape) was a pivotal event for Apple. 

As part of Google, the sky is the limit for Motorola, and I'm excited to be advising this team. One of my first actions is to create a Google+ community about mobile devices. The community is for mobile devices from any manufacturer running any operating system on any carrier's network. I hope you'll join it: 

https://plus.google.com/communities/112915392661745517235 

Photo credit: Wikipedia 

#HolyKaw﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-cx9iiLf8orw/US5NJ5znUrI/AAAAAAAEBQk/68UcUdTntDM/w426-h469/IMac_Bondi_Blue.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/111091089527727420853/albums/5639672659667042657/5639672659082922802</link><title>Silicon Valley/SF companies: What's for lunch? 

Ken Ryu (pictured here) has an answer for you: http://getquik.com which lets you order lunch and have it delivered to your place of work. But this is no boring catering company, they work with hundreds of restaurants. Unfortunately it's just for SF Bay area now (Los Angeles is being developed, with other markets coming soon). 

I'm seeing a ton of new companies like this. What's your favorite way to get lunch delivered to your company?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-QwK646_K284/TkQkZzYeyzI/AAAAAAAAGwU/hVtQnS8AE8w/w426-h318/getquik.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7061-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/startup%20advisors%20chicago/photos/111635150542674847021/albums/5946219314823088897/5946219320197960626</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7061_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-9nuP-hOtNnw/UoU296D207I/AAAAAAADTyE/wzgSUF-Z-i4/w426-h468/1395447_631637206878467_47161428_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>