<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 15:31:04" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/101576281369213753133/albums/5832519713971063009/5832519719463994162?authkey=CPa0mPbJ_bu4Cg</link><title>A Flash Mob Performs 'Here Comes the Sun' in a Spanish Unemployment Office | +The Atlantic Cities 

To cheer up the crowd at one of the country's very full unemployment offices, Spanish radio program Carne Cruda 2.0 organized a flash mob of musicians to come and play a version of the Beatles' classic "Here Comes the Sun." 

Watch the video here http://bit.ly/WzOlTn﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-OyPpoh6h4Yc/UPFFyGgcwzI/AAAAAAAAXM8/PlrJtcgbsX0/w426-h240/sun.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/101728170107556489506/albums/5750180264874067249/5750180264402928898</link><title>Spanish Unemployment Rates (or "why I can't sleep at night")﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_02_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uA97_QC7820/T8y-fBYyxQI/AAAAAAAAB58/RFbEfJMJtTE/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/110077329003015050270/albums/5919417850589187937/5919417850890039890</link><title>"Spanish unemployment falls by 31 jobs, 0.00%" http://spainr.pt/17wZ6is﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-KNpRNgcjdPY/UiX_LEdoMlI/AAAAAAAAAGA/SaJCsuLaQ4A/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/102864308558790279203/albums/5702339467914156817/5702339467104061202</link><title>Spain's unemployment total passes five million 
Spain unemployment: Your stories 

The BBC's Tom Burridge: "Spain is hurting" 
Spain's unemployment figure passed the five million mark in the last quarter of 2011, official figures show. 

The National Statistics Institute said 5.3 million people were out of work at the end of December, up from 4.9 million in the third quarter. 

The rate rose from 21.5% in the third quarter to 22.8% - the highest rate in nearly 17 years. 

Spain already has the highest jobless rate in the 17-nation eurozone and is expected to slide back into recession. 

The 22.8% rate is more than twice the average unemployment rate of the eurozone, which stood at 10.3% in November, according to data released earlier this month. 

The Spanish figures show almost half of all 16-24 year-olds in the country are jobless - 48.6% compared with 45.8% before. 

Spain's new ruling Popular Party conservative government has pledged labour reforms to try to imporve the jobs market. 

Continue reading the main story 
Analysis 

Tom Burridge 
BBC News, Madrid 
Rising unemployment is a double blow for the relatively new administration of Mariano Rajoy. The more people who are registered as out of work, the more the Spanish government has to pay out in unemployment benefits. And fewer people in work means fewer people paying income tax, so less revenue for the government. 

On top of that, if people are not earning then they spend less and that is driving Spain into recession. 

Unemployment has been high ever since 2008, when Spain's housing boom burst and thousands of people working in the construction industry were laid off. 

The Spanish government will soon announce labour reforms so that employers can hire and fire people more easily. 

The last time I went to talk to people at a job centre in Madrid, people were waiting outside because there weren't enough chairs inside. 

Spain unemployment: Your stories 
On Thursday, public service employees staged a series of demonstrations across Spain to protest against unemployment and increasing austerity measures. 

Budget cuts 
Spain has struggled since the property bubble burst in 2008. 

In the years between 2004 and 2008, the average house price in Spain rose 44%, Construction represented about 16% of GDP by the end of the boom, and the unemployment rate was down to 7.95%. 

However, rising house prices fuelled the sub-prime mortgage market, leading the Spanish to borrow more as they struggled to get on the housing ladder. 

The downturn has seen repossessions of Spanish properties rise 32% in the past year. 

The range of austerity measures proposed by new Prime Minister Mariano Rajoy's government angered many ahead of this week's protests. 

His measures include 8.9bn euros in new budget cuts, and tax increases designed to boost government coffers by 6.3bn euros. 

However, there are concerns that Mr Rajoy will be unable to meet his pre-election pledge to cut the country's deficit to 4.4% of GDP in 2012. 

The Bank of Spain predicts the country's economy will shrink by 1.5% this year, saying the eurozone debt crisis has destroyed business confidence and closed off bank credit, causing a large drop in domestic demand.﻿

Meer lezen (81 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-YvIBqLNYXI4/TyLHiHVthxI/AAAAAAAAAko/bEG_0wNgeyI/w426-h240/_58139696_jex_1303319_de27-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/118002574519323574476/albums/6010949401800805553/6010949405285861634</link><title>http://propertymarbellaapartments.com/blog/2014/05/08/best-spanish-unemployment-figures-in-18-years/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AQ1QBZuZN3Q/U2suowDoyQI/AAAAAAAAAnY/GxWXVOyHPEI/w426-h320/Best%2BSpanish%2Bunemployment%2Bfigures%2Bin%2B18%2Byears.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/103780376865975473149/albums/5763854001895009265/5763854001148924850</link><title>Spanish-German cooperation helps 565 jobseekers find work 

As Spain’s unemployment rate continues to rise, new ideas for boosting recruitment nationwide are being tested. One of the most successful is bilateral employment cooperation with other EU Member States and in the case of Spain and Germany, 565 Spanish jobseekers have found employment with German companies over the past 12 months. 
Read more: http://bit.ly/NqwCwu﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/--X-IaLJquRM/T_1SrQOyE7I/AAAAAAAAALc/M2kugBdWfxw/w426-h320/SP-DE%2Bcooperation_Dmitriy%2BShironosov%2B_shutterstock_62758198.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/103128834341873598552/albums/5794622940176328609/5794622944389231730</link><title>Forex: EUR/USD falls on Spanish rising unemployment 
http://www.fxstreet.com/news/forex-news/article.aspx?storyid=3f2e63bf-f10c-4c9a-a09c-f8ff97ad404a 

Forex Flash: EUR/USD should fail at 1.2960/1.3000 - Commerzbank 
http://www.fxstreet.com/news/forex-news/article.aspx?storyid=4dc55d6e-99a1-458f-94bc-2c2a0899fc62﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-gx8i_p_fKoo/UGqi3d-l9HI/AAAAAAAABOE/GLqInEAwF4c/w426-h237/EURUSD%2B121002-10.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/114912524016147124146/albums/6014714575509962001/6014714579645862754</link><title>The elections for the European Parliament will take place next Sunday, 25th of May. 
This is a very difficult phase for the European community and its population. 
Poverty and unemployment are very high in countries like Spain, Portugal and Greece, Cyprus, France, Croatia, Italy and others. 

All of these countries have a youth unemployment quota of more than 25%, Greece and Spain of more than 50%. 

There are lots of young Spanish people coming to Germany to look for work, I hear a lot of Spanish spoken in Supermarkets and Cafes, and I welcome them and wish them the best of luck. 
 I used to live for a while in Salamanca, Spain, during my university years and I have come to really like the Spanish people and their culture. 

These people coming to Germany is one result of the European Union or to be more precise, the Treaty of Schengen. 
All people from countries of the European Union can move to other countries without having to ask for permission. There is a sizable German community in Mallorca, Spain, for example. 
So these elections will be highly interesting, since there are several anti European political parties that will take part in these elections. 

Sadly, at least in Germany it seems that the non-voters will become the strongest party again, gaining more than half of all votes. Below I attached a diagram, projecting the last election's results on the current one. 

I will definitely vote, but I am not yet sure which party. 
I am really confused and the complexity of Europe's problems seem so high, that I frankly do not trust any of our existing parties and their staff to be able to solve them. 

There is always an easy solution to a complex problem, but it's usually wrong. 

Addition: In the company I work for there are employees from 39 different countries, which is, from my point of view, a big advantage. 
#election2014 #europeanelections2014 #complexity #unemployment 
#nonvoters  ﻿

Meer lezen (39 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_08_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-KqSCL0haj2o/U3iPCvknk2I/AAAAAAAANMg/rgnmFgNsECg/w426-h237/eu-wahlprognose.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/112975080212497501042/albums/5870894882017312369/5870894883909743458?authkey=CNqvhemT2cO3gwE</link><title>Incredible how the unemployment in Spain has evolved over the last 6 years, Started with a 9,6% of Spain's unemployment and as of 31st March 2013, a 26%. Spanish Govt. and Europe should realise that so many cost cuts and tax increases doesnt' necessarily mean job creation and country development.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-vjyrIrqDVRU/UXmbyqUZM2I/AAAAAAAAAM4/vObq7IaOx4U/w426-h271/Paro%2B2013.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7063-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Spanish%20unemployment/photos/108966127324917372093/albums/5885331931282803041/5885331931596070834?authkey=CMzV69DEpcavXw</link><title>European Youth Flee Poorer Countries 

Who can blame them, with unemployment of the young in the 20-40% range? 

Some cited, modest improvements appear to be largely from the unemployed fleeing for more affluent areas, some university grads even leaving Europe for South America. 

Meanwhile, London's financial center is booming, places that offer champagne with hot dogs are stepping in as traditional pubs are shuttered across the city. Austerity is working great -- for some people, just not for most. 

"More than 2% of Portugal's population have emigrated in the past two years....Most were young, highly-educated people fleeing to Switzerland or the oil-rich former Portuguese colony Angola."- BBC News, 25 January 2013 

http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-21206165 

"Spain's jump in unemployment has seen an exodus of youth, with tens of thousand of young Spaniards, many of them university graduates, looking for better opportunities in countries such as Germany and Britain and former Spanish colonies in Latin America......"A study by analyst Real Instituto Elcano in February shows 70 percent of Spaniards younger than 30 have considered moving abroad."- Al Jazeera English, 7 April 2013 

http://www.aljazeera.com/video/europe/2013/04/201347202557756205.html 

Graphic and content Francis Coppola: 
http://coppolacomment.blogspot.ch/2013/06/the-movement-of-people-and-its.html ﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7063_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/--nvg9w_XEEk/UazmNcAMH7I/AAAAAAAAMYY/naSy3cCFgsE/w426-h237/BLwr1OACEAEtGAi.jpg-large.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>