<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:41:29" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/113926520452996677020/albums/5845118513021310641/5845118518602714034?authkey=CK-_-qPw7e76_wE</link><title>The SanDisk Extreme Pro CompactFlash Memory Card brings our fastest data speed and expansive capacities to your DSLR camera or HD camcorder. Equipped with SanDisk's latest memory technologies, this memory card is the professional's choice. 
for more info: http://tinyurl.com/cz9wlp6﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-wLczNJ8FVvQ/UR4IUutfS7I/AAAAAAAAAf8/OAVFRUtXCOU/w426-h355/Sandisk-128GB-Extreme-Pro-C.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/105845950081369884986/albums/5781644549758469169/5781644549888060706</link><title>Pelican 0945 Compact Flash Case ( in stock ) 
price : 260 EGP 

Keep your compact flash memory cards safe and secure with the Pelican compact flash memory card storage and protector case. Store up to 4 compact flash memory cards in a single case.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-flW6b2Sv3CA/UDyHFe2mrSI/AAAAAAAABr4/YK6Xy0MCbgg/s426/showimage%2B%25281%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/116485222102689674037/albums/5827074057601923905/5827074060214191394?authkey=CPvepIaMjrO3swE</link><title>Big cards vs. Many small cards 
128GB CF for $170 64GB COMPACT FLASH FOR $85 

One of the many arguments/religions of serious photographers is whether to use many small memory cards (these days 8gb or 16gb) or a few big cards. 

Today Amazon is having a sale on 128GB compact flash and 64gb compact flash made by brand name Lexar (tho they are 400x rather than the fastest 1000x) 
http://www.amazon.com/gp/goldbox/discussion/A255GY6XQM6GKK/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_gb_eSE3qb0RN6FEN 

Here's my take on the big vs. small cards 

MISSING A SHOT vs. SMALL CHANCE OF LOSING ALL SHOTS 
Murphy's law guarantees your memory card will be empty at the critical moment. Any time you are shooting action you have the chance to miss the decisive moment. Yes, can change the card early but then you need that many more small cards and increase your risk of losing one. 

Statistically, if you have 1 card you are at risk of 1/X of the time having it die on you. If you have 10 small cards you are risk of losing 1/10th of your pictures 1/X of the time, or differently said you are 10 TIMES as likely to lose some pictures. 
And given humans ability to track many small items that fall out of pockets and such it's probably way more than 10x. 
BUT you say, I only lose 1/10th my photos rather than all my photos! True, but big cards are cheap enough with the above amazon deal that you can have two and swap them back and forth during idle times in the action. Or cameras like 5d Mark III and canon 1D series let you write jpegs to a second card as backup which you should be doing if you're a wedding photographer and the mother in law is going to go ballistic if you lose any shots anyway. 

I'm happy to go in to more detail on my reasoning and the math behind 
USE BIG CARDS 
if people are interested. 

Anyway, checkout the amazon sale and have your camera pretty much always say 999 shots remaining!﻿

Meer lezen (40 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-0FRS6nrBmJM/UN3s_A71xSI/AAAAAAAAFRo/KSIzmglnqG8/w426-h639/IMG_0141.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/104476427991703947407/albums/5866675086043633057/5866675084704870610</link><title>Does anyone have a CompactFlash card that is 2GB or smaller they don't want? 

I have an old camera I want use but it's so old that the largest memory card it supports is 2GB, and the smallest cards I have are 4GB. Surprisingly you can still buy the old cards (assuming its not a stock control error) but they cost the same as cards that are four times larger and four times faster.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-5B2t9zZKYUc/UWqd6BR38NI/AAAAAAAAQTE/qkTdz6Uk1g4/w426-h257/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/110837982014303057310/albums/5913907969349496241/5913907972795211362</link><title>Get a memory card fast enough to keep up with you. SanDiskExtreme Pro CompactFlash cards write up to 100MB/s, now from $59.95: http://adr.ma/16CIR4W﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-towah9-YhMo/UhJr99DPHmI/AAAAAAAAHPk/HD0hlnWOYsA/s426/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/100192879878228567635/albums/5966528715740782897/5966528718494025602?sqi=110729656096374290306&amp;sqsi=ffa9e300-e5fd-44d1-be3e-4631c98b863a</link><title>The World's Fastest Memory Card 
 Lexar's 3333x CFast 2.0 ratchets up the read speed of Compact Flash cards to a dizzying 500MB/s—and that is very, very fast. 
They'll be available in in 32GB, 64GB, 128GB and 256GB sizes. It's worth noting that you could theoretically fill up the smallest one in around a minute if you were so inclined. A minute. 
http://gizmodo.com/this-is-the-worlds-fastest-memory-card-for-a-little-w-1496961460?utm_campaign=socialflow_gizmodo_twitter&amp;utm_source=gizmodo_twitter&amp;utm_medium=socialflow﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-pgtIPASH2NQ/Us1eQegAx4I/AAAAAAAAA34/bf3W4x0hdp8/w426-h240/ku-xlarge.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/114598714278063968813/albums/5962328853970849329/5962328858768451058</link><title>Software regains corrupted, formatted or lost digital data from memory card. Card Recovery Program smoothly works with SD cards, MMC card, xD card, Compact flash card and other multimedia card.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_07_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-kJ1FrkBf3Vk/Ur5ygdz0JfI/AAAAAAAAA9s/qF2oEgroxXk/w426-h320/hundred.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/100046874749680776316/albums/5793459552091762337/5793459557483185266</link><title>Recover Deleted Files and Lost Data Software (license) Microsoft Office Garbage Characters. Repair a Damaged or Corrupt Files 
Easily repair corrupt Microsoft Word files with Repair My Word. ... It is designed to recover text from damaged or corrupt Word files (.doc files) that will not ... This program work for Office 2007 .docx files. ... into Microsoft Word version 6.x or 7.x, the document contains garbage characters. ... All .doc files supported 
Repair options for Microsoft Outlook and Email files – Outlook (PST, OST), Outlook Express 
(DBX), Word (DOC), Excel (XLS), Access Database (MDB), PowerPoint (PPT) and Zip (ZIP) 
Details: 
All Memory Card Recovery Software (license) 
Details: 
Photo recovery software for memory card used by digital camera. It can effectively 
recover lost, deleted, corrupted or formatted photos and video files from various 
memory cards. It supports almost all memory card types including SD (Secure 
Digital) Card, CF (Compact Flash) Card, XD Picture Card, Memory Stick, 
MicroDrive, SmartMedia Card, MMC (Multimedia Card), Micro SD, MiniSD, SDHC 
and more. 
Data Recovery - Sim Card Software (license) 
PhoneBooknumber, Inbox Sms, Outbox Later Sent SMS, deleted SMS﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-4HWh0v_p3fE/UGaAxcBghHI/AAAAAAAAAEw/xg2U8ZHyM64/w426-h551/All%2BMemory%2BCard%2BRecovery%2BSoftware%2B%2528license%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/112063946124358686266/albums/5713857648700764449/5713857650595668386</link><title>Well, recently I've had some photography bad luck (http://bit.ly/y6FbGd), and it seems to be continuing tonight! +Trey Ratcliff and I just got home from a full day of shooting (part of which was the PhotoWalk we hosted today http://bit.ly/vZQLWz). 

When I put my brand-spanking new 32GB SanDisk Compact Flash card into my card reader, nothing showed up. I couldn't import! Then we tried two other card readers laying around. Nothing. So I put the card back in my camera, and tried to view them there. I got the "Folder Contains No Images" message familiar to Nikon users. 

At this point, I downloaded a program called "Card Rescue" for Mac to see if the files had somehow been corrupted or damage. Trey had successfully used this program to recover some files before. After running a scan for nearly an hour, it said it couldn't find any files. Whenever I tried to import from the card, it referred to my CF card as "JO NAMA" ... Strange name, and I have no idea where it came from. 

So either someone out there has some good ideas for better card recovery software, or SanDisk is out there and they can help me, or there may be something to those ghost stories people tell about the Queen Mary. That was the last location of the evening... Me and Trey drove down to Long Beach to shoot some parts of the ship that are supposedly haunted. All in good fun you'd think, until the electromagnetic field generated by the ghosts wipe out your memory card... ! ;-) Or maybe it was the nuclear reactor on that Scorpion submarine we climbed onto? 

Here's a ghostly image I caught of myself a few months ago, before my camera fell into the Ocean, before I got arrested for taking photos (another story I haven't told), and before my memory card went dead! 

#LAPhotoWalk Unfortunately this means I have zero photos from the PhotoWalk, unless I can somehow get the photos back!﻿

Meer lezen (32 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-JZkt_8fJu08/T0uzQojnIaI/AAAAAAABU6U/j9J6Cr0XeKk/w426-h282/DSC_6869_70_71_tonemapped.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7070-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/compact%20flash%20memory%20card/photos/117584144972640014548/albums/5714098953999937361/5714098954547135138</link><title>The Peli 0945 Memory Card Case for compact flash cards is also coming to Europe in May :-) Niko﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7070_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-F5FLVbZKwMc/T0yOuX02gqI/AAAAAAAAAEE/QrjGEL_g9_0/w426-h360/0945.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>