<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:04:39" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/114586260715687570728/albums/6005543105839552593/6005543111671840402</link><title>200 girls are missing in Nigeria – so why doesn't anybody care? 

Where are they? 

Every morning for a week the news has been dominated by the South Korean ferry tragedy. The terrible grief of the parents, the shocking response of the crew to the unfolding disaster, and the inexorably rising body count. 

Two days before the South Korean students boarded their ferry for a study trip to the nearby island of Jeju, terrorists broke into a girls' school in Chibok, in the remote state of Borno, in north-eastern Nigeria. They shot guards and abducted about 200 students, who were loaded into trucks and, it seems, taken off into the forest. Two groups of the girls, perhaps 30 in all, managed to escape. The rest have simply disappeared. 

No one has admitted carrying out the mass kidnapping, although it is assumed to be the work of Boko Haram, the al-Qaida-linked jihadi group. Amnesty International says 1,500 people have been killed this year in the conflict between Boko Haram and Nigerian security forces, more than half of them civilians. The latest bombing by the group was in Abuja, on the same day the girls were abducted, in which at least 70 people died. Nigeria's president, Goodluck Jonathan, was soon on the scene. The first appearance of the Borno state governor in Chibok came yesterday, eight days after the attack. 

The fate of the Nigerian girls, who had been recalled to class in order to sit a physics exam, when all the other schools in the area were closed by security fears, has not been entirely ignored by the world's media. But it has been overwhelmed by the story of the sinking of the Sewol. 

Some of the reasons for that are obvious. The South Korean story has unfolded on camera, in a first-world country with every facility for news reporting. In contrast, the young Nigerians have vanished into the darkness of a dangerous world. 

Read More: 
http://www.whenthenewsstops.org/2014/04/200-girls-are-missing-in-nigeria-so-why.html﻿

Meer lezen (38 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZwrOfJlooQQ/U1f5pC5-fpI/AAAAAAAAE-o/7Oaqx9snbD0/w426-h256/Soldiers-stand-guard-in-f-009.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/102316005489588840863/albums/5846539277415876513/5846539284842772770?authkey=CKPBksPx-PK8tQE</link><title>[TRANS] The Japanese Media Reports, “TVXQ Have The Highest Worldwide Sales Amongst K-Pop Groups” 

The K-pop group with the highest worldwide sales is TVXQ. 

On the 10th of February, local Japanese press released an article with the title, ‘The rankings of K-pop artistes with the highest worldwide sales are revealed’. 

According to the article, a post about ‘Korean artistes’ sales rankings’ was posted on an online foreign community thread and is spreading rapidly. 

The group that came out on top of the rankings is TVXQ. TVXQ’s total sales count is more than twice the amount of Girls’ Generation, who came in at second place, and boasted the group’s superiority. Second place was taken by Korea’s most representative girl group Girls’ Generation, and they were followed by KARA in third place. Big Bang, Super Junior, SHINee, 2PM, CN BLUE, JYJ and B2st made up the rest of the top 10. 

The rankings include the official information from over 10 different websites of sales of albums, singles, DVDs, Blu-rays, photobooks, live concert albums, videos and CDs. The validity of the rankings can’t be ignored as the Korean sales counts are taken from the Gaon Charts and the Hanteo Charts, and the Japanese sales counts are taken from the Oricon charts. 

Japanese netizens who heard the news left a variety of comments such as, “As expected from TVXQ”, “I wonder who earned more money, Psy with Gangnam Style or TVXQ”, “TVXQ’s popularity is amazing,” and “I’m surprised by the surge in popularity for Girls’ Generation and KARA.” 

Meanwhile, TVXQ are currently juggling both individual and group activities. Jung Yunho is appearing in the SBS Monday-Tuesday drama ‘Queen of Ambition’ while Shim Changmin is showing off his humorous wit in KBS 2TV’s ‘Moonlight Prince’. Not only this, but they are also planning to release their new Japanese album ‘TIME’ on the 6th of March. 

Source: [newsen] 
Translated &amp; Shared by: dongbangdata.net﻿

Meer lezen (39 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-j-UTd6gw4kk/USMUgNZreSI/AAAAAAAAJdI/DSJpxVFNx_Q/w426-h296/560357_567729686580015_388324693_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/116890489070887664371/albums/5932741729853363697/5932741735515931266</link><title>Lotus F1 Team Previews the 2013 Japanese Grand Prix 
The #F1  party is just getting started at #Suzuka! Catch up with the full #LotusF1Team  cast as we count down to the weekend's action... 

Kimi #Raikkonen  Q&amp;A -&gt; http://bit.ly/19dUmz8 
Romain #Grosjean  Q&amp;A -&gt; http://bit.ly/1e7K5pi 
Eric #Boullier  Q&amp;A -&gt; http://bit.ly/16vhWXD 
Alan #Permane Q&amp;A -&gt; http://bit.ly/19gxYTO ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Zo5zeig72iw/UlVVLOmPwoI/AAAAAAAAL-E/4i6ijCLt0_s/w426-h284/13.10.10.Web.News.2.Logo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5959281953365638625/5959281957378595330</link><title>What Happens if Dennis Rodman and His NBA Team Beat The North Koreans?   http://b4in.org/ttY 

Dennis Rodman is set to travel to North Korea for the third time today. His visit is to help train a North Korean basketball team prior to a game in January when they will play against former NBA stars. 

Sponsored for the trip by PaddyPower, an Irish  bookmaker, Rodman is hoping to bring basketball diplomacy to the North Korean regime. 

This is the biggest load of crap I have ever heard. It’s about the money. PaddyPower will make millions from bets on the outcome of the game, altruism and world peace have nothing at all to do with it. 

Rodman and his new handlers may like to consider what will happen if North Korea loses. We are talking about a regime where the state is everything and individuals count for nothing. 

Rodman could be accused of deliberately not training the North Korean team well enough. 

Rodman could be detained as he has caused the North Koreans to lose face. 

The whole NBA team could be detained for causing the North Koreans to lose face 

The North Korean team could well face harsh punishment for losing and making North Korea lose face 

The North Korean team win and Rodman loses all credibility for throwing the match 

More  http://b4in.org/ttY﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-d0Ks-_cvaXI/UrOfXdnyGgI/AAAAAAAAB3A/pqjofWYrsqQ/w426-h240/rodman%2Bkim.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/102316005489588840863/albums/5740786200661985473/5740786205745182546</link><title>[Info for International-Fans] 
English Sites to Preorder Junsu’s Solo Album, To Count Towards Hanteo Chart 

Music shows and Golden Disk Award count album sales from the Hanteo Chart. To help Junsu’s album get on the Hanteo Chart, International Fans must purchase his album on sites that specify their purchase will count towards that chart. 
Some are listed below: 
1) DVDHeaven: http://dvdheaven.com 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet] Buy Here 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet + Poster] Buy Here 

2) Kpoptown: www.kpoptown.com 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet] + Folded/Unfolded Poster (optional) Buy Here 

3) GMarket Buy Here 

4) Kpopmart 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet] + Poster (optional) Buy Here 

=================== 
5) ***Yesasia (note: the english description is not clear whether or not the 40p Photo Booklet is included but it is listed under the product info in korean) 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet] + Poster (in tube) Buy Here 
Xia – Tarantallegra [+40p Photo Booklet] + Poster (folded) Buy Here 

***According to their Customer Support Page, sales on YesAsia count towards the Hanteo and Gaon music charts. 
Shared by: JYJ3﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-pFeRZjzXdk8/T6teo1znd1I/AAAAAAAAFHQ/kMUnW8qH0d4/w426-h308/16173988.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/113387364733697674508/albums/5791674573570697521/5791674576164996642</link><title>Samsung Galaxy S III Available in Korea in Pink This Week!!! 

Samsung’s back in shape with another color palette for its flagship quad-core smartphone device, bringing the total count to seven. The Galaxy S III has been unveiled donning a pink shade and will be hitting Korean markets this week. 

Unfortunately, it’s unclear where or when this colour will be available in Singapore although Samsung made mention that the shades’ availability will depends on different regions and carriers. The current shades available in or will be coming to Singapore include Marble White, Pebble Blue, Amber Brown, Garnet Red andTitanium Grey (LTE model for now only). 

Source:gsmarena﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Gg_vSOaQt7Q/UGApV2b5xiI/AAAAAAAAABM/fdFk4A3YenA/w426-h519/pinks3.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/101635970862489953037/albums/5945590965446089249/5945590962000485154</link><title>NaNoWriMo and Writing Bilingual Characters 

November is shaping up to be a very busy month in my household. My husband is participating in the Movember movement, a call to men not to shave their mustaches for the entirety of the month in the name of cancer awareness My daughter is exploring the exciting world of pillow forts because November is when winter’s chill starts to make itself known in my neck of the woods, and her outside time is becoming limited by weather conditions and the length of the day. I, on the other hand, am firmly entrenched in National Novel Writing Month (NaNoWriMo). 

As of this moment I am ahead of my projected word count for the week. You can’t see, what with the whole internet between us, but I’m doing a little happy dance. I didn’t think there was enough coffee in the world to get me as productive as I have been, but apparently there is. 

My favorite NaNoWri-moment so far: when I finally typed out my first line. I am the kind of person who agonizes over such things, but I put myself in the place of my protagonist (a woman having a bad day that gets worse when she is taken hostage during a bank robbery. It’s a comedy) and the stream of consciousness just manifested itself. 

“Nice shoelaces. I know that’s a strange thing to think about someone who just threatened to blow off the bank’s collective head, but there it is, face-down and about 15 seconds from peeing myself and that’s my first thought—nice shoelaces. Maybe I’m in shock. Oh no, they’re pointed this way…” 

Other than my daughter finding my laptop and popping off half the keys, I haven’t had too many setbacks yet. My natural inclination towards run-on sentences has proven itself advantageous, as has my knowledge of other languages, in my attempts to reach word count goals. 

Putting myself in the position of someone in a high stress situation, I can say with some level of certainty that I (and most, if not all, members of my family) would probably shift into Spanish speaking mode. Anyone with bilingual parents knows that when any strong emotion presents itself—especially anger—their language usually reverts to its default setting. At least it does with most people I know. This realization really helped me add a bit of authenticity to my novel in the making. No matter where you go in an English speaking country there will always be a few people who don’t speak English natively, and this is a situation where those people might make themselves known. 

One of my hostages speaks Spanish as their first language and another speaks Korean. Writing a character who speaks Spanish was fairly easy for me, but the mechanics of writing the Korean was a bit of a mental work out. Thankfully once I realized that my main character spoke neither language, it opened up the option of having the Spanish speakers speak Spanglish (so that some of it would be understood by people who speak no Spanish), and the Korean speaker only gets a few syllables across that the main character can make out. 

Would I recommend someone learn a new language solely for the purpose of creating a character that appears in only a few pages of prose? No, not unless the writer has other reasons for wanting to learn the language. But I can say, without a doubt, that whether or not my November novel ends up being destined for the rubbish bin, it’s much better for having an authentic representation of the community I live in. 

What novels have you read with bilingual characters? Do you think they make the story more believable, or confusing? 

http://www.languagetrainers.co.uk/blog/2013/11/07/nanowrimo-writing-bilingual-characters/﻿

Meer lezen (68 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-F3GE8K4XXlU/UoL7epXP2yI/AAAAAAAAAHU/t9nZwF_FY60/w426-h240/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/110456355529414581848/albums/5989941398956463889/5989941398203236898</link><title>Down for the count 
Remind me to not eat Korean BBQ again. Ever again. 

I think I have food poisoning. I've been barely functional since Sunday. Things were improving and now I'm worse today! I am writing this laying down. I've realized there aren't many things one can do well while lying in bed. 

I've become very fond of Pepto-Bismol this week. Oh, and have you met my friend Gravol? 

I hope you are having a more upright and productive week than I am. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-FPIESnPlONo/UyCL9zFPgiI/AAAAAAAACzU/jOK-r7chIoE/w426-h281/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/116134589015846644252/albums/5857197769786209057/5857197768601560626?sqi=111184421292514092257&amp;sqsi=d817accd-e576-474e-bbd6-c00ef6208302</link><title>Bibimbap is a signature Korean dish. The word literally means "mixed rice" Great #vegan meal! Thanks to my wonderful wife +Jennifer McNally! I'm losing count on which day it is of my vegan adventure. Heck, it doesn't matter. I'm a vegan! ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-6N_kdp1UHl8/UUjyVni05jI/AAAAAAAALUw/5vDWSAqrKQE/s426/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7078-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/count%20in%20korean/photos/105843915768153948564/albums/5999726835002192433/5999726831978539554</link><title>Count this as a kind of  #PDA ? &lt;3 &lt;3 

ABOKI #Raglan-Sleeve #Sweatshirt 
http://www.yesstyle.com/en/aboki-raglan-sleeve-sweatshirt-gray-navy-blue-s/info.html/pid.1035400410 

Up to 60% off Menswear at  #YesStyle ! 
Mens #KoreanFashion : http://www.yesstyle.com/en/korean-fashion-men ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7078_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-sUmvR_7Lyco/U0NPxAl16iI/AAAAAAAAIqI/45XqLCr3F8I/w426-h349/ABOKI%2BRaglan-Sleeve%2BSweatshirt.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>