<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:12:22" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/109355856112312423489/albums/5901971822128634833/5901971827492223442?authkey=CMC0oMuUqsa-eg&amp;sqi=111509531389964764379&amp;sqsi=60486843-7d2b-4a07-a3cc-08cc52f994ca</link><title>Cubicle 7 and Sophisticated Games announce Hobbit Tales - A One Ring Card Game 

‘Queer things you do hear these days, to be sure,’ said Sam. ‘Ah,’ said Ted, ‘you do, if you listen. But I can hear fireside-tales and children’s stories at home, if I want to.’ ‘No doubt you can,’ retorted Sam, ‘and I daresay there’s more truth in some of them than you reckon. Who invented the stories anyway?’ --The Lord of the Rings, J.R.R. Tolkien 

Players are Hobbits telling tales in front of a mug of beer at their favourite inn in the Shire. Silent woods and remote mountains, Elves, Goblins and Giants populate their stories... 

During the game, players take turns as the Narrator and improvise a story using a hand of illustrated cards. The other players try to twist the tale, playing hazards and fearsome monsters. Drinks are served, smoke-rings are blown, and the best narrator is cheered by everyone present. 

Hobbit Tales is a game for 2 to 5 Hobbits, authored by the award-winning designers Marco Maggi and Francesco Nepitello, creators of the Tolkien-themed War of the Ring strategy game and The One Ring role-playing game. 

This game contains a set of rules, 1 board, 75 Adventure cards, 40 Hazard cards, 5 coasters, a set of cardboard tokens and a twelve-sided The One Ring Feat die. 

Includes rules to use Hobbit Tales in conjunction with the The One Ring, Cubicle 7’s role-playing game set in Tolkien’s Middle-earth. 

Retail release November 2013 

The One Ring, Middle-earth, The Hobbit, The Lord of the Rings, and the characters, items, events and places therein are trademarks or registered trademarks of the Saul Zaentz Company d/b/a Middle-earth Enterprises and are used under license by Sophisticated Games Ltd and their licensees.﻿

Meer lezen (34 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-pKOwlDMj6dI/UegEG2wJedI/AAAAAAAAAN0/eHQkE6yQxVM/w426-h612/HobbitTalesCoverforSolicitation_lowres.tif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/109201681846030076792/albums/5823384714139080993/5823384718699425682?authkey=CL6xv8GcyZ-mHQ</link><title>Hobbit Bar in New Zealand ... Amusing Planet \- "If you are a Lord of the Rings fan, here is another reason to visit New Zealand. A Hobbit-style bar called the Green Dragon Pub has opened at Hobbiton near Matamata - the same location where the movies were filmed. Art director and project manager Brian Massey led the construction of the Green Dragon Pub, and a team of 80 labourers assisted in adding the themed attraction to the beautiful stretch of land. The bar was reportedly opened by none other than New Zealand’s prime minister John Key himself. ..." http://www.amusingplanet.com/2012/12/hobbit-bar-in-new-zealand.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-R1ny_uXS_wI/UNDRjEyEb5I/AAAAAAABeRU/XAduRwESRnc/w426-h285/hobbit-bar-1%252525255B7%252525255D%255B1%255D.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/109201681846030076792/albums/5926079711637267265/5926079717625471922?authkey=CMuYppimhbu7nAE</link><title>Sept. 21, 1937 – J. R. R. Tolkien's The Hobbit is published ... Wikipedia \- "The Hobbit, or There and Back Again, better known by its abbreviated title The Hobbit, is a fantasy novel and children's book by English author J. R. R. Tolkien. It was published on 21 September 1937 to wide critical acclaim, being nominated for the Carnegie Medal and awarded a prize from the New York Herald Tribune for best juvenile fiction. The book remains popular and is recognized as a classic in children's literature. 

Set in a time "Between the Dawn of Færie and the Dominion of Men", The Hobbit follows the quest of home-loving hobbit Bilbo Baggins to win a share of the treasure guarded by the dragon, Smaug. Bilbo's journey takes him from light-hearted, rural surroundings into more sinister territory. The story is told in the form of an episodic quest, and most chapters introduce a specific creature, or type of creature, of Tolkien's Wilderland. By accepting the disreputable, romantic, fey and adventurous side of his nature and applying his wits and common sense, Bilbo gains a new level of maturity, competence and wisdom. The story reaches its climax in the Battle of Five Armies, where many of the characters and creatures from earlier chapters re-emerge to engage in conflict. 

Personal growth and forms of heroism are central themes of the story. Along with motifs of warfare, these themes have led critics to view Tolkien's own experiences during World War I as instrumental in shaping the story. The author's scholarly knowledge of Germanic philology and interest in fairy tales are often noted as influences. 

Encouraged by the book's critical and financial success, the publisher requested a sequel. As Tolkien's work on the successor The Lord of the Rings progressed, he made retrospective accommodations for it in The Hobbit. These few but significant changes were integrated into the second edition. Further editions followed with minor emendations, including those reflecting Tolkien's changing concept of the world into which Bilbo stumbled. The work has never been out of print. Its ongoing legacy encompasses many adaptations for stage, screen, radio, board games and video games. Several of these adaptations have received critical recognition on their own merits. ..."﻿

Meer lezen (34 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-O26y4FAatCY/Uj2qGv-2o7I/AAAAAAACSMM/Y_1VosXIaaQ/w426-h533/TheHobbit_FirstEdition%5B1%5D.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/113244533795832439660/albums/5821067805292145345/5821067802262007634?authkey=CJGZg7bwzbDxBQ</link><title>Watched the Hobbit last night at the advance screening! Really really liked it, it has the same spirit of the Lord of the Rings movies, but with a larger sense of wonder. After all,  differently from Frodo, Bilbo does not carry such a heavy burden or a doomed mission - he is out for an adventure! 

The movie is lighter and episodic in nature (it was originally a bedtime story) and has tons of small changes from the book and additions. Even as a Tolkien aficionado, I was pretty satisfied with the changes (except one for comedic purposes, but I'll refrain from mentioning it here). One of my favorite things was music (wondrous!), specially the Dwarves theme. Looking forward to the special editions if they have more songs... 

Thanks for my good friend +Rodrigo Paoletti who scored the tickets and invited me! Woohoo! ﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-jwniKlcvsh8/UMiWUydKb1I/AAAAAAAAQks/Frg2hcnlknw/w426-h320/IMG_20121211_202451.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/112815794394767726853/albums/5717227570593846513/5717227574699281954</link><title>Eye of Sauron 
is the image most often associated with Sauron. Sauron's Orcs bore the symbol of the Eye on their helmets and shields, and referred to him as the "Eye" because he did not allow his name to be written or spoken, according to Aragorn (a notable exception to this rule was his emissary, the Mouth of Sauron). Also, the Lord of the Nazgûl threatened Éowyn with torture before the "Lidless Eye" at the Battle of the Pelennor Fields. 

In the Mirror of Galadriel, Frodo had an actual vision of this Eye: 

The Eye was rimmed with fire, but was itself glazed, yellow as a cat's, watchful and intent, and the black slit of its pupil opened on a pit, a window into nothing. 

Later, Tolkien writes as if Frodo and Sam really glimpse the Eye directly, not in any kind of vision. The mists surrounding Barad-dûr are briefly withdrawn, and: 

one moment only it stared out...as from some great window immeasurably high there stabbed northward a flame of red, the flicker of a piercing Eye... The Eye was not turned on them, it was gazing north...but Frodo at that dreadful glimpse fell as one stricken mortally. 

Gollum (who was tortured by Sauron in person) tells Frodo that Sauron has, at least, a "Black Hand" with four fingers. The missing finger was cut off when Isildur took the Ring, and the finger was still missing when Sauron reappeared centuries later. (Similarly, the injury to Sauron's throat in the much earlier battle with Lúthien and Huan is maintained even after his transformation. 

In the third volume, The Return of the King, the heralds of the Army of the West call Sauron out before the Battle of the Morannon, telling him to "come forth", which would seem pointless if he did not have a body. 

In one of his letters Tolkien does state that Sauron had a physical form in the Third Age: 

...in a tale which allows the incarnation of great spirits in a physical and destructible form their power must be far greater when actually physically present. ... Sauron should be thought of as very terrible. The form that he took was that of a man of more than human stature, but not gigantic. 

Tolkien writes in The Silmarillion that "the Eye of Sauron the Terrible few could endure" even before his body was lost in the War of the Last Alliance. 

J. R. R. Tolkien: Artist and Illustrator includes Tolkien's own drawing of Sauron, showing him as a humanoid with literally black skin. 

In the draft text of the climactic moments of The Lord of the Rings, "the Eye" stands for Sauron's very person, with emotions and thoughts: 

The Dark Lord was suddenly aware of him [Frodo], the Eye piercing all shadows... Its wrath blazed like a sudden flame and its fear was like a great black smoke, for it knew its deadly peril, the thread upon which hung its doom... its thought was now bent with all its overwhelming force upon the Mountain..." 

Christopher Tolkien comments: "The passage is notable in showing the degree to which my father had come to identify the Eye of Barad-dûr with the mind and will of Sauron, so that he could speak of 'its wrath, its fear, its thought'. In the second text...he shifted from 'its' to 'his' as he wrote out the passage anew." 

Most adaptations of the story to visual media depict the Eye as visibly present; for obviously the Eye of Fire is visually effective, whereas references to Sauron's never-seen body are so few that even readers of the novel often overlook them. 

In the same work, he is revealed to be the same character as The Necromancer from Tolkien's earlier novel The Hobbit. In Tolkien's The Silmarillion (published posthumously by Tolkien's son Christopher Tolkien),[2] he is also revealed to have been the chief lieutenant of the first Dark Lord, Morgoth. Tolkien noted that the "angelic" powers of his constructed myth "were capable of many degrees of error and failing", but by far the worst was "the absolute Satanic rebellion and evil of Morgoth and his satellite Sauron." 
Before creation of the world 
The cosmological myth prefixed to The Silmarillion explains how the supreme being Eru initiated his creation by bringing into being innumerable spirits, "the offspring of his thought", who were with him before anything else had been made. The being later known as Sauron thus originated as an "immortal (angelic) spirit."[4] In his origin, Sauron therefore perceived the Creator directly. As Tolkien noted: "Sauron could not, of course, be a 'sincere' atheist. Though one of the minor spirits created before the world, he knew Eru, according to his measure." 

In the terminology of Tolkien's invented language of Quenya, these angelic spirits were called Ainur. Those who entered the physical world were called Valar, especially the most powerful ones. The lesser beings of the same race, of whom Sauron was one, were called Maiar. In Tolkien's letters, the author noted that Sauron "was of course a 'divine' person (in the terms of this mythology; a lesser member of the race of Valar)".[6] Though less mighty than the chief Valar, he was more powerful than many of his fellow Maiar; Tolkien noted that he was of a "far higher order" than the Maiar who later came to Middle-earth as the Wizards Gandalf and Saruman.[7] As created by Eru, the Ainur were all good and uncorrupt, as Elrond stated in The Lord of the Rings: "Nothing is evil in the beginning. Even Sauron was not so." 

Rebellion originated with the Vala Melkor (Morgoth). According to a story meant as a parable of events beyond Elvish comprehension,[9] Eru let his spirit-children perform a great Music, the Music of the Ainur (Ainulindalë), developing a theme revealed by Eru himself. For a while the cosmic choir made wondrous music, but then Melkor tried to increase his own glory by weaving into his song thoughts and ideas that were not in accordance with the original theme. "Straightway discord arose around him, and many that sang nigh him grew despondent ... but some began to attune their music to his rather than to the thought which they had at first." 

The discord Melkor created would have dire consequences, as this singing was a kind of template for the world: "The evils of the world were not at first in the great Theme, but entered with the discords of Melkor." However, "Sauron was not a beginner of discord; and he probably knew more of the Music than did Melkor, whose mind had always been filled with his own plans and devices."Apparently Sauron was not even one of the spirits that immediately began to attune their music to that of Melkor, since it is elsewhere noted that his fall occurred later (see below). 

The cosmic Music now represented the conflict between good and evil. Finally, Eru abruptly brought the Song of Creation to an end. To show the spirits, faithful or otherwise, what they had done, Eru gave independent being to the now-marred Music. This resulted in the manifestation of the material World, Eä, where the drama of good and evil would play out and be resolved. Eru allowed the spirits who so wished to enter into the new world of Eä and follow its history from inside. Many did so, Sauron among them. By granting free will to enter into Eä, Eru allowed great evil, as well as great good. 

[edit]First Age 
Entering Eä at the beginning of time, the Valar and Maiar tried to build and organise the world according to the will of Eru. Each of the Maia spirits was associated with one of the powerful Valar whom they served; for example, Ossë and Uinen, who were spirits of the sea, served Ulmo, the lord of the oceans. Sauron was prominent among the Maiar who served Aulë the Smith, the great craftsman of the Valar. As a result, Sauron came to possess great knowledge of the physical substances of the world, forging, and all manner of craftsmanship — emerging as "a great craftsman of the household of Aulë".Sauron would always retain the "scientific" knowledge he derived from the great Vala of Craft: "In his beginning he was of the Maiar of Aulë, and he remained mighty in the lore of that people."[14] Sauron's original name was Mairon (the Admirable), but this name was changed to Sauron after he joined Melkor. However, during the First Age Sauron continued to call himself Mairon. 

[edit]Sauron's fall 
Melkor opposed the other Valar, who remained faithful to Eru and tried to carry out the Creator's designs. Around this time, Sauron fell victim to Melkor's corrupting influence: "In the beginning of Arda Melkor seduced him to his allegiance. 

As for Sauron's motives, Tolkien noted that "it had been his virtue (and therefore also the cause of his fall ...) that he loved order and coordination, and disliked all confusion and wasteful friction." Thus "it was the apparent will and power of Melkor to effect his designs quickly and masterfully that had first attracted Sauron to him. This shows one of the great paradoxes of Sauron: he wanted order and industry, but followed Melkor's destructive and chaotic path to obtain it. 

For a while, Sauron apparently kept up the pretence that he was a faithful servant of the Valar, all the while feeding Melkor information about their doings. Thus, when the Valar made Almaren as their first physical abode in the world, "Melkor knew of all that was done; for even then he had secret friends and spies among the Maiar whom he had converted to his cause, and of these the chief, as after became known, was Sauron. 
Melkor soon destroyed Almaren, and the Valar established a new abode in the Uttermost West: the Blessed Realm of Valinor. They still did not perceive Sauron's treachery, for he too became "a being of Valinor 

At some point, Sauron left the Blessed Realm and went to Middle-earth. In one text, Tolkien wrote of Sauron that "in Valinor he had dwelt among the people of the gods, but there Morgoth had drawn him to evil and to his service".[19] Sauron deserted his service to the Valar and openly joined their great enemy: "Because of his admiration of Strength he had become a follower of Morgoth and fell with him down into the depths of evil." 

[edit]The Lieutenant of Melkor 
After joining his new master in Middle-earth, Sauron proved to be a devoted and capable servant: "While Morgoth still stood, Sauron did not seek his own supremacy, but worked and schemed for another, desiring the triumph of Melkor, whom in the beginning he had adored. He thus was often able to achieve things, first conceived by Melkor, which his master did not or could not complete in the furious haste of his malice."[20] "In all the deeds of Melkor the Morgoth upon Arda, in his vast works and in the deceits of his cunning, Sauron had a part. 

In chapter 3 of The Silmarillion, Tolkien writes that by the time the Elves awoke in the world, Sauron had become Melkor's lieutenant and was given command over the newly-built stronghold of Angband. To protect the Elves, the Valar made war on Melkor and captured him, but could not find Sauron. 

Thus, "when Melkor was made captive, Sauron escaped and lay hid in Middle-earth; and it can in this way be understood how the breeding of the Orcs (no doubt already begun) went on with increasing speed." In the Blessed Realm, Melkor feigned reform, but eventually escaped back to Middle-earth, holding the Silmarils of Fëanor. By then, Sauron had "secretly repaired Angband for the help of his Master when he returned; and there the dark places underground were already manned with hosts of the Orcs before Melkor came back at last, as Morgoth the Black Enemy."[22] 

Shortly after the return of Morgoth, the Noldorin Elves also left the Blessed Realm of Valinor in the Uttermost West, against the counsel of the Valar, to wage war on Morgoth, who had stolen the Silmarils. In that war, Sauron served as Morgoth's chief lieutenant, surpassing all others in rank, such as Gothmog, the Lord of Balrogs. Known as Gorthaur the Cruel, Sauron was at that time a master of illusions and shapeshifting; werewolves and vampires were his servants, chief among them Draugluin, Father of Werewolves, and his vampire herald Thuringwethil. 

When Morgoth left Angband to corrupt the newly-created Men, Sauron directed the war against the Elves. He conquered the Elvish island of Tol Sirion and its watchtower Minas Tirith, so that it became known as Tol-in-Gaurhoth, the Isle of Werewolves. 

Ten years later, Finrod Felagund, the king of Nargothrond and former lord of Tol Sirion, came there with Beren. He battled Sauron using sorcery but was defeated (in part because of the curse of Fëanor). Later, he died fighting a wolf in Sauron's dungeons to save Beren. 

Soon afterwards Lúthien and Huan the Wolfhound arrived, hoping to rescue Beren. Aware of a prophecy to the effect that Huan would be killed by the greatest wolf ever, Sauron himself assumed a monstrous wolf-like form and attacked him. But the prophecy actually applied to the still-unborn Carcharoth, and Sauron could not prevail against Huan. 

Eventually, Huan had Sauron by the throat. Lúthien gave Sauron two choices: either surrender to her the magical control he had established over Tol-in-Gaurhoth, or have his body destroyed so that his naked ghost would have to endure the scorn of Morgoth. Sauron yielded, and Huan let him go. Lúthien destroyed the tower and rescued Beren from the dungeons. 

Sauron fled in the form of a huge vampiric bat, and spent some time as a vampire in the woods of Taur-nu-Fuin. Nothing is told of his subsequent activities in the First Age until the end. 

Following the voyage of Eärendil to the Blessed Realm, the Valar finally moved against Morgoth. In the resulting War of Wrath, the Dark Lord was defeated and cast into the Outer Void beyond the world. But "Sauron fled from the Great Battle and escaped." 

Chastened, Sauron assumed his most beautiful form and approached Eönwë, emissary of the Valar, who nevertheless could not pardon a Maia like himself. Through Eönwë, Manwë as Lord of the Valar "commanded Sauron to come before him for judgement, but [he] had left room for repentance and ultimate rehabilitation." Unwilling to bow before the Valar, Sauron escaped and hid in Middle-earth. 

[edit]Second Age 
About 500 years into the Second Age, Sauron reappeared. "Bereft of his lord...[he] fell into the folly of imitating him. "Very slowly, beginning with fair motives: the reorganizing and rehabilitation of Middle-earth, 'neglected by the gods,' he becomes a reincarnation of Evil, and a thing lusting for Complete Power," eventually rising to become "master and god of Men." 

As for Sauron's "fair motives", Tolkien emphasized that at this time he "was not indeed wholly evil, not unless all 'reformers' who want to hurry up with 'reconstruction' and 'reorganization' are wholly evil, even before pride and the lust to exert their will eat them up". 

"[T]hough the only real good in, or rational motive for, all this ordering and planning and organization was the good of all inhabitants of Arda (even admitting Sauron's right to be their supreme lord), his 'plans', the idea coming from his own isolated mind, became the sole object of his will, and an end, the End, in itself. ... [H]is capability of corrupting other minds, and even engaging their service, was a residue from the fact that his original desire for 'order' had really envisaged the good estate (especially physical well-being) of his 'subjects'." 

[edit]The Rings of Power 
As part of a plan to seduce the Elves into his service, Sauron assumed a beautiful appearance as Annatar, "Lord of Gifts,"befriended the Elven-smiths of Eregion, led by Celebrimbor, and counselled them in arts and magic. Sauron hinted that he was an emissary of the Valar, specifically of Aulë, whom the Noldor in Exile held in high regard. Some of the Elves distrusted him, especially the Lady Galadriel and Gil-galad, the High King of the Noldor. The Elves in Eregion, however, did not heed their warnings. 

With Sauron's assistance, the Elven-smiths forged the Rings of Power, which conferred great power upon their bearers. He then secretly forged the One Ring in the volcanic Mount Doom in Mordor. This "One Ring to rule them all" had the power to dominate the other Rings and enslave their wearers to Sauron's will. The Rings of Power were extremely potent, however; to create an instrument that could dominate even them, Sauron was forced to transfer a great part of his native power into it. Yet "while he wore it, his power on earth was actually enhanced". 

Sauron's plan would have succeeded had the Elves not detected his influence when he put on the One Ring. It was then the Elves saw him for who he really was, removed their Rings, and did not use them for as long as Sauron retained the One Ring. Enraged, Sauron initiated a great war and conquered much of the land west of Anduin. The Three Rings, however, had been forged by Celebrimbor himself without Sauron's help. These rings were saved and remained in the hands of the Elves, specifically Gil-galad, Círdan, and Galadriel. 

This began the Dark Years. He overran Eregion, killed Celebrimbor, leader of the Elven-smiths, and seized the Seven and the Nine Rings of Power that had been previously forged with his assistance. Sauron besieged Imladris, battled Moria and Lothlórien, and pushed further into Gil-galad's realm. The Elves fought back, however, and with the aid of a powerful army from Númenor, they destroyed Sauron's army and drove the remnant back to Mordor. The Númenóreans were descended from the Three Houses of the Edain who helped the Elves in their war against Morgoth. They lived on the island of Númenor in the seas between Middle-earth and Valinor, a reward for their service from the Valar, and theirs was the most powerful kingdom of Men at this time. 

In Unfinished Tales, "The History of Galadriel and Celeborn" states that Sauron and his bodyguard were all that was left of his original army. Gil-galad's power after the War was such that Sauron was unable to move out of Mordor for some time. 

[edit]Resurgence from Mordor 
From this time on, Sauron became known as the Dark Lord of Mordor. Sauron fortified Mordor and completed the Dark Tower of Barad-dûr, already centuries in the building, and distributed the remaining rings of the Seven and the Nine to lords of Dwarves and Men. Dwarves proved too resilient to bend to his will, but the Men were enslaved by Sauron as the Nazgûl, his most feared servants. Well aware of the strength of the Númenóreans after his earlier defeat, Sauron withdrew from the costs and for a long time avoided directly challenging them, although he managed to use some of the Nine rings to snare three of their great lords. 

Sauron regained control over most of the creatures that had served Morgoth in the First Age (such as Orcs and Trolls). Sauron also gained power over most of the Men in the East and the South, becoming their god-king. 

According to Tolkein's letters, the second Dark Lord was now at the height of his power, having become "almost supreme in Middle-earth. … He rules a growing empire from the great dark tower of Barad-dûr in Mordor, near to the Mountain of fire, wielding the One Ring."[30] However this is contradicted by the Appendices in "The Return of the King" which states that Sauron never fully recovered his former strength when he returned from Númenor and attacked the Númenórean exiles. 

Toward the end of the Second Age, as the Númenóreans withdrew from the coasts after their people were divided by strife over the fear of death, Sauron began assailing their Middle Earth strongholds and assumed the titles of Lord of the Earth and King of Men. 

Destruction of Númenor 
Toward the end of the Second Age, Ar-Pharazôn, who would turn out to be the last and most powerful of the Númenórean kings, had just ascended to the throne when he was angered by reports of Sauron's increasing power. In a show of force, Ar-Pharazôn led a massive army to Middle-earth to reassert Númenórean dominance. Sauron, realizing he could not defeat the Númenóreans with military strength, surrendered. Clad in a beautiful incarnation, he came to Ar-Pharazôn's camp to swear allegiance to the king, and allowed himself to be taken as a prisoner to Númenor. 

This was part of his plan to corrupt Númenórean civilization from inside. "Sauron's personal 'surrender' was voluntary and cunning: he got free transport to Númenor."[31] When Ar-Pharazôn in his arrogance took Sauron hostage, he failed to realise with whom he was dealing: Sauron "was of course a 'divine' person ... and thus far too powerful to be controlled in this way. He steadily got Arpharazôn's [sic] mind under his own control, and in the event corrupted many of the Númenóreans." 

The Akallabêth, the account of the history of Númenor, does not specifically mention the One Ring much, and it has been suggested that Sauron left it at Barad-dûr before he became a hostage of Ar-Pharazôn. In his letters, however, Tolkien noted that Sauron "naturally had the One Ring, and so very soon dominated the minds and wills of most of the Númenóreans."[31] Through the power of the Ring, Sauron soon became an advisor of the king, and he used his influence to undermine the religion of Númenor. He represented Eru as an invention of the Valar that they used to justify their decrees, and substituted the worship of Melkor, with himself as high priest, for that of Eru.[6] The worship of Melkor, with human sacrifice, became mandatory in Númenor. Sauron also helped the people to design greater engines and amass more wealth, and soon the Númenoreans returned to Middle-Earth where they cruelly hunted and enslaved the Men there for eventual sacrifice. While Sauron ruled behind the scenes, Ar-Pharazôn became the mightiest tyrant in the world since Morgoth. 

But there was seen the effect of Melkor upon Sauron: he spoke of Melkor in Melkor's own terms, as a god, or even as God. This may have been the residue of a state which was in a sense a shadow of good: the ability once in Sauron at least to admire or admit the superiority of a being other than himself. ... But it may be doubted whether even such a shadow of good was still sincerely operative in Sauron by that time. His cunning motive is probably best expressed thus. To wean one of the God-fearing from their allegiance it is best to propound another unseen object of allegiance and another hope of benefits; propound to him a Lord who will sanction what he desires and not forbid it. Sauron, apparently a defeated rival for world-power, now a mere hostage, can hardly propound himself; but as the former servant and disciple of Melkor, the worship of Melkor will raise him from hostage to high priest.[32] 

Ar-Pharazôn, despite his power, eventual became fearful of his approaching death. Sauron convinced the king that he now had the status to take what was rightfully his, and suggested that the Númenoreans send a great armada upon Aman in order to seize immortality by force from the Valar.[6] Sauron expected the Valar to respond by destroying Ar-Pharazôn and his naval might, thus removing Sauron's greatest obstacle to domination of Middle-earth. But the Valar had no direct dominion over the Children of Eru, so in the face of this challenge they laid down their guardianship of the world and appealed to Eru for a solution.[33] 

Eru's divine intervention did indeed bury the king's armies and drown the armada; but Númenor itself was swallowed by the sea, and the Blessed Realm was removed from the physical world. Sauron had not foreseen this, and his body was destroyed in the destruction. Having expended much effort in the corruption of Númenor, he was diminished [34], particularly as he forever loss the ability to take a fair form. Yet his spirit rose out of the abyss, and he was able to carry with him the one thing that mattered most. Wrote Tolkien, "I do not think one need boggle at this spirit carrying off the One Ring, upon which his power of dominating minds now largely depended."[34] 

In the chapters "Akallabêth" and "Of the Rings of Power and the Third Age", Tolkien wrote that Sauron "took up" the Ring after his spirit returned to Middle-earth. Sauron also found that Gil-galad's power had grown great during his absence and now spread across the Misty Mountains and Greenwood the Great, drawing nigh to places that Sauron initially thought secure before leaving for Númenór. 

War against the Last Alliance 
The few faithful Númenóreans were saved from the Downfall. With Elendil as their leader, they escaped the cataclysm and founded the kingdoms of Gondor and Arnor among the Númenórean colonists and the natives of north-western Middle-earth. At first they believed that Sauron had perished in the Downfall, but it soon became evident that the Dark Lord had returned to Mordor. The Appendices in "The Return of the King" writes that while Sauron's power had not yet been rebuilt, he had decided to attack the Númenóreans before they could become too strong in their new realms. 

Sauron struck first, capturing Minas Ithil and destroying the White Tree, although Isildur managed to escape down the Anduin and seek Elendil, while Anárion defended Osgiliath and for a time drove Sauron's forces back to the mountains. In "Of the Rings of Power and the Third Age" and the The Fellowship of the Ring, Tolkien wrote that Elendil and his sons forged the Last Alliance of Elves and Men with Gil-galad, as they realized that unless they united, Sauron would destroy them each individually. 

The Alliance won a great victory on the plain of Dagorlad and invaded Mordor, laying siege to Barad-dûr for seven years. Finally, Sauron was forced to emerge from his tower and fight against the Last Alliance himself. During the final challenge on the slopes of Mount Doom, Sauron slew both Gil-galad and Elendil. When Elendil fell, his sword, Narsil, broke beneath him. Taking up the hilt-shard of Narsil, Elendil's surviving son, Isildur, cut the One Ring from Sauron's hand. "Then Sauron was for that time vanquished, and he forsook his body, and his spirit fled far away and hid in waste places." 

Elrond and Círdan, Gil-galad's lieutenants, urged Isildur to destroy the Ring by casting it into Mount Doom, but he refused and kept it for his own: "This I will have as weregild for my father's death, and my brother's. Was it not I that dealt the Enemy his death-blow?" 

Third Age 
The traumatic loss of the Ring greatly weakened Sauron; he spent the first thousand years of the Third Age as a shapeless, dormant evil. Nonetheless, his servants were involved in several events that gradually weakened the Númenórean exile kingdoms, although it is unclear if Sauron was actively involved in directing them. 

A few years after the War of the Last Alliance, Isildur's army, marching to Rivendell, was ambushed and overwhelmed by a band of Orcs in what became known as the Disaster of the Gladden Fields. Isildur put on the Ring and attempted to escape by swimming across Anduin, but the Ring — which had a will of its own and a desire to return to Sauron — slipped from his finger. He was spotted and killed by Orc archers. The Ring would remain lost beneath the water for thousands of years, with many believing there was no way Sauron could return or so long as the Ring was lost Middle Earth was safe. 

The Lord of the Nazgûl oversaw the destruction of Arnor (Arthedain, Rhudaur, and Cardolan), followed afterward by the capture of Minas Ithil from Gondor; also ending the line of kings in each realm. 

Between the fall of Arnor and Minas Ithil, the long-dormant Balrog in Moria slew King Durin VI and drove the dwarves away (as Balrogs were Maia of the same degree as Sauron, it is not known if Sauron influenced it or not). Dragons also began attacking the other dwarf kingdoms (again it is unknown if they were under Sauron). Meanwhile, the surviving Noldorian Elves in Middle-Earth generally lost interest in their lands and departed for Valinor. 

[edit]The Necromancer of Dol Guldur 
Around the year 1050,[38] a shadow of fear fell on the forest later called Mirkwood. As would later become known, this was the first intimation of Sauron manifesting himself yet again, but the Elves did not recognise him at first. As mentioned in The Hobbit, he was known as the Necromancer. He established a stronghold called Dol Guldur, "Hill of Sorcery", in the southern part of the forest. 

The Valar would not act to defeat Sauron in a massive intervention comparable to the War of Wrath that overthrew Morgoth, as they feared it could end in widespread destruction; rather, they sent five Maiar in the form of Wizards, the most prominent being Gandalf and Saruman. 

Around the year 1100, "the Wise" (the Wizards and the chief Elves) became aware that an evil power had made a stronghold at Dol Guldur. Initially it was assumed that this was one of the Nazgûl rather than Sauron himself. About the year 1300, the Nazgûl did indeed reappear, and their influence would have serious consequences for the nations established by the Númenórean exiles. 

Over the ensuing centuries, the Witch-king of Angmar (the chief Nazgûl, acting on Sauron's behalf) repeatedly attacked the northern realm of Arnor, first in 1409 and finally overrunning the realm in 1974. Six years later, the Witch-king entered Mordor and gathered the Nazgûl there. In 2000, the Nazgûl issued from Mordor and took the city of Minas Ithil (later known as Minas Morgul) in one of the mountain-passes. Thereby they also captured an object that would prove most valuable to Sauron: a palantír, one of the seven seeing stones that Elendil's people had brought with them from Númenor at the eve of the Downfall. 

As the power of Dol Guldur grew, the Wise came to suspect that the controlling force behind the Witch-king and the other Nazgûl was indeed their original master, Sauron. In 2063, Gandalf went to Dol Guldur and made the first attempt to learn the truth, but Sauron retreated and hid in the East. It would be almost 400 years before he returned to his stronghold in Mirkwood, and his identity remained undetermined. 

Sauron finally resurfaced with increased strength in 2460. About the same time, the long-lost Ruling Ring was finally recovered from the River Anduin, found by a Stoor Hobbit[39] named Déagol. His relative[40] Sméagol killed him for the Ring, and was eventually corrupted into the creature Gollum. Banished by his family, he took the Ring, which he called his "Precious," and hid in the Misty Mountains. 

In 2850, Gandalf made a second attempt to spy out Dol Guldur. Stealing into the stronghold, he was finally able to confirm the identity of its lord, later reporting to the White Council of Elves and Wizards that Sauron had returned. Saruman, hoping thereby to acquire the One Ring for himself, dissuaded the Council from acting against him. 

Eventually, the Wizards and chief Elves combined to put forth their might, and drove Sauron out of Mirkwood in 2941. During the White Council's delay he had, however, prepared his next move, and was willing to abandon Dol Guldur. 

Just before Sauron fled Dol Guldur, the hobbit Bilbo Baggins, on an improbable adventure with a party of Dwarves, stumbled across the Ring deep within the Misty Mountains. After his quest was over, Bilbo brought the Ring back to Hobbiton in the Shire. Decades later, he passed it on to his heir, Frodo. 

Sauron's power had now recovered to the point that he was able to extend his will over Middle-earth. The Eye of Sauron, as his attention and force of will was perceived, became a symbol of oppression and fear. Following his expulsion from Dol Guldur, he returned to Mordor in 2942, openly declared himself nine years later, and started raising Barad-dûr anew. In preparation for a final war against Men and Elves, he bred immense armies of Orcs, augmenting them with Men from the East and South to create the monstrous Uruk-hai. 

[edit]The War of the Ring 
The three volumes of The Lord of the Rings tell the story of Sauron's last attempt at achieving world dominion, as the Third Age reached its climax in the years 3018 and 3019. 

In The Fellowship of the Ring, Gandalf deduced that the Ring of Power that Bilbo had found in Gollum's cave was indeed Sauron's lost Master-ring. He informed Frodo about the true nature of the heirloom Bilbo had left for him, and its terrible potential if Sauron should ever regain it: "The Enemy still lacks one thing to give him strength and knowledge to beat down all resistance, break the last defences, and cover all the lands in a second darkness. He lacks the One Ring... So he is seeking it, seeking it, and all his thought is bent on it."[41] 

Gandalf went for advice to Saruman, but discovered that he had been corrupted by his long studies of Sauron. Using the palantír in the tower of Orthanc, Saruman was now in communication with the Dark Lord and acted as his ally, though he also secretly hoped to gain the Ring for himself and use its power to supplant Sauron. Gandalf was held captive atop Orthanc for a time, but soon escaped with the help of one of the giant Eagles of Manwë. 

Having captured and tortured Gollum, Sauron learned that the Ring had been found by a Hobbit named "Baggins." Sauron sent the Nazgûl to the Shire, Bilbo's home, but Bilbo had left years earlier. Frodo was likewise on his way out of the Shire (on Gandalf's advice). The Nazgûl pursued Frodo and his companions and nearly killed Frodo, but were defeated near Rivendell. 

In Rivendell, Elrond convened a high council of the peoples of Middle-earth to decide how to handle the crisis. The council determined that the Ring must be destroyed where it was forged, since it was utterly impervious to any other flame than the volcanic fires at its place of making. Frodo and his friend Samwise Gamgee joined the Fellowship of the Ring, accepting the council's mission to cast it into the volcano. 

In The Two Towers, Saruman used his own army on Sauron's behalf and invaded Rohan. Gandalf, Théoden King of Rohan and the Ents, led by Treebeard, finally defeated Saruman's forces. His stronghold at Isengard was overthrown and Saruman left trapped within the Tower of Orthanc. Thus, one of Sauron's most powerful allies was neutralized. 

During Saruman's confrontation with Gandalf, the palantír of Orthanc fell into the hands of the Fellowship. Gandalf handed it over to Aragorn, a direct descendant of Isildur and Elendil and hence the rightful owner of the Stone. In The Return of the King, Aragorn used it to show himself to Sauron (who still controlled another Seeing Stone, the one captured from Minas Ithil centuries earlier). Aragorn was leading Sauron to think that he now had the Ring and was preparing to turn its power against its maker. The Dark Lord was troubled by this revelation, and therefore attacked sooner than he had planned by sending an army to overthrow Minas Tirith, capital of Gondor. (See Battle of the Pelennor Fields) 

Immediately after the huge army left Mordor through the pass of Cirith Ungol, Frodo and Sam attempted to enter the Black Land the same way. They had been previously met by Gollum, whom Sauron had earlier released from captivity while letting him think that he escaped by accident. For a while, Gollum had acted as a guide for Frodo and Sam. However, he finally betrayed them to Shelob – a monstrous, spider-like creature that guarded the pass. 

In the end, Sam drove off both Gollum and Shelob, but Frodo had been stung by Shelob and appeared to have died from her venom. The Orcs found Frodo's body and stripped him of his gear, but Sam (thinking his master dead) had already secured the Ring. Frodo regained consciousness and was freed by Sam, and the two started the gruelling journey across the plains of Mordor towards Mount Doom. 

Aragorn marched on the Black Gate of Mordor with 7000 men. After a brief encounter with the Mouth of Sauron, the battle was joined and went very poorly for the outnumbered Gondor/Rohan armies. Now convinced that Aragorn had the Ring, Sauron apparently reacted just as Gandalf had thought he would: "I will crush him, and what he has taken in his insolence shall be mine again for ever." 

Even as the Captains of the West were about to be utterly defeated by the superior might of Sauron's grand armies, Frodo reached his goal, entering the fiery interior of Mount Doom. However, his will failed at the last moment; unable to resist the growing power of the Ring, he put it on his finger and claimed it for his own. Sauron was instantly aware of him, and his gaze turned immediately to the Door in the Mountain. Recalling his remaining Nazgûl from the ongoing battle, he commanded them to hasten to Mount Doom in a desperate attempt to secure the Ring. It was too late, however: Gollum attacked Frodo, bit the Ring from his finger, then lost his footing and fell with the Ring into the fire. With "a roar and a great confusion of noise", the One Ring perished along with all the power Sauron had invested in it – Gollum inadvertently achieving the quest after Frodo's failure. 

At the Ring's destruction, Sauron's power was immediately broken and his form in Middle-earth was destroyed. His departing spirit towered above Mordor like a black cloud, but was blown away by a powerful wind from the West (the direction of the Blessed Realm and the Valar). His vast empires collapsed, his armies lost heart and were easily overcome, the Dark Tower of Barad-dûr crumbled and the Nazgûl were consumed in a hail of fire from the Mountain. Sauron himself was crippled for all time. Thus, on March 25, Third Age 3019, the long reign of terror of the second Dark Lord finally came to its end. 

Gandalf had predicted what the destruction of the Ring would mean to Sauron: "If it is destroyed, then he will fall, and his fall will be so low that none can foresee his arising ever again. For he will lose the best part of the strength that was native to him in his beginning, and all that was made or begun with that power will crumble, and he will be maimed for ever, becoming a mere spirit of malice that gnaws itself in the shadows, but cannot again grow or take shape. And so a great evil of this world will be removed." 

[edit]Names and titles 

In some of Tolkien's notes, it is said that Sauron's original name was Mairon or "the admirable", "but this was altered after he was suborned by Melkor. But he continued to call himself Mairon the Admirable, or Tar-Mairon "King Excellent", until after the downfall of Númenor.[15] 

The name Sauron (from an earlier form Thauron) originates from the adjective saura "foul, putrid" in Tolkien's invented language of Quenya, and can be translated as "the Abhorred" or "the Abomination". In Sindarin (another Elf-language created by Tolkien) he is called Gorthaur, "the Abhorred Dread" or "the Dread Abomination". He is also called the "Nameless Enemy". The Dúnedain (the descendants of the Númenóreans) call him "Sauron the Deceiver" due to his role in the Downfall of Númenor and the forging of the Rings of Power. In the Númenórean (Adûnaic) tongue he was also known as "Zigûr", The Wizard. 

His two most common titles, the "Dark Lord of Mordor" and the "Lord of the Rings", appear only a few times in The Lord of the Rings. His other titles or variants thereof include "Base Master of Treachery", the "Dark Lord", the "Dark Power", "Lord of Barad-dûr", the "Red Eye", the "Ring-maker" and the "Sorcerer". 

In the First Age (as detailed in The Silmarillion) he was called the "Lord of Werewolves" of Tol-in-Gaurhoth. In the Second Age he assumed the name Annatar, which means "Lord of Gifts", and Aulendil, meaning "Friend of Aulë", as well as Artano, meaning "High-Smith", with which he assumed a new identity and tricked the Elves into working with him to create the Rings. In the Third Age he was known for a time as the Necromancer of Dol Guldur because his true identity was still unknown. 

Russian historian Alexandr Nemirovsky suggests that the name Sauron is meaningful in the Hurrian language. He derives the name from the Hurrian sequence Sau-ra-n(ne), meaning "possessing the weapon" or "armed". 

[edit]Appearance 

Nowhere does Tolkien provide a detailed description of Sauron's appearance during any of his incarnations. 

According to The Silmarillion, Sauron was initially able to change his appearance at will. In the beginning he assumed a beautiful form, but after switching his allegiance to Morgoth, he took a sinister shape. In the First Age, Gorlim was at one point brought into "the dreadful presence of Sauron", but the only concrete hint about his appearance is a reference to his daunting eyes.[44] 

As part of a plan to destroy Huan, Sauron took the form of the greatest werewolf in Middle-earth's history till then. When the plan backfired, he assumed a serpent-like form, and finally changed back "from monster to his own accustomed form".The implication is that his "accustomed form" was not, at least, overtly monstrous. It is understood to have been humanoid. 

Sauron took a beautiful appearance once again at the end of the First Age in an effort to charm Eönwë, near the beginning of the Second Age when appearing as Annatar to the Elves, and again near the end of the Second Age when corrupting the men of Númenor. 

One version of the story describes, in general terms, the impression Sauron made on the Númenóreans. He appeared "as a man, or one in man's shape, but greater than any even of the race of Númenor in stature... And it seemed to men that Sauron was great, though they feared the light of his eyes. To many he appeared fair, to others terrible; but to some evil." 

Like Morgoth, Sauron eventually lost the ability to change his physical form (his hröa). After the destruction of his fair form in the fall of Númenor, Sauron was unable to take a pleasing appearance or veil his power again. Thereafter, at the end of the Second Age and again in the Third, he always took the shape of a terrible dark lord. His first incarnation after the Downfall of Númenor was extremely hideous, "an image of malice and hatred made visible".Isildur recorded that Sauron's hand "was black, and yet burned like fire..." Gil-galad perished from Sauron's heat.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sauron#Eye_of_Sauron 

darkstokes666.blogspot.com 
#gif #animation #animated #dark #evil #skull #death #darkness #saron #eyeofsaron﻿

Meer lezen (784 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_05_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-b-RFAPhBY_Y/T1esMCIEziI/AAAAAAAEnUQ/vTnJEVsvUFs/w426-h320/507854w75480754w087%2Bchristopher%2Bstokes.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/109756091596998868747/albums/5818114158117819937/5818114159823668978</link><title>Speak “Friend” and Eat It: Making a Mines of Moria Birthday Cake 

In my efforts to slowly but surely brainwash my nephew into being a geek, I’ve gradually been introducing him to Tolkien. 

First, I gave him a copy of The Hobbit. Then I let him watch the first of the Lord of the Rings movies. I even agreed to watch with him the Rankin-Bass cartoon of The Hobbit. (It’s not as bad as I remembered. Peter Jackson could learn a thing or two about brevity from that adaptation.) 

Then, for his latest birthday, his 10th, after clearing it with his parents, I went deep into the mines. I made him search for his presents, via a riddle game/scavenger hunt inspired by Bilbo and Gollum. My nephew had to solve one clue, which led him to the next clue, which led him to the next, which finally led him to his birthday prize: a fancy, illustrated hardcover edition of The Hobbit, and a Lego Mines of Moria set. A geek he is becoming. 

The topper was this Mine of Moria-themed cake, which I managed to put together in about two hours. Making this monstrosity, about 12″ x 18″ in the end, was actually not that hard, and as you can see, I took some liberties with the canon. Think of the project as a (mostly) edible diorama. I wish I had taken photos of the cake in process, but alas. 

Here’s how I did it: 
http://www.wired.com/geekdad/2012/12/moria-birthday-cake/﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MTF-kYvDheY/UL4YAK71xvI/AAAAAAAAAM0/wL3egD7NLak/w426-h568/moria-cake-1-660x880.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/108863110264782262414/albums/5764347073106925569/5764347071977407042</link><title>Good afternoon, Plusers and Scavengers! It's about time that I release this photo from the May edition of +Chrysta Rae's Photography Scavenger Hunt. The theme was Smoke, and after seeing some of the incidental smoke photos from the Drinks on Fire category of the previous Hunt I knew I had to do something special to stand out among these excellent Scavengers, something unique - easier said than done! 

That's the great thing about the Hunt - we always want to improve, knowing at the same time that the other Scavengers are also improving each round, and although this is a fun, friendly contest, part of that fun is a product of the competition - both against the other participants and against ourselves. The Hunt forces us to climb outside of our respective ever-expanding thinking-boxes to improve ourselves each month in an attempt to come up with something new and refreshing that will blow everyone away with its awesomeness! At least, that's the plan. ;-) So I wanted to do something completely different. 

I love smoke photography and have tried it myself in past, but this time I wanted to turn that smoke into a shape, like +Christopher Germano had done with his smokey skull in the previous round. Since +Chrysta Rae specifies in the rules that photoshopping is not only allowed but also encouraged, I explored ways of manipulating my smoke photos with CS5. The shaky concepts in my head gradually grew into a firmer idea: a scene from a book being played out in the smoke from a candle, as if the viewer were staring into the fog and daydreaming (like you might do with clouds). Naturally I thought to recreate a scene from The Hobbit, by my favourite author, J.R.R. Tolkien, especially considering the imminent and highly anticipated film release by Peter Jackson coming in December. 

So I had three main elements to piece together: the dragon (Smaug), Bard the bowman, and a candle illuminating an open book and emitting the smoke (I know, I know, candles don't smoke very much when there's a flame - sometimes you just have to use that artistic license). 

To manipulate the shape of the dragon I first needed to capture some good smoke photos. I set up an incense stick in front of a black foam board and arranged my two flash units to fire from each side of the smoke source - catching it in a crossfire of light, if you will, having wrapped cardboard around the front of the flashes to direct that light straight at the smoke and prevent the illumination of the entire room (I believe the technical term is to "snoot"). This setup kept the background relatively dark and the smoke relatively bright, although there was much adjustment of lights required before a reasonable result was achieved. I shot about 100 photos of smoke that night, loaded them into the computer, picked out interesting shapes, imported them to Photoshop, resized, rotated and stretched many layers of them into a shape that started to resemble a dragon. This was the hard part, both creatively and mentally, and I won't get into the technicalities of the procedure unless asked, but suffice to say I stacked 40 or more layers of smoke, masking out bits here and there, dodging and burning other bits to emphasize the dragon's shape. For much of the time I worked on this project there was no certainty a dragon would ever emerge from the flames...when it finally took shape I was almost surprised. 

Dealing with such a massive, multilayered file, I literally (yes, literally) spent more time waiting for the computer to process and render each move and click of the mouse than I did doing actual work. My PC is a few years old, and it was never equipped for a full Photoshop onslaught. If you've ever watched a video online as it loaded and had to wait for it to buffer a minute for every few seconds of play, you know what it felt like working on this large file, and I was at it for almost two full days, afternoon to 4 or 5am in the morning doing little else but working on this stupid smoke creation. I think I went slightly mad. :p Since it took about 15 minutes to save the file I only did so every few hours, and one time, just a few minutes before I was finished for the night, Photoshop crashed (the only time it has done so for me) and I lost two hours of work. It's amazing I have any hair left after this project, as it was one of the most frustratingly slow experiences... 

Anyway, I got that part done with a day left before the submission deadline for the Hunt. That left time to photograph myself in front of a white wall wearing a cloak (blanket) holding a bow (a real bow) and pretending to aim for the soft spot on Smaug's chest with my last remaining Black Arrow. I cut and pasted my bowman into the scene and painted the arrow digitally (was too dangerous to pull an arrow indoors). 

Dusting off my favourite, John Howe illustrated copies of The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings, I opened The Hobbit to the page where Bard confronts Smaug, arranged the books dangerously close to a candle along with a replica of Bilbo's sword for extra authenticity, lit the books by candlelight and blue led, and ultimately used this photo as the background for my little scene. The rest was a matter of composition and color adjustment. I finished the "photo" a few hours before the deadline. 

(by the way, if I may shamelessly plug, the thing holding the book open is a product my family makes called the Bookhug). ;) 

It turned out to be much more of a digital artwork than anything that could be described as a photo, but every single element, with the exception of the arrow, was photographed by me during the Hunt, so it fit within the rules as I understood them. In any case, it's one of the single best pieces of art that I've created, far surpassing anything I thought I was capable of, and for that reason I'm unusually proud of it and was extremely excited that +Sandra Parlow chose this as her 2nd place finisher in the category (thank you again!!! =D) but mostly thankful for this wonderful Scavenger Hunt, without which I would never have made this kind of photo/manip/art. :-) 

The 1st place winners of the Smoke category - congrats, +Barbara Matthews, +Ed Sweeney and +Brandon Luk!: https://plus.google.com/103211003560717503058/posts/EF71PutKC6H 

The full album can be viewed here: https://plus.google.com/photos/103211003560717503058/albums/5752840577519315089 

~~~ 

So, are there any hardcore Tolkien readers here? I'd like to hear from you! And if you're a fan of Peter Jackson's film adaptations of J.R.R.'s books, check out this G+ Hobbit page run by +Daniel James for all the latest news about the upcoming epic film: gplus.to/TheHobbitMovies 

#scavengerhunt   #mayscavengerhunt   #tolkien   #thehobbit   #hobbit   #dragon   #smoke   #photomanipulation     #dragonthursday  ﻿

Meer lezen (122 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Ktppo1D5WkQ/T_8THwNGwkI/AAAAAAAABxo/QhiwdeVcTtQ/w426-h582/Smoke%2Bby%2BDerek%2BKind.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/117540808102521281396/albums/5843003533766552033/5843003534099741954?authkey=CKKV39aU75OkEA</link><title>Music From The Hobbit And The Lord Of The Rings, composed by Howard Shore, Performed by The City Of Prague Philharmonic Orchestra 

Label: Silva Screen Records 
Release Date: 4th February 2013 

The album contains some of the best themes from The Lord Of The Rings trilogy and The Hobbit. Howard Shore has composed some of the best and greatest music in films. However, fans of the Middle Earth music may be disappointed with this album. It is a brief capture of a great and wonderful canvas. I did like the album for this brief capture. It is a nice overview of the huge volumes of music. 

The City Of Prague Philharmonic Orchestra play with their usual brilliance. I have always cherished this orchestra. The sound is crisp, and the music flows smoothly. 

With an hour's worth of music, this is a good introduction to Middle Earth music. Recommended.﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-6YPNhh0hdbE/URaEwbdd_QI/AAAAAAAADWE/VOBfzGp_sI4/s426/hobbit.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/102252942326161956509/albums/5748377808357308369/5748377810876379346</link><title>Guardians of Middle-earth heading to Xbox Live 
Guardians of Middle-earth is the next "massive online battle arena" heading to Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network. Warner Bros. Interactive's Monolith Productions is crafting the Lord of the Rings/The Hobbit-themed MOBA, and the studio plans on launching the game this fall (ahead of this December's film, The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey). According to the announcement, 10 players will battle in five-on-five matches set against the backdrop of Middle-earth. Various Lord of the Rings bulletpoints will be hit, of course, with characters like Gollum and Sauron available for fighting (as "Guardians" – think League of Legends' "Hero" characters). We'll assuredly get a closer look at the game next week during E3. for more on this follow the link........ http://www.rheena.com/showthread.php/154278 

#guardiansofmiddleearth #microsoft #monolith #monolithproductions #playstation #ps3 #warnerbrosinteractive #xbox #guardians-of-middle-earth #monolith-productions #warner-bros-interactive﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-9huC8Ay0Uzw/T8ZXKawGMNI/AAAAAAAANIw/LhEldndg95o/w426-h237/lotrhobbit.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7080-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lord%20of%20the%20rings%20hobbits%20theme/photos/109619348009948114051/albums/5827247418314299409/5827247423215243378?authkey=COnk6MHL_963SA</link><title>Ok my thoughts on The Hobbit. 

I've tried not to read too many reviews on the Hobbit as most people were bagging the HFR 3D effect. This is going to be about the actual film (I saw it in regular 2D). I thought It was very good, not great, or brilliant, just very good. 3 hours is a long time but i've you've seen LotR in the cinema you should cope with this. It did drag a bit here and there but I have the feeling that it is setting up some exposition that is needed for the other two films to come. The action scenes are amazing and it seems to take itself a little less seriously than LotR, which is a good thing. I think if Peter Jackson tried to make something better than the trilogy it wouldn't have worked (Apparently it's one of the reasons he was reluctant to do the Hobbit in the first place). There are many winks and nods to the trilogy, perhaps a little too many for my liking, the Hobbit needs to stand on it's own and it would have done this very well. But we are in Middle Earth and the Hobbit book is a prelude to the Lord of the Rings. The music was fantastic, can anyone else spot "the ring" music that was only played for a three notes, barely a few seconds, before being cut short? In fact I really enjoyed the music. Howard Shore has done a great job linking each theme and building on it. There's the dwarven theme, the ring theme, Frodo's theme, all the different musical cues. If you liked the music you'll love the soundtrack.I've heard a lot of press about how it's not close to the book and i'm going to give this film the benefit of the doubt. Jackson and co took three huge books and made them into 3 fantastic movies and there were bits from the book that were added to and bits that never saw the light of day, and that's ok because the films aren't meant to be replicas of the books they were based on them. If you've read the Hobbit go into seeing the movie as a 'take' on the book. A lot of people complain when they hear that it's three films and to you I say NERRRR if Jackson wants to make 3 films let him. He has not done a George Lucas on us here, this is not a terrible movie preceding an amazing trilogy. This is a great adventure film that leads up to the more serious Lord of the Rings. 

The picture is a photo taken 9 years ago! When +Astrid Lee  and I went to New Zealand to see the RotK world premiere, and yes that's me wearing a hobbit cape. My hairy feet allows me to do such things. NO SHAME! 

You should also go and see Les Miserables. A tale of.... well everything really.﻿

Meer lezen (38 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7080_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9u7F2wbyun8/UN6KqEcOEHI/AAAAAAADmpI/EcpK3jwrOmk/w426-h320/20031130_19_04_01.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>