<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7081">translation bloopers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:19:18" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/107246750453437459942/albums/5883070673522867905/5883070673568495810?authkey=CNrZ8LfLqdGAYA&amp;sqi=117699187083688492968&amp;sqsi=ab896c84-9734-452b-9740-824935756c81</link><title>TOKIO HOTEL (NEW VIDEO [Rutube] + DOWNLOAD + Spanish Translation) [28.05.2013] - "Tokio Hotel bloopers! What MTV didn't show you. Haha… Tom" http://tokiohotelaliensspain.blogspot.com.es/2013/05/tokio-hotel-new-video-28052013-tokio.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-kAysyH0RTyI/UaTdm5aReMI/AAAAAAACF0w/gyzz-JASvXg/w426-h258/pizap.com13697563909003.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/107561115969255376648/albums/5916109721671873585/5916109943090159954?authkey=CNfNxPqloKuTfg</link><title>[BAD PICTURES - MISSED SHOTS - BLOOPERS &amp; OTHER MISSHAPPENINGS] 

I will start this section now. We are used to see the "good" stuff published, but it is almost never that we get to see the misshappenings of the photographer's trade, still i do believe it is useful to see it, for the more experienced ones it gives a chance to study what happened and learn from it, for the beginner photographer it not only teaches but also encourage to know that behind the nice pictures posted out there there are also bad ones, sometimes really bad ones! 

In my line of work misshappenings are the everyday's bread, different from other specialties where you always have control over the shooting conditions, in nature photography everything can happen at any time, the subjects wont stay still, nor look here, look there, blink an eye, can't control lighting, sometimes they are in the perfect spot just to turn the other way on the next second and have them completely backlit. 

Among all wildlife, the small they are the harder they are to depict, not only because of the technical difficulties, focal lenght, etc, but mainly because of how fast they move!! I believe that at least half of my missed shots are due to either the animal suddenly moving or becuase of the action of wind, this last is specially annoying in flower's photography. 

Shot from the car, this big fellow decided not to pose for the camera, it was a matter of seconds, not even enough time for proper focusing :-( It would have been an awesome shot otherwise! Didn't even had time to shot a second frame. 

#badpictures  ﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5rL9r-mBQrQ/Uho-pfoLoVI/AAAAAAAAKn4/nzDVG7k_cIQ/w426-h285/RV_20130817b-011_NIKON+D200_500+mm_f-8_1-750+s_ISO-400_filtered.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/101181422073201532085/albums/5774759743732129985/5774759748138337714</link><title>Hiring a qualified translator is crucial to marketing success internationally. Have you seen any unintentionally humorous translations? 

http://www.atanet.org/client_outreach/translation_bloopers.php﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_03_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Ope7hBJPyHQ/UCQRZRsChbI/AAAAAAAAAc0/eRlTszlwgA0/w426-h320/TranslationBloopers.PNG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/104386117252837770895/albums/5664522539308541009/5664522538712816866</link><title>Super Mario Bros. 
From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia 

This article is about the Mario video game for the Nintendo Entertainment System. For other uses, see Super Mario Bros. (disambiguation). Super Mario Bros. (スーパーマリオブラザーズ Sūpā Mario Burazāzu?) is a 1985 platform video game developed by Nintendo, published for the Nintendo Entertainment System as a sequel to the 1983 game Mario Bros. In Super Mario Bros., the player controls Mario (and in a two-player game, a second player controls Mario's brother Luigi) as he travels through the Mushroom Kingdom in order to rescue Princess Toadstool from the antagonist Bowser. For over 20 years, Super Mario Bros. was the best-selling video game of all time (before being outsold by Nintendo's own Wii Sports in 2009), and has sold more than 40 million copies worldwide. As a launch title, it was largely responsible for the initial success of the Nintendo Entertainment System, as well as ending the two-year slump of console game sales in the United States after the video game crash of 1983. As one of Shigeru Miyamoto and Takashi Tezuka's most influential early successes, it has inspired many clones, sequels, and spin-offs. The game's theme music by Koji Kondo is recognized worldwide, even by those who have not played the game, and has been considered a representation for video game music in general. The success of Super Mario Bros. has caused it to be ported to almost every one of Nintendo's major gaming consoles. In late 2010, as part of the 25th anniversary of the game's release, Nintendo released special red variants of the Wii and Nintendo DSi XL consoles in differently re-packaged, Mario-themed, and limited edition bundles in all regions. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario_Bros.﻿

Meer lezen (25 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-dJZ0ttxc-8A/TpxtPK4r3OI/AAAAAAAAElw/UJxg79ZeET0/w426-h539/mario.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/117593897807431937507/albums/5948883741826235521/5948883748796998450</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/--Xgl2B6XGZc/Uo6uQEEjozI/AAAAAAABH68/aMi2a8_e03o/w426-h360/bloopers-and-funny-pictures-fort.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/117788694868270223910/albums/5910052899463152545/5910052904305247170?authkey=CKrMqpru_9O2SA</link><title>This traditional tapas menu is a bit "lost in translation." How many mistakes can you spot?  Help these guys fix their menu! 
#LanguageBloopers ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Q0rFz6_5VOM/UgS5zbzhQ8I/AAAAAAAAA0E/NwBPiBevDW8/w426-h568/Language-Bloopers-Tapas-Menu.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/101461294586787090793/albums/5786074028611359121/5786074031222805826</link><title>Château de Cadillac Church 
#châteaudecadillac﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-2XJSvBN25k0/UExDrOsl1UI/AAAAAAAAMfM/2uJXykjfFXE/w426-h568/Russell%2BDavison.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/105479712798762608629/albums/5958783187704364433/5958783187234408290</link><title>If you're a young adult under 26, the Affordable Care Act lets you stay on your parents' health plan while you pursue your career. This benefit has already helped more than 3 million Americans #GetCovered.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wJafEsE95AI/UrHZvOCtR2I/AAAAAAABkKc/FcgaGtAASmY/w426-h284/12.18.13%2BYoung%2BAdults%2B1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7081-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/translation%20bloopers/photos/100876551275065134925/albums/5980321094276261105/5980321092719293282</link><title>DICE level artist Linnea Harrison answers YOUR questions on ‪#‎BF4‬ level design: http://bit.ly/LWC39F﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7081_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-WUfzqncbGYc/Uv5eWUZPM2I/AAAAAAABBzQ/VtT1et6hRaQ/w426-h240/leveldesign.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>