<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:32:47" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/108036467414278720268/albums/5658662793533290193/5658662798053727570</link><title>Film Review - Red State 

Kevin Smith is back! Easily his best film for a decade, Red State demonstrate a real ballsiness and confidence like we've never seen from him before. His directorial style has picked up a few new tricks, and they're used surprisingly effectively, reminding me at times of Tarantino at his best, Inglourious Basterds in particular. He rackets up the tension, the action, the claustrophobia with a deftness he's never shown before. 

However, it's not all great news. Things begin to get a bit tedious and repetitive in the second half, thanks to shoot-out after shoot-out after tedious bloody shoot-out, followed by a sudden Coen-brothers-style interruption where we're told the story's ending, rather than see it for ourselves. Comparisons to Burn After Reading may be considered a compliment to some, but not to me. 

But we are talking minor niggles here. If Kevin Smith hadn't shot himself in the foot by recently pissing off both film critics and distributors, this might have been his best shot at Oscar glory. The screenplay is one of his best- considered and intelligent, with his trademark base humour down a necessary, effective minimum. But the cast are flawless. Melissa "fucking" Leo outdoes her Oscar-winning turn in The Fighter by a long shot, Michael Parks is terrifyingly sincere and John Goodman grounds things superbly. Even the bit players get so show off some highly convincing acting chops. 

Genuinely unpredictable, but nowhere near as unpalatable as you might expect.﻿

Meer lezen (25 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Mbf0mhyxW2g/Toeb1X213VI/AAAAAAAAAaA/etsmWtau_dQ/w426-h639/11%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/106573170491455105558/albums/5988951193696604449/5988951197660158146?sqi=117743408409885855607&amp;sqsi=bfa015a1-5d48-4923-b63a-ea163977bb5c</link><title>Many years ago, we set out to make a documentary out at Burning Man. The film is finally done and available!!!! 

http://www.facebook.com/asthedust 

The film is live on hulu!!!! 
www.hulu.com/watch/605701 

and amazon Instant: 
www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00IOSPAP0/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B00IOSPAP0&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=asthduse-20 

here's a review that Burn After Reading Magazine just put up: 
http://burnafterreadingmag.com/as-the-dust-settles-brings-first-person-perspective/ 

for all links including Vimeo VOD, Reelhouse, Indieflix etc visit our website: 

http://www.asthedust.com/ 
cheers 
Mike﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-jkeWmrP6_4s/Ux0HYimvGMI/AAAAAAAAAbU/BbrTBu61LcY/w426-h237/1779297_10152296592318665_715075227_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/116126477206840673489/albums/5844032336178479905/5844032342793347890?authkey=CNaFueSYwMOyOQ</link><title>Ever fallen over at the end of a WOD? After reading this you may want to reconsider. 

"If there’s one thing that I don’t agree with when it comes to typical CrossFit behaviour it is the crash and burn at the end of every workout." Katie Hogan 

http://therxreview.com/katie-hogan-a-crossfit-competitors-mindset/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-obLrKUMf_z8/URosc-gXYzI/AAAAAAAAAf0/Pq9a7nMnQEs/w426-h348/577743_10150760992516106_803872993_n.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/102062373234332211376/albums/5779531331319546017/5779531332030832162</link><title>Book review \- Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury. 

Ray Bradbury's 1953 novel Fahrenheit 451 is a science fiction classic that, somehow, I'd never read.  With Bradbury's recent death, I decided it was time to remedy that.  Unfortunately, I was severely underwhelmed by Fahrenheit 451, and found it lacking in many ways. 

Fahrenheit 451 is a dystopian novel that, despite prominently featuring book-burning, posits dystopia-by-entertainment, like Aldous Huxley's Brave New World, as opposed to dystopia-by-oppression, like George Orwell's 1984 or Margaret Atwood's The Handmaid's Tale.  The evil of the Fahrenheit 451 is not censorship, but television, which has made people so dumb and uninterested in the world that (almost) no one even cares that firemen now burn books, instead of putting out blazes. 

The main character is Guy Montag, one of these firemen, who, after a few chance conversations with a young girl next door, realizes he's doing bad things and that the world is a mess.  This pushes him to start to consider reading the books he's supposed to be burning, and the novel moves on from there. 

Montag, and the other characters in the book, all seem flat.  Part of this is  that there's no real dialogue or conversations in the book.  With the exception of Guy's horrid wife and her friends who basically say "Shut up, my shows are on!" all book, every time a character opens their mouth, it seems they launch into a diatribe - the protagonist and his allies for books, and the antagonists against them.  There's no real debate of ideas, and the characters all seem like mouthpieces for Bradbury, either for his anti-technology position or straw men for the anti-book position. 

The idea of a dystopia brought on by entertaining the citizens into apathy is a perfectly good one, and Huxley did a fine job with it in Brave New World.  However, I just couldn't buy Bradbury's take.  As far as he's concerned, technology can only be used to placate the masses through their wall-sized TV's or proto-Walkmen.  In Fahrenheit 451, the means of content creation still rest, as they did in the '50's, in the hands of the few.  This fails to account for the way technology really played out.  Sure, we all have huge HDTV's and smartphones with Bluetooth headphones, but we also use all this fantastic technology to connect with people around the world in ways never before possible, and we seek out alternate sources of information that could never have reached nearly as as many people.  Sure, plenty of people just let TV rot their brains, but I'm not convinced that's any different today than the '50's, and the technology now has so many other fantastic and worthwhile uses Bradbury ignores or can't predict.  Bradbury also ignores that a large percentage of books aren't any better than TV.  Just because it's printed on a dead tree doesn't make it Plato or Dickens. 

Let me also say something about the end of the novel and the war background thread.  All through the novel there's imminent threat of war, though - perhaps this is to reflect the characters' lack of concern - what the war is about, who it's with, or how it will be fought is never really addressed, until the end of the book.  All of a sudden, it pops up in a major way, and then a page or two later the book's over.  It's like Bradbury ran out of story and decided "Eh, I'll just toss in a mention or two of war earlier in the book, then let that take care of everything at the end."  Maybe this is related to the fact that Fahrenheit 451 started as a short story, was expanded to a novella, then expanded again to a novel.  Maybe there just wasn't enough story to flesh the ideas out to that long a format.  In any case, the war thread is a horrible deus ex machina (see 1984 for how to weave war into a dystopian story effectively), and the ending is almost a non-ending.  I don't mind a grim or ambiguous ending, but Fahrenheit 451 can't even deliver in that way. 

The writing style also gave me problems.  Bradbury goes on for paragraphs describing scenery in repetitive flowery language, then in a plain sentence or two you hardly notice, he slips in a major event with little emphasis.  It's just uneven, tedious, and makes things hard to follow. 

I love golden age science fiction from Isaac Asimov and Robert Heinlein, so it's not that I don't enjoy the genre or the era.  Yeah, 1950's science fiction has its issues these days, but I don't mind those too much, as writers like Asimov an Heinlein penned entertaining  stories with lasting messages.  I know Bradbury is looked at in a similar way, but from Fahrenheit 451, I just can't put him in the same class as Asimov or Heinlein. 

I listened to Harper Audio's 2001 production of Fahrenheit 451, read by Ray Bradbury.  I thought it would be interesting to hear the book as envisioned by the author.  I was wrong.  Bradbury was not an effective narrator.  He has a single tone in which he reads.  It can be hard to tell if he's narrating description or reading dialogue, or if he's reading dialogue, which character is speaking.  Conversations (such as they are, see above) are horrible to try to follow.  I just can't recommend anyone, even a hardcore Bradbury fan, listen to this production.  There are other versions out there read by professional audio book readers.  Get one of them.  It has to be better.  One other problem with the production are the track times.  These are rarely worth mentioning for audio books, but in this case, they are.  The tracks range from 1:37 to 28:37 in length, and for no apparent reason.  Tracks aren't tied to chapters or anything else I could discern.  They just vary wildly in how long they are, which makes it very hard to keep track of where in the book you are.  There's no reason for this.  The production includes a 2001 interview with Bradbury after the book itself.  The entire production runs approximately 6 hours, and about an hour of that is the interview. 

I can't recommend Fahrenheit 451.  Yes, it has an interesting premise, but Bradbury just isn't up to turning it into a compelling story.  If you're looking for a good dystopian novel, you'd do better to read 1984, The Handmaid's Tale, or Brave New World.  And if you still want to read Fahrenheit 451, do not under any circumstances listen to Bradbury's narration of it. 

Related reviews: 
1984 by George Orwell - https://plus.google.com/u/0/102062373234332211376/posts/Lu8BDZPfDz5 
The Handmaid's Tale by Margaret Atwood - https://plus.google.com/u/0/102062373234332211376/posts/GxLS1k6PQmH﻿

Meer lezen (111 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BWbAowoduc4/UDUFIA3wHiI/AAAAAAAAJQk/USS1hPDIx7Q/w426-h705/fahrenheit-451.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/108188503262756167529/albums/5675300945504031793/5675300952878118578</link><title>Book Title: "The Burning Soul" 
Author: John Connolly 
Published By: Atria Books (Simon &amp; Schuster) 
Age Recommended: 18+ 
Reviewed By: Kitty Bullard 
Raven Rating: 5 

Review: John Connolly has been hailed as a best-selling novelist for a while now, constantly making his appearances on the New York Times coveted list. I can honestly say after reading the first book I've ever read by him that he has earned this spot a thousand times over. 

His writing ability surpasses many of the best today and his mixture of the paranormal with the world of crime is superb. "The Burning Soul" is a book that has the power to burn itself into your memory and secure a place there that will resurface time and again throughout the course of your life. There are moments that will have you glancing at your silent television set expecting to see a face... not your own, staring back at you. A face that holds a silent scream frozen forever in time... read the book and you'll find out what I mean. 

Highly recommended, one of the best books by far that I've read all year! 

Read more: http://www.greatmindsthinkaloud.proboards.com/index.cgi?action=display&amp;board=thrillers&amp;thread=827&amp;page=1#ixzz1dnlVzRUD﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MXFYBZGVXMs/TsK4Jcm8drI/AAAAAAAAA7Q/NxKn0cd9ALM/w426-h656/BURNING%2BSOUL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/102168647176964480401/albums/6005103822065740257/6005103827488699282?sqi=113639835380393274110&amp;sqsi=3099d9ed-9c89-4c45-8110-60d64854a58c</link><title>Our final entry into the Battle of the Waifus and Husbandos is a special shout out to +Dmaest Grim +Chibi Reviews and my Khaleesi +Nagisa chan. I give you Bandere! The Yandere version of Banri! He dual wields chainsaws of death! Guys it has been fun making these posts and suffering through writers block over the unfamiliar characters has made me a better content maker. I look forward to creating more fun things to promote the community and cannot wait to see how the tournament goes! GO ERZA!!!!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-rmhbTHoG4c0/U1ZqHVzNc5I/AAAAAAAABUY/3wVIqY0TDOc/w426-h240/Banri1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/117668392750579292609/albums/5949858028865991009/5949858028193116290</link><title>Doctor Who Review - The Day of the Doctor 

Writing an anniversary special is something of a poison chalice at the best of times. Writing a 50th Anniversary special for a show that has to appeal to all ages in prime time and has a rabid fan base who have memorised every detail of the shows inconsistent continuity and will pick it to death is and all of those people expect references to their memories of the show…. Well  Moffat was the script writer on the day it wasn’t possible to get it right really wasn’t he? 

No, The Day of the Doctor is not the perfect Doctor Who episode. It can’t be, because it has too many roles to fill. But that said, it does a lot of things right. 

So let’s just get the weaknesses out of the way at the beginning. 

\- The Zygon plot is pretty much by the numbers for modern Who and it doesn’t get what you’d call a satisfactory resolution. 
\- This is a giant honking retcon. If you care about such things. 
\- OCD fans are going to be foaming at the mouth about numbers 
\- There are a good number of big ideas that are thrown out there without explanation or follow through. 
\- The Time War remains largely unseen and while what we do see is an epic battle, it also lacks any actual… you know.. time elements. 

All of the above is true and lets be honest somewhat typical of Steven Moffat’s Doctor Who in general. The show was in fact packed with Moffatisms both good and bad. ALthough the longer running time does help to alleviate the over-compression that I’ve felt about recent episodes 

Unlike previous multi-Doctor stories, time travel was actually central to the story-telling here and threaded throughout. There are mirror constructs throughout the story as well. Moffat knows his story structure. The story is also meta-commentary on the show itself, another thing that Moffat is fond of. 

It’s All About Matt Smith 

This is an 11th Doctor story (no I’m not wasting my time on the stupid numbering debate and neither should you) and it follows the emotional beats of Matt Smith’s Doctor as we’ve been exploring them since his arrival. 

Other Doctors are present, but it’s made very obvious that this story changes nothing for them. It does however change the current Doctor’s perspective. 

By introducing The Curator at the end Moffat both signals a new theme/direction to pursue in future seasons and also (don’t forget the meta) winks to the audience and says.. but guess which actor won’t be there to see it through. 

Mirror Structures Everywhere 
Right from the beginning we have references and mirror structures. The opening sequence directly copies that of the very first episode. Then Smith hanging from the TARDIS mirrors his first episode The Eleventh Hour. 

But that’s just the start of it. 

We learn about the Omega Arsenal. And just how bloody were the Ancients of Gallifrey anyway? Later on we learn about UNIT’s Black Archive. Similar anyone? It could also be seen as a direct replacement to the defunct Torchwood. 

The structural mirroring goes beyond that though because we get The Moment from the Omega Arsenal and we discover there’s a nuke under The Black Archive. The parallels are obviously not accidental. This is a direct mirror to the Doctor’s intention to destroy Gallifrey. Murdering millions to save billions as Kate Lethbridge-Stewart puts it. But as Tennant responds: 

"This is not a decision you will ever be able to live with." 
"What I did that day was wrong. Just wrong." 

There has to be a better way right? After all. This is Doctor Who. There’s always a better way. It’s a central tenet of the show. 

And of course there is. In fact the final solution is another bit of structural mirroring being the exact method they used with the Sonic Screwdriver earlier on. Nicely done Mr. Moffat. 

Meta... Meta... Meta... 

Being a Doctor Who anniversary special you have to address the fans directly and The Day of the Doctor does that in spades. In fact there are so many little references I can’t even attempt to catch them all. 

-The clock near the beginning that showed the exact time the first episode of Doctor Who was broadcast 
\- Ian Chesterton as school governor 
\- Tennant not liking the changes to the TARDIS 
\- Osgood and her scarf (two for one) 
\- The way when menaced by Zygons people press themselves back into a corner 

But there are much bigger meta-discussion and structures at play here. The direct reference to The Three Doctors is not accidental as this episode is clearly partially patterned against that. Certainly far more so than The Five Doctors. 

Here John Hurt (fabulous in the part incidentally) taking a similar role to William Hartnell as the crotchety old man while Matt Smith is clearly The Clown (Patrick Troughton) and yes David Tennant is The Dandy notice how they played up his tendency to woo the ladies? Hurt even gets a Hartnell line near the end when he regenerates. 

Hurt serves another purpose here as well. A purely meta one. He acts as an old-school Doctor and directly lobs some of the criticisms that long-time fans have had of nu-Who: 

"Am I having a mid-life crisis?" 
"They're screwdrivers. What are you going to do? Assemble a cabinet at them?" 
"Timey what? Timey Wimey?" 
"Are you capable of speaking without flapping your hands about?" 
"Is there a lot of this in the future?" \- Referencing Tennant kissing Queen Elizabeth. 
"Oh for gods sake! Gallifrey stands" \- Referencing Allons-y and Geronimo. 

But he also serves as notice that…. it’s changed okay. Nu-Who is not the same as old Who. But that doesn’t make it worse. Throughout the episode he is the odd one out. In several places Tennant and Smith’s Doctor’s are showing working in unison. Clearly parts of the same whole. Hurt stands apart. A different era. Someone whose experiences have shaped him very differently. 

And yet in the end he respects the newer Doctors: 

"How many worlds has his regret saved to you think?" 
"Then all things considered. Time I grew up." 

Yes thats directly referencing the on-going plot but it’s also talking about how the show has changed. In the old days the Doctor did save people. But it was almost by accident. He stumbled into situations and did the best he could. With perhaps the exception of Sylvester McCoy’s Doctor he wasn’t trying to save the world. 

Snappy Dialogue 

What would modern Doctor Who be without the witty banter hmm? Well we got that in spades and here I think Tennant got some of the best material: 

"It's a machine that goes ding" 
"You are basically just a rabbit aren't you?" 
"Compensating?" 
"Sandshoes" 
"We're confusing the polarity!" 
”Spoilers!” 
"The round things! I love the round things! What are the round things?" 

I also, incidentally love and miss the roundels. They’ll come back eventually. 
We also discovered that when you put the cleverest person in the room in the room three times over they all miss the obvious solution. The door isn't locked. 

Who Is The Doctor 

If you were to ask me what this episode was really about, I would say it was an exploration of what it means to be The Doctor. 

While fans are busy wasting their time arguing over whether we call him 8.5 or 9 or Theta Sigma they are sadly missing the far bigger points that were being made. Bad Wolf Rose’s dialogue hits the nail on the head when talking about the arrival of the TARDIS: 

"That sound brings hope to anyone who hears it. Anyone Doctor. Even you." 

What is the Doctor? According to this episode he’s a promise: 

Never cruel or cowardly 
Never give up. Never give in. 

But above all he is the bringer of hope. He makes things better. And there was one point in his history when he himself had  no hope. And the only person who could bring him that hope… was himself. 

"You were the Doctor on the day it wasn't possible to get it right." 
"You don't have to do it alone." 
"Either I destroy my own people or let the Universe burn." 

Physician heal thyself. 

Yes it’s a retcon. It’s a giant stinking retcon. But Doctor Who doesn’t have continuity. It never did. That’s a fan construct. It’s ever changing ever evolving. And while the battle damaged Doctor made an easy entry point for new fans and gave depth to the character for those who didn’t already know his whole history… Well the behavior it really never did sit well with the Doctor’s core character did it? 

Stop Sweating The Small Stuff 

Fans have a tendency to fixate on the small and largely unimportant details. LIke the correct number of Doctors and the regeneration limit. In this episode Moffat basically tells us to stop wasting our energy. It will all get squared away. 

First we have the thirteenth incarnation of the man who calls himself The Doctor showing up. And at no point do they feel the need to actually assign numbers to themselves. Then we have what it’s strongly hinted is a future incarnation re-using a favorite face put in an appearance basically telling us the regeneration limit is no big thing. 

"In years to come you might find yourself revisiting a few. But just the old favorites eh?" 

Moffat also has Smith explicitly say both that he doesn’t remember how old he is and that he might be lying. So can we stop worrying about exactly what age he is at various stages? It doesn’t matter. 

A Few More Thoughts 

I really wish we’d had this version of Rose in the Tennant era. She was so much more appealing than the character we actually got. 

John Hurt is wonderful as an older and war weary Doctor. As much as I love Paul McGann his Doctor couldn’t have pulled that off. And no… neither could Eccleston’s. 

Speaking of which.. really Chris? You couldn’t have come back to give us the 1 minute of footage we needed for a proper regeneration? 

The Doctor Is Going Home…. Eventually 

So let’s wrap this up in a bow. We get a big celebration of what came before. A re-tuning of where we are going next. Oh and lots of fun along the way. 

No it’s not a perfect story, but I don’t think you could make an anniversary special that got any closer. 

Amazon.com: http://amzn.to/1cafNAZ﻿

Meer lezen (237 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-63MXUe22l5U/UpIkWlp08II/AAAAAAAArN0/CplGFUdP4Sk/w426-h240/Doctor-Who-Day-of-The-Doctor-Preview.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/105744372055117875664/albums/5691694879181797729/5691694881137665154</link><title>My 2 Day Review of the Galaxy Nexus 

I'm not a big gadget guy and my iPhone 3gs is the only mobile phone I've ever owned, so take whatever I say with a grain of salt. I mainly just want a mobile computer, voice is a nice add on, that's all. 

After my 2 year indentured servitude ended, I was in the market for a new-gen phone. I ran away from the iPhone 4 because it betrayed the elegance of engineering that was the 3gs. The 4 is a clumsy brick in comparison to the 3gs, which just feels beautiful in the hand. 

None of the androids were enticing until the nexus. I wanted a bigger screen and a fast 4g network. Riding the new android release was a bonus. 

Big screen. It's great. Big and sharp. I can read emails no problem. There's just more space everywhere, which I like. The nexus doesn't feel too big, but I have biggish hands, so that may be just me. The iphone and the nexus weigh about the same to me, with the nexus being slightly slimmer. 

4g. When 4g works: wow! It's lightening fast. Much faster than my home wifi network. The problem is at our house it drifts in and out of 3g, for reasons I don't understand, and sometimes there's no 3g or 4g at all. This never happens to my iphone or my ipad which has verizon 3g. Coverage is also not as wonderful as I was dreaming. Parts of santa cruz have nothing. As an att customer, when my phone had no signal, I would ask people whose connections were still going fine, who their provider was, and it was always verizon. So I don't know if it's the nexus that has problems or I just have to adjust my expectations. But I love the 4g speed. I got the 10 gig plan to start with to see home much I used so I can dial it down when I learn my usage patterns. I don't plant to watch a lot of movies, though youtube videos are great on the big screen. 

Onboarding experience. Sucked. The iphone just works. With the nexus there's a ton of packaging and sim card and battery to install. I see the wisdom of apple's approach here. We found out later that the manual in the box doesn't match the nexus, it's generic. And the second instruction is to call for activation. First line support was very confused. Nice and polite, but confused. They couldn't understand why our phone wasn't showing up in their system, so we were stuck on hold for quite a while until we were passed to second line support, who was also confused, nice, but confused. Eventually we figured out the nexus doesn't need activation. You just stick the battery and sim card in and it will activate itself. No call needed. This is exactly the opposite of what the manual says to do. That's pretty bad. And it was obvious the support people weren't familiar with the nexus yet as they didn't know how it worked or which buttons did what. But they were nice and helpful. 

Like the cover. The iphone is a delicate little flower. The nexus is made of plastic, which lacks the sexiness of the iphone, but it looks good enough and it seems like I won’t break it, which my clumsy self appreciates. 

Keyboard. I like the keyboard touch feedback. When you press a key it makes a sound or something that makes you feel like you've actually touched a button. Much nicer than the iphone. 

Snappy feel. Definitely doesn’t feel underpowered. Everything is fast and feels good. 

3 “virtual” buttons. The iphone has the physical home button whereas the nexus has 3 permanent virtual buttons. The middle is a home looking icon, which takes you home. The leftmost button one quickly learns is "go back." The rightmost button is a pair overlapping rectangles, which I had no idea what it was. It turns out this is a most recent command list. The consistent back button is very nice, the iphone is very confusing with apps and web pages behaving completely differently. 

LED. There’s a LED on the bottom that flashes. Still really no idea why it flashes. 

Notifications. Notifications, like that there’s email, show up on the top of the screen and you draw your finger down to see what’s waiting. Works nicely. 

Battery drains fast. Seems to really drain fast. Turning off all the sync seems like a bad fix, but it’s necessary. On the other hand there’s all these cool performance counters that tell you what parts of the system are using power. In general the monitoring part of the system is quite well done, especially compared to the iphone. There’s a lot of information available if you dig around. If you navigate to the left of the home page there’s a power control widget which is quite helpful in limiting power usage. It’s trivial to toggle on and off wifi, syncing, gps, and the display. 

Huge volume button. On the left side of the phone there's this giant volume button which is imposible not to hit. No idea why it's so large. 

Uneven experience. Generally not as clean, consistent, or as attractive as the iphone. The color scheme is just kind of muddled. Dark colors. Some applications have their settings in the settings pane and some don't. There's are a lot more menus and other ways to trigger commands than on the iphone, which is confusing. It took me quite a while to figure out to go back to the inbox on gmail required using the go back button. The icons could look better, the lock screen is kind of ugly, the choice of wallpapers is horrendous. The swiping gesture to login seems clunky. The slider to accept a call is far less clear than pressing accept/decline on the iphone. Things like a phone symbol on a red bar to stop a call just doesn’t seem good looking or obvious. There’s just a lot more that could be improved in the UI. It should look stunning. 

No apps on the home page is disconcerting. When you enter the phone for the first time there's virtually nothing on the screen, there's just this ugly looking clock. I felt like what now? 

Nice google integration. You might expect this, but gmail, contacts, etc all work great. The exception is Picasa, which seems to be the red headed step child of the group. The only way for photos to go to picasa is via auto sync. When I try to push a pic to picasa it asks me to login, which I already should be, and when I login it says I'm already logged in. Not good. And flickr is a lot better than picasa, but I guess they couldn’t use that. 

Really like how it handles spelling corrections. It suggests a few alternatives and you can pick which you want. The iphone just makes the correction for you, which fails far more than it succeeds. 

Love the flash and zoom on the camera. The pictures in general look good to my non expert eyes. Having a zoom is something I’ve wanted for a long time, so it’s a great feature. The camera has some built in editing features, lighting control, and just generally seems to be well thought out. 

There’s no way to add a phone number to a contact, you have to make a new contact, which is not what I would like. 

Voice input is meh. I tried a few voice searches and it got it wrong every time. Maybe it’s my voice. 

Can’t tune the gmail sync period. You can turn syncing on or off, that's it. With battery being at such a premium we should have more control. 

Browser problems. Interestingly web pages are still more readable on the iPhone. The nexus displays the whole page in a smallified version, the iPhone just displays part of the page in a larger more readable format, and you just scroll to see more. The iphone approach works much better. 

Good speaker. It's loud compared to the iphone, which just whispers at you. I don't generally carry ear buds so I like that. 

How do you power cycle this thing? I couldn’t find anyway other than to reseat the battery. 

In general I find I like the web version of application like google docs than the app version. 

Twitter didn’t let me cancel from a failed sign in attempt. It just kept on spinning. It should let you cancel rather than burn power on retries. 

The google sync model of content in the cloud fits more naturally with my mental model compared to the apple’s device syncing via the icloud approach. But since I’ve never use icloud I may be wrong about that. How does android keep devices in sync? 

So, that’s just a few first impressions from a naive iphone user. While I don’t think the overall experience is as tight as the iphone, it has been just fine. The biggest win is 4g. That changes everything. Hopefully we can get some competition so that we can have fast and unlimited wireless at a reasonable price. The bigger screen is also a big win for me, so overall I’m happy. What could make me very unhappy is battery problems and if my signal problems get worse, it has been intermittent, which makes me worried. But there’s just another year until the iphone 5...﻿

Meer lezen (166 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-1TwlU3TFMHw/Tvz2VqgepII/AAAAAAAABBA/8rvxNpesZqg/w426-h320/samsung-galaxy-nexus-next-to-iphone-4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/100801061924982065053/albums/5735438182471103297/5735438179743906882</link><title>Will you see The Hobbit even if the reviews are bad?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Ga7h8edJVK0/T5heowbZPEI/AAAAAAABNew/TUDncWRFFt0/w426-h433/3129.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7084-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Burn%20after%20reading%20review/photos/100309716718451042779/albums/5997454836753232209/5997454834961697490?sqi=116640187442726311437&amp;sqsi=38916ac4-7e6a-4c0e-8d69-888334945661</link><title>BRIEF COMIC REVIEWS 
Oh my god, so very many comics this week I thought last week was a refreshing increase after a couple of quieter weeks. The gods of comic shipping must have heard me and decided that my wallet needed punishing as a result. It’s a great haul, though. 

A+X #18 
The final issue of the crossover title A+X brings us the last part of Cyclops + Captain America, a romp involving skrulls, Dr Doom, the uneasy alliance of the most uptight heroes in the Marvel universe and Cyclops in a cowboy hat. Some of the actions seem a little out of character, but it’s great to see how Cyclops and Captain America go from fighting to teamwork (and back to fighting) of course. There’s a solution to Tempus’ time-stopping from Uncanny X-Men and the casual banter of professionals who have had to part ways. Cap would rather Cyclops turn himself in than for a brawl to happen, Cyclops is aware that life isn’t as easy as that while he’s on a mission. Like the Wolverine &amp; The X-Men comic with Cyclops drinking with Logan, it’s nice to see him having interactions with his rivals which doesn’t just involve shouting and punching. 
The first story of the issue is a Kitty Pryde and Vision crossover, where the pair are lured into the long-abandoned Murderworld, stripped of their powers for unknown reasons and having to contend with what appear to be the ghosts of the people Arcade has murdered. I won’t spoil any of the twists, but this isn’t the best use of either character even though their similar power sets do make them an ideal team-up. Given that this involves Murderworld I’m pleased that there’s a good eye towards the continuity of both the past Arcade stories and Avengers Arena. 
As a whole A+X has been a series which could only go on a limited time. Anthologies don’t tend to last long in mainstream comics these days and it’s impressive that these fast and loose team-ups have managed to keep going. The creative teams have really differed and there have been some lovely little stories which wouldn’t fit anywhere else. In all it’s added more interesting content than fluff to the Avengers and X-Men stories, although there’s definitely been fluff. 

AMAZING X-MEN #5 
The final part of the search for Nightcrawler ends with some swashbuckling fun, a fight between tiny furry monsters and a few questions raised. The last few issues have reminded us how key Nightcrawler is, which combined with his status as a native of heaven and son of Azazel explains why the team are so quick to have him as captain of the Warship Xavier. Speaking of which he was an unexpected cameo in this story arc, giving disapproving looks to his students even from beyond the grave. There are several moving pieces in this story including the teachers from Wolverine &amp; The X-Men, the issue of Wolverine’s missing healing factor and the Bamfs warring against evil red Bamfs. Despite all of this, Jason Aaron is so innately familiar with the cast and the current situation in the Jean Grey School that he deftly tells a story with all these components which doesn’t need knowledge of all of them. The bit of news we all knew ends this story; Nightcrawler is back. The thing is, he has entered a pact with the Bamfs to do this and it’ll be interesting to see what the repercussions are. 
Ed McGuinness’ art continues to impress, having been mainly about blocky action figure-looking artwork when he was at DC, he’s come on a long way and provides distinctive, dynamic looks to the cast. There’s a great energy to the Nightcrawler/Azazel fight where they are fencing and teleporting through the scene. It’s easy to lose the sense of location on the ship but that barely matters when it looks so cool. 

AVENGERS #27 
The current Avengers storyline has sidelined our Avengers for a set of robot “Adaptoid” Avengers and some alternate reality Avengers who seemed like some pretty bad dudes whose reality was destroyed in the multiversal destruction cascade which has been going on in New Avengers. “Bad dudes” has been highlighted and emphasised in this issue as you get the tragedy of the lobotomised Bruce Banner and his tales of an Avengers team who took their world over. The fight between good and evil Avengers is fun, seeing how the different takes on each character deal with their alternate selves. The Avengers have been at this long enough that they can at least make quips about their evil selves (like the promotion General America gave himself in that world). Salvador Larroca makes the AIM beekeeper outfits look closer to The Tallest from Invader Zim in a good way, as well as having some clean art and nice visual differences between the different versions of each character to help us keep track of them. 

GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY #13 (THE TRIAL OF JEAN GREY PART SIX) 
The actual trial of Jean Grey lasted maybe one issue of this series, the rest being Jean in captivity and the combined X-Men and Guardians tracking her down. Jean ended last issue looking like she would give in to the judgement of the Shi’ar. Her stance is far better defined here as Jean’s had enough time to process her case. There’s a lot less punching in this issue, but there are a couple of great moments evocative of Moffat-era Doctor Who where the Doctor can talk or shout down an almost insurmountable foe simply with their reputation. Young Cyclops has a badass moment talking far beyond his actual capabilities. Jean has a Phoenix-style freakout which looks like it might be the advancement of her powers which would have happened if she wasn’t so intrinsically-tied to the Phoenix Force. Whatever it is, the strange pink glowing psychic energy form Jean gets not only seems to be vastly powerful but also only barely controllable. I like that this further cements this Jean Grey as her own character… although maybe it’s a portent to her becoming the Jean-Xorn from Battle of the Atom. 
Cyclops leaves the team this issue, something spoiled in solicitations and creating another rift in the originals. It’s a shame we’re not going to see any Laura/Scott interaction and where he, his adult self and Jean Grey all stand in this era. I’m sure he’ll return one day. 

HAWKEYE #18 
Clint Barton’s still bleeding from the head in his apartment building somewhere in New York, we saw some Kate, some metaphorical Christmas animals and now we’re back to Kate. Hopefully Clint won’t bleed out any time soon. 
Kate’s turn as a PI has been fairly inept, with her gay neighbours, dog and mysterious cat food PI man as helpers who kept her from killing herself or others. It’s not her fault, it’s difficult switching coasts and jobs, but now the slow build of Madame Masque’s revenge seems to have caught up with her. The old cat food PI, Harold H Harold, wants to leave LA and like previous cases has a twisted tale of the darkness in LA which has caused his current state. I love that hokey villains like Count Nefaria and Madame Masque can seem infinitely more threatening when they’re put in a relatively mundane setting like LA from a ground level. Maggie Wu’s art layouts seem more rigid than the strange and wonderful David Aja but her art definitely makes up for it. Like last week’s Superior Spider-Man annual the colour plays a large part in setting scenes and showing the climactic final page of the issue. The message Kate’s intercepted may bring the two stories back and I’m torn about her potential return to New York; Wu’s great artwork and the attempts of Kate to strike out on her own have been great but Clint really needs her help to keep his life… well, just his life right now. 

INDESTRUCTIBLE HULK #20 
Mark Waid is a great writer, but this issue still feels like a rushed conclusion to a series. We still didn’t quite get what made this series “indestructible” either, but overall this is still a good comic despite these gripes. The Humanity Bomb story closes with Jessup abducted by mad scientists (are there any other kind of scientist?) He’s going to permanently change into a rage vampire monster thing if he doesn’t keep his emotions in check, while the science team try to point Hulk at their enemies and let him do the rescuing with his fists. The story is told through Bruce’s not entirely honest report to Maria Hill, making a nice parallel to the first issue as it’s a kind of ‘exit interview’. Next issue, possibly next week, we have a new issue one and a new status quo. 

MARVEL KNIGHTS X-MEN #5 
So there used to be a comic called X-Men Unlimited back in the long, long ago. It featured odd little stories and often introduced one-off characters who wouldn’t turn up again. This feels like that kind of story. Everything wraps itself up neatly with good hallucinations summoned by the cast to fight the town’s worth of evil hallucinations. The two new mutants look like the kind who will vanish after the end of the story but only time will tell. Brahm’s art is weird and scratchy making for some interesting looks at the X-Men. The project feels very much like a reason for him to draw everything in the X-Verse and while that’s not great thing the story doesn’t feel like there was enough there to fill out five issues. 

NEW AVENGERS #16.NOW 
There’s been an a lot of repetition of scenes in New Avengers; we see a world and then it’s destroyed. Since issue one there’s been a lot of this with only a gap for Infinity. Recently the Illuminati have used Reed Richards’ reality bridge to check out the past and future of some realities which means we’ve had the same again but with small amounts of information added to the mix. This jump-on issue reiterates that we’ve seen realities fall to collisions with each other or to the sinister threats colonising and harvesting realities. Black Panther and Namor who are hardly the best of friends witness a very different reality. The cast of heroes in that world are less like the 616, being closer to the Squadron Supreme under the leadership of Sun God. They have had a Secret Invasion incident which killed a bunch of people and like the 616 crew they have seen the destruction of realities. Unlike our guys they seem to have been able to fight their way to victory. There’s even a great parallel speech to Reed’s from early in this run about how, “Everything Dies.” We’ve seen Reeds from all over the multiverse deliver similar speeches but with Sun God we finally see, “Everything Lives.” I have to wonder if this is going to make them allies or a massive threat as the story unfolds… 

ORIGIN II #4 
Gillen played me, and in an interesting way. The revelations are about what you expect from the typical Wolverine story, and indeed from the first Origin. James Howlett is on the run with Victor Creed and the burn-faced Clara. He’s trying not to have a savage PTSD freakout so often but that’s proved almost impossible so far. He and Clara finally get together, something which was pretty much expected after the last issues, deviating from the norm only because she doesn’t have red hair. Still, Nathaniel Essex’s army of Marauders attack and things go wrong for Clara in the same way that they tend to with everyone who gets off with Wolverine. He really needs to be more mindful of people around him. Still, it doesn’t quite go how you’d think. The end of the issue throws a nice twist which could have repercussions reaching into the present day. 
Adam Kubert’s people look almost identical to how they did back when he was an Ultimate X-Men artist, functional and distinctive but he’s not advanced much in that respect. He has however become fantastic with his backgrounds. Old time New York is beautifully-rendered and his use of the perspective of the frames in one page makes it look like we’re panning slowly around James and Clara as they talk. 

SATELLITE SAM #7 
I swear, this comic is Mad Men’s seedy little cousin sometimes. Michael White’s re-enacting the sexy photos his dad took, first with a pair of extras from the show and later with the single mother of a fan. This is getting to be a weird kink for Michael, after using the photos to try and find out who may have murdered his father. There’s a big revelation seven issues in as the motive someone may have had for killing Carlyle, the original Sam, is revealed. Everyone is a dick to Libby, the AD of the show, and the acting is about as bad as you expect when the cameras start to roll. I’ll admit with a cast this size I still have to flick back to the first page with the cast list to keep up with who everyone is, luckily Fraction makes all the descriptions fantastic each issue. 

SILVER SURFER #1 
“Beautifully insane” is the short review of this comic. Superior Spider-Man’s Dan Slott and the Magnificent Mike Allred kick off this new volume of Silver Surfer. The comic starts with Eve and Dawn, a pair of twins who are adventurous and homebound in that order. Eve travels the world while Dawn loved her home town and the B&amp;B her father runs. Her side of the story just screams ‘quirky manic pixie dream girl’ at the moment, but hopefully when she’s introduced to the main plot she’ll show more depth than that. 
The Silver Surfer is feared by many as the Herald of Galactus and trying to save civilisations to make up for those he led to the destruction of in his evil years. This isn’t angsty, forlorn superheroing though, his journey of redemption is a weird and wonderful exploration of the depths of space. After saving a micro-sun, Silver Surfer is summoned to an Impossible Palace to help them out with a problem which has claimed several champions before him. The palace is gorgeously and strangely illustrated by the Allreds. It’s full of psychedelic imagery of infinite markets, towers with their own moons, flowers to ski down… it’s like the weirdest offerings Kirby and Ditko had to offer kicked up a notch on the odd scale. 
The art is gorgeous, the story is strange and evidently very influenced by Doctor Who. There’s no need to know anything going into the comic so it’s a perfect jumping on point for people who want to experience a fun comic in the Marvel universe.. 

SUPERIOR SPIDER-MAN #30 (GOBLIN NATION PART FOUR) 
Okay, there will be spoilers. Seriously, I have things to talk about, skip to Uncanny Avengers if you don’t want to be spoiled about what happens in this comic. 
So if you’re still reading this review you’re okay to have the events of this issue spoiled? Good. 
So Otto Octavius is gone. The Goblin King has proven himself the perfect enemy to Otto because he knows exactly how Dr Octopus thinks. The Superior Spider-Man has been a supervillain solution to superhero problems, using the moral short absolutism of a villain and the resources like mechs, minions and a lair to keep ahead. The thing is, when the Goblin knows about all of those he can dismantle it. 
Dr Octopus decides that the best solution to the Goblin King is a simple one; bring back Peter Parker. Otto’s genius is not questioned; he won against Parker because he was smarter, he was taken down by the Goblin King because his smarts were predicted and when he kills himself to bring back Parker then it’s the smartest decision to make. He was superior, efficient, and now that Parker’s back it’ll be really interesting to see how he deals with the world he’s returned to. Ghost Parker’s return is expected but great, while he’s been lost in Otto’s past he reaches the point where Otto was forced to watch Peter’s memories after the original brain swap. This provokes him into thinking like Parker again. The double-page spread using panels from all over Spider-Man’s history has him tell us that he wants every tragedy and every triumph, that he loved being Spider-Man. I get the feeling this is going to be a mood which carries on in the new Amazing Spider-Man comic. 

UNCANNY AVENGERS #18.NOW 
This is apparently the first part of the last arc of this whole Apocalypse Twins thing. The remaining twin, Eimin, has apparently convinced all the mutants in the world that the Avengers caused the destruction of Earth, Wolverine, Rogue, Scarlet Witch, Wonder Man and I’m probably missing a few others. The only people who know the truth are Havok and Wasp who have a kid now because it’s the future and they’re the only sane ones. Well, Beast is on their side too, trying to use the technology he had in All-New X-Men to go back and stop this fiasco. The Brotherhood of Mutants are now “X-Force” and hunting Wasp &amp; Havok because they’re preaching that this world is a lie. Frankly after House of M, Age of Apocalypse and all that, if an X-Person says that reality is wrong I’d believe them. Still, the world is blindly fine accepting a stranger who abducted them and says Earth’s Mightiest Heroes killed the Earth. There’s a level of banter which tries a little too hard to be glib and makes everyone the same level of unfunny. 
The art is good though. Daniel Acuña has looked a bit odd and splotchy before but he’s perfect for this kind of science fiction looking story. The future city and daring chase is great, even if he have to look at Blob with most of his clothes off. 

THING OF THE WEEK 
Avengers #27 came bundled with Invaders #1 which seems okay as a premise. There are cosmic people who found out that in World War II Baron Strucker found a way to control a god, only the surviving Invaders know about it so they’re being hunted for the knowledge. I’m not a fan of the era or comics but it was an okay read. 
Superior Spider-Man #30 contained Black Widow #1 which was a really good fun spy story with gorgeous art by Phil Noto. Phil was made to draw these kind of action-packed spy adventures and the deceptive, mercurial Black Widow is fun to read even though she seems elusive even as a protagonist. 

COMIC OF THE WEEK 
Superior Spider-Man #30 is my book of the week and it’s a really difficult choice this week. Silver Surfer was a perfect first issue, Guardians of the Galaxy a perfect finale to a crossover. Still, Superior Spider-Man showed us the culmination of Otto’s journey and made him bring Peter back. It’s a perfect move for a villain who has definitely done as the mission statements (Marvel’s and his) and shown him not only as ‘superior’ but also as a redeemed villain.﻿

Meer lezen (307 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7084_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Dooy-plLBm4/Uzs9ZYJXStI/AAAAAAAAEqQ/I1aUmQTtr3U/w426-h318/photo.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>