<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7086">falsifying pictures 21st centurie</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 15:38:46" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/116078767850550744794/albums/6014892166790981649/6014892168281522130</link><title>"Russia-China cooperation has reached its highest level ever, Russian President Vladimir Putin has said in an interview with Chinese media on the eve of his visit to Shanghai, where a record package of documents is expected to be signed by the two nations. 
Below is the full transcript of the Russian president’s interview with Chinese Central Television, Xinhua news agency, China News Service, The People's Daily, China Radio International, and Phoenix Television. 
Question: What are your expectations concerning the upcoming visit to China? What results do you expect from the Summit of the Conference on Interaction and Confidence Building Measures in Asia in Shanghai? 
Vladimir Putin: I am always happy to visit hospitable China. It is a pleasure to see how our neighbour is transforming right before our eyes. Shanghai is a vivid illustration of this. 
Establishing closer ties with the People’s Republic of China – our trusted friend – is Russia's unconditional foreign policy priority. 
Now Russia-China cooperation is advancing to a new stage of comprehensive partnership and strategic interaction. It would not be wrong to say that it has reached the highest level in all its centuries-long history. 
I am looking forward to a new meeting with President of China Xi Jinping, with whom I have good working and personal relations. We will discuss how previous agreements are being implemented and outline new objectives for the future. I am sure that the upcoming talks will give a powerful impetus to further strengthening of bilateral cooperation in all areas and deeper coordination in the international arena. The summit’s results and future plans will be reflected in the Joint Statement by the Heads of State and a strong package of documents expected to be signed during the visit. 
Russia and China have actively advocated establishing a new security and sustainable development architecture in the Asia-Pacific. It should be based on the principles of equality, respect for international law, indivisibility of security, non-use of force or threat of force. Today this task is becoming increasingly important. The forthcoming Summit of the Conference on Interaction and Confidence Building Measures in Asia (CICA) serves to contribute to addressing this task. 
CICA is a well-established cooperation mechanism. It has been successfully working in such spheres as security, new challenges and threats, economy, environmental protection and humanitarian issues, all of which are important for the region. 
Russia has taken an active part in CICA’s activities. In mid-April 2014, members of the Conference approved the Statute of the CICA Business Council sponsored by Russia. I am confident that the launch of the Council will enhance practical ties between business communities of the Asian countries. 
At the upcoming summit, the Secretariats of CICA and SCO are expected to sign a Memorandum of Understanding. That would serve as another step towards shaping a framework of partnerships between this region’s organisations and forums. 
Q: China is consistently making progress towards the "Chinese dream", i.e. a great national rebirth. Russia has also set a goal of restoring a powerful state. How, in your opinion, could our countries interact and help each other in fulfilling these tasks? What areas can be prioritised in this regard? 
VP: Promotion of friendly and good-neighbourly partnership relations is fully consistent with the interests of both Russia and China. We do not have any political issues left which could impede the enhancement of our comprehensive cooperation. 
Through joint efforts, we have established a truly exemplary collaboration, which should become a model for major world powers. 
It is based on respect for the fundamental interests of each other and efficient work for the benefit of the peoples of our two countries. 
Russia and China successfully cooperate in the international arena and closely coordinate their steps to address international challenges and crises. Our positions on the main global and regional issues are similar or even identical. 
It is encouraging that both sides are willing to further deepen their cooperation. Both Moscow and Beijing are well aware that our countries have not exhausted their potentials. We have a way to go. The priority areas of collaboration at the current stage include the expansion of economic ties and cooperation in science and high-technology sector. Such pooling of capacities is very helpful in fulfilling the tasks of domestic development of our countries. 
Q: Cooperation between China and Russia has been steadily increasing, but uncertainties in global economy persist. The emerging markets are faced with new challenges and slowdown of economic growth. How can our two countries help each other to counter these challenges? How can we ensure steady increase of mutual trade and reciprocal investments? 
VP: In the context of turbulent global economy, the strengthening of mutually beneficial trade and economic ties, as well as the increase of investment flows between Russia and China are of paramount importance. This is not just a crucial element of socioeconomic development of our countries, but a contribution to the efforts aimed at stabilising the entire global market. 
Today, Russia firmly places China at the top of its foreign trade partners. 
In 2013, the volume of bilateral trade was close to $90 billion, which is far from being the limit. We will try to increase trade turnover to $100 billion by 2015 and up to $200 billion by 2020. 
Our countries successfully cooperate in the energy sector. We steadily move towards the establishment of a strategic energy alliance. A large‑scale project worth over $60 billion is underway to supply China with crude oil via the Skovorodino-Mohe pipeline. 
The arrangements on export of Russian natural gas to China have been nearly finalised. Their implementation will help Russia to diversify pipeline routes for natural gas supply, and our Chinese partners to alleviate the concerns related to energy deficit and environmental security through the use of "clean" fuel. 
At the same time, we are working actively to reduce dependence of bilateral trade on external market conditions. Therefore, in order to develop trade and economic cooperation we pay particular attention to the breakthrough areas such as higher energy efficiency, environmental protection, production of drugs and medical equipment, developing new information technologies, as well as nuclear energy and outer space. 
We implement a list of joint projects in 40 priority areas with total investments of about $20 billion. 
These areas include civil aircraft industry. An agreement has been reached on joint design of a wide-body long-range aircraft. In the future we will develop a heavy helicopter. I am sure that our companies can manufacture and supply competitive products to the world markets. 
We also intend to actively develop investment cooperation, the scope of which obviously does not meet real capacities and needs of our countries yet. We have examples of successful projects. I would like to note the participation of Chinese capital in the reconstruction of an airport in the Kaluga Region and building of plants for production of automotive parts and construction materials in that Russian constituent entity. 
To our mind, there are many other promising areas for investments. We can point to different branches of machine engineering, processing of agricultural products, mining operations, and development of transport and energy infrastructure. 
We must also strengthen financial cooperation and protect ourselves from exchange-rate fluctuations among the world's major currencies. Therefore, we are now considering how to increase mutual settlements in national currencies. 
Q: Russia has recently announced the creation of a special economic zone in Vladivostok. What could, in your view, be the role of China in its creation and in the development of the Russian Far East as a whole? 
VP: Accelerated socioeconomic development of Siberia and the Far East is one of Russia's key national priorities for the 21st century. We are now implementing a whole package of programmes to modernise and upgrade transport, energy and social infrastructure in these regions. 
We are aiming at the creation of special areas of advanced economic development with an investment-friendly environment. 
Competitive conditions for launching export-oriented enterprises in non-primary sectors have been created. 
In the areas of advanced development, new companies will enjoy some substantial benefits. These are tax holidays with respect to a number of taxes and reduced insurance premium rates; liberalisation of the customs regime, including free customs zones; special rules for access to land and for connecting to infrastructure facilities. 
Today, the relevant federal law is being finalised. Development institutions are being created and promising centres are being selected. One of them will probably be established in Vladivostok on Russky Island where the APEC 2012 Summit took place. 
Obviously, we are interested in Chinese businessmen making use of these opportunities and becoming one of the leaders here, since both Russia and China will benefit from an accelerated development of the Russian Far East. 
It is important not to limit our relations to trade. It is essential to establish strong technological and industrial alliances; attract investments to the infrastructure and energy sectors; to jointly promote scientific research and humanitarian contacts; lay a solid foundation for a sustainable long-term development of our trade and economic relations. And the Russian Far East can and must become a natural venue for the said efforts. 
Q: How would you rate the present level of cooperation between our countries in the humanitarian sphere and its prospects? Which projects within the framework of reciprocal theme years (national, language, tourism, youth exchanges) have impressed you most? 
VP: The humanitarian contacts between Russia and China are in keeping with the steady development of the whole complex of strategic partnership relations between our countries. At the moment, their level is as high as never before. The major projects of national, language and tourism theme years in which millions of our citizens participated, have played a significant role in that. 
It is noteworthy that a number of events are now being carried out on a regular basis. These are festivals of culture, film weeks, youth sports games, student festivals, camps for schoolchildren and students, fora for university principals, exhibitions of educational services and many other events. 
An intergovernmental project of the Russia-China Youth Friendly Exchanges Years planned for 2014–2015 was launched this March. The performance of the recently created Russian-Chinese philharmonic youth orchestra, headed by the artistic director and principal conductor of the Mariinsky Theatre Valery Gergiev, has become a highlight of the theme years’ launch in St Petersburg. 
Of course, we are not going to settle down. The mutual interest of youth in history, culture and traditions of the peoples of China and Russia is increasing. It is an objective process, and we are committed to fully supporting it in the future. 
Q: In 2015, our countries will celebrate the 70th anniversary of Victory over fascism. What is the impact of joint Russian-Chinese efforts to oppose the attempts aimed at challenging the results of World War II? 
VP: It is true that the attempts to rewrite and distort history are becoming more frequent. 
Four years ago Russia and China adopted a Joint Statement on the 65th Anniversary of Victory in the Second World War. 
We share an idea that it is unacceptable to revise the results of the war, as the consequences will be extremely grave. 
It is clearly evident from the tragic events currently unfolding in Ukraine, where violent neo-Nazis are waging a real campaign of terror against civilians. 
I would like to express my gratitude to our Chinese friends for cherishing the memory of thousands of our compatriots, who sacrificed their lives to liberate Northeast China from invaders. 
Next year we will hold a range of joint events to mark the 70th anniversary of Victory both in the bilateral and the SCO format. During these events, youth will be in the focus of our work. 
We will certainly continue to oppose attempts to falsify history, heroize fascists and their accomplices, blacken the memory and reputation of heroic liberators." 

Source:  http://rt.com/news/159804-putin-china-visit-interview/﻿

Meer lezen (208 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-N_F5d1rSRdk/U3kwjwyy_9I/AAAAAAABDpo/vHAk9T7oetg/w426-h280/Russia+China+ties+are+the+highest.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/108583689259233675704/albums/5961242638933063505/5961242643157985986</link><title>PART 2.  It is believed the pyramid was built as a tomb for fourth dynasty Egyptian pharaoh Khufu and was constructed over a 20 year period. Khufu's vizier, Hemon, or Hemiunu, is believed by some to be the architect of the Great Pyramid.[4] It is thought that, at construction, the Great Pyramid was originally 280 Egyptian cubits tall, 146.5 metres (480.6 ft) but with erosion and absence of its pyramidion, its present height is 138.8 metres (455.4 ft). Each base side was 440 cubits, 230.4 metres (755.9 ft) long. The mass of the pyramid is estimated at 5.9 million tonnes. The volume, including an internal hillock, is roughly 2,500,000 cubic metres (88,000,000 cu ft). Based on these estimates, building this in 20 years would involve installing approximately 800 tonnes of stone every day. Similarly, since it consists of an estimated 2.3 million blocks, completing the building in 20 years would involve moving an average of more than 12 of the blocks into place each hour, day and night. The first precision measurements of the pyramid were made by Egyptologist Sir Flinders Petrie in 1880–82 and published as The Pyramids and Temples of Gizeh. Almost all reports are based on his measurements. Many of the casing stones and inner chamber blocks of the Great Pyramid were fit together with extremely high precision. Based on measurements taken on the north eastern casing stones, the mean opening of the joints is only 0.5 millimetres wide (1/50th of an inch). 

Great Pyramid of Giza from a 19th-century stereopticon card photo 
The pyramid remained the tallest man-made structure in the world for over 3,800 years, unsurpassed until the 160-metre-tall (520 ft) spire of Lincoln Cathedral was completed c. 1300. The accuracy of the pyramid's workmanship is such that the four sides of the base have an average error of only 58 millimetres in length. The base is horizontal and flat to within ±15 mm (0.6 in). The sides of the square base are closely aligned to the four cardinal compass points (within 4 minutes of arc) based on true north, not magnetic north, and the finished base was squared to a mean corner error of only 12 seconds of arc. The completed design dimensions, as suggested by Petrie's survey and subsequent studies, are estimated to have originally been 280 cubits high by 440 cubits long at each of the four sides of its base. The ratio of the perimeter to height of 1760/280 cubits equates to 2π to an accuracy of better than 0.05% (corresponding to the well-known approximation of π as 22/7). Some Egyptologists consider this to have been the result of deliberate design proportion. Verner wrote, "We can conclude that although the ancient Egyptians could not precisely define the value of π, in practice they used it". Petrie, author of Pyramids and Temples of Gizeh concluded: "but these relations of areas and of circular ratio are so systematic that we should grant that they were in the builder's design". Others have argued that the Ancient Egyptians had no concept of pi and would not have thought to encode it in their monuments. They believe that the observed pyramid slope may be based on a simple seked slope choice alone, with no regard to the overall size and proportions of the finished building. The Great Pyramid consists of an estimated 2.3 million limestone blocks which most believe to have been transported from nearby quarries. The Tura limestone used for the casing was quarried across the river. The largest granite stones in the pyramid, found in the "King's" chamber, weigh 25 to 80 tonnes and were transported from Aswan, more than 800 km (497 mi) away. Traditionally, ancient Egyptians cut stone blocks by hammering wooden wedges into the stone which were then soaked with water. As the water was absorbed, the wedges expanded, causing the rock to crack. Once they were cut, they were carried by boat either up or down the Nile River to the pyramid. It is estimated that 5.5 million tonnes of limestone, 8,000 tonnes of granite (imported from Aswan), and 500,000 tonnes of mortar were used in the construction of the Great Pyramid 
At completion, the Great Pyramid was surfaced by white "casing stones" – slant-faced, but flat-topped, blocks of highly polished white limestone. These were carefully cut to what is approximately a face slope with a seked of 5½ palms to give the required dimensions. Visibly, all that remains is the underlying stepped core structure seen today. In AD 1300, a massive earthquake loosened many of the outer casing stones, which were then carted away by Bahri Sultan An-Nasir Nasir-ad-Din al-Hasan in 1356 to build mosques and fortresses in nearby Cairo. The stones can still be seen as parts of these structures. Later explorers reported massive piles of rubble at the base of the pyramids left over from the continuing collapse of the casing stones, which were subsequently cleared away during continuing excavations of the site. Nevertheless, a few of the casing stones from the lowest course can be seen to this day in situ around the base of the Great Pyramid, and display the same workmanship and precision that has been reported for centuries. Petrie also found a different orientation in the core and in the casing measuring 193 centimetres ± 25 centimetres. He suggested a redetermination of north was made after the construction of the core, but a mistake was made, and the casing was built with a different orientation.Petrie related the precision of the casing stones as to being "equal to opticians' work of the present day, but on a scale of acres" and "to place such stones in exact contact would be careful work; but to do so with cement in the joints seems almost impossible". It has been suggested it was the mortar (Petrie's "cement") that made this seemingly impossible task possible, providing a level bed which enabled the masons to set the stones exactly 
Many alternative, often contradictory, theories have been proposed regarding the pyramid's construction techniques. Many disagree on whether the blocks were dragged, lifted, or even rolled into place. The Greeks believed that slave labour was used, but modern discoveries made at nearby workers' camps associated with construction at Giza suggest it was built instead by tens of thousands of skilled workers. Verner posited that the labour was organized into a hierarchy, consisting of two gangs of 100,000 men, divided into five zaa or phyle of 20,000 men each, which may have been further divided according to the skills of the workers. 
One mystery of the pyramid's construction is its planning. John Romer suggests that they used the same method that had been used for earlier and later constructions, laying out parts of the plan on the ground at a 1-to-1 scale. He writes that "such a working diagram would also serve to generate the architecture of the pyramid with precision unmatched by any other means." He also argues for a 14-year time span for its construction. 
A modern construction management study, in association with Mark Lehner and other Egyptologists, estimated that the total project required an average workforce of 14,567 people and a peak workforce of 40,000. Without the use of pulleys, wheels, or iron tools, they used critical path analysis to suggest the Great Pyramid was completed from start to finish in approximately 10 years 
New evidence regarding pyramid's construction has recently been found at the site of the ancient port of Wadi al-Jarf on the Red Sea coast of Egypt. An archeological team led by Pierre Tallet (University Paris IV-La Sorbonne) restarted work there in 2011. 
Large limestone slabs inscribed with Khufu' name were found, as well as some well preserved papyri. The majority of these documents date to the 27th year of Khufu's reign and describe how the central administration sent food and supplies for large work teams. 
The diary of Merrer, an official involved in the building of the Great Pyramid, was discovered. Using the diary, researchers were able to reconstruct three months of his life, providing new insight into everyday lives of people at the time. The papyri are the oldest ever found in Egypt 
The original entrance to the Great Pyramid is 17 metres (56 ft) vertically above ground level and 7.29 metres (23.9 ft) east of the center line of the pyramid. From this original entrance there is a Descending Passage 0.96 metres (3.1 ft) high and 1.04 metres (3.4 ft) wide which goes down at an angle of 26° 31'23" through the masonry of the pyramid and then into the bedrock beneath it. After 105.23 metres (345.2 ft), the passage becomes level and continues for an additional 8.84 metres (29.0 ft) to the lower Chamber, which appears not to have been finished. There is a continuation of the horizontal passage in the south wall of the lower chamber; there is also a pit dug in the floor of the chamber. Some Egyptologists suggest this Lower Chamber was intended to be the original burial chamber, but Pharaoh Khufu later changed his mind and wanted it to be higher up in the pyramid. 
At 28.2 metres (93 ft) from the entrance is a square hole in the roof of the Descending Passage. Originally concealed with a slab of stone, this is the beginning of the Ascending Passage. The Ascending Passage is 39.3 metres (129 ft) long, as wide and high as the Descending Passage and slopes up at almost precisely the same angle. The lower end of the Ascending Passage is closed by three huge blocks of granite, each about 1.5 metres (4.9 ft) long. At the start of the Grand Gallery on the right-hand side there is a hole cut in the wall, (and now blocked by chicken wire). This is the start of a vertical shaft which follows an irregular path through the masonry of the pyramid to join the Descending Passage. Also at the start of the Grand Gallery there is a Horizontal Passage leading to the "Queen's Chamber". The passage is 1.1m (3'8") high for most of its length, but near the chamber there is a step in the floor, after which the passage is 1.73 metres (5.7 ft) high. 
The Queen's Chamber is exactly half-way between the north and south faces of the pyramid and measures 5.75 metres (18.9 ft) north to south, 5.23 metres (17.2 ft) east to west, and has a pointed roof with an apex 6.23 metres (20.4 ft) above the floor. At the eastern end of the chamber there is a niche 4.67 metres (15.3 ft) high. The original depth of the niche was 1.04 metres (3.4 ft), but has since been deepened by treasure hunters. 
In the north and south walls of the Queen's Chamber there are shafts, which unlike those in the King's Chamber that immediately slope upwards, are horizontal for around 2 m (6.6 ft) before sloping upwards. The horizontal distance was cut in 1872 by a British engineer, Waynman Dixon, who believed a similar shaft to the King's Chamber must also exist. He was proved right, but because the shafts are not connected to the outer faces of the pyramid or the Queen's Chamber, their purpose is unknown. At the end of one of his shafts, Dixon discovered a ball of black diorite (a type of rock) and a bronze implement of unknown purpose. Both objects are currently in the British Museum. 
The shafts in the Queen's Chamber were explored in 1992 by the German engineer Rudolf Gantenbrink using a crawler robot he designed, Upuaut 2. After a climb of 65 m (213 ft) he discovered that one of the shafts was blocked by limestone "doors" with two eroded copper "handles". Some years later the National Geographic Society created a similar robot which drilled a small hole in the southern door, only to find another larger door behind it. The northern passage, which was difficult to navigate because of twists and turns, was also found to be blocked by a door. 
Research continued in 2011 with the Djedi Project. Realizing the problem was that the National Geographic Society's camera was only able to see straight ahead of it, they instead used a fiber-optic "micro snake camera" that could see around corners. With this they were able to penetrate the first door of the northern shaft and view all the sides of the small chamber behind it. They discovered hieroglyphs written in red paint. They were also able to scrutinize the inside of the two copper "handles" embedded in the door, and they now believe them to be for decorative purposes. They also found the reverse side of the "door" to be finished and polished, which suggests that it was not put there just to block the shaft from debris, but rather for a more specific reason 
The Grand Gallery continues the slope of the Ascending Passage, but is 8.6 metres (28 ft) high and 46.68 metres (153.1 ft) long. At the base it is 2.06 metres (6.8 ft) wide, but after 2.29 metres (7.5 ft) the blocks of stone in the walls are corbelled inwards by 7.6 centimetres (3.0 in) on each side. There are seven of these steps, so at the top the Grand Gallery is only 1.04 metres (3.4 ft) wide. It is roofed by slabs of stone laid at a slightly steeper angle than the floor of the gallery, so that each stone fits into a slot cut in the top of the gallery like the teeth of a ratchet. The purpose was to have each block supported by the wall of the Gallery rather than resting on the block beneath it, which would have resulted in an unacceptable cumulative pressure at the lower end of the Gallery. 
At the upper end of the Gallery on the right-hand side there is a hole near the roof which opens into a short tunnel by which access can be gained to the lowest of the Relieving Chambers. The other Relieving Chambers were discovered in 1837/8 by Colonel Howard Vyse and J. S. Perring, who dug tunnels upwards using blasting powder. 
The floor of the Grand Gallery consists of a shelf or step on either side, 51 centimetres (20 in) wide, leaving a lower ramp 1.04 metres (3.4 ft) wide between them. In the shelves there are 54 slots, 27 on each side matched by vertical and horizontal slots in the walls of the Gallery. These form a cross shape that rises out of the slot in the shelf. The purpose of these slots is not known, but the central gutter in the floor of the Gallery, which is the same width as the Ascending Passage, has led to speculation that the blocking stones were stored in the Grand Gallery and the slots held wooden beams to restrain them from sliding down the passage. This, in turn, has led to the proposal that originally many more than 3 blocking stones were intended, to completely fill the Ascending Passage. 
At the top of the Grand Gallery there is a step giving onto a horizontal passage approximately 1.02 metres (3.3 ft) long, in which can be detected four slots, three of which were probably intended to hold granite portcullises. Fragments of granite found by Petrie in the Descending Passage may have come from these now-vanished doors. 
The King's Chamber is 10.47 metres (34.4 ft) from east to west and 5.234 metres (17.17 ft) north to south. It has a flat roof 5.974 metres (19.60 ft) above the floor. 0.91 m (3.0 ft) above the floor there are two narrow shafts in the north and south walls (one is now filled by an extractor fan in an attempt to circulate air inside the pyramid). The purpose of these shafts is not clear: they appear to be aligned toward stars or areas of the northern and southern skies, yet one of them follows a dog-leg course through the masonry, indicating no intention to directly sight stars through them. They were long believed by Egyptologists to be "air shafts" for ventilation, but this idea has now been widely abandoned in favour of the shafts serving a ritualistic purpose associated with the ascension of the king’s spirit to the heavens. 
The King's Chamber is entirely faced with granite. Above the roof, which is formed of nine slabs of stone weighing in total about 400 tons, are five compartments known as Relieving Chambers. The first four, like the King's Chamber, have flat roofs formed by the floor of the chamber above, but the final chamber has a pointed roof. Vyse suspected the presence of upper chambers when he found that he could push a long reed through a crack in the ceiling of the first chamber. From lower to upper, the chambers are known as "Davison's Chamber", "Wellington's Chamber", "Nelson's Chamber", "Lady Arbuthnot's Chamber", and "Campbell's Chamber". It is believed that the compartments were intended to safeguard the King's Chamber from the possibility of a roof collapsing under the weight of stone above the Chamber. As the chambers were not intended to be seen, they were not finished in any way and a few of the stones still retain masons' marks painted on them. One of the stones in Campbell's Chamber bears a mark, apparently the name of a work gang, which incorporates the only reference in the pyramid to Pharaoh Khufu. 

The entrance of the Pyramid 
The only object in the King's Chamber is a rectangular granite sarcophagus, one corner of which is broken. The sarcophagus is slightly larger than the Ascending Passage, which indicates that it must have been placed in the Chamber before the roof was put in place. Unlike the fine masonry of the walls of the Chamber, the sarcophagus is roughly finished, with saw marks visible in several places. This is in contrast with the finely finished and decorated sarcophagi found in other pyramids of the same period. Petrie suggested that such a sarcophagus was intended but was lost in the river on the way north from Aswan and a hurriedly-made replacement was used instead. 
Today tourists enter the Great Pyramid via the Robbers' Tunnel dug by workmen employed by Caliph al-Ma'mun around AD 820. The tunnel is cut straight through the masonry of the pyramid for approximately 27 metres (89 ft), then turns sharply left to encounter the blocking stones in the Ascending Passage. Unable to remove these stones, the workmen tunnelled up beside them through the softer limestone of the Pyramid until they reached the Ascending Passage. It is possible to enter the Descending Passage from this point, but access is usually forbidden 
The Great Pyramid is surrounded by a complex of several buildings including small pyramids. The Pyramid Temple, which stood on the east side of the pyramid and measured 52.2 metres (171 ft) north to south and 40 metres (130 ft) east to west, has almost entirely disappeared apart from the black basalt paving. There are only a few remnants of the causeway which linked the pyramid with the valley and the Valley Temple. The Valley Temple is buried beneath the village of Nazlet el-Samman; basalt paving and limestone walls have been found but the site has not been excavated. The basalt blocks show "clear evidence" of having been cut with some kind of saw with an estimated cutting blade of 15 feet (4.6 m) in length, capable of cutting at a rate of 1.5 inches (38 mm) per minute. John Romer suggests this "super saw" may have had copper teeth and weighed up to 300 pounds (140 kg). He theorizes such a saw could have been attached to a wooden trestle and possibly used in conjunction with vegetable oil, cutting sand, emery or pounded quartz to cut the blocks, which would have required the labour of at least a dozen men to operate it. 
On the south side are the subsidiary pyramids, popularly known as Queens' Pyramids. Three remain standing to nearly full height but the fourth was so ruined that its existence was not suspected until the recent discovery of the first course of stones and the remains of the capstone. Hidden beneath the paving around the pyramid was the tomb of Queen Hetepheres I, sister-wife of Sneferu and mother of Khufu. Discovered by accident by the Reisner expedition, the burial was intact, though the carefully sealed coffin proved to be empty. 

Group photo of Australian 11th Battalion soldiers on the Great Pyramid in 1915. 

Aerial photography, taken from Eduard Spelterini's balloon on 21 November 1904 
The Giza pyramid complex, which includes among other structures the pyramids of Khufu, Khafre and Menkaure, is surrounded by a cyclopean stone wall, the Wall of the Crow. Mark Lehner has discovered a worker's town outside of the wall, otherwise known as "The Lost City", dated by pottery styles, seal impressions, and stratigraphy to have been constructed and occupied sometime during the reigns of Khafre (2520–2494 BC) and Menkaure (2490–2472 BC). In the early 1970s, the Australian archaeologist Karl Kromer excavated a mound in the South Field of the plateau. This mound contained artifacts including mudbrick seals of Khufu, which he identified with an artisans' settlement. Mudbrick buildings just south of Khufu's Valley Temple contained mud sealings of Khufu and have been suggested to be a settlement serving the cult of Khufu after his death. A worker's cemetery used at least between Khufu's reign and the end of the Fifth Dynasty was discovered south of the Wall of the Crow by Zahi Hawass in 1990 
There are three boat-shaped pits around the pyramid, of a size and shape to have held complete boats, though so shallow that any superstructure, if there ever was one, must have been removed or disassembled. In May 1954, the Egyptian archaeologist Kamal el-Mallakh discovered a fourth pit, a long, narrow rectangle, still covered with slabs of stone weighing up to 15 tons. Inside were 1,224 pieces of wood, the longest 23 metres (75 ft) long, the shortest 10 centimetres (0.33 ft). These were entrusted to a native boat builder, Haj Ahmed Yusuf, who slowly and methodically worked out how the pieces fit together. The entire process, including conservation and straightening of the warped wood, took fourteen years. 
The result is a cedar-wood boat 43.6 metres (143 ft) long, its timbers held together by ropes, which is now currently housed in a special boat-shaped, air-conditioned museum beside the pyramid. During construction of this museum, which stands above the boat pit, a second sealed boat pit was discovered. It was deliberately left unopened until 2011 when excavation began on the boat 
Although succeeding pyramids were smaller, pyramid building continued until the end of the Middle Kingdom. However, as authors Briar and Hobbs claim, "all the pyramids were robbed" by the New Kingdom, when the construction of royal tombs in a desert valley, now known as the Valley of the Kings, began.Joyce Tyldesley states that the Great Pyramid itself "is known to have been opened and emptied by the Middle Kingdom", before the Arab caliph Abdullah al-Mamun entered the pyramid around AD 820. 
I. E. S. Edwards discusses Strabo's mention that the pyramid "a little way up one side has a stone that may be taken out, which being raised up there is a sloping passage to the foundations." Edwards suggested that the pyramid was entered by robbers after the end of the Old Kingdom and sealed and then reopened more than once until Strabo's door was added. He adds: "If this highly speculative surmise be correct, it is also necessary to assume either that the existence of the door was forgotten or that the entrance was again blocked with facing stones", in order to explain why al-Ma'mun could not find the entrance. 
He also discusses a story told by Herodotus. Herodotus visited Egypt in the 5th century BC and recounts a story he was told about vaults under the pyramid built upon an island where the body of Cheops lies. Edwards notes that the pyramid had "almost certainly been opened and its contents plundered long before the time of Herodotus" and that it might have been closed again during the Twenty-sixth dynasty of Egypt when other monuments were restored. He suggests that the story told to Herodotus could have been the result of almost two centuries of telling and retelling by Pyramid guides 
Because of their fame, Khufu and his pyramid are object of several modern receptions, similar to kings and queens such as Akhenaten, Nefertiti and Tutankhamen. Khufu's historical figure appears in movies, novels and documentations. Already in 1827, female science fiction author Jane C. Loudon wrote the novel The Mummy! A Tale of the 22nd Century. The story describes the citizens of the 22nd century, which became technologically advanced on one side, but unanimously immoral on the other side. In the story, only the mummy of Khufu can save them. In 1939, Nagib Mahfuz wrote the novel Khufu's Wisdom, which leans on the stories of Papyrus Westcar; In 1997, French author Guy Brachet composed the novel series Le roman des pyramides, including five volumes, of which the first two (Le temple soleil and Rêve de pierre) are picking out Khufu and his tomb as a theme. In 2004, Page Bryant wrote the Sci-Fi story The Second Coming of the Star Gods, which deals with Khufu's alleged celestial origin. The novel The Legend of The Vampire Khufu, written by Raymond Mayotte in 2010, deals with king Khufu awakening in his pyramid as a vampire. 
Well known cinematic movies, which deal with Khufu or at least have the Great Pyramid as a theme, are Howard Hawks' Land of the Pharaohs from 1955, a fictional account of the building of the Great Pyramid of Khufu, and Roland Emmerich's Stargate from 1994, in which an extraterrestrial device is found near the pyramids. 
Khufu and his pyramid are furthermore object of pseudoscientific theories which deal with the idea that Khufu's pyramid was built with the help of extraterrestrials and that Khufu simply seized and re-used the monument, ignoring all archaeological evidences or even falsifying them. 
Khufu and his pyramid are even thematized in several computer games such as Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation, in which the player must enter Khufu's pyramid and face the god Seth as the final boss.﻿

Meer lezen (404 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-D8QMlfl5uQE/UrqWmZVXqsI/AAAAAAAADJc/fQs5WHMAibA/w426-h251/imagesYK8EDPEV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/115356803742267309917/albums/5798821363331581393/5798821367530678290</link><title>How To Detect And Void A Nigerian Scam Fraudster - 419 
 WHAT DO YOU THINK OF NIGERIANS ? 
I will address the problem of Nigerian fraudsters, more so, how to combat the global menace and raise the public awareness on finding solutions. 
As a Nigerian, this negative image of my country is very disturbing. I wonder about my country, in my days as student in Mushin boy's high school Okota Lagos I lived and grew up among the rascals and hoodlums in Mushin Lagos, though I am from a humble background, my condition then was to juxtapose, my social life was unbearable our peer discussion was either women or money, we all sought greener pastors abroad to take advantage of foreign nationals either by marriage to secure a foreign stay or get hold of Their credit cards in order to zero Their accounts. was our further motive, several young men specialize in document falsification in those days the center of forgery was the popular "Oluwole market" in Lagos island, at a low cost you can change ownership passport, you can Obtain any European country international traveling passports, American traveling documents even flood the market up to the year 2000 you can always forge any documents in "Oluwole market." This market is not a hidden place, and to the knowledge of Both were and federal agencies. This place is the birthplace and the genesis of Nigerian 419 scam and all fraudulent activities perpetrated by Nigerian and neighboring countries in all parts of the world. This market have flourished for over 30 years and presently, the Nigerian economic and financial crime commission have invaded and Decentralized fraudulent activities while the Lagos government were recruit and gave the market a new face lift Why Do Fraudsters Still Flourish Flourish. Today I ask myself the question is why do these fraudsters still flourish? The answer is multifaceted but we can say in one word "corruption". Most fraudsters arrested still walk freely on the street, they buy their freedom With Their Loots, they manipulate Their family, friends and acquaintance in government to become untouchable in our societies, most fraud cases are in connivance with top government officials, They provide them with government procedures, official secrets, letterheads, stamps and government signature specimens and more so they guide them on the modus operandi of how to sucessfully perpetrated the crime. They pose as fake officials of government, banks, multinational companies and CAN in Nigeria. View on Nigerian Fraud As in Nigeria, we do not see fraudulent ways of making money as abnormal. If our brothers travel abroad and make money from credit card scam drug trafficking, the Society Recognizes them as senior citizens worthy of chieftaincy title and our universities than decorated with honorary degrees. In the social gathering praise singers and musician announce Their names to a dancing ovation, they acknowledge These praise singers with monies in Thousands in Both local and international currencies, just to arrest praise singer in Nigeria and you will get the full list of fraudsters and drug barons. The local government name streets after them and Institutions. Shockingly, most of political office holders make Their money from this organized financial fraud, among them were sponsored by These fraudsters. As a Nigerian That we all know most of our leaders are fraudulent, we all can not deny this truth. Most of them work as government officials before Their election but prior to Elected office they live in palatial mansions in choice areas in Nigerian assets with runing into hundred of millions, countless members of staff and landed properties in Nigeria and oversea. Their Loots were from government treasuries and international scams, but Because our society and most Nigerians do not see it as abnormal, we ignore Their inglorious path to prosperity, we celebrate them and use them as role models to our children, as this tradition have to stay ever since our independence in 1960. An average Nigerian will rather look for similar opportunity to get rich quickly rather than sourcing for a System That Will confiscated the loot of the "thief." In the 1980's Nigeria financial experts established businesses businesses businesses businesses businesses Financial Houses right before my eyes These experts established businesses businesses businesses businesses businesses financial houses and swindled the poor of Their meager income with the hope of Obtaining loans, the Abacha government came, arrested, jailed and today most of These bankers and accountants and banks still Such as our head, still remains business as usual. majors in our beliefs, visions, ethics, societal norms and values, we are just the type of people who celebrate success without any moral value attached to it, but today in the history of the nation Nigeria is labeled as the number one most fraudulent country despite the abundant natural resources at our disposal. In Nigeria today, economic crimes and fraudsters is a war That Belongs To EFCC and not only Nigerians, nobody wants his kinsmen and kiths presented as fraudster and corrupt leaders, we protect our people, we even go to the extent of praying for them in churches and mosques, our pastors and imams pray for protection from prosecution Their knowing fully That Their sources of fortune is fraudulent, some of them build churches and mosques and donated to intensify prayers That will shield them from persecution. How Investors Can Overcome Fraudsters To invest in Nigeria, the primary objective of the investors is the security of his capital. Well meaning Nigerians and foreigners have fallen prey to Nigerian fraudsters and Such as it has discouraged foreign and direct investment into our economy. I Dreamt of a time When the 419 scam will be lost in time, When investors can safely invest without the fear of advance fee fraudsters. Nigeria needs to be Salvaged from this 21st century thieves. It is a pity at the history of our nation every Nigerian That is a first suspect of fraud, scam, forgery and drug peddling. On most occasion When chatting with foreigners in online as soon as they request for your profile and discovers That you are a Nigerian, he will either shut further correspondence with you, or ignore your calls or embittered Those will tell it straight to your face That you a fraudster, fake or impostors. Our image as a Nigerian is in our hand, even your fellow Nigerian at home or abroad is sacred even to do business with you and at the end our national economy Suffers Setback in Because of the activities of this minute unscrupulous Nigerian who are unpatriotic, they live only for today and eat up the future of Nigeria unborn generations. How To Secure Your Capital Against Fraud Knowing how to secure your capital is paramount to investment in Nigeria. Interestingly, it is a well known consensus That 50% of those who fall victim to fraudsters become a victim as a result of Their personal greed. Both of them are out to cheat somebody or a system. There is always a two-way communication and acceptance of request. The fraudster Proposes mouth watering offers with huge profile and discounts to the victim, These offers are ordinarily That it can not be Obtained over the counter, the victim interiors are to save money, bypass official protocols and requirement to Obtain Such an offer, Also the victims crave for enormous profit above what is obtainable, this is the reason why several more December December December December December greedy businessmen and individual continue to fall prey to fraudsters of a different direction. Majority Of Those who have fallen victim of Nigerian 419 fraudsters Are Those who wants to do legitimate business in Nigeria but do not want to follow the legitimate official procedures. Instead of dealing Directly with the Nigerian government or companies they ignore this channel and go through middlemen who offer them discounts or less cumbersome procedures at the end, they fall victims to fraudsters and interestingly they never approach the government to complain Their loss, nor invite the police to investigate the fraudsters, this is simply Themselves Because they are guilty of economic crimes and sabotage. The best way to avoid fraudsters in Nigeria is to avoid bypassing official's procedures in business transaction, and more so, to avoid greed, in the form of excessive profit. Fraudsters capitalize on people's greed and Their lust to save money and make excess profit. Such businessmen do not have good stories to tell about Nigeria, they are Dealt with mercilessly Because of Their filthy altitude, and in Nigeria Such victims are called "Mugun" a terminology used to mean "fool" nowadays they use the term "witch" meaning "fool". In order not to fool yourself in Nigeria, you must be a genuine businessman with a sense of moral value with an upright altitude. Once you avoid excessive profit, not bypassing official procedures and mostly, avoid illegitimate business transactions then you will be proteted From These bad elements How Nigerians Living Abroad Are Defrauded By Their Families Nigerians living abroad are one of the silent victims of the Nigerians fraudsters. Everyday a fraction of them fall prey to fraudsters and the irony of this phenomenon is the repute Those who perpetrated These acts are Their kin and kiths. Their parents, brothers, sisters, uncles, cousins, extended family and ants do away with Their hard earned currencies, Because of the trust they repose on them, and as Such Nigerians living abroad this lower Their security shield and two bypass deligence two protocols, they fall victims to fraudsters who Appear as family members. The best way to invest in Nigeria is to involve a reputable company with evident track record of credibility and and more so, appoint a lawyer to oversea your deals and Negotiations. Unfortunately, a lot of us Nigerians avoid paying legal fees, instead of Involving a lawyer, we always want to save cost by doing it our self's, this will end in disaster and loss. Most Of These family members are always looking for opportunity to make money from innocent Nigerians living abroad. Why not shift your risk and liability to a company while your lawyer helps you to verify claims before you invest, you are most vulnerable to fraud through the People That you trust most and they are mostly our family members. 

 ﻿

Meer lezen (167 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-VzE38M2muK0/UHmNT2-caBI/AAAAAAAAB-k/44r19ArTw7g/w426-h407/FRAUSTERS%2B419.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/105409749207174892295/albums/6003320677344097745/6003320680261239634</link><title>It is apparent that when Eusebius assembled scribes to write the New Testimonies, he first produced a single document that provided an exemplar or master version. Today it is called the Gospel of Mark, and the Church admits that it was "the first Gospel written" (Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. vi, p. 657), even though it appears second in the New Testament today. The scribes of the Gospels of Matthew and Luke were dependent upon the Mark writing as the source and framework for the compilation of their works. The Gospel of John is independent of those writings, and the late-15th-century theory that it was written later to support the earlier writings is the truth (The Crucifixion of Truth, Tony Bushby, Joshua Books, 2004, pp. 33-40). 

Thus, the Gospel of Mark in the Sinai Bible carries the "first" story of Jesus Christ in history, one completely different to what is in modern Bibles. It starts with Jesus "at about the age of thirty" (Mark 1:9), and doesn't know of Mary, a virgin birth or mass murders of baby boys by Herod. Words describing Jesus Christ as "the son of God" do not appear in the opening narrative as they do in today's editions (Mark 1:1), and the modern-day family tree tracing a "messianic bloodline" back to King David is non-existent in all ancient Bibles, as are the now-called "messianic prophecies" (51 in total). 

The Sinai Bible carries a conflicting version of events surrounding the "raising of Lazarus", and reveals an extraordinary omission that later became the central doctrine of the Christian faith: the resurrection appearances of Jesus Christ and his ascension into Heaven. No supernatural appearance of a resurrected Jesus Christ is recorded in any ancient Gospels of Mark, but a description of over 500 words now appears in modern Bibles (Mark 16:9-20). 

Despite a multitude of long-drawn-out self-justifications by Church apologists, there is no unanimity of Christian opinion regarding the non-existence of "resurrection" appearances in ancient Gospel accounts of the story. Not only are those narratives missing in the Sinai Bible, but they are absent in the Alexandrian Bible, the Vatican Bible, the Bezae Bible and an ancient Latin manuscript of Mark, code-named "K" by analysts. They are also lacking in the oldest Armenian version of the New Testament, in sixth-century manuscripts of the Ethiopic version and ninth-century Anglo-Saxon Bibles. However, some 12th-century Gospels have the now-known resurrection verses written within asterisks-marks used by scribes to indicate spurious passages in a literary document. 

The Church claims that "the resurrection is the fundamental argument for our Christian belief" (Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. xii, p. 792), yet no supernatural appearance of a resurrected Jesus Christ is recorded in any of the earliest Gospels of Mark available. A resurrection and ascension of Jesus Christ is the sine qua non ("without which, nothing") of Christianity (Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. xii, p. 792), confirmed by words attributed to Paul: 
"If Christ has not been raised, your faith is in vain" 
(1 Cor. 5:17). 
The resurrection verses in today's Gospels of Mark are universally acknowledged as forgeries and the Church agrees, saying, 
"the conclusion of Mark is admittedly not genuine ... almost the entire section is a later compilation" 
(Encyclopaedia Biblica, vol. ii, p. 1880, vol. iii, pp. 1767, 1781; also, Catholic Encyclopedia, vol. iii, under the heading "The Evidence of its Spuriousness"; Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. iii, pp. 274-9 under heading "Canons"). 

Undaunted, however, the Church accepted the forgery into its dogma and made it the basis of Christianity. 

The trend of fictitious resurrection narratives continues. The final chapter of the Gospel of John (21) is a sixth-century forgery, one entirely devoted to describing Jesus' resurrection to his disciples. 

The Church admits: 
"The sole conclusion that can be deduced from this is that the 21st chapter was afterwards added and is therefore to be regarded as an appendix to the Gospel" 
(Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. viii, pp. 441-442; New Catholic Encyclopedia (NCE), "Gospel of John", p. 1080; also NCE, vol. xii, p. 407). 

Modern-day versions of the Gospel of Luke have a staggering 10,000 more words than the same Gospel in the Sinai Bible. Six of those words say of Jesus "and was carried up into heaven", but this narrative does not appear in any of the oldest Gospels of Luke available today ("Three Early Doctrinal Modifications of the Text of the Gospels", F. C. Conybeare, The Hibbert Journal, London, vol. 1, no. 1, Oct 1902, pp. 96-113). Ancient versions do not verify modern-day accounts of an ascension of Jesus Christ, and this falsification clearly indicates an intention to deceive. 

Adopting the decrees of the Council of Trent (1545-63), the Church subsequently extended the process of erasure and ordered the preparation of a special list of specific information to be expunged from early Christian writings (Delineation of Roman Catholicism, Rev. Charles Elliott, DD, G. Lane &amp; P. P. Sandford, New York, 1842, p. 89; also, The Vatican Censors, Professor Peter Elmsley, Oxford, p. 327, pub. date n/a). 

In 1562, the Vatican established a special censoring office called Index Expurgatorius. Its purpose was to prohibit publication of "erroneous passages of the early Church Fathers" that carried statements opposing modern-day doctrine. 

When Vatican archivists came across, 
"genuine copies of the Fathers, they corrected them according to the Expurgatory Index" 
(Index Expurgatorius Vaticanus, R. Gibbings, ed., Dublin, 1837; The Literary Policy of the Church of Rome, Joseph Mendham, J. Duncan, London, 1830, 2nd ed., 1840; The Vatican Censors, op. cit., p. 328). 
Important for our story is the fact that the Encyclopaedia Biblica reveals that around 1,200 years of Christian history are unknown: "Unfortunately, only few of the records [of the Church] prior to the year 1198 have been released". It was not by chance that, in that same year (1198), Pope Innocent III (1198-1216) suppressed all records of earlier Church history by establishing the Secret Archives (Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. xv, p. 287). Some seven-and-a-half centuries later, and after spending some years in those Archives, Professor Edmond S. Bordeaux wrote How The Great Pan Died. 

In a chapter titled "The Whole of Church History is Nothing but a Retroactive Fabrication", he said this (in part): 
"The Church ante-dated all her late works, some newly made, some revised and some counterfeited, which contained the final expression of her history ... her technique was to make it appear that much later works written by Church writers were composed a long time earlier, so that they might become evidence of the first, second or third centuries." 
(How The Great Pan Died, op. cit., p. 46) 

Supporting Professor Bordeaux's findings is the fact that, in 1587, Pope Sixtus V (1585-90) established an official Vatican publishing division and said in his own words, 
"Church history will be NOW be established ... we shall seek to print our own account" (Encyclopédie, Diderot,1759). 

Vatican records also reveal that Sixtus V spent 18 months of his life as pope personally writing a new Bible and then introduced it into Catholicism a "New Learning" (Catholic Encyclopedia, Farley ed., vol. v, p. 442, vol. xv, p. 376). The evidence that the Church wrote its own history is found in Diderot's Encyclopédie, and it reveals the reason why Pope Clement XIII (1758-69) ordered all volumes to be destroyed immediately after publication in 1759. 

So Just what is Christianity? cos if the New Testament is not historical, what is it? 
Christianity is an adaptation of, 
Mithraism welded with the Druidic principles of the Culdees 
some Egyptian elements (the pre-Christian Book of Revelation was originally called The Mysteries of Osiris and Isis) 
Greek philosophy 
various aspects of Hinduism 
Replica of book of Daniel 

Why are there no records of Jesus Christ? It is not possible to find in any legitimate religious or historical writings compiled between the beginning of the first century and well into the fourth century any reference to Jesus Christ and the spectacular events that the Church says accompanied his life. 

This confirmation comes from Frederic Farrar (1831-1903) of Trinity College, Cambridge: 
"It is amazing that history has not embalmed for us even one certain or definite saying or circumstance in the life of the Saviour of mankind ... there is no statement in all history that says anyone saw Jesus or talked with him. Nothing in history is more astonishing than the silence of contemporary writers about events relayed in the four Gospels." 
(The Life of Christ, Frederic W. Farrar, Cassell, London, 1874) 
This situation arises from a conflict between history and New Testament narratives. Dr Tischendorf made this comment: 
"We must frankly admit that we have no source of information with respect to the life of Jesus Christ other than ecclesiastic writings assembled during the fourth century." 
(Codex Sinaiticus, Dr Constantin von Tischendorf, British Library, London) 
There is an explanation for those hundreds of years of silence: 
the construct of Christianity did not begin until after the first quarter of the fourth century, and that is why Pope Leo X (d. 1521) called Christ a "fable"(Cardinal Bembo: His Letters..., op. cit.). 

The question remains to those believing in a black messiah, in your opinion given the fabrications of doctrine and the construct of the name Jesus:  do you believe Black Jesus is a fable, if not, how do you prove otherwise? Is their archeological/historic/religious evidence to support your claims?﻿

Meer lezen (181 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-tuQvhCwhUKE/U1AUWgu6Q1I/AAAAAAAACW0/XNwaeIisOPw/w426-h341/JEBUS.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/112600010909645008639/albums/5787709169902318977/5787709169439602562</link><title>The truth about Prophet Muhammad (Peace Be Upon Him) 

Loving him is following him 

Muslims all over the world are deeply hurt by the recent caricatures of our beloved Prophet Muhammad , in Danish and several other publications. 

Every now and then, some Western media outlets provoke Muslims by insulting the Prophet Muhammad . The baiting often succeeds in eliciting Muslims' outrage and sporadic violence. 

The latest incident started with a Danish newspaper's caricature portraying the Prophet Muhammad as a terrorist. To add insult to injury, Norwegian, French, German, Dutch and a few other newspapers reprinted the defamatory cartoons to "defend"—they claimed—the freedom of expression. 

The real issue is not the freedom of expression. Free speech is not and was never meant to be absolute. There are laws in the West that ban certain kinds of speech, including those that incite anti-Semitism, racism and violence. Moreover, some countries have laws against blasphemy and defamation. To Muslims, banning blasphemy against Allah and the Prophet Muhammad has a higher priority. 

For the European newspapers to reprint the offensive cartoons to show solidarity with their Danish counterpart seems akin to the plot the leaders of Quraysh had hatched to assassinate Prophet Muhammad . 

The Quraysh masterminds had figured that including representatives from major tribes of Makkah in the heinous plot would make it impossible for the Prophet's clan, Banu Hashim, to avenge. But Allah willed that the Prophet Muhammad would migrate to Madinah unscathed while the plotters laid siege to his house. 

The West often underestimates the Muslims' reverence for their beloved Prophet Muhammad, (sallallallahu alayhi wa sallam) and is, therefore, staltred by the fierce Islamic reaction to an insult against him. Few in the West know that for Muslims, loving their Prophet more than themselves is a matter of faith, not choice. 

Further, the depiction of the Prophet Muhammad , as a terrorist is a falsification of history. He was considered "Al-Ameen," the trustworthy, by his people even before he received the Prophethood. 

Once, when asked by some of his followers to invoke Allah's wrath on the enemies, he refused saying he had been sent as a mercy unto mankind. 

Objective Western intellectuals have acknowledged the superior character of Prophet Muhammad . In his “The 100, a Ranking of the Most Influential Persons in History," Michael H. Hart ranked Prophet Muhammad, (sallallallahu alayhi wa sallam) No. 1 because "He was the only man in history who was supremely successful on both the religious and secular levels.” 

Alphonse de Lamartine, a renowned 19th Century French writer, had this to say about the Prophet Muhammad : "As regards all standards by which human greatness may be measured, we may well ask, is there any man greater than him?” 

Unfortunately, some Muslims forget that loving their Prophet Muhammad (Peace be upon him) means following him. Burning Danish embassies, as they did in Damascus and Beirut, to avenge the insult to the Prophet Muhammad is a complete disservice to him. Our violent reaction only plays into the hands of those who wish to reinforce the negative stereotypes about Muslims. 

Do Muslims need reminding that Prophet Muhammad , forgave the people of Ta'if who had rejected his message of monotheism and pelted him with stones, bloodying him? Islamic tradition has it that when Jibreel (Archangel Gabriel) sought his permission to punish the perpetrators, the Prophet, instead prayed that some day the inhabitants of Ta'if would leave their idols and worship Allah alone. Within a few years they did. 

Prophet Muhammad's, (sallallallahu alayhi wa sallam) servant once noted his forgiving disposition, said, "I served the Prophet, for ten years, and he never said ‘uf’ (a word indicating impatience or discontent) to me and never blamed me by saying, `Why did you do so or why didn't you do so?" (Al-Bukhari and Muslim) 

Prophet Muhammad's, (sallallallahu alayhi wa sallam) archenemies hated his Message and hurled malicious insults at him, to which he responded with forbearance. Years later when he, sallallallahu alayhi wa sallam returned as victor to Makkah, his city of birth which he was forced to leave, he asked its awed citizens, "What do you think I'm going to do to you." They said, "You are a noble brother, son of a noble brother; we expect only good from you." The Prophet responded with a general amnesty. 

Let Muslims not forget that the Prophet, encouraged freedom of expression. In the Battle of Badr, he changed the battlefield against his own opinion due to the passionate advice of some young soldiers. 

Part of the West's success today is the freedom of expression, of thought, of religion—that draws Muslims to it from their oppressed societies. For that, Muslims should be thankful to the West. After all, freedom is an Islamic value that the West has embraced while Muslim societies have forsaken. 

Defending Prophet Muhammad requires allowing freedom and practicing compassion and forgiveness, like he did. In his lifetime he, bore insults with magnanimity and devoted his time to spreading the Message of Allah. In fact, he never avenged anyone for a personal offence. Can we really respect him by violent retaliation? 

Muslims should turn this extremely painful incident into something positive, by teaching the world what the Prophet, means to us and what his life was like. 

As for the West, there really is a need to reexamine the notion of free speech. Without safeguards, the exercise of this freedom can be lethal, as we have seen. 

One may ask, is it morally defensible to provoke violence, cause death, and create a civilizational conflict for one cartoonist's freedom of expression? 

The West already has laws to protect religious freedom, which Muslims and other peoples of faith admire. What it now needs to do is protect this freedom from being trampled by unbridled free speech. No one should have to insult Prophet Muhammad, Jesus, or Moses, may Allah exalt their mention to speak freely. 

We can turn these negative, malicious cartoons into something positive by learning about the Prophet, by following him, and educating others about his teachings. 

Allah described the Prophet in the verse (which means): "And verily, you (O Muhammad) are on an exalted standard of character." (Quran 68:4) 

And (what means): "Indeed in the Messenger of Allah there is a good example to follow for him who hopes in (the meeting with) Allah and the Last Day and remembers Allah much." (Quran 33:21) 

By a divine decision, the status of Muhammad was raised forever, as in the verse (which means): "And (has Allah not) raised high your fame?" (Quran 94:4) 

Muslims were commanded to lower their voices low in the presence of the Prophet , out of respect, as in the verse (which means): "O you who believe, raise not your voices above the voice of the Prophet, nor speak aloud to him as you speak aloud to one another lest your deeds be rendered fruitless while you perceive not. Verily, those who lower their voices in the presence of Allah's Messenger, they are the ones whose hearts Allah has tested for piety. For them there is forgiveness and a great reward." (Quran 49:2-3) 

While other prophets were sent to their own people, Muhammad was appointed as the Messenger to all mankind. And such he was asked to declare (what means): "Say (O Muhammad): `O mankind, verily I am sent to you all as the Messenger of Allah - to Whom belongs the Dominion of the heavens and the earth." (Quran 7:158) 

On the Day of Judgement he will be the only Messenger to intercede with Allah to seek forgiveness for the wrongdoers. 

As blasphemous as the drawings are, we believe that behind all events there is Allah's pre-decree and wisdom that mortal beings fully understand only in hindsight. In the end, this deeply hurtful incident would be seen as benefiting the image of the Prophet . 

A case in point is the verse (which means): "Verily, We have given you (O Muhammad) a manifest victory." (Quran 48:1) 

When this verse was revealed, even some of the most exemplary Muslims could not understand how being prevented from performing pilgrimage by the enemies could be a manifest victory. Prophet Muhammad had just signed a treaty with non-Muslims of Makkah that imposed unfair restrictions on Muslims. 

The Prophet swore by Allah that no matter how restrictive this treaty seemed, it was a clear victory for Muslims. Within a few years, the victory became abundantly clear when Muslims marched into Makkah, not just as pilgrims but as victors. 

Our love for the Prophet Muhammad cannot be expressed except by following him. If we did that, we will see how Allah can change this painful incident into a great opportunity for the Islamic cause. 

Welcome to my blog 
http://about--islam.blogspot.com/﻿

Meer lezen (186 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-BiMa7mY75uk/UFIS0zO394I/AAAAAAAAAZo/KZYUcEZiQ7k/s426/2012%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/112177048419373530737/albums/6009659368799465105/6009659374297760914</link><title>Quick translation Google 

Search 
The Jews have no right to religious 

Dr Saleh Hussein Alrqub 
Associate Professor - Faculty of Theology 
Islamic University - Gaza Strip 
Palestine 

In the name of God the Merciful 

Praise be to Allah , we praise Him and seek His help and forgiveness , and we seek refuge with Allah from the evils of ourselves and from our bad deeds of Allah guides not misleading him , and not mislead Hadi . And I bear witness that there is no god but Allah , and I bear witness that Muhammad is His slave and Messenger . 
Research objectives : - 
• Abolition of the Jewish and refute the claim that they have a historical right to Palestine . 
• statement of the facts and fallacies concerning on peoples that inhabited the land of Palestine . 
• identification of Arab Palestine since ancient times , and they are still Arab and Muslim , Arabs and Muslims are the heirs of the prophets who lived in the land of Palestine or passed through it since Abraham until Mohammad peace be upon him . 
Research Methodology : - 
Researcher adopted the historical method , and analytical Valosfi , by collecting information from sources and analyzed to try to reach the desired results . 
Find sources : - 
The researcher on historical sources available in his hands , and relied on the Bible as a historical source authentic Jews , and the words of the Jewish scholars and Christian Europeans of historians and specialists in archeology. 
The most important results : - \- The historical source of the allegations of Zionism in the historical right in Palestine is the Bible have , and this source is not fit to be a historical document reliable ones because of its myths and legends , and that the hand of misrepresentation and fraud has extended to him , has proven facts of science and archaeological discoveries that matter . 
\- The Arab Canaanites were the first to have access by the tribes of this land , which was later on their behalf , to understand its indigenous population , as demonstrated by historical studies , and also proved that the Bible itself , this fact was confirmed by scientists history of non-Arabs and Muslims . 
\- The Bible is the land of Canaan, the land of weird for the Prophets of Israel , and the first of them Abu prophets Abraham . 
\- The kingdoms established by the Jews in Palestine are small-sized kingdoms , baptized a small period of time and then ended . The presence of Jews on the land of Palestine was sporadic presence , while the presence of the Arabs was a constant presence since three thousand years BC till now . 
\- The right of the Arabs in Palestine constant: the right of conquest , and the right of limitation , the right to waive . 
\- The archaeological discoveries by Jewish scholars belie claims of Jews in the historic right , and prove that it is not relevant to the legends of scientific truth . 
\- The majority of today's Jews have no connection or relationship Hebrews and Israelis who inhabited ancient Palestine , and not linked to race High , they are of Aryan origins Thudt throughout history . This fact was confirmed by European scientists and scholars Darcoa mortal races . 
\- The land of Palestine, Arab identity and history , and then became the Islamic conquest of Islamic identity and belonging , but also extend to Islamic identities of the prophets and messengers who lived in them throughout history , because of all the prophets are Muslims , and Muslims of the people of Palestine are the rightful heirs to the Hour . 
\- And do it all fall claims and allegations Jewish about the right of Jews historic Palestine and the legitimacy of their state list through conquest, colonization, and by means of terror and oppression practiced against the Arabs of Palestine . Remains the historic right fixed to her family Arabs who lived in them before other nations and peoples . 
Introduction: 
        Has consistently leaders of Israel 's political and religious leaders to say that the blessed land of Palestine is the land of Israel is historical in which he lived grandparents and parents , the Hebrews and the Israelis , and that this land is not of a people others , so they are the owners legitimate , and that the Palestinian Arabs strangers about, and they have to leave it to the country other . 
          Says : Prime Minister of the Zionist entity, the previous ( Golda Meir ) in a statement to the newspaper " Sindaa Times " of London on 15/05/1969 AD has no Palestinian people ... who feels like we came to get him out of his home and the seizure of his country. Understand ( the Palestinians ) do not exist .. " . Due to owning the Jews in the world and the media industry, media and public opinion , we have been able to make fabrications Facts Muslim tautology by the minds of many of the Christians of the West , due to the recovery of their leaders such as these lies and delusions I saw my duty to my statement historical truth in it, and expose falsehood about, relying on the Koran, and historical sources - available in the hands - and the Bible when the Jews. 
     I have tried in this research that proved false claims of Jews in the Holy Land , and that proved to Arabism and Islamic land of Palestine , this land inherited by Muslims worshipers of God righteous according to the law of God Almighty scheduled to inherit the earth , Allah says : {And We have written in the Psalms, after the male shall inherit the earth righteous slaves } . ( [1] ) 
         This research has been made ​​in several demands , including the right to criticize Jewish Historical maligned , and prove that the blessed land of Palestine to the Muslims followers of the prophets and messengers . 
        The State of Israel on a range of myths and allegations of religious and historical collection of the leaders of the Zionist Jews of the world in this land based on that, and they took falsify history and claim that they have a historical right to the land of Palestine , and thus the right to have the legality of returning to it , and the establishment of the state in which they have , is the right idea historical maligned in Palestine of the most important arguments on which the Zionist movement , which Hst out the brains of the world's Jews and Christians, the brains of a lot of Europe and America. The Jews claim that they are the owners of the Holy Land - Palestine - because their grandparents and their parents stayed there for a period of time in ancient history , and established kingdoms Jewish , and the kingdom of David and his son Solomon peace be upon them , then the Kingdom of Judah in the south of Palestine , and the kingdom of Israel in the north , since three thousand years . 
To invalidate this claim , and a statement Thavth , recall the faces of the following : - 
The first face : the bond revocation of the right to religious historical alleged : 
   The Old Testament - the Bible when the Jews - source historical basis for the allegations and Zionist claims about the historical right of the Jews in Palestine did not reach us bail frequently connected to Moses or Solomon or other prophets , could not rabbis - whatever they used to trick and cunning and savvy - that establish single piece of evidence of that. 
 The Bible must prove Sindh frequent road hyperbolic , and frequent collection of the accounts of the people believe in their complicity and to lie about the collection like him even its limit , which was revealed to the Prophet and greeted him from God . ( [2] ) 
"The attempt Torah highlighting incidents of Jews and show figures that are relevant to them as far as their opinion may come to serve their purpose, the political in an attempt to show the long history of the Jews in the region , and provided they are human on the other folks the island to support the idea of ​​creating a separate entity for them depends on the historical roots strike in the foot and originality , especially after the Babylonian captivity . came recording incidents Torah service to try ( Cyrus ) , which aimed to establish a Jewish state in Palestine to protect the western border of the Persian Empire from the attacks of the Byzantine to the west . has issued a decision to the return of the Jews to Palestine to build their state on its midst . Vschroa service to this goal, all the physical and intellectual energies have prepared their blog historical ( Torah) to play a role in this direction. " ( [3] ) 

 The evidence of invalidity as follows: 
First: The earliest version of undiscovered from the Old Testament version is discovered in the caves ( Qumran ) , located in the hills on the shore of the Dead Sea in 1947 AD , and this version does not represent the entire Old Testament , but lacked a bit too much , there is little travel version of this complete unless little and varied views of historians in the history of writing , scholar American " Albright " went to it was written about two hundred - 200 - BC , and went Others , including the British ( Driver ) it back until after the Islamic conquest , and if you take the opinion of the first as belonging to two hundred BC , it states that the difference in time between the version discovered and between Moses His Torah at least a thousand (1000 ) years , and between them and the Solomon peace be upon him builder structure about seven hundred (700 ) years. Can this version to prepare a reliable historical document them , to prove the allegations of the Jews in the historic right ? . ( [4] ) 
Second: The Old Testament stated in more than one place that many of the Prophets of Israel and the followers of the prophets have lied to God , and distorted his words and Tenbioa false dreams ... and here we mention some of the texts of the Bible : - 
* What David said on the lips of the Lord : "What is made by my people , the whole day they twist my words " ( [ 5 ] ) . 
* What Jeremiah on the lips of the Lord : " The Lord said to me: The prophets prophesy lies in my name, did not send them , nor commanded them , nor their word visions false , and deceit Heart predict " ( [6] ) , " The burden of the LORD there they had learned after because the word everyone to be The revelation may burden; words of the living God our God, the Lord of hosts " ( [7] ) . 
   The archaeologists Jews demonstrated through the relics unearthed in the land of Palestine that the current Torah is full of myths and allegations that superceded by scientific facts that are based on recent discoveries . 
  Third, tell God in his book , which is not done wrong in the hands of his successor - what did the Jews in the Torah , which was revealed to Moses, peace be upon him , where they switch distortions in Olvazaa and her words and their meanings . He says: of those who are Jews twist on the floor anywhere and say we have heard and disobeyed ... } ( [8 ] ), and the Almighty said: Fbma breaking of their covenant to Anahm and made their hearts cruel twist on the floor anywhere and forgotten fortunate than stated by } ( [9] ) . he said: { It is those who are Jews Smaon to lie Smaon for folk others did unto thee distort speech after Moadah say Ootim this Fajdhuh although not Tatoh Vahdhiroh ... } . ( [10] ) , and said : { The team had them hear the word of God and then Ihrvonh after they understood it and they know } . ( [11] ) and said : {And of them are illiterate and do not know the book , but the aspirations and they only think woe to those who write the book with their hands and then say this is from Allah to buy him a bit pricy foil them , which I wrote hands and woe to them than earn } ( [12] ) . 
Fourth: According to the " Encyclopedia Britannica " that the authors of the books of the "Old Testament " unknown , and it is not known if it was collected has been at the hands of individuals or groups , and it was written " in Hebrew only , except for some short clips rare codified in Aramaic , but Jewish community deliberately , for reasons of jurisprudence , to translate the Bible from Hebrew to Aramaic , has lost manuscripts of the Hebrew original , did we receive only translations In the third century AD , the scholars of the Jews translated the Hebrew canon to the Greek knows ( translation Septuagint ) then resulted in the spread of Christianity to the translation the texts of the Bible ( old and New Testament ) in different languages ​​( [13] ) . 
  Fifth: According to the Encyclopedia of the French ( " Kiye Quillet") that the oldest full-text of the Old Testament in Hebrew, dating back to the year 950 AD , did we receive from him , before , only to pluck a few " except scripts desert Jewish dating , usually to the second century BC. M. and back to all the books of the Old Testament , except the Book of Esther . " She wrote most of the Old Testament in Hebrew ( Semitic language used in Palestine until the sixth century BC. AD ), while there were some sections of the Scriptures in Aramaic ( the language of international traded in Asia old , and used by the Jews since their captivity to Babylon ) as the last travel from the Old Testament . It is wise to travel , to have been written in the Greek language . ( [14] ) 
  Sixth: The majority of scholars and researchers of the ancient and modern - including Jews and Christians - reckon that the author of the current Torah is the priest Ezra , who Ptlfikha and collected from different sources mixed , and assisted by some of the priests who worked under Raasth and guidance , and has been writing after the return of the Jews from Babylonian captivity , who happened to them after the death of Moses, peace be upon him hundreds of years , ( [15] ), which make these research scientists are discovering that : the language of the Torah , and her words , and lack of mastery of the scribes of the process of fabrication , change and distortion . ( [16] ) have recognized this fact Jewish Encyclopedia , and the American Encyclopedia , which said : the scribes have changed the intent and inadvertently in the documents and travel Judaism they wrote over the period of the century atheist century BC to the first century AD, we have not received a copy the original author of this travel . ( [17] ) and Dr Jewish Arthur Rowen professor of sociology at the Hebrew University in Jerusalem : the Bible scholars are all unanimous that the Old Testament was developed during and after the exile to Babylon ( [18] ) . He said this is also a gathering of Jewish scholars veterans , including : Samuel son Judah (d. 570 AH ), which is called after his conversion to Islam as " Highness Al Ben Yahia Moroccan " - where he put a book decided this belief , supported by the evidence and proofs ( [19] ) . Including : ( Orbel Acosta 1585-164 AD ) who was accused of inks and soothsayers twisting book, which was revealed to Moses, peace be upon him , said that the Bible is filled with contradictions between the current texts . Including : Jewish philosopher ( Baruch Spinoza 1632-1677 AD ), which deepened in the study of Jewish thought and came out one result, namely that the books of the Torah and the rest of the Old Testament Jews had nothing to do with Moses peace be upon him , but I wrote after several centuries , and they are not alive divinely directly . ( [ 20 ] ) 
And give us a researcher , " Thomas Thompson " in his book "The ancient history of the people of the" Israeli " another example of Western historians who expose fraud historic for" Israel " ancient , and adopts " Thompson " on the theory of the German scientist ," and the night is the weight of " the hypothesis documentaries that you see that it must understanding ( four sources , namely: Jewish documents , and documents of divinity , and Deuteronomy , and the law of priestly ) . 's Fluorescence the first five of the Old Testament - the Bible - as documents literary composed as written , and in the late period of the events contained therein hundreds of years , a reflection of honest to understand and know the authors and their world , and this can not be considered as a history significant , as it can not take advantage of them to reshape the history of ancient Israel , the former time -authored , and the events that are received not supported by evidence from archaeological discoveries , or sources of foreign non-Jewish . ( [ 21 ] ) 
  If the current Torah was written after Moses, peace be upon him several centuries , where the Torah was handed down to Moses, the prophet of God ? The gathering of rabbis and theologians Christians contend with loss and lost ark, the sacred , and it was seen by one of the sons of the prophets of Israel and the rulers who came after Moses . ( [22] ) 
Fifth: The Bible is full of texts contrasting conflicting , has proven that scientists and researchers in the study of Jewish thought and its sources , and Muslim scholars : Brand Ibn Hazm in his book : Chapter in boredom and passions , bees , and God's mercy Indian in his book : to show the truth, and Ibn al-Qayyim in his book : Hidayat confused in the answers to the Jews and Christians , and examples of contradiction and difference : 
1 - difference and contradiction in identifying animals phones in Noah's Ark : 
* In Genesis 16:20 : number of each type , two by two , male and female 
* At the same travel 17 : 2-3 : number seven male and a female of clean beasts , beasts and unclean two male and female , and birds of the sky also seven male and a female . 
* At the same travel, same chapter 17:15 : The ship entered two and two of all flesh, wherein is the breath and life . 
2 - determine the duration of the flood on the ground : - 
* In Genesis chapter VII , paragraph 17 : And the flood was forty days upon the earth , and in paragraph 24 the same chapter : And the waters prevailed upon the earth a hundred and fifty days . 
3 - Adam to Noah to recognize and inequality in the past : 
* Samaritan Torah said : Adam, Noah realized , and lived with him : 253 years . 
* The Hebrew Bible : that Noah did not realize Adam , Venouh born after the death of Adam 126 years . 
* The Greek Bible : Noah did not realize Adam , but Noah was born after the death of Adam are 732 years old . 
4 - came in my going out and Deuteronomy ( [23] ) : 
* The Israeli who sells himself for his brother selling optionally in the case of the Israeli destitution and need to paper money does not last only six years . 
* As stated in my Allawin ( [24] ) that the paper may last for decades , as stipulated : that the paper does not end only by the Jubilee Israeli ( Feast Jubilee comes every fifty years ) , that is, if he sold the Israeli himself to his brother after the feast days will continue in slavery to the second coming of Eid after fifty years . 
 VI : The Bible is full of events and facts that occurred after the death of Moses, peace be upon him , and if they were alive divinely revealed to Moses, peace be upon him to empty it out. Examples include : - 
 * Novels that talk about the death of Moses and buried , and his tomb and that it exceeded the prophets who came after him, and he does not have a prophet of the Children of Israel - after Moses - peace be upon him like Moses . 
  * Found in the Torah names for places not fired and did not know the time of Moses, peace be upon him , but released the names and knew after Moses a time , for example : the city, " Dan " mentioned in Genesis , the name of the city that did not call and did not know until after the death of Joshua the son of Nun boy Moses who died after him . 
 * Exodus talked about food ( manna ) which eat the children of Israel for forty days , until they came to a land inhabited the borders of Canaan, and this happened after the death of Moses, peace be upon him . 
 * According to the Book of Genesis : " And these are the kings who reigned in the land of Edom , before he perished to the king of the children of Israel " chapter 36 : 31, and it is known that the era of the Kings was the Israelis after the death of Moses tens of years. 
 Seventh: The Bible is full of novels and issues contrary to science and modern knowledge , has noted that a number of researchers, specialists such as : Ibn Hazm in his book " chapter in boredom and whims and the bees " , and Maurice Bucaille in his book : " the study of the Holy Scriptures in the light of modern knowledge ." 
   It said Maurice Bucaille : "I found statements can not be reconciled with the more data flag firmly in our time " ( [25] ) , and also " a few of the topics addressed by the Old Testament allows against the facts of modern science , but when a conflict occurs between the text of the Torah and science , it comes in matters that can be described mission " ( [26] ) , and also " found in the Old Testament stories are different in one subject , and historical errors and things contradictory, and other unreasonable or impossible to agree with the scientific data fixed . " ( [ 27 ] ) the transfer Maurice Bucaille, a number of critics of European theologians of words showing their attitudes towards scientific errors in the texts of the Old Testament . " ( [28] ) 
 Eighth: The contemporary science , especially Monetary German proved after extensive research on ancient monuments , history, linguistics , that the current Torah : is not the Torah original which has been inflicted on Moses, peace be upon him , but rather the work of inks and clergy came after him after two years long , and the most famous of these critics : Richard Simon , author : monetary history of the Old Testament in 1678 AD , and the doctor critic Jean Astruk His critical study about the Bible , published in 1753 AD , and the world of Julius Wellhausen scholars of the nineteenth century , researcher and critic Oikhhorn (d. 1782 ) , and researcher lukewarm , and Elgin 1798 , the French researcher Maurice Bucaille owner the book referred to in the proof of the previous edition of the book has appeared in French in 1978 . ( [29] ) 
The second aspect : historical studies : - 
   The oldest human races mentioned in history as residents of the country , known in ancient history and the sacred books of the Jews and the Christians as the land of Canaan, the Canaanites , who are named after the country in their name. 
  The Arabs were the first to come to the land of Palestine , and earlier in that of the Hebrew tribes that came to it later . The reason for that is that historical studies have proven documented the arrival of regiments of the Arab tribes to the land of the Arabian Peninsula, an immigrant to the Levant in the fourth millennium BC, these tribes settled the Mediterranean coast , in what is now Syria , Lebanon and Palestine . 
     He was on the tribes that settled in the northern coast of the Mediterranean Phoenicians for getting employed to extract and trade Alvins , was launched at the Canaanites who settled in south-central land of Canaan - the Jerusalem area today - the name of the Jebusites , and those who lived in the far south of the land of Canaan name Anakim , and those who are set up four city known as Habrn . ( [30] ) 
    ﻿

Meer lezen (380 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OHYFja1fx3I/U2aZXEIdRJI/AAAAAAACGd4/14pGIj3heXw/w426-h629/Untitled54875.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/103198124146258055902/albums/5879866009360633233/5879866007272287778</link><title>WARNING RACIST insult by gaijin Anti-Japanese moron GERRY SUPPAN [https://plus.google.com/u/0/110462580813539761408/posts] and Bill page [https://plus.google.com/u/0/115753718076949408368/posts] 
Bill page why do you want Toru Hashimoto to be raped you mentally distubed creature?as a fellow brit I say that you are a disgraceful role model for your British/Japanese children You PIG! 
 and mr EASY-LIFE-IN-JAPAN SUPPAN why should Japan apologize for korean prostitution. 
 GERRY I am highly disappointed in you !You are foreigner in japan of over 30 years why do feel the need to go on childish misinformed Japan bashing rants? lso Gerry  suppan and bill page when you shit on Japan PLEASE also write in Japanese so people can see you for the disgusting two faced snakes that you are! 

DO NOT INSULT JAPAN WITH FALSIFIED STATEMENTS!! 

The Facts regarding the korean led sex slave myth and recent Toru Hashimoto comments covered by a May 2013 slanderous news story by the BBC which is full of inaccuracies and lies. 

The purpose of this comment is to present historical FACTS. 

At the end of April 2011, an paid advertisement by south korean government purporting to tell "The Truth about Comfort Women" appeared in the Washington Post. 

The claims contained in these statements, though, were anything but the "truth." 

Rather than being based on "facts," they appeared, if anything, to be the products of "faith." 

The people of Japan have the highest respect for the United States as a fellow democratic nation and as a strong and reliable ally. For democracy to operate effectively, though, the freedom of speech, thought, academic research, and religion must be guaranteed so that individual citizens can draw their own appropriate conclusions. 

To enable this, people must have access to correct facts, rather than fallacies, distortions, biases, and factual errors. 

This public comment seeks to present a number of historical facts relating to "comfort women" that have not been adequately brought to light so as to enable the readers of this respected publication to draw their own conclusions. 

Fact 1 

No historical document has ever been found by historians or research organizations that positively demonstrates that women were forced against their will into prostitution by the Japanese army. A search of the archives at the Japan Center for Asian Historical Records, which houses wartime orders from the government and military leaders, turned up nothing indicating that women were forcibly rounded up to work as ianfu, or comfort women." 

On the contrary, many documents were found warning private brokers not to force women to work against their will 

Army memorandum 2197, issued on March 4, 1938, explicitly prohibits recruiting methods that fraudulently employ the army's name or that can be classified as abduction, warning that those employing such methods have been punished. A Home Affairs Ministry directive (number 77) issued on February 18, 1938, states that the recruitment of "comfort women" must be in compliance with international law and prohibits the enslavement of abduction of women. A directive (number 136) issued on November 8 the same year, moreover, orders that only women who are 21 years old or over and are already professionally engaged in the trade may be recruited as "comfort women." It also requires the approval of the woman's family or relatives. 

A historian who claims that the number of "comfort women" reached 200,000 - a contention frequently quoted in the US media - believes, on the other hand, that the memorandum offers proof of the army's active involvement. 

Fact 2 

There are many newspaper articles, moreover, that demonstrate that these directives were dutifully carried out. The August 31, 1939, issue of Dong-A Ilbo, published in Korea, reports of brokers who forced women to become ianfu against their will being punished by the local police, which was under Japanese jurisdiction at the time. This offers proof that the Japanese government dealt severely with inhumane crimes against women. 

Unscrupulous Brokers Run Rampant 

Abduction of Rural Women and Girls 

More than 100 Women Victimized Pusan Police Officers Dash Off to Mukden 

Pusan - Unscrupulous brokers have been conspiring to abduct women from poor families by promising them generous rewards in Manchuria (where Japanese soldiers are claimed to be visiting brothels in swarms). Forty-five such brokers were found to be working in Pusan, where they hired unsuspecting young women away from their families and sold them into prostitution in Manchuria. Over 100 women have already been victimized. Intensive investigation by Pusan police has revealed the identity of a Mukden dealer involved in these activities, and six officers were dispatched in the evening of August 20 to the city to arrest this dealer. The arrest is expected to fully expose the nightmarish activities of these brokers. 

Fact 3 

There were admittedly cases, though, of breakdowns in discipline. On the island of Semarang in the Dutch East Indies (now Indonesia), for instance, an army unit forcibly rounded up a group of young Dutch women to work at a "comfort station." The station was shut down under army orders, though, when this incident came to light, and the responsible officers were punished. Those involved in this and other war crimes were subsequently tried in Dutch courts and received heavy sentences, including the death penalty. 

Fact 4 

House Resolution 121 sponsored by US Representative Mike Honda and other charges of Japanese maltreatment of "comfort women" are mostly based on testimonies by former ianfu. In none of their initial statements are there references to their being coerced to work by the army or other units of the Japanese government. 

Their testimonies have undergone dramatic changes, though, after the start of the anti-Japanese campaign. Those who testified in a House of Representatives public hearing first reported that they were whisked away by brokers, but then later claimed that their abductors were clothing that "looked like police uniforms." 

Fact 5 

The ianfu who were embedded with the Japanese army were not, as is commonly reported, "sex slaves." 

They were working under a system of licensed prostitution that was commonplace around the world at the time. Many of the women, in fact, earned incomes far in excess of what were paid to field officers and even generals (as reported by the United States Office of War Information, Psychological Warfare Team Attached to U.S. Army Forces, India-Burma Theater, APO 689), and there are many testimonies attesting to the fact that they were treated well. 

There are records of soldiers being punished for acts of violence against the women. Many countries set up brothels for their armies, in fact, to prevent soldiers from committing rape against private citizens. (In 1945, for instance, Occupation authorities asked the Japanese government to set up hygienic and safe "comfort stations" to prevent rape by American soldiers.) 

Sadly, many women were made to suffered severe hardships during the wretched era during World War II, and it is with profound regret that we contemplate this tragic historical reality. 

At the same time, we must note that it is a gross and deliberate distortion of reality to contend that the Japanese army was guilty of "coercing young women into sexual slavery" in "one of the largest cases of human trafficking in the 20th century," as the House Resolution claims. After all, two-fifth of the approximately 20,000 ianfu during the war were Japanese women, as detailed in an academic paper by historian Ikuhiko Hata. 

I am interested, foremost, in sharing the truth with the world, NOT THE paid korean propaganda and lies. Criticism for events that actually occurred must be humbly embraced. But apologies over unfounded slander and defamation will not only give the public an erroneous impression of historical reality but could negatively affect the friendship between the United States and Japan. We ask only that the Facts be objectively regarded so that we may share a correct perception of history.﻿

Meer lezen (170 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-nXeD4sbm7pw/UZl6-xJb7iI/AAAAAAAAJY4/Kaq6LrPba8g/w426-h237/hakujin%2Bsuppan2%25281%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/113630612440279083293/albums/5870141602455424113/5870141606987999890?authkey=CI-Xw52gs-_f8QE</link><title>Just in case you've forgotten how Charles and David Koch engage in extreme unethical behavior, here's some reminders. Don't forget, dozens of high-level Republicans will be joining with the Kochs on April 28-29 to discuss how to further destroy America. 

For six decades around the world, Koch Industries has blazed a path to riches -- in part, by making illicit payments to win contracts, trading with a terrorist state, fixing prices, neglecting safety and ignoring environmental regulations. At the same time, Charles and David Koch have promoted a form of government that interferes less with company actions. 

Koch Brothers Flout Law Getting Richer With Secret Iran Sales 

In May 2008, a unit of Koch Industries Inc., one of the world’s largest privately held companies, sent Ludmila Egorova-Farines, its newly hired compliance officer and ethics manager, to investigate the management of a subsidiary in Arles in southern France. In less than a week, she discovered that the company had paid bribes to win contracts. Koch Industries fired her in June 2009, calling her incompetent, even after Koch’s investigators substantiated her findings. She sued Koch-Glitsch in France for wrongful termination. 

Charles, 75, and David, 71, each worth about $20 billion, are prominent financial backers of groups that believe that excessive regulation is sapping the competitiveness of American business. They inherited their anti-government leanings from their father. 

_Not happy to be excessively wealthy by stealing, paying bribes, causing deaths, and severely damaging the environment*, the Kochs use their wealth for purposes of dismantling America's democracy and social system: 

Abolishing Social Security 

In 1980, David Koch ran for vice president on the Libertarian ticket, pledging to abolish Social Security, the Federal Reserve System, welfare, minimum wage laws and federal agencies -- including the Department of Energy, the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Central Intelligence Agency. 

What many people don’t know is how the Kochs’ anti- regulation political ideology has influenced the way they conduct business. 

A Bloomberg Markets investigation has found that Koch Industries -- in addition to being involved in improper payments to win business in Africa, India and the Middle East\-- has sold millions of dollars of petrochemical equipment to Iran, a country the U.S. identifies as a sponsor of global terrorism. 

The Koch Method is To Lie, Cheat, and Steal To Get Ahead 

Internal company documents show that the company made those sales to Iran through foreign subsidiaries, thwarting a U.S. trade ban. Koch Industries units have also rigged prices with competitors, lied to regulators and repeatedly run afoul of environmental regulations, resulting in five criminal convictions since 1999 in the U.S. and Canada. 

From 1999 through 2003, Koch Industries was assessed more than $400 million in fines, penalties and judgments. In December 1999, a civil jury found that Koch Industries had taken oil it didn’t pay for from federal land by mismeasuring the amount of crude it was extracting. Koch paid a $25 million settlement to the U.S. 

Death of Others Matters Not to These Evil Twins 

In 1999, a Texas jury imposed a $296 million verdict on a Koch pipeline unit -- the largest compensatory damages judgment in a wrongful death case against a corporation in U.S. history. The jury found that the company’s negligence had led to a butane pipeline rupture that fueled an explosion that killed two teenagers. 

Sally Barnes-Soliz, who’s now an investigator for the State Department of Labor and Industries in Washington, says that when she worked for Koch, her bosses and a company lawyer at the Koch refinery in Corpus Christi, Texas, asked her to falsify data for a report to the state on uncontrolled emissions of benzene, a known cause of cancer. Barnes-Soliz, who testified to a federal grand jury, says she refused to alter the numbers. 

“They didn’t know what to do with me,” she says. “They were really kind of baffled that I had ethics.” 

“How much lawless behavior are we going to tolerate from any one company?” asks David Uhlmann, who oversaw the prosecution of the Koch refinery division when he was chief of the environmental crimes unit at the U.S. Department of Justice. “Corporate cultures reflect the priorities of the corporation and its senior officials.” 

Lobbying Washington 
Since David Koch had to deal with severe humiliation after losing his 1980 political bid as veep to Ed Clark, including ridicule by 99% of the public, the brothers have worked behind the scenes to advance their perverted ideology. 

The Koch brothers have vaulted into the American political spotlight in recent years. Koch Industries has spent more than $50 million to lobby in Washington since 2006, according to the Center for Responsive Politics, a nonpartisan group that tracks political donations. The company opposed derivatives regulation and greenhouse gas limits. 

The brothers have backed a foundation that has trained thousands of Tea Party activists. Sixty representatives of Congress, out of a total of 435, identify themselves as Tea Party members. Virtually every Republican candidate for president -- including Texas Governor Rick Perry and Minnesota Congresswoman Michele Bachmann -- has solicited the group’s support. 

http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2011-10-02/koch-brothers-flout-law-getting-richer-with-secret-iran-sales.html 

Charles, David Koch try to oust Obama, limit government 

The Kochs aren’t finished. Win or lose in November, they plan to start a new fight. They are organizing dozens of groups to build support for eliminating all corporate and agricultural subsidies. 

Well, that sounds great, right? NO, only because of the motive behind this change of heart: 

“How is any American going to feel good about reforming Medicare, Medicaid and Social Security when there is so much cronyism going on with these companies, and businessmen are making off with so many tax dollars?” Fink asked. Rich Fink is the brother's longtime political strategist. 

The Kochs won’t say how much they are spending or specifically what they are doing to defeat Obama, but it’s enough to prompt critics to question how much political influence one family should have. 

“The Koch political machine is the most elaborate, comprehensive financial dip into American politics since Standard Oil and the robber barons a century ago,” said Larry Jacobs, a political scientist at the University of Minnesota. 

“This is the 21st century version of how you buy yourself a government in America.” 

‘RULING ELITE’ 

The Kochs think government is an obstacle to making money that should be removed, said Jim Steele, who with Don Barlett just released “The Betrayal of the American Dream.” The book accuses the “ruling elite” — including the Kochs — of impoverishing the American middle class by pushing initiatives such as deregulation, outsourcing and balanced budgets to enrich themselves. 

“We feel that the views of the foundations that they support … have been really instrumental in undermining the economic well-being of the middle class,” Steele said. 

Free markets to the Kochs mean freedom to make money, Steele said. 

The Kochs have spent more than three decades building a sophisticated network of think tanks, university researchers and citizen groups to advocate for limited government, lower taxes and limited regulation. 

One of the biggest idea generators is the Mercatus Center, started by Fink with seed money from Charles Koch. The group has studied the privatization of Social Security and analyzed environmental regulations. 

In 2004, The Wall Street Journal called the Mercatus Center the most important think tank you’ve never heard of. When President George W. Bush’s Office of Management and Budget sought suggestions for regulations in need of reform, 14 of the 23 “high priority” changes it considered came from Mercatus. Eight of those dealt with environmental regulations. 

http://www.idahostatesman.com/2012/10/21/2317856/brothers-in-political-arms.html#storylink=cpy 

It's time for these two, old, perverted destroyers of the American Dream to butt out...permanently. Six foot under would satisfy permanently. 

#kochbrothers   #perverted   #greedylyingbastards  ﻿

Meer lezen (180 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-pX0FJ0zEAus/UXbusLHCqpI/AAAAAAABH90/Ih-jH_nJKWU/w426-h321/koch-brothers-letter425x320.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/113868135922706813676/albums/6014796154014336385/6014796157768893202</link><title>U.S. National Climate Assessment Released This Month 

The U.S. National Climate Assessment has been released this month. The report takes an in-depth look at the scientific evidence of climate change in the United States. The first sentence of the Introduction reads "Climate change, once considered an issue for a distant future, has moved firmly into the present." The assessment goes on to report "key findings" in 12 areas, including extreme weather, human health, and agriculture. 

The report website has some very nice interactive graphics. See the Overview here: 
http://nca2014.globalchange.gov/highlights/overview/overview 

#climatechange   #globalwarming   #visualization   #science   #sciencecommunication   #nationalclimateassessment  ﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/--M7KE6qiI8A/U3jZPNwzAxI/AAAAAAAAINw/AKjUO7sTlOQ/w426-h335/NCA.tiff</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7086-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/falsifying%20pictures%2021st%20centurie/photos/103395051486199182632/albums/5983075725199771969/5983075725804809826?sqi=115648838428680928177&amp;sqsi=8114aaf7-053b-4af7-af65-10a05e7aa445</link><title>The Arab slave trade was the practice of slavery in the Arab world, mainly in Western Asia, North Africa, Southeast Africa, the Horn of Africa and certain parts of Europe (such as Iberia and Sicily) during their period of domination by Arab leaders. The trade was focused on the slave markets of the Middle East, North Africa and the Horn of Africa. People traded were not limited to a certain race, ethnicity, or religion.[1] 

During the 8th and 9th centuries of the Fatimid Caliphate, most of the slaves were Europeans (called Saqaliba) captured along European coasts and during wars.[2] Historians estimate that between 650 and 1900, 10 to 18 million peoples were enslaved by Arab slave traders and taken from Africa across the Red Sea, Indian Ocean, and Sahara desert.[3] However, slaves were drawn from a wide variety of regions and included Mediterranean peoples, Persians, peoples from the Caucasus mountain regions (such as Georgia, Armenia and Circassia) and parts of Central Asia and Scandinavia, English, Dutch and Irish, Berbers from North Africa, and various other peoples of varied origins as well as those of African origins.[citation needed] 

Toward the 18th and 19th centuries, the flow of Zanj (Bantu) slaves from Southeast Africa increased with the rise of the Oman sultanate, which was based in Zanzibar in Tanzania. They came into direct trade conflict and competition with Portuguese and other Europeans along the Swahili coast.[4] The North African Barbary states carried on piracy against European shipping and enslaved thousands of European Christians. They earned revenues from the ransoms charged; in many cases in Britain, village churches and communities would raise money for such ransoms. The British government did not ransom its citizens. 

Historians estimate that between 650 and 1900, 10 to 18 million peoples were enslaved by Arab slave traders and taken from Africa across the Red Sea, Indian Ocean, and Sahara desert.[5][6][7][8] The term Arab when used in historical documents often represented an ethnic term, as many of the "Arab" slave traders, such as Tippu Tip and others, were physically indistinguishable from the "Africans" whom they enslaved and sold. Due to the nature of the Arab slave trade, it is impossible to be precise about actual numbers.[9][10][11] 

A recent and controversial topic 
The history of the slave trade has given rise to numerous debates amongst historians. For one thing, specialists are undecided on the number of Africans taken from their homes; this is difficult to resolve because of a lack of reliable statistics: there was no census system in medieval Africa. Archival material for the transatlantic trade in the 16th to 18th centuries may seem useful as a source, yet these record books were often falsified. Historians have to use imprecise narrative documents to make estimates which must be treated with caution: Luiz Felipe de Alencastro states that there were 8 million slaves taken from Africa between the 8th and 19th centuries along the Oriental and the Trans-Saharan routes.[32] 

Olivier Pétré-Grenouilleau has put forward a figure of 17 million African people enslaved (in the same period and from the same area) on the basis of Ralph Austen's work.[33] Paul Bairoch suggests a figure of 25 million African people subjected to the Arab slave trade, as against 11 million that arrived in the Americas from the transatlantic slave trade.[34] Ronald Segal estimates between 11.5 and 14 million were enslaved by the Arab slave trade.[35][36][37] 

Another obstacle to a history of the Arab slave trade is the limitations of extant sources. There exist documents from non-African cultures, written by educated men in Arabic, but these only offer an incomplete and often condescending look at the phenomenon. For some years there has been a huge amount of effort going into historical research on Africa. Thanks to new methods and new perspectives, historians can interconnect contributions from archaeology, numismatics, anthropology, linguistics and demography to compensate for the inadequacy of the written record.[citation needed] 

The Arab trade of Zanj (Bantu) slaves in Southeast Africa is one of the oldest slave trades, predating the European transatlantic slave trade by 700 years.[38][39][40] Male slaves were often employed as servants, soldiers, or laborers by their owners, while female slaves, including those from Africa, were long traded to the Middle Eastern countries and kingdoms by Arab and Oriental traders as concubines and servants. Arab, African and Oriental traders were involved in the capture and transport of slaves northward across the Sahara desert and the Indian Ocean region into the Middle East, Persia and the Far East.[39][40] 

The most significant Jewish involvement in the slave-trade was in Al-Andalus, as Islamic Spain was called.[41] According to historian Alan W. Fisher, there was a guild of Jewish slave traders in Constantinople, the capital of the Ottoman Empire. The guild had about 2000 members.[21] The city was a major center of the slave trade in the 15th and later centuries. By 1475 most of the slaves were provided by Tatar raids on Slavic villages.[21] Until the late 18th century, the Crimean Khanate maintained a massive slave trade with the Ottoman Empire and the Middle East, exporting about 2 million slaves from Poland-Lithuania and Russia over the period 1500–1700.[42]﻿

Meer lezen (90 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7086_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-8U5GsKg6gc0/UwgnrETbrmI/AAAAAAAAHIg/URESqefBG-A/w426-h355/2014%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>