<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7089">varese ionisation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:43:20" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7089-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/varese%20ionisation/photos/118147601998005724143/albums/5682818444202258673/5682818445320494626</link><title>KSC Percussion Ensemble 

When: Thursday, 8 December 2011 
Time: 7:30pm 
Where: Alumni Recital Hall, Redfern Arts Center, Keene State College 

Let the Keene State College Percussion Ensemble take you on a chronological tour of early American percussion ensemble music from 1929-1941. Works to be performed in order of composition are Amadeo Roldán’s Ritmicas No. 5 &amp; 6, Edgard Varèse’s Ionisation, Henry Cowell’s Ostinato Pianissimo, John Cage’s Living Room Music, and Lou Harrison’s Labyrinth No. 3. These works represent a select group of 20th-Century composers who scored original works for percussion ensemble in search of new sounds. In this search for new sound, they created the foundation for the modern percussion ensemble. The pieces are scored from 4 to 13 players and take advantage of a wide array of instruments from the standard drums, cymbals, and gongs to the not so standard rice bowls, glasses, bottles, handsaws, playing cards and magazines. Please join us for this rare opportunity to hear this classic literature performed consecutively.﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7089_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-9gk7DCwG0gI/Tt1tRGRdniI/AAAAAAAAACk/f5OLQ8iBUNE/w426-h656/372954_206497182759308_1027759907_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7089-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/varese%20ionisation/photos/106416358990735869560/albums/5980685194765369041/5980685197057207442</link><title>Drei Klangvisionäre auf einer CD: Mariss Jansons deutet Hector Berlioz’ „Symphonie fantastique“ und „Ionisation“ von Edgard Varèse. Mariss Jansons, Chefdirigent des Symphonieorchesters des Bayerischen Rundfunks, spürt in zwei epochalen Werken der Musikgeschichte romantischen Traumwelten nach und lässt komplexe musikalische 
Strukturen zum unmittelbar sinnlich erlebbaren Ereignis werden. http://bit.ly/1fbPTg1﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7089_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-sEGNpTHPUQ0/Uv-pf-wILJI/AAAAAAAACJY/VTTMqj-w5BY/w426-h375/900121.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7089-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/varese%20ionisation/photos/114963786071989905755/albums/5751834770704999729/5751834768330026418</link><title>THE IMPORTANCE OF UNDERSTANDING LANGUAGE 

“In fact, since language is largely a mental phenomenon, its study may be Con-Sidered a branch of Psychology. An adequate theory of human psychology must give some account of thought processes; language is of central importance here because so many of our thoughts assume linguistic form. 

The relationship between language and concept formation is of great in-terest to psychologist, since many if not most of our concepts are given verbal labels of some sort. 

Language also provides a significant test for theories of psychological organization. Language are highly structured, and we have learned to identify and describe their structure in considerable detail; any theory of psychological organization, therefore must adequately accommodate the kinds of structures we know to be characteristic of human languages. 

The Concepts and techniques of linguistic analysis have influenced the other social sciences to some degree, anthropology in particular. 

Since language is more obviously structured than other facets of human psy-chology, such as systems of belief or networks of social organizations, social scientists interested in these other domains may learn something of value from the analysis of language.” 

Language And It's Structure 
Some fundamental linguistic concepts 
Ronald W. Langacker 

A Thumbnail History of Language Study 

“Western grammatical tradition can be traced to the ancient Greeks, who raised the question of whether there is something essential in the rela-tion between a word and the thing to which it refers or whether the relation is an arbitrary one. 

For example, is there some way in which the word “fish” is especially (or uniquely) suited to the creatures we “angle” for with hook, line, and sinker, or is the fact that we call these creatures fish just an accident of linguistic history.” 

Language And It's Structure 
Some fundamental linguistic concepts 
Ronald W. Langacker 

ar·chi·mage (är'kə-māj') n. A great magician or chief wizard. [Late Greek 

arkhimagos : ARCH- + magos, magician, from Old Persian maguš (see magh- 1 in Appendix*).] 

ar·chi·man·drite (är'kə-măn'drīt') n. Greek Orthodox Church. 1. A cleric ranking below a bishop. 2. The head of a monastery or group of monasteries and the equivalent of a Western abbot. [Late Latin archimandrītēs, archimandrīta, from Late Greek archimandrītēs ARCH- + mandraϯ, monastery, from Greek, enclosure, cattle pen.] 

Ar·chi·me·de·an (är'kə-mē'dē-ən, -mī-dē-ən) adj. Of or per-taining to Archimedes or his inventions. 

Archimedean screw. An ancient apparatus for raising water, consisting of either a spiral tube around an inclined axis or an inclined tube containing a tight-fitting, broad-threaded screw. Also called “Archimedes' screw.” 

Ar·chi·me·des (är'kə-mē'dē-z). 287?-212 B.C. Greek mathe-matician; made discoveries in mechanics and hydrostatics. 

ar·chine (är-shēn) n. Also ar·shin. A Russian unit of linear measure equivalent to 28 inches. [Russian arshin, of Turkic origin, akin to Turkish and Kazan Tatar aršyn, An ell.] 

Ar·chi·pen·ko (är'kĭ-pĕng'kō), Alexander (Porfirievich). 1887-1964. Russian-born American abstract sculptor. 
archit. Architecture 

ar·chi·tect (är'kə-tĕkt') n. abbr. arch., archt. 1. One who de-signs and supervises the construction of buildings or other large structures. 2. Any planner or deviser: “Chief architect and plot-ter of these woes.” (Shakespeare). [Old French architecte, from Latin architectus, archhitectōn, from Greek arkhitektōn, master builder : ARCH- + tektōn, carpenter,craftsman (see teks- in Appendix*).] 

ar·chi·tec·ton·ic (är'kə-tĕk-tŏn'ĭk) adj. Also ar·chi·tec·ton·i·cal (-ĭ-kəl). 1. Of or pertaining to architecture or design. 2. Having qualities characteristic of architecture; designed and structured. 3. Philosophy. Relating to the scientific systematiza-tion of knowledge. 

ar·chi·tec·ture (är'kə-tĕk-tŏn'ĭk) n. Abbr. arch., archit. 1. The art and science of designing and erecting buildings. 2. A structure of structures collectively. 3. A style and method of design and construction: Byzantine architecture. 4. Any design or orderly arrangement perceived by man: the architecture of nature. [Old French, from Latin architectūra, from architectus, ARCHI-TECT.] -ar'chi·tec'tur·al adj. -ar'chi·tec'tur·al·ly adv. 

ar·chi·trave (är'kə-trāv') n. Architecture. 1. The lowermost part of an entablature, resting directly on top of a colum in clas-sical architecture. Also called “epistyle.” 2. The molding around a door or window. [Old French, from Old Italian, “chief beam” : ARCH- trave, beam, from Latin trabs (see treb- in Appendix*).] 

ar·chi·val (är'kī'vəl) adj. Of, pertaining to, or kept in archives. 

ar·chi·val (är'kīvz) pl.n 1. An organized body of records per-taining to an organization or institution. 2. A place in which such records are preserved. 3. Any repository of evidence or information: the archives of the mind. [French, originally sin-gular archive, from Late Latin archīum, archīvum, from Greek arkheion, public offfice (plural arkheia, public records, archives), from arkhē, beginning, hence first place, government, from arkhein, to begin. See arkhein in Appendix.*] 

THE NATURE AND DEVELOPMENT OF THE THAI LANGUAGE 

“Fund-a-mentally the Thai language in mono-sylla-bic in its formation of words. It is a characteristic to be found also in Chinese and, more or less, in other language groups of South-East Asia. Due to the limited number of combinations of sounds which consonants admit, there arises naturally a multitude of words with the same sound but with a difference in meaning ( = homonyms)... Any word may become a noun, a verb, an adjective or adverb, etc., simply through the position of the word in the sentence.” 

Examples of a euphonic word: 
“Ngo” means “stupid” in Thai and has “ngau” as its euphonic ending” 
“Nga” is identical with the Thai “nga” meaning tusk, ivory. 

PERSEPOLIS ~ 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Persepolis_%28film%29 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Persepolis﻿

Meer lezen (135 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7089_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-DHBcxmnb6VQ/T9KfP00NbbI/AAAAAAAAAT0/OWMVCgZfHOM/w426-h320/ActOfTheCoverNet.wmv</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>