<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:03:00" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/100087422333079667433/albums/5820749921026394449/5820749920986834178?authkey=CMWc04HnyZKf2QE</link><title>This is my biggest seller. 50,000 grain capacity Fleck Water Softener 
If your water supply has an extreme amout of Iron, Smell, or black Manganese then You will probably also need an iron filter.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/--3DeZIPQGNM/UMd1NqbNpQI/AAAAAAAAAKE/4QvOEF0Z5ug/w426-h568/camera%252520089.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/100282968888030008096/albums/5659050981433089569/5659050980952610626</link><title>Red iron oxide that I made with a couple of iron screws and an old wall-wart power supply. Most of the time, iron oxide is considered a by-product of the electrolysis process. Today, I was specifically looking for it. 

The chemical starts out black and turns a ruddish brown as the water evaporates on the edges of the container. After a few hours, there is a ring of red powder around the edge of the electrolysis container, that I could easily sweep up with a paint brush and apply to a canvas. Basically watercolor painting.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-wXSAYLXLW8g/Toj84l2Bl0I/AAAAAAAACPU/Uw26rJY_mio/w426-h336/eye2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/103264645106286817206/albums/5866657289852602689/5866657286939337650?authkey=CJeL4vPD8qDR7QE</link><title>Blood iron and vitamins needed by the body 

al shortness of breath during physical activity. 
5 - rapid heartbeat. 
6 - Cold hands and feet. 
7 - Headache - Dizziness - feeling of light-headedness. 
8 - brittle nails. 
9 - tinnitus and ringing in the ears. 
10 - Irritability - sleepiness - reduced learning - poor concentration. 
11 - a painful inflammation of the tongue. 
12 - Loss of appetite, especially in infants and children. 
13 - chest pain. 
14 - frequent infections. 
15 - longiAnemia or anemia (anemia) occurs when the level of hemoglobin (hemoglobin) in your blood decreases. Hemoglobin is the protein in red blood cells that carries oxygen from the lungs to all parts of the body. Hemoglobin in red blood is due. To report site to Doctors Without Borders, a large body of red blood cells in the bone marrow (eg, hip) are produced. Bone marrow to make red blood cells, hemoglobin, iron, vitamin b12 and folic acid needs. Iron deficiency anemia is a common cause. Symptoms of anemia: 
1 - can be asymptomatic. 
2 - pale skin, gums, and nail beds. 
3 - Fatigue and weakness - reduced vigor - insomnia. 
4 - Unusung for unusual non-food substances such as ice, starch, or dirt. 
16 - difficulty swallowing. Causes of low blood iron levels: 
1 - Lack of sufficient iron in the diet. 
2 - adolescent growth spurt in children under 3 years. 
3 - Pregnancy: Pregnant or lactating women need more iron. 
4 - monthly menstrual blood loss. 
5 - loss of blood donation. 
6 - loss of blood due to internal bleeding: ulcers, and tumors of the kidney and bladder cancer, non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs such as aspirin and ibuprofen taking too much (causing bleeding into the stomach and intestines), hemorrhoids (piles), colon polyps large uterine fibroids, hiatal hernia and colon cancer can cause internal bleeding and iron deficiency. Internal bleeding in the presence of blood in the urine and feces (stool black color) displays. 
7 - inability to absorb iron: Iron is absorbed through the small intestine. Intestinal disorders such as Crohn's disease, crohn's some food in the intestinal absorption of iron deficiency is caused by disturbed. Also, by removing part of the colon surgery reduces the absorption of iron. 
8 - interfere with iron absorption from the intestine: the consumption of food sources of dietary iron absorption reduces the following we will refer to them. 
Note: The cause of anemia in healthy men and women who have left behind during menopause is likely to be internal bleeding. Diagnostic procedures: 
1 - blood iron levels tested. 
2 - Trnsfryn measuring protein (transferrin) (iron carrier protein from the intestines) 
3 - Measurement of serum ferritin levels (ferritin) (iron storage protein) 
4 - Measured hematocrit (hematocrit) (percentage of blood volume that is occupied by red blood cells and hemoglobin or red blood cells to total blood volume) 
5 - and Kvlvnskvpy endoscopy (viewing the colon using special equipment) 
Note: Ferritin levels can be misleading, because the damage to the liver, inflammation, infection and cancer, the ferritin level in a false increase. 
Note: Iron deficiency anemia may develop slowly over time. It may take several months to complete body iron stores are used. As iron stores gradually reduced bone marrow production of red blood cells is low. Prevalence of Anemia: 
On average, one out of every five women with iron deficiency anemia - a half of pregnant women are anemic iron deficiency. Risk factors for anemia: 
1 - Women who have menstrual bleeding is severe. 
2 - pregnant women. 
3 - Inadequate dietary iron. 
4 - infants and children. Babies and children who do not get enough iron through breast milk during the growth spurt are. 
5 - vegetarians: Because they do not eat meat, the iron in grains and plants, as well as the iron in meat is not absorbed by the body. 
6 - Women. Because lower body iron stores and lose blood during menstruation. 
7 - the source of internal bleeding: ulcers, tumors, uterine fibroids, polyps, colon (large intestine), colon cancer, hemorrhoids, and intestinal bleeding. Complications of untreated anemia: 
1 - heart problems: irregular and rapid heart rate and low blood CAD leads to angina. Compensate for decreased oxygen in the blood, the heart must pump more blood. 
2 - birth defects: Severe iron deficiency can lead to premature birth or low birth weight. 
3 - developmental problems in infants and children with growth delay. 
4 - General issues: increased risk of infection, decreased learning and memory, fatigue and lethargy etc.. Absorption, transport, storage and excretion of iron from the body: 
1 - absorption through the intestine occurs. Intestinal mucosal cells with Pvfrytyn protein (apoferritin) iron control. (By reducing the production of this protein is reduced iron stores and increased iron stores during the production of this protein is increased.) 
2 - Then Trnsfryn protein (transferrin) 75% iron to the bone marrow (for making red blood cells) ,20-10% of the ferritin iron storage (ferritin) and 15-15% of the iron in the blood to other processes carry. Each protein Trnsfryn carry two iron ions (ferric form) is. 
3 - iron in ferritin molecules (ferritin) is saved. The ferritin iron atom is able to store four thousand. 
4 - Full Ferritin is the iron storage capacity, Hmvsydryn (haemosiderin) in hepatic iron stores. 
5 - As the oxygen-carrying hemoglobin in red blood cells, the myoglobin (myoglobin) to protein storage and transport of oxygen in muscle cells. 
6 - the body does not have any mechanism to excrete iron physiology. So absorbed in the intestines is strictly controlled. (With low iron stores, iron absorption is increased) 
7 - small quantities of iron daily through perspiration, loss of skin cells lining the intestines and is excreted. The amount of iron excreted by taking 1-2 mg of iron from the diet will compensate. 
Note: The male body and the female body about 4 grams, 3 grams of iron (36-60 mg iron per kg of body weight) 0.2 / 3 the amount of iron in hemoglobin and myoglobin, and the remainder in the liver (as ferritin and Hmvsydryn ), bone marrow and spleen are stored. 
Note: The body recycles iron. Lifetime ends when the red blood cells, iron is returned to the bone marrow to be used again in the manufacture of red blood cells. 
Note: The average lifespan of a red blood cell is 120 days. Iron functions in the body: 
1 - hemoglobin and myoglobin (transport and storage of oxygen in the blood and muscles) 
2 - Iron is found in some immune enzymes. Thus, the absence or deficiency of the immune system weakens. 
3 - Iron is essential for the chemical reactions to produce energy from food. Thus, iron deficiency leads to loss of energy in the body. 
4 - Iron is involved in cell division and production of neurotransmitters. 
5 - Iron is important in production of the protein collagen. The recommended amount of iron: 
1 - 10 mg per day for adult men. 
2 - Women 11 to 50 years: 15 to 18 mg daily. 
3 - Women above 50 years: 10 mg daily. 
4 - Pregnant women: 30 mg daily. 
5 - Youth male: 16 mg daily. 
6 - adolescent girls: daily 27 mg. 
7 - Children 1-10 years: 7-10 mg daily. Iron poisoning: 
Doctors Without Borders report site, need more iron in the blood is toxic to humans. Because excess ferrous iron reacts with peroxides in the body of free radicals are produced. When the iron-saturated protein Trnsfryn and physiological mechanisms of the body to excrete excess iron does not have any, iron toxicity is provided. When iron intake of 20 mg per kg of body exceeds the toxicity of iron and 60 mg per kg of body weight would be beyond death. 
Note: It usually take 25-75 mg of iron per day in adults is tolerated. 
Tip: Healthy men and women who have gone through menopause and suffering from anemia should not take multi-vitamins containing iron. Causes an increase in blood iron level: 
1 - disease, hemochromatosis (hemochromatosis): a genetic disorder that increases iron absorption from the intestine. 
2 - excessive intake of iron supplements. 
3 - Receive frequent blood. Symptoms of iron levels: 
1 - fatigue and weakness. 
2 - lose weight. 
3 - shortness of breath. 
4 - palpitations. 
5 - chronic abdominal pain. 
6 - * S * goblin impairment in activities of 
7th - changes in skin pigmentation (gray or yellow spots on the skin). 
8 - joint pain and fatigue. Effects of excess iron accumulation in the blood. 
1 - iron in the liver, pancreas, endocrine glands, heart, skin, intestines and joints and can be stacked. Iron accumulation in the coronary organ damage, heart failure, liver cancer, liver cirrhosis, colon cancer will follow. 
2 - excessive intake of iron supplements cause vomiting, diarrhea, and damage to the intestines. 
3 - Iron pills can be very dangerous for children and can be fatal. So take iron supplements out of the reach of children. Treatment: 
1 - pills Deferoxamine (deferoxamine), which is excreted from the body by binding to the iron atoms. 
2 - bloodletting (the disease, hemochromatosis) forms of iron: 
1 - ferrous iron (ferrous) fe +2 
2 - ferric iron (ferric) fe +3 
Note: ferric iron will be absorbed better than ferrous iron. 
Note: Most of the ferrous iron in the ferrous iron and ferric iron than is found in most. 
1 - iron (haem): red meat, poultry, fish and liver are found. (Hemoglobin and myoglobin of meat is supplied) 
2 - Non-time-iron (non haem): vegetables, herbs, dairy products, fruits, grains, nuts (nuts) and eggs are found. 
Note: The iron content of red meat more than it is. 
Note: iron means iron atoms to molecules bind together, and the meaning of non-ferrous metal binding to the molecule. 
Note: with a variety of food sources does not interfere with iron absorption. (Unlike non-time-iron) 
Note: only 10-20% of the iron consumed, and only 2-10% of the body absorb iron intake Ghyrhm. 
Note: 10-25% of the iron and steel, non-ferrous metal lunch together make up 75 to 90 percent. 
Note: A good source of iron in cow's milk and goat, not iron. It contains very little iron, and only 5% of it is absorbed. 
Note: the iron in breast milk is no exception. Despite the low levels of iron in breast milk, but also acts like iron and iron absorption in the body for up to 50 percent. 
The diet should be composed of iron-rich foods rich in iron and Ghyrhm be combined. Factors affecting the absorption of non-time: 
1 - factors other than the increased iron absorption: 
* Low iron stores in the body. 
* Hydrochloric acid in the stomach. (Otherwise the iron will turn into a time) 
* Vitamin c. 
* Thankful for. 
* Sources of heme iron (red meat, poultry and fish) 
* Amino Acids. 
* Citric Acid. 
2 - factors other than the decrease in iron absorption: 
* Tea, coffee and cocoa. (Due to the presence of tannins and phenolic) 
* Milk and cheese. 
* Reduce stomach acid (antacid) 
* Oxalic acid (oxalic) in spinach. 
* Phytic acid (phytic) in the bran. 
* Calcium, copper, magnesium, manganese and zinc compete with iron absorption. So much of any of them leads to iron deficiency. 
* An increase in iron stores in the body. 
* Aspirin. 
* Egg yolk. 
* Fiber. 
Note: vitamin c along with meat or vegetables and other non-ferrous materials, the absorption is not the same as 4 times. 
Note: At least two hours after a meal, drink tea and coffee. 
Sources of vitamin c: 
Broccoli - Kiwi - tomatoes - citrus (lemon and tangerine Portugal) - green pepper - strawberries. Iron-rich foods: 
1 - liver. 
2 - red meat, fish and poultry. 
3 - seafood. 
4 - Dry fruits like apricots, prunes and raisins. 
5 - vegetables (spinach and broccoli) 
6 - complete whole grains (whole-wheat) 
7 - iron-fortified breads and cereals. 
8 - Brains. 
Note: due to a vitamin in the liver (causing harm to the fetus) in pregnant women should not use the liver as a source of iron. Iron supplements: 
There are two types of ferrous and ferric to ferrous form is better absorbed by the body. 
1 - ferrous sulfate (ferrous sulfate) 
2 - ferrous gluconate (ferrous gluconate) 
3 - ferrous fumarate (ferrous fumarate) 
4 - ferrous Svkynat (ferrous succinate) 
5 - Capsule Hmatynyk (hematinic): contains iron + folic acid + vitamin b12 and vitamin c as well. 
Note: Iron supplements cause black stools are painted. Side effects of iron supplements: 
1 - heartburn. 
2 - constipation or diarrhea. 
3 - abdominal pain. 
4 - stimulates the digestive tract. 
5 - nausea. How to use: 
Take half an hour before meals. If constipation is associated with fiber consumption. 
Note: The use of low-dose iron supplements start and gradually reach the level recommended by your doctor. 
Tip: Better take iron supplements along with the sources of vitamin c. 
Note: If you are prescribed iron supplements for anemia treatment should be used continuously for at least 3-6 weeks. 
Note: only 20 percent of the iron in iron supplements are absorbed. 
 or megaloblastic anemia (megaloblastic): 
Deficiency of vitamin b12 and folic acid (folate) can cause the bone marrow to produce red blood cells larger than normal size, which is not enough hemoglobin. Anaemia in erythrocyte numbers decreased production. Its symptoms are similar to symptoms of anemia. Underlying causes of inadequate intakes of these vitamins through diet or intestinal trouble attracting them. Of folate and vitamin b12 supplements to cure. 
Food sources of vitamin b12: Liver - beef - tuna - Road - Milk - Cheese - Eggs. 
Folic acid sources: Liver - Kidney - meat - beans (white kidney beans) - soybean - wheat bran - vegetables (spinach, kale, lettuce, M. Rchvbh) - fruits (bananas, water and Portugal) 
Prevention and control of vitamin A: 
Vitamin A is one of the essential nutrients and important role in the health of the body organs. The vitamins in the prevention of infection, healthy skin and mucosal tissues of the mouth, gastrointestinal tract, respiratory tract, eyes, and has a considerable impact on the supply of child development. 
Vitamin A deficiency is one of the most important problems in developing countries is nutrition.million children worldwide under age 5 are at risk of vitamin A deficiency. 
Vitamin A deficiency in children with symptoms such as reduced growth rate, increased mortality and morbidity in children with infectious diseases, especially measles, diarrhea and respiratory infections are associated. So that the risk of infection and death for children 2 to 4 times the rate increases. 
Vitamin A deficiency bat, damage to the cornea (dry eye) and ultimately will lead to complete blindness. 
In a society that has suffered one percent of children under six can bat, vitamin A deficiency is a public health problem in the community. 
According to global estimates, every year from 3/1 to 5/2 million deaths can be prevented by improving vitamin A status. Because of the critical role of vitamin A on maternal and child health, prevention and control of vitamin A deficiency among policy makers and managers of health programs should be a priority. 
Role of vitamin A in the body: 

The biological role of vitamin A in vision, growth, bone development, maintenance of epithelial tissue, immune response and reproduction are known. 
\- Vitamin A for vision, eye health and vision in the dark is essential and a deficiency occurs bat. Bat or loss of sight in the darkness, the first sign of vitamin A deficiency is. 
\- Vitamin A deficiency also causes loss of mucus secreted by the epithelial cells of the skin, resulting in dry skin and mucosal tissues of the body. 
\- Vitamin A is essential for normal bone growth and lack of adverse effects on longitudinal bone growth. 
\- Dedicated to vitamin A in the body's defense mechanism is also essential vitamin deficiency risk of infection (especially diarrhea and respiratory tract infections) and mortality rate of 2 to 4 fold increase. Deficiency of vitamin A, has a longer duration of disease and its severity increases. 

\- Studies have shown that vitamin A acts as a hormone that helps the body cells to grow. 
\- Beta carotene (precursor of vitamin A) your body against the development of cancer, heart disease - cardiovascular and eye diseases such as cataracts, protects. 

Required daily amount of vitamin A: 
Generally required daily amount of vitamin A, based on age, sex and physiological (Barda 
Collapse this post﻿

Meer lezen (322 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-aBDZxOIp7RM/UWqNuDb547I/AAAAAAAAACc/VM47BkTYTts/s426/MyArticle1485288.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/115362678938018929449/albums/5879954134464925121/5879954131552784546?authkey=CLnS9v_I8saVTQ</link><title>This is one of those exceptional products that operates and performs so radically different than everything else it’s difficult to quickly or easily explain.  One of the reasons it gets over-looked is because it uses either potassium chloride or sodium chloride; and because of that, it gets lumped together with all the other salt polluting water softerners.  But it's the only GREEN water conditioner that uses salt and exceeds even the most stringent California environmental standards (intended to ban even the most efficient traditional inline injection water softeners).  And unlike any other competing GREEN products it can actually clean-up the dirtiest water better than the best traditional salt consuming water softeners (and when I say better I mean by a significant margin). 
The small unit shown here stands only about 30" tall (1/2 the size of a traditional salt consuming water softener) and can completely clean-up 50 grain hard water right down to 0.0 ppm (zero parts per million) of total hardness.  It can also remove iron from water so completely and effortlessly it can replace both a dedicated iron removal system and the separate secondary water softener typically accompanying iron removal systems required in areas with the worst possible water.  The more experienced you are at shopping and comparing equipment performance the more you'll realize this product's performance will surpass anything else currently available to condition your household water.  To say the T5000 is an exceptional water conditioner is obviously true; but still seems somewhat of an understatement given its performance lies so far outside the norm and stutus quo of typical water equipment industry standards. 
 A good way to begin explaining just how different this operates is to first describe a very basic problem ALL OTHER salt consuming water softeners have (and a problem this product doesn't have).  Sodium or potassium ions like to sink the bottom of all salt consuming water softener tanks (including this one) because it takes two sodium or two potassium ions to replace one calcium or one magnesium ion (this 2:1 salt ion ratio means the salt will be heavier and naturally sink to the bottom of the tank).  When this happens something very unfortunately and bad eventually happens over time (in all water softeners other than this one).  This natural concentration of salt in the bottom of ALL OTHER water softeners eventually becomes literally a ball of "salt slime"; and try as it may, the inline injection technology used by ALL OTHER salt consuming water softeners cannot rinse away this slime that gradually accumulates in the bottom of the tank. 
Imagine trying to rinse a heavy ball of slime from the bottom of the tank up to the top of the tank and then out the drain?  Unfortunately graviety works against slime rinsing "up hill" so it continues to grow bigger and accumulate in the bottom of the tank day after day.  This salt slime might not be such a big problem for water softeners except for the bacteria that eventually starts growing in the slime.  This type of bacteria is usually not of a dangerous variety so it’s relatively easy to keep this problem quiet in the US where there are no consumer advocacy groups to represent consumer interests or influence the largest manufacturers to offer bacteria free or slime free products.   Eventually the growing concentration of bacteria in the salt slime in the bottom of the tank will cause small fragments of the slime to break loose and flow through your household water supply.  Eventually millions of inline injection water softener owners will (and do) experience a slippery problem.  A problem you can feel when you touch the water. 
This is why some people say they don’t like the slippery feeling of showering or bathing in soft water.  Some people mistakenly believe soft water is supposed to feel slippery because that's their experience.  And it’s true, other than the T5000 all other water softeners using salt will eventually deliver slippery water because the "inline injection" conditioning process they ALL rely on cannot rinse away the bacteria laden slime that grows in the bottom of their tanks.  Unlike all other water softeners the T5000 fortunately does not use inline injection to regenerate and clean its tanks. The T5000 instead regenerates its resin bed under a vacuum that literally sucks from the bottom of the tank any salt slime quickly away and effortlessly puts it down the drain each time it regenerates. A ball of slime is never given a chance to form and if it did it would be gone within a few short seconds of the T5000's total eight minute regeneration time.  Clean conditioned water does not feel slippery.  NO SLIME AND NO SLIPPERY WATER FOUND HERE. 
 If you’ve been using a water softener for many years that uses salt and then suddenly upgrade to a T5000 you’ll immediately notice a big improvement in your water quality.  If you don’t get slime free water right away just wait a month or two.  It’s typical that the water piping in your house will become coated inside with the same salt slime your old water softener's been spewing out the bathroom shower head for years.  Upon first installing a new T5000 the salt slime inside the household pipes will continue to break loose and give you slimy water.  But it’s only a short amount of time before the clean water provided by the T5000 will wash your pipes clean to leave you SLIME FREE as promised. 
 The T5000 is the only water softener using salt that does not rely on INLINE INJECTION controllers and valves.  Common names of manufacturers of inline injection controllers and valves are Fleck, Autotrol, Clack and others; while the major water softener bands utilizing inline injection are the Who’s Who of the Water Quality Industry including Culligan, Kinetico, GE, Haige as well as other large and small players.  Inline injection systems therefore makes up the majority of all water softeners sold in the US market and 100% of the systems that consume salt (other than the ulta high efficiency salt consuming conditiones sold on this website).  You can begin to understand just how different the T5000 must really be because it’s the only system not using inline injection that still uses salt.  Unfortunately in the rush toward salt free GREEN water conditioning even the best and most popular GREEN PRODUCTS are failing to perform even as well as the old-fashioned outdated traditional inline injection water softener,  Most consumers are unaware how much more efficitent the T5000 is compared to all other salt consuming water softeners; or that there's such a thing as a GREEN water softener that uses salt while exceeding California's most stringent environmental standards. But that's all true. The T5000 is definitely GREEN but can clean up the dirtiest hard water way better than any competing green products and even better than an old fashioned inline injection water softener ever could without polluting rivers, lakes, and streams in the process. 

 What a Difference a Vacuum Makes 
Inline injection takes advantage of something called the Venturi effect; and that effect can be simply demonstrated by blowing over the top of a soda straw placed in a glass of water.  Air rushing over the top of the straw creates a vacuum that draws water up the straw and out of the glass; and if you blow hard and long enough you’ll blow water right off the end of the straw until the glass is empty.  The same thing happens when streaming water across the top of the straw instead of air and a typical garden sprayer attachment to the end of a garden hose demonstrates this.  Whatever liquid you put in the garden sprayer will be drawn up a tiny tube and mixed with the larger stream of water spraying out the nozzle of the garden sprayer.  This principle is used in all inline injection water softeners; i.e., all water softeners other than ours.  It's how salt solution in the brine tank is delivered to the resin bed in the water softener tank during regeneration.  There’s a long tube that runs to the bottom of the brine tank just like the tube in the garden sprayer.  When salt is needed to regenerate the resin bed, water is blown over the top of the tube drawing brine up out of the brine tank and into resin bed inside the inline injection water softener.  Simple enough. 
Thirty five years ago this was a very clever solution to a difficult challenge of inventing and commercializing a self-sustaining automatic regenerating water softener.  Prior to the invention of inline injection water softeners you'd have to periodically exchange your water softener tank with a fresh one and send the spent tank to a central location where it was regenerated and later returned to your use again.  So when inline injection came along and it was an incredible and great thing because it was easier and cheaper to fill a tank with salt than regenerate exhange tanks at a remote location.  But now it’s been over 30 years and the same performance limitations still exist today as they did before.  For instance you can’t help but dilute your brine solution with the water used to create the Venturi effect by streaming water over the brine tube.  In the case of single tank water softeners the brine is unfortunately diluted with dirty water since the resin bed is unavailable to provide clean water to itself during regeneration.  This is an oversimplification of how inline injection water softening works but demonstrates simple limitations and it's difficult to understand why there has been so little innovation in water softener performance in 30 years.  When you consider how much money has been spent manufacturing basically the same system over and over again for the past 30 years it's hard to find any comparable technologies in other industries with this much stagnation of innovation. 
The T5000 on the other hand is the first major improvement on the original idea of inline injection and the invention of an automatic regenerating salt consuming water softener that's occurred in the last 30 years.  It's goal is the same as inline injection except to better utilize the higher efficiencies of fine mesh resins available today.  The T5000 uses a 3 port hydraulic valve known as a Noryl valve.  Instead of creating a small localized vacuum to the brine supply (as does inline injection relies on the Venturi effect) the T5000 instead creates a hydraulic vacuum in the tanks themselves where the resin bed is located.  The vacuum is so strong it would easily crush the standard duty tanks used by today’s inline injection water softeners (so the T5000 requires a much stronger and heavier duty tanks).  This strong vacuum allows the T5000 to easily keep the bottom of it’s tank free of salt slime (and the bacteria that causes slimy bathing water) while also drawing undiluted clean brine directly from its brine tank and depositing it undiluted to the high performance resin bed of its water softening tanks.  And because the T5000 is a two tank system there is always clean water available to make new brine and keep it’s tanks and resin beds rinsed completely clean.  This is a HUGE DIFFERENCE in how this water softener operates compared to ALL OTHER salt consuming water softeners today.  When the Noryl valves are controlled by sophisticated computer logic coupled with clever “pulse water rinsing” the more advanced fine mesh resins can be used to their full potential to easily and significantly outperform ALL OTHER water conditioners. Furthermore, sophisticated computer algorythems can be effectively used to keep track of resin memory and flow rates to protect against channeling common in todays inline injection water softeners. 
 Be warned that the major manufactures of inline injection water softeners have done something a little sneaky.  Most of them offer one model with a tank(s) they fill with high performance fine mesh resin so they can summarize in a  brochure (at least one brochure for that one particular model) much higher than usual operating efficiencies.  As expected they call this one model their high efficiency unit.  The problem is it's still an inline injection valve(s) and controller that in real life it struggles to keep fine mesh resin clean and operating according to manufacturer specifications.  The truth is these novel high efficiency inline injection units don't perform well in your home particularly if you have even a trace amount of iron.  The truth is inline injection water softening is a very old technology that has not kept pace with the ever improving performance of today’s fine mesh resins. 

T5000 Performance Numbers: 

• Working Capacity Per Tank: 5,000 grains 

 • Time per Regeneration: 8 minutes 

 • Water per Regeneration: 9 gallons 

 • Salt per Regeneration: 1 pound 

 • Continuous Capacity: 625 grains per minute 

  Other Uncommon Performance Benefits of T5000 Noryl Valve Vacuum Operation 

• De-Gasifies Water to remove serious odors problems commonly found in some water supplies 

• De-Gasification Significantly Improves Water Taste 

• Less back pressure and much higher instantaneous water conditioning capacity than any other residential water softener 

• Output water has 0 ppm hardness (typical inline injection leaves 1% or more of total ppm hardness) 

• Built-in BackFlow Regulator 

• Saves Space and Cost by Replacing both an Inline Injection Water Softener PLUS a Dedicated Iron Removal System when applicable 

• Much Safer for Septic Tank Use (extremely low salt discharge compared to convential water softeners) 

• Output water has less sodium than the raw water before treatment when using sodium chloride in the brine tank*** 

Note *  How is it possible to measure less sodium in the water output of a T5000 than the raw water it conditioned?  This is possible because the ion exchange of the T5000 is so close to 100% efficient that the fine mesh resin easily removes all sodium naturally present in the raw water while only adding a very minute amount of sodium required to complete its ion exchange.  We realize this is an impossible result from any other salt consuming water conditioner that is typically at best 50% efficient; but we have repeatedly measured this from treating 20 grain hard water with a typical amount of naturally occurring sodium (and also repeatedly measure 0 ppm of total hardness also unheard of by traditional water softener standards). 

ANOTHER SIGNIFICANT DIFFERENCE:  The benefits of having two tanks are obvious.  For one thing you always have clean water to make fresh brine and clean water to rinse the tanks after regenerating the resin beds.  But you would be missing a very significant DIFFERENCE if you thought the Twin Tank T5000 operated like any other two tank systems.  IT DOES NOT! 
ALL OTHER two tank systems are commonly referred to as Flip Flops because they only use one tank at a time and flip flop back and forth.  When the softening capacity of one tank is depleted the system flip flops over to the other fresh tank while the spent tank is regenerated.  Later it flip flops back again and it does this back and forth over and over again using only one tank at a time to condition your household water.  The T5000 Twin Tank NEVER FLIP FLOPS and is the only two tank system available anywhere that IS NOT A FLIP FLOP SYSTEM.  Instead the T5000 Twin Tank uses both tanks simultaneously.  This is a very significant DIFFERENCE because using both tanks at the same time cuts the speed in half that your household water travels through the resin beds (and through the carbon overtank if you purchase a T5000 configured and built to remove household chlorine; read about that HERE).  For example, the popular Kinetico two tank system is a Flip Flop (it’s also unfortunately an inline injection water softener with all the limitations that implies) and when you run your shower or bath only one tank is used to condition your water.  Your household water will run through a Kinetico at twice the velocity it will run through a T5000 because the water flowing through the T5000 is equally split between two tanks simultaneously which causes it to run at 1/2 the speed through each tank.  Water flowing at half the speed is exposed to the T5000’s high performance fine mesh resin for twice as long which is only one of many reasons why the T5000 outperforms all other water conditioner sold anywhere at any price. visit..http://purewater4health.com/index.php?route=product/product&amp;product_id=64﻿

Meer lezen (281 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-xn0nHIGDT54/UZnLIRrLUKI/AAAAAAAAAR0/Cm1wMNWpWtI/s426/1342625582.png-500x500.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/107149658380517886781/albums/5977549699502229473/5977549703995581554</link><title>A Treat Of Mosquitoes 

1\. How does a person find out that, they had malaria? 
It was found by the analysis of bloodsamples of the patient. 
2\. What problems did they have on having malaria? 
My friends suffered from high fever. The fever came with bouts of shivering. He became very weak. 
3\. What are  the likely diseases that can be caused by mosquito bites? 
Following are some of the diseases which can be caused by mosquito bites: 
a. Dengue b. Chikungunya c. Filaria. 
4\. In which season is malaria more common? Why do you think this happens? 
Malaria is more common in rainy season. Mosquito gets suitable environment to breed during the rainy season and hence there are more cases of malaria.They breed only in fresh water. 
5\. What do you do in your house to protect yourself from mosquitoes? Also find out from your friends about what they do? 
We use mosquito repellant in our house. Some people use mosquito nets also. 
6\. What are the problems caused by anaemia? 
The newspaper report says that anaemia affects both physical and mental energy levels are down. This affects their study as well. 
7\. Name the food items which contain iron. 
Green leafy vegetables like spinach, lettuce and cabbage contain iron. 
8\. What will happen when oil is spread on the water? 
The thin film of oil on water prevents oxygen supply to eggs and larvae of mosquitoes and thus they are killed. 
9\. Which diseases are spread by flies and how? 
Following diseases are spread by flies: Dysentery, cholera, typhoid, anthrax, etc. When a fly sits on contaminated material, harmful germs stick to its legs. When the same fly sits on food, the germs get transferred to the food. Thus, a fly spreads various diseases.﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_05_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-EtBey_Ncv-I/UvSFyQ3l5HI/AAAAAAAAAkk/V39h73iEdAQ/w426-h343/2000.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/114243882334053070760/albums/5989405689346486673/5989405686746840066</link><title>Work People Do 

1\. What is occupation? 

The work people do to earn money is known as occupation. 

2\. Name three examples of occupation of the people of India. 

Farming, cattle rearing and fishing, etc. are some examples of occupation of the 
people of India. 

3\. Name any three examples of crops. 

Wheat, sugar, rice barley and maize are some examples of crops. 

4\. Name any three animals that provide milk. 

Cow, buffalo and goat are some animals that provide milk. 

5\. What is poultry farming? 

Poultry farming is an important occupation in India. Poultry farming supplies eggs 
and chicken to the local market. 

6\. Which animal help the farmers to ploughing the field? 

The bullocks help the farmers to ploughing the field. 

7\. Name two examples of oil seeds. 

The mustard and ground nut are the examples of oil seeds. 

8\. Name any three items that we get from forest. 

Rubber, gum, herbs etc. are some items that we get from forest. 

9\. Name any three examples of minerals. 

Iron, coal and mica are some examples of minerals. 

10\. What is irrigation? 

To supply land with water through pipes, canals and other ways is known as irrigation. 

11\. What is the main occupation in the coastal region? 

Fishing is the main occupation in the coastal region. 

12\. What is cotton used for? 

Cotton is used to make cloth in mill. 

13\. Where the people living in cities work? 

The people living in cities work in offices, schools, and factories, etc. 

14\. Name any three use of wood. 

Wood uses to make furniture, houses, boxes and paper. 

For further details visit www.microlifeindia.org﻿

Meer lezen (61 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_06_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SndP6CxYT0o/Ux6kvSY__AI/AAAAAAAACHE/g462Do-edz4/w426-h584/2000.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/110399001022227943180/albums/5793197935055403057/5793197940838112866</link><title>Hematite 

Hematite is used to improve relationships. If you need your personal relationship to be better, carry a hematite with you always. 

The name comes from the Greek word for blood. It has been used as an amulet against bleeding, and so is known as the "blood stone". When arranged like the petals of a flower, it is referred to as the "iron rose". Native American folklore states that war paint made from hematite will make one invincible in battle. People in the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries wore hematite jewelry during mourning. 

Hematite is a wonderful stone that is associated with the root chakra. When needed this stone can aid tremendously in grounding and aligning the root chakra. 

Scientists of the Mars Exploration Rover Project believe that deposits of hematite on Mars may help prove whether large amounts of liquid water ever flowed on Mars' surface. They say that where water was, life may have had a chance to thrive as well. 

Hematite is good for increasing intuition. In jewelry it is best in a ring worn on the left hand. 

Hematite stimulates iron absorption in the small intestine, which in turn improves oxygen supply to the body. It can be in direct contact with the skin, but results in inflammation for some people, so test it carefully on yourself before use. 

~Angelus~﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-jIse-1-LTDI/UGWS1WEuHmI/AAAAAAAACm0/mznYuUb2ytg/w426-h439/Hematite.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/102318944667464581611/albums/5758811879653130321/5758811877883790018</link><title>Apex Elegance Inc. www.apexelegance.com 
Suppliers of willow baskets, seagrass baskets, corn husk baskets, maize baskets, bamboo baskets, hyacinth baskets, lined baskets, wood baskets, shopping baskets, fabric baskets, cardboard containers, fabric lined baskets, gift baskets, corporate baskets, wine gifts, gift boxes, baby baskets, rattan baskets, baskets with handle, laundry baskets, baskets with handles, Easter baskets, Christmas baskets, spring baskets, storage baskets, hanging baskets, gift basket accessories, cellophane rolls, printed cello rolls, cellophane sheets, cellophane bags, curling ribbon, pull bows, wired ribbons, ribbons, shredded paper, crinkle cut paper, Springfill paper, parchment paper, cello shred, wood excelsior, precious metal shred, silver shred, gold shred, Glue Dots, wreath, trays, pedestal baskets, triangular baskets, oval baskets, plastic containers, acrylic containers, bamboo bowls, bamboo platters, bamboo cutlery, ceramic dinnerware, ceramic hotelware, planters, fiberstone planters, fiberglass planters, plastic planters, willow planters, twig planters, vine planters, bamboo planters, metal planters, home decor, home decorations, wall decorations, animal decorations, gnomes, fiberglass gnomes, fiberglass purses, fiberglass shoes, shoe planters, lanterns, glass lanterns, metal lanterns, resin mushroom, rattan butterfly, rattan dolphin, furniture, wooden furniture, twig furniture, accents, decorative accents, wine cabinets, console tables, large planters, zinc planters, zinc pots, candle pillars, watering cans, metal containers, metal gift pots, metal pots, metal bases, metal sleigh, wooden sleigh, wine boxes, treasure boxes, box planters, spring containers, flower containers, flower shop supplies, glass candle holders, glass vases, glass pillars, glass hurricane, chair planters, cone planters, raised planters, pedestal planters, swing planters, welcome planter, willow trellis, willow obelisks, obelisks, willow fences, balcony hangers, metal obelisks, folding planters, folding baskets, pyramid trellises, willow balls, rattan bowls, coco planters, coco pots, coco liners, coconut planters, coconut pots, cast iron hanger, cast iron decorations, elk horns, welcome plaques, cast iron horseshoe, horse hangers, trees, elk hangers, bear hangers, rooster hangers, garden hangers, lizard hangers, stepping stones, welcome signs, French signs, garden stakes, wall planters, strong planters, reindeers, vine reindeers, garden decor accents, home accents, stars, gourmet foods, gourmet supplies, gourmet basket supplies. 
We supply the folloing brands and more: coffee candy, tea candy, Rondoletti, Loacker, Trophy, Dolcetto, Lindt chocolates, Lindor chocolates, Ghirardelli chocolates, Esta truffles, truffles, coffee cups, desert cups, chocolate sticks, Toblerone, Marzipan, Baci, David's chocolate, Chocolate Cigar, Cupido chocolate, Hamlet chocolate, Delectables, Choc o lait, chocolate fudge, Mozart chocolate, chocolate pizza, Mozart Kuglen, gourmet jam, fig jam, berry jam, brandy beans, Ritter sport, Turin chocolate, Kahlua chocolate, Bailey's chocolate, Malibu chocolate, liquor chocolate, Chcola's, chocolate thins, Cashew Roca, Brown &amp; Hailey, Almond Roca, Caffee cups, Belgian chocolates, Belgian truffles, Excelcium pralines, Sofiato pillows, Sofiato wafer rolls, Dolcetto Petites, Dolcetto wafer rolls, Loacker, Tortina, Wernli cookies, Gille cookies, Manner cookies, Napoli wafers, Manner wafers, Royal Dansk, butter cookies, Angelina cookies, wafer cookies, Lacey's, Viennese rolls, Lambertz, Pfeffer Nusse, Epicure double chocolate cake, raspberry cake, Biscotti, Mom's Best, Bebop, Primo Dolce, short bread cookies, Royal Edinburgh, All Gold, Peppermint Popcorn, chocolate pretzels, Fontazi pretzels, Trophy pop corn, Beth's chocolate, Dolcetto wafer squares, Focaccia crisps, Los Olivos, wine and cheese, Monet water crackers, Artisan Breadsticks, Amor di Pane, grissini, Flatbread sticks, bruschetta crackers, sourdough, cucina chips, gourmet chips, cheese straws, smoked almonds, almonds, nuts, crackers, trial mix, cranberry harvest medley, salad sensation, savory snacks, dips, French dips, spreads gourmet spreads, pepper jelly, Sahale snacks, Sahale almonds, Sahale cashews, dipping pretzels, seasoned pretzels, East Shore pretzels, dipping caramel, mustard, Rosenborg cheese, brie cheese, camembert cheese, gourmet cheese, Select cheese, pasta, Pirro pasta, Cara Nonna pasta, Primavera, olive oil, gourmet olive oil, balsamic vinigar, gourmet vinigar, Dalla Terra, Antipasto, roasted pepper, grilled artichokes, Forrelli olives, black olives, tapenade, bruschetta, pesto, Bellagio, hot cocoa, sipping chocolate, coffee, Bellagio coffee, Bellagio hot chocolate, Primavera coffee, Arabiata coffee, Ernest Hemingway tea, Cafe latte, Wolfgang Puck coffee, Bentley's tea, Coffee candy, Latte candy, Espresso candy, green tea candy, RJ's licorice, licorice logs, strawberry licorice, Liberty orchards, Fruit delights, Aplets and cotlets, Cambridge and Thames, Jelly Belly, Java Bon, Vanilla Caramels, Cedrinca, Mandy's peppermint, Mrs. Beasley, Petite de Fruits, Menz Gasser jams, minim jams, almond brittle, gourmet coffee, roasted coffee., 
Gift baskets Toronto, gift baskets Mississauga, gift baskets in Ontario, gift baskets in Canada, wholesalers in Mississauga, Unique gift baskets, Unique gourmet gift baskets, gift food baskets, gift basket gourmet, wine gift baskets, wholesale baskets Mississauga, basket suppliers Mississauga, basket wholesale suppliers Mississauga, Toronto basket suppliers, Toronto garden centre suppliers, gourmet food suppliers Mississauga, wholesale gourmet supplies, wholesale suppliers, wholesale gift supplier, wholesale gift box, cheap baskets, cheap wholesale, food wholesale, wholesale foods, gourmet food distributors, gourmet food products, Gift baskets supplies wholesale, Gift basket supplies, Gourmet baskets, Baskets wholesale, Gift supplies. We are located within the Mississauga gift trade area, in the old Action Imports, and later, the old Saksco location.﻿

Meer lezen (90 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-13_hRNquXIQ/T-to5DWQQsI/AAAAAAAAAD0/EvoCjM_iojI/w426-h335/plastic.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/110340353477287461867/albums/5859437058792244289/5859437060843674242</link><title>Urgent health warning issued over Adya Clarity detox liquid containing aluminum, sulfuric acid 

The non-profit Consumer Wellness Center (www.ConsumerWellness.org) has issued a consumer health warning over Adya Clarity, a "detox" product that was seized by the FDA in 2012 and tested at over 1200ppm aluminum. The product is currently being marketed through a series of highly deceptive webinars that claim almost magical powers for the product. In reality, the product is primarily made of metals dissolved in sulfuric acid, and it was imported into the United States using the description "battery acid" on import documents. 

Adya Clarity's two most prominent metals are aluminum and iron. The manufacturer of Adya Clarity intentionally and deliberately refused to list aluminum on the label, instead listing beneficial trace elements such as magnesium. Even so, they recommended the product for internal consumption every 12 hours, saying: 

"As far as super shots are concerned; taking a super shot is an off label use. Mix 1 teaspoon of ADYA in 1 oz. of water. If this is too strong to the taste, you can use more than 1 oz of water. Drink one Supershot immediately upon waking in the morning. Repeat every 12 hours." 

Here's the chemical breakdown of Adya Clarity, as tested by the FDA after they seized the product: 

• Aluminum average 1040 ppm 
• Iron average 1070 ppm 
• Sulfuric acid average .927 % 
• Lead .012 ppm 
• Arsenic .027 ppm 

Would you drink something that's over 1000ppm aluminum and 1000ppm iron? If so, you might also enjoy taking vaccine shots, which have far lower levels of aluminum. 

Aluminum sulfate poisoning 

The primary metal compound in Adya Clarity is aluminum sulfate. In 1988, a 20-ton load of aluminum sulfate was accidentally dumped into the municipal water supply in a town in the UK. What followed was a mass poisoning of the citizens in a 140-square-mile area. As reported in the Dailymail (http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-502442/A-lethal-cover-Britain...) : 

"As she starts to walk, it is with a heavy limp and within 50 yards she is so exhausted that her entire body shakes uncontrollably. After Angela finally reaches the local coffee shop, the trembling of her swollen legs is so bad that the table rocks haphazardly, threatening to spill her mug and croissant onto the floor. 

No wonder, near to tears, she declares bravely: "When I am dead, I want an autopsy done on my body. It might help all the people who, like me and my two children, drank the water in Camelford all those years ago." 

For she and her family were victims of one of Britain's most high-profile public health scandals in which victims complained of brain damage, memory loss and joint problems." 

Also from the story: 

...dead women had "high levels" of aluminium in their brains... 

...Hundreds began to suffer effects after drinking or bathing - including skin peeling, hands and lips sticking together, hair turning green and fingernails blue. 

...By nightfall that day, people were vomiting and had diarrhoea. Next morning, many had skin burns, aching joints and mouth ulcers that took weeks to heal. 

...A few months later Angela became ill. 

...She was diagnosed with cancer of the lymph glands of the leg. She had an operation to remove the resulting malignant growth on her left thigh. She has since undergone another operation to remove a new growth on the same leg." 

Adya Clarity "recalled" by top distributor 

Adya Clarity was "recalled" by its top distributor in 2011, during which that distributor apologized for promoting a product with possible health risks and issued over $1 million in refunds and store credit to customers. His statement includes, "I feel deeply saddened at this situation; please forgive me for not taking action sooner." 

An Adya Clarity shipment was seized by the FDA in 2012, and the FDA confirmed the product's label contained multiple label violations. You can see some of the FDA's findings here. 

Why the Adya webinar is a fraud 

The marketing of Adya Clarity is based on a parlor trick of pouring an acidic liquid containing dissolved metals into a glass of water, which is more alkaline. The sudden shift in alkalinity causes particles (metals) to appear in the water. This is described by the deceptive marketers as a "cleaning" of the water. Promoters of Adya Clarity, which include Matt Bakos and Kacper Postawski, claim that when the product is consumed internally, it pulls metals out of your body. In reality, the product introduces potentially toxic levels of non-organic iron and aluminum into your body. 

Users of Adya Clarity have reported "black stuff" coming out of their ears and fingernails. One video shows an Adya Clarity user raving about how great Adya Clarity is, even though the woman appears to be completely insane (medically psychotic). Click here for the video and forward to the end to see this woman. 

The deceptive marketing of Adya Clarity is based on the idea that aluminum binds to other metals. But so does mercury. Mercury is used throughout the mining industry, in fact, to pull gold flakes out of slurry. This does not mean that mercury is safe to drink. Neither is aluminum safe to drink in large quantities. Anyone concerned about chemtrails (aluminum and barium salts) or vaccines should be similarly concerned about drinking Adya Clarity which contains over 1200 ppm aluminum, according to FDA lab tests. 

The claimed "water purification" benefits of Adya Clarity are highly deceptive, as the product does not come with a physical filter to trap the aluminum that has bonded with other particles. Thus, anyone who drinks this liquid is drinking both the aluminum as well as whatever it has bonded to. Adya Clarity is mined in Japan near Fukushima, Japan, the site of the nuclear accident. 

Fraudulent claims of "approval" by Health Canada 

Adya Clarity has never been approved by the FDA for any purpose, and it is not "harmonized" with the FDA as deceptively claimed by its marketers. Adya Clarity is also not approved by Health Canada as the marketers deceptively claim. Rather, Adya is only listed as an "iron supplement" with Health Canada, meaning the Health Canada listing was fraudulently acquired by intentionally misstating the intended marketing and use of the product. This is a violation of Health Canada regulations. 

Adya Clarity is also now being promoted by Brian Clement at the Hippocrates Health Institute, a claimed "doctor" who HushLeaks.com says acquired his doctorate through a diploma mill. NaturalNews confirmed that the accreditation organization overseeing the "university" that granted Brian Clement his "doctorate" is operated out of a run-down building in North Kansas City where the phone is answered, "This is bob." Everyone promoting Adya Clarity is making huge profits on the product. It was imported as battery acid for pennies per gallon, but it is sold at obscene markups to an unsuspecting public. 

Adya Clarity is currently being promoted at Rense.com and other alternative news websites. Jeff Rense is probably not aware of the full story of Adya Clarity, or he would surely not promote it. Alex Jones has long banned Adya Clarity from being promoted on InfoWars.com and PrisonPlanet.com. If Rense.com continues to promote the product after this warning is published, it would greatly harm the credibility of Jeff Rense himself, who has long fought against metals poisoning of food, water and the atmosphere. 

Adya Clarity, by the way, threatened to sue Natural News to prevent the website from warning consumers about the possible health risks of consuming the product. This is information the Adya marketers do not want to be widely known. 

If you purchased Adya Clarity from a webinar, request an immediate refund 

If you recently purchased Adya Clarity due to the recent release of a highly deceptive marketing webinar, you are encouraged to return the product and ask for a full refund. Do not consume the product internally. The product contains a high level of aluminum that far exceeds EPA limits for safe water consumption. Most of the marketing claims for the product are dubious and deceptive. 

Many Adya Clarity distributors refuse to honor refund requests, so if necessary, you may wish to issue a chargeback with your credit card company to dispute the charge for the product. 

Adya Clarity stands in terrible contradiction to the principles of good health. There are 12 primary contradictions you need to know about, including: 

#5) We should avoid aluminum cookware and aluminum foil. 
But Adya Clarity contains over 1,000PPM of aluminum sulfate, dissolved in sulfuric acid, and you're supposed to drink it! 

#6) Vaccines are dangerous because they contain aluminum and mercury. 
But Adya Clarity contains high levels of aluminum and iron in their sulfated forms! And it was marketed as a "mineral supplement" so powerful that if you sat in a bathtub with Adya added to the water, the minerals would "penetrate to your bone marrow," claimed the founder of Adya, Inc. 

False and deceptive marketing claims 

Here are some of the health claims that Matt Bakos has made about Adya Clarity, which has been marketed as a dietary supplement for internal ingestion: 

"...the minerals will penetrate to your bone marrow," says Bakos. (Aluminum is the second most common mineral in the product, and aluminum toxicity is strongly linked to dementia, psychosis and delusional thinking.) 

"Water is the number one cause of death on this planet." 

"These minerals, because they're pre-digested, your body has to do nothing to get 'em into your cells." 

"I once had this woman who's severely obese, who started taking our product, and in the first three days, she passed out three two-to-three foot long sucker fish snakes out of her bowels." 

"In fact, if you notice your lips begin to get dry in the beginning, that means your colon is hydrating." 

"Believe it or not, our product is harmonized by the FDA to come into the United States. So the FDA actually knows our product's being consumed." 

"To achieve a proper health, you've gotta get out those multivalent ions that are trapped in your body that cannot move." 

"This product goes right into the system, there's no metabolization needed, you can sit in a hot tub of this [Adya Clarity] water, and the minerals will penetrate to your bone marrow." 

"Well, no wonder why everybody's divorcing and can't stand each other, it's because they're demineralized, they can't energetically communicate with one another."﻿

Meer lezen (228 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-rd-Qpxx9Dr8/UVDm9lNYmoI/AAAAAAAAAc8/KwCT8u8Q3_s/w426-h237/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7095-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/iron%20in%20water%20supply/photos/116457185499275551171/albums/5917598925521795809/5917598929598109410?authkey=CITs67nFofPSjgE</link><title>Water is a precious resource that we all rely on. However, many of us take it for granted that our tap water is drinkable, but does that mean it’s pure? 

There are still traces of sediment, chemicals, and even lead. These combined impurities can lead to serious health problems over time. 

Watermart has a complete line of water filters that eliminates nitrates, chlorine, cloudiness, chemicals, iron and lead (yes, this is all in your current water supply!) http://www.watermart.com/ 
Unlimited, clean, pure water at your fingertips.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7095_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-WBrlUhbnp5U/Uh-I36ntVuI/AAAAAAAAAmM/aN7d5G3n_SM/w426-h442/pure-water.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>