<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7100">korean bbq san francisco review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 15:46:35" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7100-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/korean%20bbq%20san%20francisco%20review/photos/106073502505833617615/albums/5650769650238406209/5650769647279772386</link><title>Jessi's Must-Eat List For Travelers 

Being on the road all the time has it's good parts, but also it's bad parts. Eating while traveling can definitely be put into both categories. Some days, I'll eat at the best steakhouse in town, or that awesome Diner everyone loves. Others, it's fast food all day. 

Now, I've eaten at almost all the same places as Guy Fieri from "Diner's, Drive-in's, and Dives" and some of those places are the best eats in this country. And this made me wonder: "How many of those places are out there that haven't been found yet??" 

So, there are tons of lists of "must eat places" out there, but most of them, the author never went to all of them. Well, I'm going to make a list of Must eat places for travelers, places I personally recommend from having eaten there, so people on vacation or traveling for work can know a few good places in town, so they don't have to rely on chain restaurants while on the road, or crappy hotel food... 

So here's where you guys come in. I want to know your favorite restaurants!! Tell me about your favorite Grubbing places either around your usual watering holes, or from somewhere you visited, and I'm going to go try them once I'm in the area. Then, we're going to make a list of places in every major city in America! 

So share this, plus one this, do what you want, but make sure you leave me your favorite restaurant, where it is, and why... And when I go there, I'll let you know, and G+ know, what I thought, and if it makes the list!! Let's get as many suggestions as possible. 

A girl's gotta eat you know!! ;) 

(Picture Credit: Scott See's Portrait of Jessi June, cropped for G+...)﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7100_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-o-EuFVcJBK8/TmuRDh2rkuI/AAAAAAAAUis/MJguQ83PAS4/w426-h323/Jessi%2527s%2Blist.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7100-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/korean%20bbq%20san%20francisco%20review/photos/114963786071989905755/albums/5807026553946078929/5807026558894429938</link><title>SPRINGFIELD AIRPORT; Grand Father Burial Plane to Greenville Sino County (Ritual Death)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7100_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-40gTormsCK4/UJaz42wpVvI/AAAAAAAAKpI/QilW91TfLgM/w426-h297/Plane%2Bto%2BGreenville%2BSino%2BGrand%2BFather%2BBurial.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>