<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7101">innodb versus myisam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:39:42" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7101-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/innodb%20versus%20myisam/photos/101251958784716332736/albums/5960979335484533905/5960979341356201346?sqi=116467282805285517388&amp;sqsi=51ec82c1-8933-45cb-ade1-a0bcf9fd109f</link><title>Hi, 

It's been a long time since I started a design for a  fresh database and I want to make sure I use the correct database model and figured you guys are the experts. So I wanted to run the design past you. 

1) The database is used to track events and people that attend. 
2) Users must login to mark that they have attended an event or create an event. 
3) Events and Users have addresses (shared table to reduce redundancy) 
4) eventUserType is either going to be 
"Admin" =&gt; Created Event or 
"Attendant" =&gt; "Visited Event"﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7101_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-S9w1tP_1DvM/UrmnINr6dYI/AAAAAAAAD-Q/m-dFhKKfHao/w426-h278/err.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7101-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/innodb%20versus%20myisam/photos/100117221369889575257/albums/5998042075223518017/5998042079827362706</link><title>http://www.linux.org.ru/forum/general/10350059/ 
ОП этого треда — конченый извращенец, это намного круче чем простой DROP DATABASE. 
Вот нахуя нужно было /var/ таскать туда-сюда? Да еще без бекапов...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7101_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-yu-Os6nsAeg/Uz1Tfhv0g5I/AAAAAAAAbFc/QbmniV--Ak8/w426-h366/dropDB.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7101-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/innodb%20versus%20myisam/photos/110709349930282719518/albums/5887456891072069697/5887456893585532162?authkey=CKyenLqGzf-QRA&amp;sqi=114175980151299757659&amp;sqsi=7dbe31fe-ec7d-4c77-8900-741af8b3bc6a</link><title>Dearest web developers and data guys, I call for your help. 

I'm considering to deploy this schema to my new web application project. 
The project will require the best possible small data frequent reads performance, while I don't mind sacrificing a bit of writing performance. 

Being a corporate application developer, I always work with complex very constrained schemas. 
This one is a personal project. I first thought of doing the more traditional relational approach, but then I realized that the more features I added, the more complex it was becoming. And I wish to add more features in time without constantly stepping up the schema complexity. Besides, I want to keep it read-friendly. 
So I came up with this. The idea is to have a simplified data store and leave the constrains and rules to a rest webservice software layer which the various UIs (web site, android app, chrome app, etc) will communicate with. 

I also should point out that I don't have the possibility of deploying a noSQL Key-Value solution like Mongo. I must use Ms SQL Server or MySQL. 

What I need from you guys is to tell me if and how is this a bad idea, what are the pitfalls and so on, and if there are any obvious better alternatives. 
Secondly, I'd also love some advice on which database solution should I adopt for this (MySQL or SQL Server), what's the best engine for it, and if there are any possible optimizations to be made to the database configuration when hosting this kind of schema. 

My very best regards. 

[edit] I've just noticed the 1/n notation is switched. Luckily it's pretty obvious what the relations are.﻿

Meer lezen (32 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7101_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-N0FUs2vEWpc/UbRy2gSXJQI/AAAAAAAAIrY/ppg2pneQTxU/w426-h237/RIRDataModel.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7101-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/innodb%20versus%20myisam/photos/111869347391871267742/albums/5840412159429180113/5840412159093091778?authkey=CLGvzu2atJ_9igE</link><title>Привет, телезрители, эцсамое. В эфире телепердача «Ебаное ничего». Тема нашей сегодняшней передачи — ебаное ничего. С нами в студии Рей и ебаное ничего. Пушо эцсамое, ага. 

Потыкал MongoDB, снова. Местами няшно, а вот язык запросов очень чудовищный, все эти, $gte, $regex. Не хотет. 

Еще я написал свой первый и последний алгоритм, который преобразует кривые svg в другие кривые, тоже svg, рендерит их и всячески &lt;del&gt;унижает&lt;/del&gt; хранит в базе данных. Не в MongoDB, в обычной СУРБД «Мой SQL». Потом я покажу вам картинки, пока эта штука еще не умеет рисовать красивые картинки, а умеет только всякие некрасивые. 

Завтра на работу T_T baww~ loli haet work.﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7101_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_fBDPyJA40M/UQ1P6jSdrcI/AAAAAAAARso/ud2L4G2j-P4/w426-h779/usagi-rei.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>