<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 15:48:13" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/101866207780882670022/albums/5711401255916859185/5711401257577340034</link><title>VLC 2.0 dark interface on Mac. 

get it on www.videolan.org﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_01_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BCvAxhUtKis/T0L5Lved3II/AAAAAAAAEag/8bToZBzPP4M/w426-h355/Screen%2Bshot%2B2012-02-21%2Bat%2B7.39.40%2BAM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/114798546917696375743/albums/5872470500058208529/5872470504509470850?authkey=CPiIibmrlbS-Jg</link><title>I find it amazing how different VLC for Mac is compared to former two platforms it supports.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-HVefyU8PWb4/UX80z2c--II/AAAAAAAAHNI/0pZKJS8g2mg/w426-h282/vlc-2.0-mac.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/113097276181543898574/albums/5710699022946167841/5710699022689246978</link><title>After 2+ years of 1.x, VLC has reached 2.0. The UI has been completely overhauled (on VLC for Mac anyway) in a very pleasing way. 

Congrats to the folks at the VideoLAN project! 

http://www.videolan.org/vlc/releases/2.0.0.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_03_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-JjOk2B2RAYU/T0B6gSqQHwI/AAAAAAABKRc/pq6LzTYugMg/w426-h359/Screen%2BShot%2B2012-02-18%2Bat%2B8.28.14%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/111465197281523456813/albums/5987859979388411281/5987859990696606898</link><title>If you have a Mac, Clementine is an awesome and vastly superior audio media player. If Windows, AIMP3. And if Linux, you know the deal. 

For videos files cross-platform, one VLC to rule them all. 

#notanexpert   #notacrook   #clementine   #aimp   #aimp3   #vlc   #mac   #windows   #rain   #backgroundmusic   #bgm   #allhailthehypnotoad   #hypnotoad   #hashtagsoup  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_04_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-e50CVzTpc2M/Uxkm774-vLI/AAAAAAAAXUY/DYDpXy8Qan4/w426-h301/Screenshot%2B2014-03-06%2B20.46.54.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/101693597219413173200/albums/5909283443283964177/5909283441178469826?authkey=CLjst5ydv_rw0QE</link><title>Anyone out there still remember Winamp? 

Winamp for Mac. 
http://www.winamp.com/mac' 

Update 
Nevermind the app kinda sucks. Better off using Spotify or VLC.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_05_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MQz2234fLoY/UgH9-ySKZcI/AAAAAAABhZI/q9Umw26i0mA/w426-h284/Screen+Shot+2013-08-06+at+11.55.00+PM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/113174899095029964471/albums/5955699487479782833/5955699494855845266?sqi=107259666512014228221&amp;sqsi=3ad15bd4-5879-4fe9-96de-f52317241062</link><title>New VLC Media Player 2.1.2 release, comes with improved responsiveness and fixes opening subtitles 
Also fixes digital playback and stuttering or silent playback when using sound enhancers or external audio devices on OS X. 

Download, review and more details at http://mac.softpedia.com/get/Video/VLC-Media-Player.shtml﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Hbjw71yHD5g/UqblIsvbJZI/AAAAAAAADyU/WETHLMKpej8/w426-h237/vlc-2.0-lion.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/108058675047399135236/albums/5889614649661480529/5889614646978741730?authkey=COiKhdL4s7jxeA</link><title>Stream live and wireless with  a GoPro to a PC/Mac/Linux 

Yesterday I found out that I can stream from a GoPro to a computer in a very simple way. If interested, read further and I'll explain you how I made this happen thus this shot possible. 

In foreground you see the picture of the GoPro taken by me, the image of me that you see in background  is filmed by the GoPro and  streamed live to my computer then displayed on a large monitor. 
With a bit of software, all available free and relatively simple to operate, one can also record this stream or, even better, forward the stream to a live broadcast for example. 

Now, mind you, resolution of this stream it's not HD and it's not real-time, the process adds a perfectly acceptable 4 seconds delay and a less than desirable 240p image resolution (nothing dramatic though). 

If you want to give it a go, you need the following: 

\- A PC/Mac/Laptop with a wireless connection 

\- A Video player able to play HTTP live streaming (it's an Apple standard). VideoLAN, also known as VLC, does the job perfectly. If you don't have it, go ahead and install it (http://www.videolan.org/) 

\- A GoPro with Wifi set to ON (so make sure it's either well charged or keep it wired to a wall plug, with wifi on the batteries are drained ridiculously fast) 

\- Make sure that in the settings of the GoPro, namely in the WiFi section, you are set to GoPro App and not WiFi-RC (that's pretty much the only configuration you need to know about ) 

\- Now go ahead and connect you computer to the Wifi AP of the camera, it's easy to spot in the list of available wireless networks, so proceed as if you were connecting to a standard router , and use the appropriate password. If you don't know what password I am talking about, chances are that you never setup a wifi password on your GoPro and you can simply google for the default gopro wifi password. 

Please Note While connected to the camera, if your Internet connection is also wireless, you will obviously loose Internet and maybe discover that life goes on anyway without it :-) anyway, print these instructions or take a screenshot of them. 

\- Next steps are even simpler: You are given the IP 10.5.5.109 and the camera holds the IP 10.5.5.9. If you want to amuse yourself immediately, open a web browser and navigate to http://10.5.5.9:8080/live and if you want to amuse yourself and your partner, start Videolan go to Open Network Stream and punch in the address: 

http://10.5.5.9:8080/live/amba.m3u8 

there is your live stream. 

\- If you intend to amuse yourself, your partner and your boss well, forget about VLC and fire up FFMPEG, but if you know what ffmpeg is I don't need to say anything further: you're all set for live broadcast! 

The camera I am using is a  GoPro 3 Black edition, I am not sure if the Silver and White respond in exact the same way, but it's  worth a shot. After I approached this matter I discovered that there is a bunch of other geeks that, much like me, like to explore things and they also found that you can control most of the functions of your camera by using HTTP RESTful commands. You can turn on/off the camera, set the resolution, the field of view, start a recording, delete files (well...) and so forth.﻿

Meer lezen (67 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/--TRWWNxQnzA/UbwdUSEbBeI/AAAAAAAANgA/UO-0t4tKuRA/w426-h284/Low_res_Copyright_VDC_VDC_6566.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/118081200942191165328/albums/5636787476447751633/5636787478598156274</link><title>Falls sich schonmal jemand darüber gewundert hat, dass VLC unter Mac OS X trotz QT garnicht deplaziert wirkt, dem sei gesagt, dass VLC zwar durchaus QT nutzt aber nur unter Windows und Linux, auf Mac OS X kommt hingegen eine native graphische Schnittstelle zum Einsatz. 
http://wiki.videolan.org/Interfaces﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_08_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-3yOs4zQtT8k/TjnkWMg2f_I/AAAAAAAAAKk/geTvD8zTOYE/w426-h237/Bildschirmfoto%2B2011-08-04%2Bum%2B02.14.00.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/104080403697863288449/albums/5722119495542471089/5722119498704712786</link><title>おはようございます！　Mac OS Xに最近のバージョンのVLCをインストールしました。新しいUIは便利でいいですね。使いやすい！ 

皆さん、今日も元気で頑張ってください！ 
宜しくお願いします。 

Good morning everybody. Today I Just installed the latest update of VLC Player with a new user interface. Very easy to use and no any clutter on the desktop like the old one with main windows and video window stay apart. 

Have a nice day !﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_09_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-KQkNAY5AA40/T2kNXfKhdFI/AAAAAAAAGpc/ZkuwVYjaBp8/w426-h259/%25E3%2582%25B9%25E3%2582%25AF%25E3%2583%25AA%25E3%2583%25BC%25E3%2583%25B3%25E3%2582%25B7%25E3%2583%25A7%25E3%2583%2583%25E3%2583%2588%2B2012-03-21%2B8.05.33.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7102-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vlc%20mac/photos/117500022326299148658/albums/5657811611512880449/5657811614024298114</link><title>If you own a Mac and you don't have VLC installed, you are a rookie.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7102_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-kTZLnUrkzwk/ToSVr8P_boI/AAAAAAABipU/WoE-pkOEebw/s426/20110929-vlc-icon.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>