<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:45:48" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/100470681032489535736/albums/6000335215119386257/6000335220803933330</link><title>Some diseases, such as haemophilia and cystic fibrosis, are caused by broken genes. Doctors have long dreamed of treating them by adding working copies of these genes to cells in the relevant tissue. This has proved hard. Recently, though, new approaches have been devised. The Economist explains why gene therapy just got easier http://econ.st/1hhlRgd ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-mUXDJWJbSN8/U0V5F5lIlJI/AAAAAAABots/pOzYKJ1dOFc/w426-h240/Gene%2Btherapy.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/100963885365648206716/albums/5852006915723868209/5852006913224123186?authkey=CLzN8Lz9ndeZMg</link><title>Help raise $10k for @MauliOlaFoundation Proceeds help patients with Cystic Fibrosis have the opportunity for a natural treatment (Surfing) The salt found in the ocean helps to relieve their congested lungs ultimately enabling patients to breath better naturally. Vote for @WhoIsJOB (Jamie O'Brien) Please Google 4G4Hope OBrien to cast your VOTE or go to http://4g4hope.modernluxury.com/hawaii-obrien ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-2vyq_DS8Whk/UTaBSEXaozI/AAAAAAAAAOI/NiPGSjYdpMo/s426/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/103430773410928392958/albums/5984519968822422801/5984519973587955906</link><title>Sinonasal inhalation of tobramycin in CF 

Rationale: In cystic fibrosis (CF), the paranasal sinuses are sites of first and persistent colonization by pathogens such as Pseudomonas aeruginosa. Pathogens subsequently descend to the lower airways, with P. aeruginosa remaining the primary cause of premature death in patients with the inherited disease. 

Unlike conventional aerosols, vibrating aerosols applied with the PARI Sinus™ nebulizer deposit drugs into the paranasal sinuses. This trial assessed the effects of vibrating sinonasal inhalation of the antibiotic tobramycin in CF patients positive for P. aeruginosa in nasal lavage. 

Objectives: To evaluate the effects of sinonasal inhalation of tobramycin on P. aeruginosa quantification in nasal lavage; and on patient quality of life, measured with the Sino-Nasal Outcome Test (SNOT-20), and otologic and renal safety and tolerability. 

Methods: Patients were randomized to inhalation of tobramycin (80 mg/2 mL) or placebo (2 mL isotonic saline) once daily (4 minutes/nostril) with the PARI Sinus™ nebulizer over 28 days, with all patients eligible for a subsequent course of open-label inhalation of tobramycin for 28 days. 

Nasal lavage was obtained before starting and 2 days after the end of each treatment period by rinsing each nostril with 10 mL of isotonic saline. 

Results: Nine patients participated, six initially receiving tobramycin and three placebo. Sinonasal inhalation was well tolerated, with serum tobramycin &lt;0.5 mg/L and stable creatinine. P. aeruginosa quantity decreased in four of six (67%) patients given tobramycin, compared with zero of three given placebo (non-significant). 

SNOT-20 scores were significantly lower in the tobramycin than in the placebo group (P=0.033). 

Conclusion: Sinonasal inhalation of vibrating antibiotic aerosols appears promising for reducing pathogen colonization of paranasal sinuses and for control of symptoms in patients with CF. 

Read this original research and sign up to receive Drug Design, Development and Therapy journal here: http://www.dovepress.com/articles.php?article_id=15758﻿

Meer lezen (41 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2_qCHzvnDB4/Uw1JNWjwsMI/AAAAAAAABA8/5IkWxEo5TgE/w426-h401/F%2B1.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/107589421331343468741/albums/5904175914590331937/5904175918668894258?authkey=COLx0K_yj4GeUg</link><title>The Cystic Fibrosis Foundation consistantly raises the median predicted survival age by using 90 cents of every dollar of revenue raised to support CF research, care and education programs that make a difference every day. The CF Foundation recently announced a major advance in the mission to defeat CF -- a breakthrough new drug to treat this disease. This drug is Kalydeco. Your financial support is urgently needed. Join Team Clarksville, and the Cystic Fibrosis Foundation, in fueling the science that will find the cure for CF. Donate today. http://www.cff.org/great_strides/TeamClarksville﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_04_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-pmxJb9KD4gg/Ue_Yt2Os0DI/AAAAAAAABdk/IVrsk7fctLQ/w426-h246/age_001.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/106839369988146837501/albums/5938482930992913537/5938482932656957522</link><title>Yoga supports cystic fibrosis. The Big Breathe: Soft Moments Between The Breath 

When my son was only four years old, he came to me and asked me why he was born with cystic fibrosis. In his young mind, he couldn’t understand why he had to sit through hours of treatments every day, swallow a handful of pills before each meal and even occasionally worry about being admitted to the hospital. All he knew was that his friends, and even his younger sisters, did not have to do these things. Like any other child his age, he didn’t want to be different. He felt frightened and alone, and wanted those feelings to go away... http://bit.ly/1bk0kxg #cysticfibrosis #cysticfibrosisfoundation #disability #disabilities  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-zkRFy_jPhhE/Umm6w4m86FI/AAAAAAAACC0/FTAOSeoi2Zo/w426-h318/Picture%2B166.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/114230492766303116510/albums/5973607133120337505/5973607137383495298</link><title>Did you know cystic fibrosis is a very serious genetic disease that affects 1 in 4,000 children in the United States? In the 1950s, few children with cystic fibrosis lived to attend elementary school. The good news is that breakthroughs in research and medical treatments have further enhanced and extended life for children living with the disorder. www.unitypoint.org/blankchildrens/cysticfibrosis﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-610A7NwreBs/UuaECrt7NoI/AAAAAAAACDk/K1cU7eM8wxA/s426/1532124_10152155383841100_31993838_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/116810319920183767232/albums/5969554677617070193/5969554675261782466</link><title>New research explores quality of life in young adults w/ cystic fibrosis. But it's more than keeping tabs—learn how the data may eventually inform future treatments for this rapidly emerging patient population. http://on.bchil.org/1cvlGH8﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MHzdQ7ujG_A/UtgeWV5AOcI/AAAAAAAABbQ/h3NxDGobUR8/w426-h702/82e831dc-11bb-4901-a6a4-4809aa32517b</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/115526856822176417318/albums/5967220522897108353/5967220528105589266</link><title>#Nebulizer Air-Compressing is essential #drug delivery devices… 

Uses - Treatments of asthma, Cystic Fibrosis and all breathing related diseases. 

• Product Price - INR 2975 
• Product Code - TOL034 

Nebulizer-delivered therapies is best health care technique to use in asthma. http://ow.ly/srYdV﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-bczixg0W9hk/Us_TdGInChI/AAAAAAAAAa8/2mH8Ay3KGBE/w426-h349/8%255B1%255D.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/104765717987042844598/albums/5756246971414935121/5756246975355556962</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis Gene Therapy 

12 years ago, a group of scientists from Imperial College in London, Oxford and Edinburgh formed the Cystic Fibrosis Gene Therapy Consortium. This year they started the world's biggest trial of gene therapy for cystic fibrosis. Funded by the Cystic Fibrosis Trust, the Medical Research Council and The National Institute for Health Research, the trial will treat 120 CF patients with either a placebo or a healthy copy of the gene that causes CF. The gene is wrapped up in a fat globule, or liposome and delivered in aerosol form directly to the lungs. 

Programme: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01jxs8q 
Stream: http://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/console/b01jxs8q 

Photo: http://www.cfgenetherapy.org.uk/﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Td2aK7NO8iI/T-JMIE18FGI/AAAAAAAAA1I/EnCx321OUl8/w426-h640/StagedFrontPageDelivery.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7103-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cystic%20fibrosis%20treatment/photos/101365300451322355488/albums/6003238222910462001/6003238222223891490</link><title>#CysticFibrosis: Causes,Symptoms And Treatment 

http://www.healthresource4u.com/cystic-fibrosis-causessymptoms-and-treatment.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7103_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Ov9RlQ661ns/U0_JW0mz3CI/AAAAAAAABAU/F_uJISc82n4/w426-h373/079524fc-e740-4db8-8fd5-2a3cc289ea21</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>