<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:57:15" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/113104944605785201866/albums/5999965762833904129/5999965761928809458?sqi=105794646381494402222&amp;sqsi=7ec2f4bf-6fc7-410f-a6de-b91175b45cc1</link><title>Photo Location Guide: An Unconventional Way to Photograph New York 
Living in Eastern Canada (Montreal) near the US border has a big advantage for any travel photographer or photo enthusiast; it puts you within driving distance of two beautiful and extremely photogenic cities; Boston, and New York 

I have a tradition where I visit New York at least once a year. Even if I have happened to visit during my business trips, I still try to find time to return on my own. Since I am not a winter person, and I do not enjoy outdoor photography in wintertime, most of my visits to New York have been in the summer. 

It is not easy to photograph New York in the middle of summer. Any place you go is full of tourists, and sometimes it is not easy to frame an interesting shot without people in it ... 

Find complete article with the map and photos 
http://goo.gl/rjWFgH﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ZKf7Sg9qaiw/U0QpEkBFy_I/AAAAAAAA7Bs/zutLbAkfATI/w426-h641/Travel_Photography_Blog_New_York_Manhattan_Sunset_Reflections_FULL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/111812141797720239929/albums/5697829959823060529/5697829957081449426</link><title>New York Rangers at Montreal Canadiens (NHL) Jan. 15th, 2012 7:00 PM EST 

According to Z Code Calculations, based on statistical analysis since 1999 The New York Rangers are a favorite with a 53% chance to beat the Montreal Canadiens. 

They are 15-6-2 on a road this season. According to bookies the odd for NY Rangers moneyline is 1.80 and the spread line is -1. The calculated chance to cover the +1.5 spread for Montreal is 76.53% 

The latest streak for NY Rangers is W-L-W-W-W-W 

Next games for NY Rangers against: Nashville (Burning Hot, 10th Place), Pittsburgh (Dead Up, 19th Place) 

Last games for NY Rangers were: 3-0 (Win)@Toronto(Average, 17th Place) 14 January, 3-0 (Loss) Ottawa (Burning Hot, 8th Place) 12 January 

The Over/Under line is 5. The projection for Under is 50.53%. 
NY Rangers team: 
Who is hot: Henrik Lundqvist (goalkeeper, 3 place in Top50, SV%=0.937), Marian Gaborik (34 points), Ryan Callahan (31 points), Brad Richards (31 points), Derek Stepan (29 points) 
Who is injured: Brandon Dubinsky, Jeff Woywitka, Michael Sauer, Steve Eminger 
Montreal team: 
Who is hot: Carey Price (goalkeeper, 21 place in Top50, SV%=0.913), Tomas Plekanec (31 points), Erik Cole (30 points), Max Pacioretty (29 points), David Desharnais (28 points) 
Who is injured: Andrei Markov, Brian Gionta, Rene Bourque, Ryan White 
Hot trends: 

NY Rangers won 80% in favorite status in last 5 games 
83% Winning Rate Predicting Last 6 Montreal games 

Recommendations: 

Very high chance 77% of the tight game that can go into overtime﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_02_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SFc4CyHSKnw/TxLCKFZrQ9I/AAAAAAAAEkc/2YWs0J2TuSA/w426-h311/Screenshot_115.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/118025217575229002011/albums/5801548503400106881/5801548508457923778</link><title>Fall colours - Amtrak Montreal to New York 

Great sites in the fall via Amtrak Montreal to New York.  This is shot from our window seat on the train.  I enjoy the train for comfortability and convenience over flying.  At least I haven't had my private parts patted down taking the train.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-S_HsiJR-8p0/UIM9oWnU9MI/AAAAAAAAHkU/42uZf0juyGc/w426-h237/Fall%2Bcolours%2B-%2BAmtrax%2BMonreal%2Bto%2BNew%2BYork-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/102355438470080501971/albums/5728332338236594273/5728332338739156978</link><title>The New York, Boston &amp; Montreal was a victim of the Panic of 1873. They were going to connect New York to Boston by using some existing railroads, and building some connector lines. This cut was east of Carmel, NY, and was to carry the traffic north from the Putnam Branch. They built some culverts nearby, and some fills, but the longest single piece I found was only about 200' long. 

That seems to be the pattern when building a railroad. You don't just start at one end and keep building out. You start at multiple ends, build pieces and connect them all together. Or, in this case, if you've run out of money, not connect them together.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5HbWxEvKrZs/T38f6X3uF_I/AAAAAAAAFUc/OXOjQZdUJ2g/w426-h237/NYMB-cutting.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/116760645337871263375/albums/5935040456685626017/5935040460545790914</link><title>Get in on the Newest Social Movie App -- Before it hits iTunes!!! 

iOS App Testing Begins First Week Of November 2013. 
24 Slots left --- Act Fast!! 

Interested?  - Sign Up Now! - www.cinealoop.com 

Team CineaLoop 

#beta #testing #app #iphoneapp #mobile #movienight #moviedate #moviegroup #tryitout #iphone #moviegoer #movie #cineama #mobileapp #ios #Montreal #Quebec #Toronto #NewYork #Sanfrancisco #LosAngeles #Boston #Houston #startup #staruplife #earlyadopters #social #new﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ymv8KNSeij4/Ul1_2opnE8I/AAAAAAAAAw8/kq4HhEjHarI/w426-h284/CineaLoopFullTake134.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/118025217575229002011/albums/5709788572640478481/5709788571542678866</link><title>What an awesome trip Montreal to New York. Can't wait to go again, tor the trip and especially to see my daughter. 

You got to love both Montreal and New York two amazing cities so close together.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MIfzVeVfzn0/Tz0-dD1i7VI/AAAAAAAAEAY/Q4yaoqhfkj8/w426-h283/Amtrak%2Bto%2BNew%2BYork-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/118025217575229002011/albums/5685867120704960417/5685867122991964530</link><title>Old Town, Montreal. Filled with brick streets. 

Montreal and New York are two great places to visit to take photography. Lots to see and explore. I am going through a whack of photos that I took about a year ago. Makes me want to go back, that and I really want to go back and see my daughter.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-2sRcIXNx5a8/TuhCBfoCIXI/AAAAAAAACu4/IzssLdSjzkk/w426-h630/Old%2BTown-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/108494779459623667377/albums/5946919197976470481/5946919197735493234</link><title>Do the +Canadiens de Montréal get their second win at Madison Square Garden this season vs. the +New York Rangers tonight? 

Watch on: #NHL Network-US, CBC, RDS, MSG2. http://s.nhl.com/qSX68﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-5KaeefhzHgY/UoezgJD5nnI/AAAAAAAApmI/U62XHHxY6bo/w426-h284/3Kc73.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/116992234810067730471/albums/5704965769116220433/5704965771308223426</link><title>For all you East Coasters 
Especially for the +New England Patriots ( GO PATS ) and +New York Giants fans on this Super Bowl weekend a shot of home from the ISS. 

This Jan. 29 panorama of much of the East Coast, photographed by one of the Expedition 30 crew members aboard the International Space Station, provides a look generally northeastward: Philadelphia-New York City-Boston corridor (bottom-center); western Lake Ontario shoreline with Toronto (left edge); Montreal (near center). An optical illusion in the photo makes the atmospheric limb and light activity from Aurora Borealis appear "intertwined." 
Image Credit: NASA﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-8BnpRXWURb4/TywcJI6Wy8I/AAAAAAAALYQ/aOUbuy5sUnw/w426-h320/620617main_iss1600_1600-1200.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7104-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/How%20to%20go%20from%20New%20York%20to%20Montreal/photos/113732859109750622157/albums/5930124838067103313/5930124836413649954</link><title>NEW REVIEW! 

Colors, coasts and coves - New York to Montreal on #OceaniaCruises  #Regatta 
"What makes this line the best for us is the wonderful service everywhere on board. Their marvellous staff to passenger ratio is reflected in the fact that the, mainly Indian, Indonesian and Philippines crew quickly get to know you..." 

Read more: http://bit.ly/15KJYL2﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7104_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_Rwe3trsbqI/UkwJHpwoNCI/AAAAAAAAAqA/NHrdZTlkvLI/w426-h320/Oceania_Regatta_013.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>