<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:20:31" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7108-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/renting%20car%20seattle/photos/115043743501206260205/albums/5932383696440018721/5932383695625914610</link><title>Save 10% on October Rentals in Seattle. Choose your car today and save. http://goo.gl/SGHsWG #ezrentacar﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7108_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-IvhcQzH9CmY/UlQPikEaCPI/AAAAAAAAAfg/J6IcbR1ZHBI/s426/3mFuL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7108-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/renting%20car%20seattle/photos/115043743501206260205/albums/5929785447903776209/5929785446309433746</link><title>Save 10% in Atlanta on October car rentals. Reserve now and save http://ow.ly/pnMlv. #ezrentacar #atlanta﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7108_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-A_v2ezGov4k/UkrUcjGOEZI/AAAAAAAAAds/3YivgHRKcUA/s426/3iyzT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7108-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/renting%20car%20seattle/photos/114121932233302784420/albums/5908285900543376097/5908285902452216610?authkey=CPKvz5WB4NuBsgE</link><title>Domestic Bliss is a Battalion of Earwax and a Hot Cup o'Joe \- If Aeschylus were to write the scripts for 1950's teenage hygiene shorts, he would likely hit upon +Andrew Wright's current little predicament. He has the mad fortune of prodigious earwax production. This, in turn, means that he can hear a small percentage of anything of sweetly mordant susurrations and a large percentage of our married life involved him looking at me with the Andrew "huh" face (raised eye brows, pursed lips, and a fight-or-flight anchoring posture just in case I just warned him of impending attack). To ameliorate this, he attempted to solve the problem with some OTC ear wax drops. Predictably they had the opposite effect and currently he is one step closer to Pinball Wizardry (deaf, not-so-dumb, and near-sighted, boy who will definitely come to the mirror at the slightest provocation!) 

It raised an interesting conversation to which I shall give short shrift in attempt at pith. Andrew was saying he had heard that we only actually hear a small percentage of the words people use, but our brains are able to fill in the blanks of sentences. He wondered if it was that he heard fewer words than others or if he filled in fewer blanks. I reflected that, as somebody who relies heavily on the filling in blanks, I can generally predict with very strong accuracy the general content of a sentence based on context, body language, tone, and remembered/predicted patterns of communication previously used by my interlocutor. When I'm listening to a person, I think that my brain runs parallel in their voice. From that prediction, my brain also can prospectively predict the sentence being uttered based on the first few words and merely flag the operative words that would be in conformance or in contrast to my initial expectations. I often find myself finishing sentences aloud with them (and for my own part, trailing off in the expectation that others will finish mine.) From my observation, Andrew tends to rely less on body language/expression/etc., and has a less accurate memory for ways that others talk or what exactly people have said before, in what tone, and . He also seems much more focused on single words in a sentence and will have less facility juggling synonyms or different ways of saying the same thing. I suggested this made me think that he probably did less filling in of blanks. Then again, he seems pretty darned congested. Naturally, this is all speculation. 

At the moment it's not just me and my buttery intonations that fall on deaf ears: Last night he could not even hear the booming timbre of my brother-in-law (the first, so not Andrew's biological brother). Yes, this is family invasion season! Yesterday night was only a preview, as they are immediately skipping the country. So far, their byzantine travel plans have so far involved driving to Chicago, taking a plane to Seattle, renting a car for the drive from Seattle to Bellingham, and then returning one car and returning the other in Bellingham. Prospectively they are now taking this new rental car across the border, hopping a ferry, driving across Galliano Island, and finally taking a Whaler to my father's property in the Gulf Islands. I imagine they will then hang glide to Salt Spring Island, where the boys will grab a jet ski and Rachel will commandeer a helicopter from which she will parachute onto a paddle board in the middle of the Atlantic Coast and eventually, presumably, swim back to shore, while the boys meet up with a train and head their way back. No, really, I believe they take the ferry back here and spend about ten more days in mid-August in Bellingham with us. 

 Shockingly there were snares along the way. The Bellingham rental car was long gone upon their arrival. The boys came to Round Table to meet us and Rachel stayed behind to get a special "upgrade" to an uncleaned Tahoe that apparently may be running a little low on gas. By a little low, turns out they meant "sucked dry." She did not even make it to the gas station two miles away. Tow trucks were involved, as were some choice words on both ends. 

My nephews have, as always, glommed onto Gramma Pam, our extended family lightening rod for all things exuberant and attention-seeking. Who can blame them, since she is darned fun. Hopefully she doesn't need to sleep for the remainder of August, because she's not going to get a chance to do so. 

I am still on the OK, list, although at a much lower level of immediate interest when Gramma Pam is around. Andrew was accepted but mostly unacknowledged at this juncture. They'll remember him later, but it was a nice way for him to wade back into the fray for his first official turn as an uncle. His comment upon two hours of hanging out at Round Table: "You know, if you just wanted to stop at one, that's totally ok with me." 

Aside from my new turn as a stage actress - I must enunciate to the back row - and the momentary preview of nephew-mania our weekend has followed a generally typical pattern.I cannot say that I suggest laundering your jacket with a ziplock bag of soynuts in the pocket. But, one must always experiment. 

Happy Sunday!! 

#sockwars  ﻿

Meer lezen (87 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7108_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-IOBYAXeb6R8/Uf5yuY8c0yI/AAAAAAAAclc/zKC1Ahg_ce0/w426-h320/20130804_073022.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7108-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/renting%20car%20seattle/photos/115043743501206260205/albums/5934978122807428273/5934978121737708674</link><title>#TT Save 10% in Las Vegas on October car rentals. Choose your car today! http://ow.ly/plS2k #travel #vegas﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7108_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-rLzhT2O7n-0/Ul1HKCfkJII/AAAAAAAAAg8/FCXJJDAaSic/s426/3qG0K.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7108-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/renting%20car%20seattle/photos/108161928669055573248/albums/5850849299784088113/5850849299641304450?authkey=CKDXtufFjqugkQE</link><title>+car2go is a good way to get around Seattle for one or two people. +SideCar is a great way for three (or four, or five?!) people to get a ride. A far better option if recreational substances are in play. There's a chance we'll meet; I share rides in my #EV  as part of the +DrivingElectric outreach project. I've given my fellow Seattleites rides by the score over the past few months. 

If you're headed out of the city, consider renting a vehicle through +RelayRides  such as this fine VW Jetta TDI which runs predominantly on #BioDiesel 
https://relayrides.com/car-rental/seattle/volkswagen-jetta/11537 (it's mine) 

#CarSharing   #RideSharing   #livecarfree  ﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7108_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/---_qWvwlSg8/UTJkcFt2hYI/AAAAAAAAmnk/i2EeSsI4mSw/w426-h320/IMG_20130302_105812.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>