<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7110">civil engineering jobs pennsylvania</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:29:37" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/107682748671253717847/albums/5696326577644066417/5696326577347694418</link><title>A totally awesome read: predictions of John Watkins, an American civil engineer, in 1900 

10 of them came through and 4 didn't. He even predicted Mobile phone when the phone itself was a miraculous achievement for the time. 
\--------------------------------------------------- 

10 predictions that Watkins got right... 

1\. Digital colour photography 
2\. The rising height of Americans 
3\. Mobile phones 
4\. Pre-prepared meals 
5\. Slowing population growth 
6\. Hothouse vegetables 
7\. Television 
8\. Tanks 
9\. Bigger fruit 
10\. The Acela Express 

...and four he didn't 

1\. No more C, X or Q 
2\. Everybody will walk 10 miles a day 
3\. No more cars in large cities 
4\. No mosquitoes or flies 
\----------------------------------------------- 
Ten 100-year predictions that came true 
By Tom Geoghegan / BBC News Magazine 

John Watkins predicted Americans would be taller, tanks would exist and C, X and Q would no longer feature in our everyday alphabet 

In 1900, an American civil engineer called John Elfreth Watkins made a number of predictions about what the world would be like in 2000. How did he do? 

As is customary at the start of a new year, the media have been full of predictions about what may happen in the months ahead. 

But a much longer forecast made in 1900 by a relatively unknown engineer has been recirculating in the past few days. 

In December of that year, at the start of the 20th Century, John Elfreth Watkins wrote a piece published on page eight of an American women's magazine, Ladies' Home Journal, entitled What May Happen in the Next Hundred Years. 

He began the article with the words: "These prophecies will seem strange, almost impossible," explaining that he had consulted the country's "greatest institutions of science and learning" for their opinions on 29 topics. 

Watkins was a writer for the Journal's sister magazine, the Saturday Evening Post, based in Indianapolis. 

The Post brought this article to a modern audience last week when its history editor Jeff Nilsson wrote a feature praising Watkins' accuracy. 

It was picked up and caused some excitement on Twitter. So what did Watkins get right - and wrong? 

10 predictions that Watkins got right... 

1\. Digital colour photography 

Watkins did not, of course, use the word "digital" or spell out precisely how digital cameras and computers would work, but he accurately predicted how people would come to use new photographic technology. 

A scan of the original article can be found online 
"Photographs will be telegraphed from any distance. If there be a battle in China a hundred years hence, snapshots of its most striking events will be published in the newspapers an hour later.... photographs will reproduce all of nature's colours." 

This showed major foresight, says Mr Nilsson. When Watkins was making his predictions, it would have taken a week for a picture of something happening in China to make its way into Western papers. 

People thought photography itself was a miracle, and colour photography was very experimental, he says. 

"The idea of having cameras gathering information from opposite ends of the world and transmitting them - he wasn't just taking a present technology and then looking to the next step, it was far beyond what anyone was saying at the time." 

Patrick Tucker from the World Future Society, based in Maryland in the US, thinks Watkins might even be hinting at a much bigger future breakthrough. 

"'Photographs will be telegraphed' reads strikingly like how we access information from the web," says Mr Tucker. 

2\. The rising height of Americans 

"Americans will be taller by from one to two inches." 

Watkins had unerring accuracy here, says Mr Nilsson - the average American man in 1900 was about 66-67ins (1.68-1.70m) tall and by 2000, the average was 69ins (1.75m). 

Continue reading the main story 
How did Watkins do? 

Patrick Tucker 
World Future Society 
Watkins' record as a forecaster, based on this small segment of his work, was less than perfect. But that doesn't mean he was a bad futurist. Although he died before the World Future Society was formed in 1966, we would have been honoured to consider him a member. We believe that talking about the future is the most important thing that people do, even though the future, by its nature, is unknowable. We invent the future through our actions and change it constantly. We can never know it fully but we can always be better prepared for what may occur. Watkins helped people begin this act of preparation and considered creation. 

World Future Society 
BBC experts predict big stories in 2012 
Today, it's 69.5ins (1.76m) for men and 64ins (1.63m) for women. 

3\. Mobile phones 

"Wireless telephone and telegraph circuits will span the world. A husband in the middle of the Atlantic will be able to converse with his wife sitting in her boudoir in Chicago. We will be able to telephone to China quite as readily as we now talk from New York to Brooklyn." 

International phone calls were unheard of in Watkins' day. It was another 15 years before the first call was made, by Alexander Bell, from one coast of the US to the other. The idea of wireless telephony was truly revolutionary. 

4\. Pre-prepared meals 

"Ready-cooked meals will be bought from establishment similar to our bakeries of today." 

The proliferation of ready meals in supermarkets and takeaway shops in High Streets suggests that Watkins was right, although he envisaged the meals would be delivered on plates which would be returned to the cooking establishments to be washed. 

5\. Slowing population growth 

"There will probably be from 350,000,000 to 500,000,000 people in America [the US]." 

The figure is too high, says Nilsson, but at least Watkins was guessing in the right direction. If the US population had grown by the same rate it did between 1800 and 1900, it would have exceeded 1 billion in 2000. 

"Instead, it grew just 360%, reaching 280m at the start of the new century." 

6\. Hothouse vegetables 

Winter will be turned into summer and night into day by the farmer, said Watkins, with electric wires under the soil and large gardens under glass. 

"Vegetables will be bathed in powerful electric light, serving, like sunlight, to hasten their growth. Electric currents applied to the soil will make valuable plants to grow larger and faster, and will kill troublesome weeds. Rays of coloured light will hasten the growth of many plants. Electricity applied to garden seeds will make them sprout and develop unusually early." 

Large gardens under glass were already a reality, says Philip Norman of the Garden Museum in London, but he was correct to predict the use of electricity. Although coloured lights and electric currents did not take off, they were probably experimented with. 

Continue reading the main story 
Who was J Elfreth Watkins? 
Lived from 1852-1903 
Was a railroad engineer until he suffered a "disabling" accident in 1873 
After that, became a clerk for the Pennsylvania Railroad 
In 1885, took a job as curator at the transport section of the US National Museum 
Source: Smithsonian Institution Archives 

"Electricity certainly features in plant propagation. But the earliest item we have is a 1953 booklet Electricity in Your Garden detailing electrically warmed frames, hotbeds and cloches and electrically heated greenhouses, issued by the British Electrical Development Association. 

"We have a 1956 soil heater, used in soil to assist early germination of seeds in your greenhouse." 

7\. Television 

"Man will see around the world. Persons and things of all kinds will be brought within focus of cameras connected electrically with screens at opposite ends of circuits, thousands of miles at a span." 

Watkins foresaw cameras and screens linked by electric circuits, a vision practically realised in the 20th Century by live international television and latterly by webcams. 

8\. Tanks 

Tweets praised Watkins' accuracy 
"Huge forts on wheels will dash across open spaces at the speed of express trains of today." 

Leonardo da Vinci had talked about this, says Nilsson, but Watkins was taking it further. There weren't many people that far-sighted. 

9\. Bigger fruit 

"Strawberries as large as apples will be eaten by our great-great-grandchildren." 

Lots of larger varieties of fruit have been developed in the past century, but Watkins was over-optimistic with regard to strawberries. 

10\. The Acela Express 

"Trains will run two miles a minute normally. Express trains one hundred and fifty miles per hour." 

Exactly 100 years after writing those words, to the very month, Amtrak's flagship high-speed rail line, the Acela Express, opened between Boston and Washington, DC. It reaches top speeds of 150mph, although the average speed is considerably less than that. High-speed rail in other parts of the world, even in 2000, was considerably faster. 

...and four he didn't 

1\. No more C, X or Q 

"There will be no C, X or Q in our everyday alphabet. They will be abandoned because unnecessary." 

This was obviously wrong, says Patrick Tucker of the World Future Society, but also remarkable in the way that it hints at the possible effects of mass communication on communication itself. 

2\. Everybody will walk 10 miles a day 

"This presents a rather generous view of future humanity but doesn't seem to consider the popularity and convenience of the very transportation breakthroughs [moving sidewalks, express trains, coaches] forecast elsewhere in the article," says Mr Tucker. 

Continue reading the main story 
And some other Watkins forecasts 
Central heating and air conditioning 
Cheap cars 
Average life expectancy to rise to 50 
Free university education 
Refrigerated transport of food 
3\. No more cars in large cities 

"All hurry traffic will be below or above ground when brought within city limits." 

However, many cities do have pedestrian zones in their historic centres. And he correctly forecast elevated roads and subways. 

4\. No mosquitoes or flies 

"Mosquitoes, house-flies and roaches will have been exterminated." 

Watkins was getting ahead of himself here. Indeed the bed bug is making a huge comeback in the US and some other countries. 

Maybe the end of the mosquito and the house fly is something to look forward to in 2100? 
http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-16444966﻿

Meer lezen (281 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-8119rqpRB9A/Tw1q13dtD1I/AAAAAAAAsgg/tcZfELIdKVY/w426-h240/_57801314_predictions_comp464.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/110695872689494369839/albums/5974999772607373073/5974999773590450370</link><title>LETTER FROM THE MOONLIGHT STATE 2014: TOTAL LUNAR ECLIPSE 
How Campbell Newman is destroying the rule of law and all standards of decency by asset stripping Queensland and turning it into an open air prison. 

Dear Brett 

It's been a while, hasn't it, since we talked. So your call the other day was most welcome, and as promised, in this letter I will follow up on my comments about the abrogation of civil society, the rule of law, and human decency in Queensland under this Newman Government. 

It's not as easy a subject to understand as some pretend. Essentially what we are witnessing is the first government of an inexperienced team of politicians, most of whom aren't particularly bright, and all of whom have no real idea about large-scale policy development or implementation. They are latching onto advice for their federal counterparts and corporate patrons to emulate American-style right wing economic doctrines, which are mostly about cutting social services and selling off public assets to private interests. There appears to be no public interest test applied to such pathological privatisation of public benefits betond the mantra of balancing budgets. 

This fetish with asset stripping is linked to a determined push to criminalise unions as a pretext to extinguish the right to collective bargaining. The goal here is to prevent union negotiations for wages and conditions as a precursor for an American-style minimum-wage. The American example tells us that this does not create more jobs, as is deceptively claimed by conservatives, but actually serves solely to immiserated the labour force so that it will work for less than poverty-line wages. A perhaps unintended but nevertheless foreseeable consequence will be what occurred in the US: an increasingly unnerved, complicit middle class that cannot yet see that its collaboration will also inevitably erode its own influence and economic wellbeing. 

At the same time, Newman's ministry is aiming at American-style police state measures, starting with the effective suspension of habeas corpus, and including mandatory minimum sentences, probably tying in with plans for privatised gaols. It all dovetails with a G20 summit management plan that essentially turns the Brisbane CBD into a porous concentration camp, with curfews for citizens and extraordinary powers approaching martial law for a new cadre of paramilitary police. 
We seem to have plenty of money to spend on making corporations richer, and kitting out our police as an army of uniformed union-busting thugs, but not to look after the interests of ordinary Queenslanders. 

The only open-ended question is whether Newman and his ministers are too dumb to see the inevitable consequences of what they are doing, or whether they are just smart enough to know exactly what they are doing when they set fire to all that is Australian about the Queensland polity. 

NEWMAN'S TEA PARTY 
To understand the principal actor in the thinly veiled tyranny that is Newman's brave new Queensland, you first need to appreciate the influences that shaped our Premier. Canberra-born Campbell Newman was raised in Tasmania by parents both of whom were ministers in conservative Federal governments. He graduated from Duntroon as a Lieutenant in 1985, and resigned eight years later after acquiring the nickname 'Noddy' for his 'attention' to detail and his leadership abilities. He probably recognised that a soldier with his skills and aptitude could never rise much beyond his final rank of Major. He did, however, acquire an engineering degree in those years, and followed up with an MBA in Queensland while working for a grain company. 

In 2004 he was elected Lord Mayor of Brisbane at the head of the Liberal team, becoming known for a patronising arrogance that might be explained by little man syndrome - attempting to compensate for his diminutive stature (about 5'3", or 163cm) with bully-boy tactics he might have learnt in the army. 

In 2008 the Queensland branches of the Liberal and National parties merged to form the Queensland-only Liberal National Party (LNP). People get confused about this because Queensland federal conservative politicians, being members of the LNP state branch, are listed as LNP rather than Liberal or National, but the latter parties have merged nowhere else in Australia, where coalition members still belong separately to the Liberal or National parties. 

In 2011, after protracted infighting among Queensland conservatives, Newman challenged for the state leadership as sitting Lord Mayor and won unopposed after the incumbent, John-Paul Langbroek from Surfer's Paradise, realised he didn't have the numbers to survive a challenge and resigned instead. 

In a dramatic but not untoward move, Newman led the LNP into the 2012 state election without holding a seat in the Queensland Parliament, winning the upper middle class seat of Ashgrove, a leafy-green dormitory west of the city, only at the election, which he won with what is correctly labelled a landslide, yielding 78 seats for the LNP, just seven for a routed ALP (and two for Katter's Australia Party). 

Because Queensland's ALP voted its upper house out of existence in 1921, the state parliament consists of a single chamber, meaning that with such an overwhelming majority, Newman is absolute master, and can count on almost no debate or scrutiny, with all legislation rubber stamped on demand. This dictatorial position, together with his arrogant brashness and his lack of stature, have seen him sometimes referred to as 'Newpoleon'. 

One of his very first acts as Premier was to appoint former federal treasurer Peter Costello as head of a Commission of Audit, ostensibly to 'discover' huge debts and distance himself from blame for the 'tough' budgetary measures 'necessary' to bring the books back into balance. However, Costello's own activities since leaving federal politics make it clear that this was an exercise of legitimating an imported American model of Wall Street economics whereby the vast number of ordinary citizens pay for subsidies and windfalls that enrich a shrinking number of already wealthy corporate citizens. Usually such wealth redistribution from the poor to the rich involves handsome brokerage and consultancy fees for people like Costello, and, maybe, Newman himself. Only time will tell what board appointments or consultancies come Newman's way after his retirement from politics. 

THE COSTELLO ABACUS 
Following a protracted bout of indecisive sulking on the backbench after the Federal Coalition's comprehensive loss in 2007, Costello is today a managing partner of corporate consulting firm BKK Partners, formed by former Goldman Sachs JB Were executives Alastair Walton, Jeremy Mead, and John Anderson. The New York parent companies of this Australian offshoot, Goldman Sachs and JBWere, were of course deeply implicated in the lies, fraud, and outright theft that brought the world's financial system to its knees in 2007; it is compelling to suspect that the same immoral corporate culture of fraud, deception, and theft has not changed in BKK. 

Costello is also chairman of ECG Advisory Solutions. ECG counts as one its clients a private correctional facility operator, Serco, which is involved in managing part of Australia's detention regime for aspiring migrants arriving by boat. I don't think it's unreasonable to suspect Serco would like to operate some of Australia's gaols as well, perhaps starting with Queensland penitentiaries, which are sure to be a thriving business following the disturbing degradation of the rule of law under Newman. 
In a separate but also disturbing development, Costello, who established the $80 billion Australian Government Future Fund in 2006, when he was federal treasurer, is now its acting chairman, and likely to be confirmed as permanent in April. The fund was established to cover the Commonwealth's superannuation liabilities, but it is in the hands of a man operating according to the same principles that in the US saw the retirement savings of millions pillaged by criminal Wall Street market manipulation. 

In my opinion it was Costello who advised Newman to publicly distance himself right now from the unprincipled and short-sighted asset stripping that has been the sole outcome of privatisation in Australia so far. Costello's public recommendations to Newman are to sell off all possible public assets to private interests until the remaining functions of the state itself resemble only those favoured by American Tea Party plutocrats: no social services, and, for 'little' people, user pays double for everything else, from water to schools, via taxation first, and then direct user-pays charges. Meanwhile corporations are freed from responsibilities like legal or regulatory obligations, including taxation, job creation, or environmental duty of care. 

One of the areas considered for privatisation is Queensland's correctional service - our gaols. Two are already under private management, and the Costello recommendations are to privatise al the others, including all ancillary services. When you put this together with figures that show Queensland gaols are already the cheapest-run in the nation, and with recent moves by Newman to legalise arbitrary arrests, to overturn the burden of proof for criminal charges, and to introduce mandatory minimum sentences, you have the American Republican formula of 'three strikes' and prisons run for profit. That is, a guarantee to private operators not only of public funds, but an endless and abundant supply of inmates to work as slave labour in simple manufactures. This undermines the employment of state correctional services officers, and smaller manufacturers with whom the private gaols will compete unfairly, given their exemption from paying decent wages for their labour force. 

Just how profitable this can be is evidenced by the bribery scandal that saw two Pennsylvania judges, Mark Ciarvarella, and Michael Conahan, sent to gaol for accepting more than $2 million in bribes to pass harsh sentences so a couple of local private prisons would have a steady stream of juvenile long-term inmates to be used as cheap labour. Their victims were not exonerated as part of the prosecution! 

That appears to be the Costello-Newman vision for newly criminalized classes of Queenslanders: make them work for nothing as an underclass of slaves. Will Serco feature in these plans? And if it does, will Costello's company make a handsome consultancy fee for legalizing slavery in Queensland? Stay tuned and judge for yourself. 

Despite promises not to go ahead with privatisation until he gets a mandate for it at the next state election, Newman has moved already, giving us a glimpse of what's to come. A multi-billion dollar, 29-year contract to build and maintain 10 new schools has been awarded to the Canadian-US Plenary Group, already involved in Gold Coast transport infrastructure. This corporation was set up with the sole purpose of exploiting the Wall Street model of siphoning off public funds for private profit. The methods are to use only the cheapest parts, cut every corner, and to create local employment only temporarily through minimum-wage labour brokers, like Manpower, that exploit every loophole to avoid the lowest working conditions enjoyed by Australian employees covered by agreements and awards. These conditions include working hours and overtime after a normal day's work, superannuation, paid leave, including maternity/paternity leave, sick leave, workers' compensation, or any kind of training and career-building. Instead Manpower and its ilk demand that its minimum-wage labourers are always on-call for temporary, part-time stints, but disposable at two hours' notice. 

For Newman the virtue of such arrangements is that it makes some salary costs disappear from Queensland's books, replaced instead by American-style minimum conditions managed by someone else. Consultancy fees, on the other hand, do not show up as wages, and are buried in one-off expenses. 

Unfortunately, and short-sightedly, privatisation inevitably means less employment in Queensland, and less money circulating in the economy. That is particularly the case when you consider that all corporations, particularly non-Australian groups, operate on the basis of minimising their taxes here, using a transfer pricing mechanism to claim that their operating costs are actually incurred in tax havens overseas, meaning it probably pays few, if any taxes in Australia while relying on taxpayer-funded infrastructure as an input into its tender. It's the standard model for international corporations: extract public money and pay none back. It is pretty standard for conservative governments not pursue tax minimisation loopholes or even direct tax fraud. You and I, on the other hand, will be hounded for every few bucks the ATO thinks we owe. 

I'll tell you how this will go, Brett, because it always goes this way. Within three years Plenary Group will encounter 'unexpected' cost overruns, completely wiping out the supposed 10 per cent cost saving that was the basis of choosing Plenary rather than using Queensland resources to do the job. Of course Plenary knew this from day one, counting on the prospect of coming back for a second bite at the same apple, with Newman's administration bailing out its failing contract to the tune of millions more. Within five years schools will begin to crumble under the shoddy materials and workmanship being used, and while the government of the day and Plenary argue about this in court, those schools will be closed, meaning that Queensland taxpayers will be up for the cost of new ones - for the second time around. Within ten years the corporation will have declared its Australian subsidiary bankrupt rather than meet its commitments, and be free and clear of the whole mess, but able to walk away with maybe a billion dollars of Queensland taxpayer dollars, leaving nothing of value behind. The very next day the corporation will establish a new Australian subsidiary with no debts, possibly to bid on rehabilitating the abandoned schools, but definitely to bid on other projects. Perhaps the board of that new subsidiary will include the then retired Campbell Newman and Queensland Treasurer Tim Nicholls, or perhaps those guys will be 'consulting' to the corporation in some other capacity. It will all pan out as a shadow play with an outcome little different to just handing Plenary a billion dollars of taxpayer funds up-front for nothing in return. No one will remember who signed the contracts, or why Newman and Nichols suddenly have lucrative retirement benefits. It's the perfect white collar crime gravy train. 

There's more to come on this front. Newman's parliamentary majority is so large that he is unlikely to lose the next election except for an unforeseen scandal. That means he will be able to claim an unfettered mandate for unchecked privatisation from 2015. 

NEWMAN'S POLICE STATE 
Underpinning this economic vandalism is Newman's approach to eliminating the rule of law. 

He has already suspended habeas corpus with old anti-communist legislation, re-tasked as the Vicious Lawless Association Disestablishment Act 2013 (VLADA), and justified as 'anti-bikie' legislation. However, he's also introduced mandatory minimum sentences for certain types of offences. Just as a new tax, once introduced, only ever increases, so the scope of both VLADA and mandatory minimums will be extended and misapplied until they can be used for any purpose at all. 

In case you don't know, habeas corpus is the long-established right to a speedy hearing for an arrested person so he cannot be held for arbitrary reasons or extended periods without bail or a magistrate's decision on detention. In addition to suspending habeas corpus, VLADA reverses the onus of proof, turning upside down the centuries old common law legal tradition that an accuser must prove an allegation, instead forcing people arrested under VLADA to prove they are not members or associates of illegal organisations. The legislation is silent on what constitutes such proof, and Newman probably relies on most people arrested in this way not being able to afford a lawyer experienced enough to cut through the bullshit. 

It's not at all an accident that this legislation can be used easily right now to revoke licenses for electricians to pursue their trades on spurious allegations that they have been, or are bikies, or known associates of bikies - meaning livelihoods can be destroyed just on the say-so of police. It also means that the Electrical Trades Union (ETU) could be blackmailed not to engage in serious negotiations on any of Queensland's major construction or resource projects. You were a sparkie once. You know how serious that could be for your family. And that's just right now. 

A bit more tweaking of the law, and other trades and their unions could be similarly affected, debarring their members from holding down jobs, virtually driving them to crime by design. It is a monstrous perversion of all that is good about Australian democracy and a petulant swipe at the Queensland-driven Harvester decision that gave us living wages rather than minimums a hundred years ago. 

These developments represent the thin end of a wedge to introduce an American-style industrial landscape in which unions have no power to collectively bargain or represent their members, and in which corporations will be able to use the court system to undercut all minimum working conditions and wages. 

In aspiring to this kind of economic vandalism, Newman is moving quite deliberately towards destroying the first layer of Australia's middle class as a prelude to abandoning Australia's egalitarian socio-economic base altogether. The ability to use the same laws discussed above to arrest and indefinitely imprison unionists or any other Australians for engaging in picketing or protests against this kind of legal tyranny is icing on the Newman cake. 

It's also not at all accidental that such arbitrary powers to arrest people solely on the say-so of police come so close to the November 2014 G20 summit in Brisbane. Premier Newman, acting with grotesquely hysterical overstatement, or military delusions of grandeur, proposes to turn the CBD into a concentration camp, with barricades, tightly controlled access and exit from the CBD, curfews for local residents (who are not permitted to enter or exit their residences while VIPs are out and about). There will be paramilitary police in the streets with even more unconscionable powers to arrest anyone for any reason at all. Like a scene from Berlin during the 1936 Olympics. Except, perhaps, the Germans were less likely to be arrested, beaten, or incarcerated than we will be. 

You could suppose Newman thinks we are all soldiers, or brown shirts obliged to obey orders as if we were conscripts in his private army, but I think he underestimates the perception by Brisbane residents that this is our city, not his, and that our liberties are certainly not to be held at the pleasure of some overfed overseas knobs coming to a talkfest to promote more Republican economic chicanery. 

As a short aside to all of this, I was wondering the other day whether Jarrod Bleijie, the incompetent nancyboy who is our attorney general, deliberately played at naming his police state law after Vlad Tepes, AKA Vlad the Impaler, the 15th century Wallachian prince who liked to have his enemies skewered from anus to neck on long wooden poles, and then left to die with the poles stood upright in a public place. You probably know that this guy was the inspiration for Bram Stoker's Dracula. 
 Knowing just how much of a moron Bleijie really is, maybe he can't see that this is not an amusing parallel to be drawing. 

In the meantime, though, it is emerging quite publicly that VLADA is completely unnecessary to accomplish the stated aim: the anti-bikie push Newman and Bleijie lied about as the reason for the new laws. The Queensland - and national - legal fraternity has been uniformly critical of these laws as actually undermining the rule of law, and there's an interesting analysis of just how insignificant bikies have been in terms of criminal arrests and charges, before and after VLADA, by Bond University Assistant Professor Terry Goldsworthy (look it up on The Conversation website). 

The whole bikie thing is just a bullshit ruse, but not many people understand it, and those who do will not really want to talk about it, because it means confronting public corruption on a grand scale. 

GOLD COAST: BENT COPPERS AND GANGSTER PARADISE 
The incident that served as a trigger for the so called anti-bikie laws in Queensland was an admittedly repugnant brawl outside a restaurant between up to 60 bikies and 'associates', followed by the siege of the Southport police station by bikies aggressively demanding the release of the arrested brawlers. However, this incident was only the latest in an escalating series of violent crimes on the Gold Coast and hinterland. 

In many ways the Gold Coast represents a second barometer of Queensland's temperament. Second to Brisbane's George Street, but as an equal half rather than an alternative. 

The Gold Coast is all neon glitz and precious metal glitter deliberately appropriated from Las Vegas and California. Wealthy retires flock from all over the region to use grotesquely ugly but expensive mansions as god's waiting rooms, like Florida's beachfront paradise, nestled next to golf courses, artificial canals, shopping malls, beachfront, theme parks, casinos (legal and not so legal), and larger than life people. Those people include real domestic gangsters, rubbing shoulders with their regional colleagues, shaking hands with legitimate business people, but also hucksters, conmen, and charlatans of every kind. This population is diluted by solidly respectable families, classic Aussie battlers, ominous hillbilly types, and the beautiful people - surgically enhanced mutton trophy wives, as yet unspoilt lambs fit to be models, bronzed surfers and iron men, 'bikini babes' and modern flower children. Sometimes it's hard to tell them apart from the rent boys and working girls who make a handsome living in that milieu. 

This anthropological oddity has all the hallmarks of King Joh's moonlight state, with brown paper bags of cash settling many deals and power-plays. It also reflects the harsher reality that Queensland never quite left its 1970s and '80s culture of corruption behind. It merely morphed into more contemporary forms. Public servants, including cops, watching their superiors get rich, and imagining or knowing about dirty cash changing hands to legitimise the blackest deals. Public servants who just want their little slice of that pie, and learning from their superiors how to get it. 

In that climate of hand-in-till business, it becomes clear that the kind of public violence Newman used as an excuse for suspending habeas corpus was merely the logical outcome of a culture of corruption in which senior cops were either completely incompetent, or on the take, because a culture of brazen crime does not erupt overnight. It is the consequence of years of turning a blind eye by hundreds of public officials, lulling the criminals into a false sense of security about a bought-and-paid-for green light to commit ever more audacious and repulsive criminal acts in plain view. That's what I think is really happening on the Gold Coast: police who turned a blind eye for too long to gangsters doing what gangsters do. On this occasion it included drug-fucked thugs not being controlled by bikie chiefs to prevent bad publicity. 

Truth be told, Brett, I think many Queenslanders who aren't on the take know corruption will always be around, and don't really mind so long as it doesn't get so obviously out of hand. Gangsters who murder or beat each other in public are just not very smart; they should limit the unpleasantness to more private venues, and make sure the innocent don't get hurt or spooked. Not to do that is bad for business, and therefore just plain stupid. As stupid as all the senior cops on the take not telling their partners in crime to chill out and back off the cowboy antics. 

It's true that this culture of corruption flourished under successive Labor governments. It is also true, though, that it was more tightly controlled and contained for the past 20 years. No matter what the propaganda says, this will hardly be the end of the drugs trade, just of a share of it for the bikie clubs. Newman and his backers need the drugs trade to continue just as much as the dealers do. 

BLOWING ECONOMIC SMOKE 
There's some simple economics behind all of this. Every prohibition of intoxicants has resulted in a lucrative black market for them. To create a prohibition is therefore the deliberate creation of that black market for pecuniary interests. Those interests aren't just about dirty cash changing hands - though that's a major motivation - but also about massive public service structures built on the lie that the illegal drugs trade perpetually requires extra police, extra judges and lawyers, extra gaols, extra doctors and rehabilitation facilities, and so on. Thousands of publicly funded careers are built on the silliness of the American concept that we need to wage war on drugs, as if that weren't a declaration of war on our children, families and neighbours. 

The louder the enforcement rhetoric, and the more expensive the measures, the more determined are its proponents to use the prohibition to drive up the price, and therefore the profitability of the black market trade. Decades of experience shows this is the sole outcome of enforcement measures, with demand and supply always rising. If this is a war, it is a phoney war. There are even cops saying that these days, but not politicians. What could be the motivation for politicians to persist with hugely expensive and demonstrably ineffective policies? The answer is always money. 

You know this already. Your Premier decriminalized marijuana. Not because he's a pot-head, or a good guy, but because it just made good economic sense not to criminalise harmless dope smokers while spending billions of taxpayer dollars on ridiculously ineffective enforcement costs. It's a lesson learnt even in a couple of states in the US, where all this anti-drugs paranoia originated in the hysteria-fuelled Anslinger era of the 1950s, probably as a service to pharmaceutical companies to maintain their oligopoly on drugs altogether, but particularly the expensive fun stuff. 

If Newman was actually serious about budget cuts and cost savings, he could do a lot worse than following Colin Barnett's lead to decriminalise marijuana. Perhaps that would yield the cost savings over the life of a single parliament to eradicate the big bogey deficit he is using as a smokescreen to promote privatisation. Less taxpayer money for police, gaols, lawyers, judges, rehabilitation services, and so on. Less associated crime and criminals. Where's the downside? Of course there would be no corporate consultancy fees, retirement bonuses, and cushy board positions for Newman and friends at the end of such a road. Worse, some people who use politicians and senior police as sock puppets would be out of pocket for billions of dollars in illegal drug profits. 

So, while Attorney General Jarrod Bleijie might be making noises like a schoolboy head prefect about the VLADA nonsense cutting into bikie drug profits, it just isn't true. The aim was never to shut down the drugs franchise, which will simply be taken up by more sedate and circumspect operators. 

FROM MOONLIGHT TO FULL LUNAR ECLIPSE 
So you see, Brett, what was once dubbed the moonlight state for dirty deals done late at night is now a state in full eclipse of even moonlight, with monstrous things done in broad daylight by people dressed like American stockbrokers. People in the ridiculously pimp-like garb so favoured by Newman and Bleijie themselves. You know the thing: loudly checked shirts, or the striped ones with the white collars just to accentuate the class distinction, worn with even louder striped ties and foppish silk handkerchiefs instead of pocket squares, all wrapped incongruously in cheap business suits, as if in homage to 1980s Wall Street brokers. In reality, though, these guys are nothing like brokers, being merely the pimps or procurers of public money to corporate masters, who must themselves be somewhat appalled to be doing business with such yokels. One must suppose that Newman and others see themselves as urbane sophisticates, but in reality almost the entire party is composed of people evocative of William Hogarth caricatures: vulgar, crass, loud, grating, and simple-minded. 

The LNP wasn't so much elected as receiving the benefit of a strong backlash against the Beattie-Bligh Labor governments of 1998 to 2012. The ALP has a lot to answer for in allowing deficits to balloon and corruption to erode the integrity of the Queensland public service. Even with that baggage, Bligh might yet have won another term had Newman not ousted Langbroek, and, more importantly, had the Murdoch press and commercial TV channels not backed him as a kind of white knight. 

Without absolving Bligh and her ministry of their mounting arrogance and incompetence, when the LNP and ALP are compared, the structure of the ALP at least widens accountability by a system of internal factions, particularly unions with their direct link to working Australians. There is no such safety valve in the LNP. Most of its members are venal mercenaries with no guiding political principles or philosophy other than taking maximum advantage of all the available perks of power. Some are creatures straight from Deliverance, others sincere but deluded, and still others sincere in their contempt for anyone who went to the wrong school. Unfortunately the majority of LNP members appear to be neither sincere nor particularly bright. But they do suffer from uncritical hero worship of tycoons and all the nonsense such people spout about the virtue of white collar theft. 

There is also a small kernel of die-hard anti-Labor people among the conservatives whose raison d'être is nothing more than denying the Labor Party legitimacy and working at destroying its base. Hence the LNP's pathological anti-union doctrine. These people would rather burn down the state than share it with Labor and unionists, and shed all human decency rather than show any to Labor or union people. Newman appears to be among those nihilists. 

This absence of unifying or guiding principles and beliefs is why the LNP, and Australian conservatives more generally, borrow American political strategies, albeit without understanding them or their consequences. It's like painting by numbers from a pre-mixed palette, understanding neither pictorial composition nor how to mix colours. They don't bother discussing or adapting formula policies to suit local conditions, apparently accepting on faith that US imperialist overreach is the right way for everyone in the world. Their leader is a man who gives every appearance of not understanding even basic economics, let alone political economy. He seems not to possess enough intellect to bother looking at the consequences to the US of its own failed policies, but he nevertheless seeks to enforce them here. 

The consequences here are unlikely to be more gentle than in the US: massive public debt fueled by wealth re-distribution to the wealthy. 

There will be no significant savings arising from cutting social services, deteriorating public infrastructure, or the declining quality of products and services inversely related to rapidly rising costs for every privatised venture. There will be no public benefits arising from a servile underclass of labourers who know their place, a devastated middle class without the power to influence government the way it used to, and an internally divided society in which poverty and crime are the only growth industries. 

What Newman does understand is military authoritarianism, enforced at gunpoint, and with stockades for the unwilling. But no concept of civil society, public ethics, or even common human decency. He probably thinks he is building a society in which a rightful ruling class can resume privileged positions they held in the 1950s and '60s, but what he's really doing is building a society for sale. It is a cash and carry doctrine that has left whole cities in the American rustbelt derelict and desolate ghost towns. 

If things weren't bad enough on those fronts, our news media are missing in action, reporting football and tits in bikinis instead of who's doing what deals with whom. The Courier Mail belongs to Murdoch's News Corporation and acts as a propaganda sheet for big business interests. The commercial TV stations don't understand, or cater to anyone who understands, more than a tweet's worth of information on any given story. The ABC is too caught up in petty internal bureaucratic squabbles, and far too much focused on Sydney and Melbourne; what few journalists it has wouldn't notice even an alien invasion until someone else reported it. The news is still there, in diffuse, scattered reporting across many outlets, but no one is tying it together or presenting any analysis, let alone critique. 

Anyway, enough cheery news from the state of total lunar eclipse. How is everything over there? I hear you've had a pretty torrid summer so far, with more to come. Let me know about the shark culling; is it going ahead and to what extent? Are you still doing the surf life saving thing, or just bending the elbow at the club? 
I trust the family is well and soldiering on. 

Until next time 
Rusty 

___ 
From Minority Reports: http://peterstrempel.com/2014/01/31/letter-from-the-moonlight-state-2014-total-lunar-eclipse/﻿

Meer lezen (600 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-wCNXgl0bx8M/Uut2ox3l8MI/AAAAAAAAMDg/-F3IFy2x-00/w426-h237/campbell-newman-mephisto.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/113630612440279083293/albums/5950687040553572785/5950687042752501570</link><title>Renewable Energy Revolution: The Biggest Business Opportunity on the Planet 

The world has seen three major energy epochs. The first started when we harnessed fire to cook, keep warm and light our nights. The second began when we figured out we could burn condensed ancient swamp muck (first coal, soon oil) to power our cars and radios. The third epoch only recently began. 

Energy, the world’s largest industry, is undergoing a tectonic shift. It’s time to stop hedging our bets. It’s time to embrace the idea that we have the power to transition the entire planet to 100% clean, renewable energy. 

What Changed? 

The shift didn’t come out of nowhere. For decades, we’ve been developing better clean energy technologies, even as the fossil fuel industry has (literally) dug itself into a very deep hole. 

The biggest story is in solar. The cost for panels has fallen by more than 99% in the past three decades, from more than $75 per watt in 1977 to about 50 cents per watt today. 

Meanwhile, as we’ve burned through the most easily accessible reserves, fossil fuel prices continue to rise. Coal prices have been steadily increasing …and oil prices have gone on a dramatic upward run (especially like now, when people plan their Thanksgiving roadtrips). 

And even accounting for the supply increases from fracking here in the U.S., natural gas prices across the world have still more than doubled in the last decade alone and the U.S. Energy Information Administration forecasts steady price increases over the next 30 years. 

The overall trend is clear. Our energy world is turning upside down. All over the world, it’s starting to make more financial sense for people to power their lives with clean energy rather than dirty fuels. 

100% is Possible 

Despite the changing economics of energy, many still question the feasibility of scaling up clean technologies. A common refrain is that renewables are too intermittent or too hard to integrate into the grid to quickly meet 100% of our energy demand. That's just pro-fossil fuel industry rhetoric. 

In 2011, two professors, Mark Jacobson from Stanford and Mark Delucchi from UC Davis, asked whether we could run our entire planet on wind, water, and the sun. Like others who have conducted similar analyses, they came to the conclusion that there are “no technological and economic barriers to converting the entire world to clean, renewable energy sources.” 

“What we lack,” they said. “is societal and political will.” 

Make no mistake: the task is huge. In Jacobson and Delucchi’s model, we’ll need to build 3.8 million large wind turbines and 90,000 solar power plants. Our roofs our going to have to shine, because we’ll need 1.7 billion rooftop solar arrays. 

Globally, the amount of investment required is on the order of $100 trillion dollars. Put simply, building out a new clean energy infrastructure may be the biggest business opportunity on the planet. 

http://ecowatch.com/2013/11/26/renewable-energy-biggest-business-opportunity/ 

Stanford researcher maps out an alternative energy future for New York 

 The plan, scheduled for publication in the journal Energy Policy, shows the way to a sustainable, inexpensive and reliable energy supply that creates local jobs and saves the state billions of dollars in pollution-related costs. 

Mark Z. Jacobson, a senior fellow with the Stanford Woods Institute for the Environment and the Precourt Institute for Energy, co-authored the study with scientists from Cornell University and the University of California-Davis. 

"Converting to wind, water and sunlight is feasible, will stabilize costs of energy and will produce jobs while reducing health and climate damage," said Jacobson, a professor of civil and environmental engineering. 

The study is the first to develop a plan to fulfill all of a state's transportation, electric power, industry, and heating and cooling energy needs with renewable energy, and to calculate the number of new devices and jobs created, amount of land and ocean areas required, and policies needed for such an infrastructure change. It also provides new calculations of air pollution mortality and morbidity impacts and costs based on multiple years of air quality data. 

The study concludes that while a WWS conversion may result in initial capital cost increases, such as the cost of building renewable energy power plants, these costs would be more than made up for over time by the elimination of fuel costs. In contrast, the fossil fuel industry is capital intensive throughout it's life cycle, and thereafter for land reclamation and remediation plans. 

Photo: Mosaic, Hundreds of clean energy investors celebrate the installation of Mosaic’s first project offering a return on investment. Fifty-two people are earning 6.38% interest each year from the solar panels located atop the Youth Employment Project in Oakland, CA. 

#renewableenergies   #solarindustry   #windenergy  ﻿

Meer lezen (106 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-3paDY1M27o4/UpUWVljIV0I/AAAAAAABy1E/vR57kGBtd48/w426-h237/mosaicmeansbusiness.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/114529371273443966439/albums/6004422887490334321/6004506497729244754</link><title>9/11 Inside Job Explained In Under 5 Minutes 
http://topinfopost.com/2013/06/17/911-conspiracy-theory-in-under-5-minutes  Lawsuits to Obtain Videos Published on Nov 26, 2012 
Video of Pentagon explosion on 9/11 with no plane, This is cctv video seized by the FBI released by the US District Court of Eastern Virginia 
Video Footage From CCTV Shows No Plane at 911 Pentagon Explosion · Released 2006 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_DtvRvfSEv4/U1RK2LCtLlI/AAAAAAACqMY/RY3Slmpfr5c/w426-h256/safe_image.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/100801061924982065053/albums/5730992894943341633/5730992896462364002</link><title>Wise words from Penn Jillette… 

(via: Poké Council)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-RPBEZt_SkcA/T4iTrNvtHWI/AAAAAAABByE/xPmeFvKDvqw/w426-h256/564645_290421804371145_275078289238830_656030_118138661_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/113751591639074735239/albums/5869872814491173409/5869872820241897826?authkey=CP3x59vwk6_BzwE</link><title>Believe it or not this is our engineers office fridge.  Cool eh? 

If you're a high achiever with talent who is looking for something more than a boring job, doesn't need to be supervised, and wants to be in at ground zero with a company that has a shot at being one of the biggest sites on the internet, then join our team! 

Apply now: 
http://www.jobstreet.com.ph/jobs/2013/4/default/80/3970774.htm?fr=21&amp;src=11 
http://www.jobstreet.com.ph/jobs/2013/4/default/80/3970763.htm?fr=21&amp;src=11 
http://www.jobstreet.com.ph/jobs/2013/4/default/80/3970767.htm?fr=21&amp;src=11 
http://www.jobstreet.com.ph/jobs/2013/4/default/80/3963672.htm?fr=21&amp;src=11﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-IgNkL_y12Rs/UXX6Ouc9GWI/AAAAAAAAC04/C45jprncRx0/w426-h568/fl-eng.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/105479712798762608629/albums/5717934504170212209/5717934501889509234</link><title>In February, the economy added 233,000 jobs. It's clear the economy is moving in the right direction. We're steadily creating jobs. Nonetheless, we need to do more. http://1.usa.gov/wmxR2r﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-yUgrJdcAdNo/T1ovInITB3I/AAAAAAAAIdM/UQwup8lb7zw/w426-h321/jobs-chart-feb.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/112118861354873908587/albums/5978093238191888577/5978093237705487986</link><title>This is an extremely powerful photo﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-77zE0bZoVP4/UvZ0IFuZtnI/AAAAAAADcHs/spha5srdGkk/w426-h396/image.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/100623276740673202144/albums/5696525299798484817/5696525303495632722</link><title>Money is always something that people don’t like to talk about. Especially freelance artists. But I think that in this new world where all the rules of how people earn a living have been thrown out the window, a little data can be very helpful. So because it may help a fellow independent artist, or someone who wants to make a living on the internet, I’ve done a little math homework, and am presenting my income from the last 5 years as a full-time artist, and typed up a breakdown of what I did right or wrong each year, and what I learned from it. 

The raw numbers: 
This is my net income, after PayPal fees and hiring other artists and such. 
2007 (Aug-Dec): $5761 2008: $18,628 2009: $7188 2010: $11,957 2011: $20,183 

Immediate takeaway: 
Man, that dude’s poor as crap, isn’t he? 
People always assume I’m rich because I travel a lot. But actually, I travel to places where I can live cheap. I would be destitute in the US, but in most places I travel, I live like a king! 

Source of income: 
Nearly all of my income comes from doing custom comics and illustrations through my site Cartoon Commune. I don’t have another day-job, so what you see is the entirety of my income. I have not yet tried to monetize my personal work, but rather given it away for Creative-Commons licensed online reading or download in order to build a readership for future projects. This year will hopefully be the year where the bulk of my income comes from personal projects. 

2007 
The number looks low, but that’s because I didn’t start until mid-August. (EDIT: Before August, I was working for Citibank, making $5000 a month to basically sit on my butt and watch movies in their Mumbai call center, but I gave that gig up to follow my dream of making my living from comics!) 
It was actually a very good year, since I started making a living right off the bat, mere hours after I launched my freelance site. The big coup though, was landing a regular gig illustrating a comic about poker. 
What I did right: I marketed my site not to my existing readers, but to anyone who might be looking for a comic. And to be honest, I don’t think any of my customers have ever been readers of my personal comics. And I made a flat rate, and a simple order form to make it as easy as possible for people to give me money. 
What I did wrong: I greatly undervalued my work. I was charging around 15 bucks per page in the beginning, with lots of discounts available. Which meant I had to work all day and night at far less than minimum wage just to have enough money to eat. 

2008 
This was a great year that SHOULD have been even better, were it not for a couple of deadbeat clients that stiffed me for $10,000 worth of work that they never paid for. But unfortunately, I was still grossly undercharging for my commissions and it meant I did nothing but draw commissions, and lost my entire readership for my personal work. I raised my prices a couple of times (to like, 50 bucks a page, I think?) to try and slow down commissions, but more kept coming in. It never occurred to me that that might mean I was undervaluing my work. The poker comic was still paying well, but toward the end, the boss-man stopped paying me, but kept getting free comics with lots of promises. This is the year that I began my very strict pay-up-front-no-matter-what policy. 
What I did right: I must have done a good time presenting myself and setting up the site, because I had a constant flow of customers without ever advertising the site. 
What I did wrong: Still not charging nearly enough, and delivering artwork before being paid. 

2009 
A bad year! Man, I was poor this year. The poker gig was over, so it was all on the Cartoon Commune. Thinking of ways to make more profit (and STILL not thinking to simply charge a decent rate) I decided to fix what wasn’t broken and start offering a wide variety of different things on the site, by different artists. Custom children’s books, music, animation, and lots more. Problem was, it was the simplicity of the site that had brought in customers, and now the site confused people. And I charged so little that the ‘cut’ I got from the work I farmed out to other artist ended up being only slightly more than the PayPal fees. Which meant I was making pennies on the new stuff, which was cannibalizing my business to begin with. 
What I did right: Not a lot. 
What I did wrong: Being a terrible business-man. 

2010 
Life was pretty awesome this year, because I was living in the jungle, playing with monkeys and swimming in the ocean on my private beach. But work-wise.... Burnout. I was so sick and tired of drawing my customers’ boyfriends as superheroes. I kept raising prices to slow down orders, and the orders kept coming. I started getting a good rate, but I ended up giving a lot of the commissions away to other people while I tried to raise money for more fun projects. I had two movie projects that failed apart because I was so sick of comics I was convinced I had to make a movie in order to tell creative stories again. But movies kind of require a lot more manpower and money than I had. I put no further effort into expanding or refining my business. 
What I did right: I focused on my awesome life instead of work. Truth is, I didn’t even realize how little I made and why until putting these numbers together. Because man, I lived like a king and was happy all the dang time. 
What I did wrong: Burning myself out on work that felt like a chore, to the point that I stopped loving one of the things I love most... making comics! 

2011 
Last year was a very good year. Not only did I make more than I’ve ever made as an artist, but I did it with minimal effort. Most of my energy this year was not on drawing my customers' boyfriends as superheroes, but on doing personal work! I finally started charging a decent rate for my commissions ($250 a page), so I was able to do one or two big jobs per month (the new rates attracted new customers like millionaire playboys, international rockstars and celebrity politicians) , farm out the ones I didn’t want while still getting a decent cut, and spend the rest of my time doing personal work. I finished my graphic novel Aki Alliance, compiled dozens of ebook collections of my work, rebuilt my site from the ground up, took 3 months off to film a season of my adventure show in South America, and I made new stuff for Google+ that earned me more than a quarter of a million followers. 
What I did right: Value my work, and more importantly, put time into work that I’m passionate about. 
What I did wrong: I think I did pretty great. I didn’t earn a lot, but my life was amazing so I think I did everything right. 

2012 
Man, I got ideas, and I got plans. Whether they work out or not, there will be a big changeup in the numbers next year. I’m focusing on telling my own stories again in a big way. I’m working behind the scenes on a lot of things that I’ll announce in due time. I’ll be excited to do one of these again in January 2013 and let you know how it went. 

Any questions? Ask them in the comments, or send me an email and I’ll be more than happy to answer.﻿

Meer lezen (133 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-qpNqXY7Oxmk/Tw4flQDhp1I/AAAAAAAAL2U/-de3nbcII30/w426-h327/chart.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7110-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/civil%20engineering%20jobs%20pennsylvania/photos/113415711878884584354/albums/5737581725122595473/5737581726615507362</link><title>Forest Resources Management Career &amp; Internship Opportunities 5/1/2012 

Listed below are a sample of career and internship opportunities found through online searches. Speak to your advisor on your desired career path. 

Get a Degree in Forest Resources Management at WVU 
http://forestresources.wvu.edu/ 

WVU Veterans http://wvuveterans.wvu.edu/ 

See Previous Career Opportunity Post http://goo.gl/7gpHm 

US Federal Jobs\- http://www.usajobs.gov/JobSearch/Search/AdvancedSearch 
Search Occupational Series Number 
0460 Forestry 
0462 Forestry Technician 
5042 Tree Trimming &amp; Removing (Urban Forestry) 
0401 General Natural Resources Mang &amp; Bio Sciences 
0499 Biological Science Student Trainee (Internship-SCEP) 

Forestry Technician (Timber Sale Administration) 
http://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/314703000 

Forester (Regional Fuels Specialist) 
http://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/311602500 

Forestry Technician (Timber Stand Improvement) 
http://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/314760900 
http://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/314762100 

Geographic Information Systems Specialist 
http://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/314792600 

Operations Forester 
http://www.forestryusa.com/j-landvest_april26_12.PDF 

Forester 
http://www.forestryusa.com/j-eastern_forest_consultants_april9_12.pdf 

Logging Management Forester Position 
http://www.forestryusa.com/j-lone_rock_timber_march23_12.pdf 

Forester Positions 
http://www.forestryusa.com/j-steigerwaldt_land_services_april30_12.pdf 

Senior Operations Forester 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=9948124 

Assistant Professor in Forest Hydrology and Watershed Management 
http://www.forestryusa.com/j-uminnesota_march15_12.pdf 

Assistant Extension Professor 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=9987639 

Forest Engineer 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=9979554 

Timberlands Planning Manager 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10099665 

PA SFI PROGRAM MANAGER 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10099779 

Forester 
http://jobview.monster.com/GetJob.aspx?JobID=109190085&amp;aid=104228377 

Forestry Technician 
http://www.berea.edu/peopleservices/jobs/20120405-staff-forestrytech.asp 

Urban Foresters 
http://jobview.monster.com/GetJob.aspx?JobID=108892491&amp;aid=104228377&amp;WT.mc_n=PSAHG10 

Postdoctoral Research Scientist, Environmental Sciences 
http://www.higheredjobs.com/details.cfm?JobCode=175624255 
http://www.higheredjobs.com/details.cfm?JobCode=175624253 

Work Planner / Utility Arborist 
http://jobview.monster.com/GetJob.aspx?JobID=108969072&amp;aid=104228377 

Arborist Salesperson, Wyckoff, NJ 
http://jobview.monster.com/GetJob.aspx?JobID=100510864&amp;aid=104228377 

Sales Arborist, Rockville MD 
http://jobview.monster.com/GetJob.aspx?JobID=98840378&amp;aid=104228377 

Plum Creek: http://www.plumcreek.com/Careers 
Silviculture Manager 315 
Resource Forester 326 
Resource Forester 317 
GIS and Forestry Inventory Seasonal Contractor 329 

Forestry/Natural Resources Advisor 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10011669 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10002915 

Research Assistantship 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10070405 

AmeriCorps Forester 
http://careercenter.eforester.org/c/job.cfm?site_id=8482&amp;job=10003022 

Career Opportunity Sites: 
Society of American Foresters http://careercenter.eforester.org 
National Association of State Foresters http://stateforesters.org/jobs.html 
National Association of University Forest Resources Programs (Faculty positions) http://www.naufrp.org/position.asp 
F&amp;W Forestry Consultants https://www.fwforestry.com/public/careers.aspx 
Weyerhaeuser http://www.weyerhaeuser.com/Company/Careers 
Bartlett Tree Experts http://www.bartlett.com/careers.cfm 
ACRT Inc http://www.acrtinc.com/hr_careers.php 
Davey Tree Experts http://www.davey.com/work/jobs.aspx?view=all 
POTLATCH http://www.potlatchcorp.com/careers.aspx 
SavATree Careers &amp; Internships http://www.savatree.com/careerslist.html 
ArborMetrics Solutions http://www.arbormetricssolutions.com/employment.htm 
Asplundh Tree Experts http://www.asplundh.com/careers.htm 
ECI Consulting http://www.eci-consulting.com/em.php 
Global Forest Information Service http://www.gfis.net/gfis/search/job+vacancies/ 
WV Division of Personnel http://www.state.wv.us/admin/personnel/jobs/default.htm 
Maryland DNR http://www.dnr.state.md.us/hr/jobs.asp 
Ohio DNR http://www.dnr.state.oh.us/default/tabid/11072/default.aspx 
Virginia State Employment Resource Center http://jobs.virginia.gov/ 
Pennsylvania Civil Service Commission http://www.portal.state.pa.us/portal/server.pt/community/jobseekers/11372 

#WVU #forest #forester #forestry #urban #arboriculture #utility #internships #employment #career #nature #natural #resources #GIS #SAF #US #jobs #outdoor #silviculture #greenjob #STEM #science #biology #hydrology #water#timber #wood #business #management #economics #dbh #WV #OH #DE #MD #PA #VA #NJ #NY #environment #veterans #GIbill﻿

Meer lezen (155 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7110_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-M6ChAyhBVH4/T5_8LmywkaI/AAAAAAAAA00/O3nEoDaGe4c/w426-h266/FRM%2Bsurveying.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>