<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:39:49" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/110050309840204703423/albums/5761569201828846481/5761569204986167074</link><title>Most graduate recruiters now looking for at least a 2:1 

More than 75% of companies require minimum of 2:1 degree, up from 52% in 2004, as scramble for graduate jobs intensifies 

More than three-quarters of graduate recruiters now use a 2:1 degree as their minimum entry requirement amid an intense scramble for graduate jobs, a poll of top employers has found. 

A total of 76% now use 2:1 as their threshold, up from 52% in 2004, in order to sift through a high volume of applications for each vacancy. According to the survey, 2.5% of recruiters demand a first. 

The survey of more than 200 firms, including Accenture, Deloitte, Marks &amp; Spencer and Rolls-Royce, conducted in May, found an average of 73 candidates chasing each vacancy, up from 30 applicants per job before the economic downturn. Retail is the most competitive sector, with more than 150 applicants for each position. 

Carl Gilleard, the chief executive of the Association of Graduate Recruiters (AGR), which commissioned the survey, said the use of the 2:1 as a filter was a response to increased competition. He said: "It's to do with the significant increase in the number of applications that businesses have been receiving. When you're recruiting 100 graduates – and multiply that by 70-odd applications per job – you've got a significant logistical challenge." 

Latest figures show 16% of all full-time undergraduates obtained a first in 2011, while 50% were awarded a 2:1, and 28% a 2:2. 

The average starting salary for graduates is predicted to rise to £26,500, according to the AGR poll. The number of vacancies is forecast to decline modestly by 0.6%. 

Gilleard said this was a sign of stability. "The graduate job market is inextricably linked to business confidence. It is encouraging to see that employers are still talent-planning for the future and that the number of graduate vacancies is remaining constant." 

A separate survey of the graduate job market, also published today, suggests there has been a small rise in the number of vacancies. The poll of 100 leading employers, conducted by High Fliers Research, indicates a 0.9% increase in vacancies. 

Although there remains a recruitment freeze at many government departments and agencies, graduate vacancies in the public sector are expected to increase by one-fifth this year – in part because of the expansion of the Teach First scheme to get graduates from top universities into schools, the High Fliers Research survey found. 

Among the employers surveyed in the poll, the average graduate starting salary is expected to remain unchanged for a third consecutive year at £29,000. The most generous salaries are those on offer from investment banks, an average of £45,000, and law firms, an average of £38,000. The public sector, at £22,200, and retailers, at £24,000, have the lowest graduate pay rates for 2012. 

Graduate recruitment at the leading employers remains below pre-recession levels, the survey found. The total number of graduate jobs on offer in 2012 across all the organisations featured in the research is still 11% below that recorded in 2007. 

Martin Birchall, managing director of High Fliers Research, said the class of 2012 faces stiff competition to secure a good graduate job this summer. 

He said: "Employers have already received an unprecedented number of applications for this year's graduate vacancies, and organisations in several of the most popular career sectors have now filled all their places for 2012 or have closed their applications early." 

Commenting on the AGR survey, Nicola Dandridge, chief executive of the vice chancellors' umbrella group, Universities UK, said: "There have been some very bleak headlines for graduates over recent years, so it is encouraging now to see real signs of recovery. Employers are investing in graduates, which is good news for them and for current students. 

"Average starting salaries for graduates are higher than predicted and we are seeing a return to stability in terms of the number of graduate vacancies. This follows three years of flat salaries and fewer graduate opportunities." 

By Jeevan Vasagar﻿

Meer lezen (81 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OU-cTnI1H7k/T_U0qnQHvyI/AAAAAAAAAl8/PI73KiUPTkA/w426-h256/a-young-woman-on-graduati-008.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/115848160366557252455/albums/5818155647527963169/5818155654392278210</link><title>PLACEMENTS!!!!! 

It's just their second year on the placement scene but the new Indian Institutes of Technology at Ropar, Patna, Hyderabad, Bhubaneswar and Gandhinagar, among others, are already nipping at the heels of their much-older and more established counterparts. 

Big-ticket recruiters like Microsoft, Amazon and Google have descended on these campuses and average salaries have shot up by 
15-20%. In comparison, the older IITs - Madras, Roorkee, Kharagpur, Bombay, Delhi and Guwahati - have recorded a 5-10% increase in salaries at the final placement offers. Also, more companies are visiting the newer IITs this year and pre-placement offers (PPOs) have increased. Top salaries have also gone up. IT services company Epic Systems, for example, offered $105,000 ( 57 lakh) to two students at IIT Ropar. It had offered $80,000 ( 43.6 lakh) last year. 

In IIT Ropar and IIT Patna, the number of PPOs this time have gone up to 10 and 3, respectively, from just a single PPO each last year. 

Also, IITs in Bhubaneswar, Gandhinagar, Patna and Ropar started their placements in as early as end-September to get an early-mover advantage. 

New recruiter BPCL's pay packages amounted to Rs 10 lakh in IIT Bhubaneswar and Flipkart offered packages between Rs 9 lakh and Rs 12 lakh in the new institutes. 

So far, students of IIT Ropar have got salary offers between Rs 11 lakh and Rs 16 lakh while those at Gandhinagar are getting between Rs 9.5 lakh and Rs 9.9 lakh. The average salary offer at IIT Ropar was Rs 8.32 lakh last year. 

Over the last two days, IIT Patna has seen 19 students of its 89-strong batch getting placement at an average package of Rs 11.3 lakh. Last year, average salary at the institute was Rs 7.1 lakh per annum, said Shashank Srivastava, student-in-charge, training &amp; placement cell at IIT Patna. "US and Japan-based companies are coming to visit us for placements which is likely to push the current year's average package even higher," he said. So far, the institute has seen a top domestic salary of Rs 16 lakh offered by Microsoft to six students. 

Microsoft has also offered packages of Rs 17 lakh to 7 students of IIT Jodhpur compared to the Rs 16 lakh offered to 2 students last year, said a student of the placement committee. Morgan Stanley, National Instruments, L&amp;T, Cisco are some of the 25 companies that have confirmed participation this season, an increase compared to last year's 21. The institute has received three pre-placement offers and is clocking in an average salary of Rs 5-6 lakh. 

Top recruiters varied across campuses. If it was Defense Research and Development Organisation (DRDO) making offers to 15 students at IIT Ropar, it was Zensar TechnologiesBSE 1.19 % with seven students at IIT Bhubaneswar, said TVS Sekhar, prof-in-charge of career development cell at IIT Bhubaneswar. Broadcom made the maximum number of 8 offers at IIT Hyderabad. 

IIT Hyderabad has also had Amazon, Google, Microsoft, Broadcom, Qualcomm among others for its 200-strong batch. Overall, 63 companies have confirmed visit and the institute expects 30-40 more confirmations later on. Works Applications made the highest offer of Rs 35 lakh for a Singapore posting, Google paid around Rs 16-18 lakh and Amazon paid Rs 12 lakh. Last year, the average salary was Rs 8.33 lakh. 

courtesy- The Times of India﻿

Meer lezen (65 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-j82p8ZcdjSA/UL49veP7bMI/AAAAAAAAByw/u3pqvubAXno/w426-h323/73055_302854559826879_1872654264_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/110050309840204703423/albums/5739024990799581361/5739024991592080706</link><title>Recruiting For Brunel University 

An INTRODUCTION TO BRUNEL UNIVERSITY An Introduction to Brunel University 

The Brunel International Scholarship Programme is an annual award run by the Brunel International office that is open to all international students. The 2012 Scholarships will offer 30 regional scholarships of £3000, as well as 8 scholarships of £2000 

Apply now to get a Scholarship 

Eligibility 

Undergraduate (Bachelor level) - Brunel University welcomes applications from students taking A Level examinations and the International Baccalaureate (IB) for direct entry into its undergraduate programmes. 

Students with ICSE or CBSE National Board Standard XII candidates will be expected to have attained an average of 75% and above. Students with Standard XII examinations from the State Boards of Gujarat, Tamil Nadu, Mahareshtra and Karnataka candidates will be expected to have attained an average of 75% and above. 

Foundation Programmes - If you do not meet the requirements for direct entry to our degree programme, we will assess your eligibility for a relevant foundation course where applicable. We offer foundation programmes in Engineering, IT, Business &amp; Management and Economics. 

Postgraduate (Masters Level) - Holders of a Bachelors (Honours) degree with good grades will be considered for entry to a Masters degree. For certain courses, work experience and/or specific academic background will be required. As a guideline, we require between 57% - 60% (or above) but exact requirements will depend on the course you are applying for. 

Fees for international students at Brunel are (11330-13860) 

Some basic features of Brunel University and the City of London 
Brunel is a campus-based university situated in Uxbridge, West London, with the River Pinn running through it and is home to nearly 15,000 students from over 100 countries worldwide. 

Why Brunel ? 

1\. The Brunel Business School is ranked in Top 20 Best Business Schools in UK according to the Financial Times 
2\. The Brunel Business School is ranked in Top 75 European Business Schools according to the Financial Times 
3\. The Brunel MBA is one of a distinguished group of MBA programmes worldwide to have achieved accreditation by The Association of MBAs (AMBA), the leading MBA accreditation body 
4\. Brunel University is ranked in the Top 5 in London for student satisfaction 
5\. Brunel University has been awarded one of the most prestigious awards – the Queen's Anniversary Prize for Further and Higher Education for its groundbreaking research 
6\. It is a member of the Association of Commonwealth Universities, the European University Association and Universities UK. 
Brunel collects Queen's Anniversary Prize at Buckingham Palace (Friday 2 March, 2012) 

Brunel University has collected the Queen's Anniversary Prize for Further and Higher Education at a ceremony at Buckingham Palace, in recognition of the Institute for the Environment's groundbreaking research into the effects of hormone disrupting chemicals. 

A Research Intensive University - The 2008 Research Assessment Exercise (RAE) judged 82% of our research to be of international standing, leading to 54.5% increase in our research funding from the Higher Education Funding Council, compared to the sector average increase of 7.8%. 

Experimental Techniques Centre (ETC) – ETC Brunel is a highly regarded consultancy and research Centre for engineering, forensic and environmental investigations, including expert witness statements for legal purposes. UKAS accreditation has been obtained for many of the services offered. 

Brunel graduates enjoy the 13th highest starting salaries in the UK, according to the recent Sunday Times Good University Guide. Their average salary of £22,323 is almost £3,000 more than the national average. 

STUDY IN U.K 
Study 1 year Masters in U.K in Engg , Business , Science and Arts with 1Year INTERNSHIP. 
Affordable Fees and Scholarships Available . Admissions available for April , May , July, and September 2012 . Scholarships Served on first come first basis . For BEST And FREE Counseling Contact : SHUSHANT 9768114144 or LOG on to www.onesourceoverseas.com 
If u LIKE our POST thn plz LIKE our PAGE ONE SOURCE OVERSEAS click on http://www.facebook.com/onesourceoverseas﻿

Meer lezen (95 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-W4FTNXyLU7c/T6Uc0rzvZUI/AAAAAAAAAP8/yBelB3z1ZHQ/w426-h315/brunel.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/100595757890924839731/albums/5837054505967305505/5837054507677113026?authkey=CPmHtubN4Ir9eA</link><title>What is More Important for Recent Grads: Salary or Benefits 
by Emily Driscoll 

For today’s graduates on the job hunt, the amount of numbers on a paycheck is becoming more important than benefits such as medical insurance and retirement plans when deciding to take a job offer. 
Earning an adequate salary to make ends meet should always take priority, but experts caution against overlooking the offerings in a benefits package. 
According to a new study by the National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE), annual salary increases are the most preferred benefit among job-seeking new college graduates.  Historically, graduating seniors taking part in NACE’s annual student survey have placed medical insurance at the top of their needs’ list. 
“We’ve basically asked the same question since 2007 and far and away, employer paid medical insurance was the number one benefit that they were seeking,” says Edwin Koc, director of strategic and foundation research at NACE. “[Now] they want to be assured that their starting salary is not going to be what they have for the next five years, but that they can actually move up a little bit.” 
Experts cite the stipulation in the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act (PPACA) that allows children to stay on their parent’s insurance coverage until age 26 as the reason for the shift. 
“Additionally, many of the recent college graduates may have short-term thinking when it comes to health care and other benefit coverage, meaning that they think they will remain healthy and won’t really use health insurance, making it less important to them than making more money,” says Tracy McCarthy, chief human resource officer at SilkRoad. 
After witnessing years of a recovering economy and tough job market, recent grads are more aware of the importance of financial responsibility, says Dan Black, director of campus recruiting at Ernst &amp; Young LLP. 
“They are very realistic about wanting to build up savings to be able to weather any potential future economic downturns because they’ve frankly had front row seats to this really soft economy and slow turn around,” he says. “They’re being very wise to think about salary as a key consideration in employment.” 
While some benefits may carry greater significance than others, it’s important for recent grads to fully understand the details of their benefits package. Here are examples of questions the experts recommend grads ask about four major benefits. 
Health Insurance Plans 
When evaluating health-care plans, experts strongly suggest asking specific details regarding plans such as monthly premium and deductible amounts, restrictions and limitations of the plans, and the exact date coverage begins. 
“Health insurance options typically have out-of-pocket cost, waiting periods and limitations and exclusions that you need to be aware of in order to fully understand your potential out-of-pocket exposure and risk,” says Nancy Thompson, senior vice president at CBIZ Benefits &amp; Insurance Services. 
“Unfortunately, many people do not even know they have limitations on their policy until they need to use their insurance for an illness or injury.” 
Retirement Plan Options 
To get a jump start on planning for retirement, grads should find out what kind of investment vehicle is offered through the company (such as a 401(k) or IRA), when they are able to start contributing and if there is an employer match and at what amount. 
“A salary deferral plan will allow graduates to enjoy a tax break, have ‘free money’ available through an employer matching, and the convenience of payroll deductions ‘out of sight, out of mind,’” says Thompson. 
Although they are not offered as much anymore, grads can also ask about the availability of pension plans in addition to a defined employer contribution plan, says Koc. 
Vacation Time/Time Off 
Because vacation and sick leave are not mandated benefits, employers’ terms vary. 
Thompson says graduates should understand when they are eligible for time off, what is the accrual criteria (daily, weekly basis), when earned and unused vacation time is paid, if vacation and sick leave is combined, if unused paid time off is paid, if sick and vacation time is accrued during holidays, and what documents are required for leave. 
“By understanding the answers to these questions, grads will avoid any unauthorized absences by following the proper procedure for request and appropriate documentation necessary to validate the leave,” Thompson says. “In addition, it is important to understand how these benefits tie into unpaid leave situations and the federal Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA).” 
Tuition Reimbursement Options 
Particularly for grads planning to return to school to update their skills or earn a higher degree, it’s especially important to inquire about any tuition reimbursement options available and the company’s conditions before enrolling in a program, says Koc. 
“If they do contribute to it, is it somehow tied to actually achieving the degree? Are there grade requirements associated with the funding? Sometimes employers require you to at least retain a B in your coursework,” he says. 
If a company doesn’t offer a certain benefit right off the bat, grads should not be afraid to ask if it might be considered for the future, says McCarthy. 
“I appreciate when employees ask this and I take it as an opportunity to help less seasoned employee’s understand business financial concepts and how benefits play into the equation,” she says. “Most employees expect and appreciate transparency.”﻿

Meer lezen (97 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-CwayWWBGv2o/UQFiJhCv2sI/AAAAAAAAAfU/TJBBgOvM05I/w426-h239/financial-planning.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/104729617658774282020/albums/5753174912288859345/5753174910983917250</link><title>Our Client Managers hear that question a lot as they spend their days on the phone with physicians looking for opportunities and clients looking for physicians. On both sides of the conversation is the issue of salary. To provide our client managers with the best information we continually collect data and do research. The concept of worth differs greatly depending upon the region and the participant in the conversation. I spoke to an in house recruiter in Chicago a few months ago who insisted he could hire an Internal Medicine physician for less than $150,000 per year. I was amazed. I spoke with a Pennsylvania clinic looking for a Family Practice physician who told me, “Oh, we are very competitive in our market, we are offering around $135,000.” Unfortunately, the more frequent question is, “What is the average salary for____?” 

Industry wide the gold standard for compensation data is the MGMA. Annually, they compile the most accurate and largest sample of data to produce a 325+ page book with the data compiled in every conceivable configuration. We review the information from the MGMA every year to make sure that we have the latest compensation data. How much you pay will vary by region of the country and by location. Also, practice setting, hospital, independent clinic, or a health center, as well as, employed, income guarantee, or RVU’s will all play a vital role in total compensation. The benefits, loan repayment and malpractice insurance all make up the total compensation package. All that being said, the chart below will report MGMA median compensation as reported in the 2011 report for Primary Care. The Inline Group specializes in matching Primary Care physicians with opportunities. Let us know if we can help you. 

All numbers are based off of median for the Primary Care specialties from the Physician Compensation and Production Survey: MGMA 2011 Report 

http://www.theinlinegroup.com/blog/post.cfm/so-what-exactly-am-i-worth ﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wplqKFOPsSA/T9diGZPizsI/AAAAAAAAADc/MuxNwUZ7XEE/w426-h239/Primarycare%2BWheel.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/110107953824427730254/albums/5952695483979687377/5952695487973846306</link><title>HOW ACADEMIA RESEMBLES A DRUG GANG 

The income distribution within gangs is extremely skewed in favor of those at the top, while the street sellers earn less than employees in legitimate low-skilled activities. 

DRUG DEALERS LIVE WITH THEIR MOMS 

If you take into account the risk of being shot by rival gangs, ending up in jail or being beaten up by your own hierarchy, you might wonder why anybody would work for such a low wage. 

Yet, gangs have no real difficulty in recruiting new members. The reason for this is that the prospect of future wealth. 

Rank-and file members are ready to face this risk to try to make it to the top, where life is good and money is flowing. 

ACADEMIA AS A DUAL LABOUR MARKET 

The academic job market is structured in many respects like a drug gang, with an expanding mass of outsiders and a shrinking core  of insiders. 

Dualisation is the strengthening of this divide between insiders in secure, stable employment and outsiders in fixed-term, precarious employment. 

HOW CAN WE EXPLAIN THIS TREND? 

One of the factors has been the massive expansion in the number of PhDs all across the OECD. 

The number of PhDs increased by about 60% in 11 years (2000 - 2011), especially in Portugal and Greece, where it nearly tripled. Increase was 60% in the UK, or nearly 40% in Germany. Since 2000 the number of OECD-area doctorates has increased at an average of 5% a year. 

OUTSIDERS 

So what you have is an increasing number of PhD graduates arriving every year into the market hoping to secure a permanent position as a professor and enjoying freedom and high salaries, a bit like the rank-and-file drug dealer. 

To achieve that, they are ready to forgo the income and security that they could have in other areas of employment by accepting insecure working conditions in the hope of securing jobs that are not expanding at the same rate. 

Because of the increasing inflow of potential outsiders ready to accept this kind of working conditions, this allows insiders to outsource a number of their tasks onto them, especially teaching, in a  context where there are increasing pressures for research and publishing. The result is that the core is shrinking, the periphery is expanding. 

VARIETIES OF DUALISATION 

The boundary of the insider and outsider group varies across countries. 

United States. More than 40% of teaching staff at universities are now part-time faculty without tenure, or adjunct lecturers paid per course given, with no health insurance or the kind of other things associated with a standard employment relationship. 

The Chronicle of Higher Education recently reported about adjunct lecturers relying on food stamps. The person mentioned in the article declares a take-home pay of 900$ per month. 

Germany. On the one hand, there are relatively good conditions at the bottom at the PhD level because of massive investments in research programs. On the other hand, there are good jobs at the top, where full professors are comparatively well paid and have a great deal of autonomy. 

Problem: there is nothing for people who just received their PhD. They can hope to get their first permanent job in their mid-40s, while this could happen ion their mid-30s in the 1970s. 

United Kingdom. Britain is the biggest academic market in Europe and lectureships provide secure employment for relatively young academics even if the starting salary is relatively low. 

A large proportion of PhD students in the UK do not have regular sources of funding, need to apply here and there to get scholarships, and when they teach they are paid per hour taught or a piece rate that can vary. 

The number of hours usually taught at UK universities is relatively moderate. 

SUMMARY 

 This form of insider/outsider divide exists everywhere and is probably expanding.  The system simply couldn’t work without this large supply of outsiders ready to accept any kind of employment contract. 

One more thing: avoid UK for your PhD and avoid Germany after your PhD. 

                     *                                *                               * 

http://tinyurl.com/oymedbf 

#academia  ﻿

Meer lezen (106 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-aYMtGSgqeX0/Upw5AfDAbSI/AAAAAAAAzEw/1V8o9yrbEf8/w426-h270/Screenshot_31.bmp</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/108910247718834175384/albums/6004791644128585169/6004791647847869394</link><title>"Top 20 countries for oil and gas salaries." 
The global average salary for oil and gas workers fell slightly in 2013 after two years of rapid growth, according to a report from recruiting firm Hays. 
See which nations offered the highest pay to workers from overseas, in this survey report http://bit.ly/1mwgBsr﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-izfSYbcwQnc/U1VOMGA0a9I/AAAAAAAAGuk/tAGa27FfWHo/w426-h335/100-different.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/117339876408829965195/albums/5867873967346351409/5867873966187127474?authkey=CN2D6Krtk-zFHQ&amp;sqi=110880245983090664592&amp;sqsi=72db51d7-3906-4339-a11f-c5f07be1cb61</link><title>A recruiter sent me this marketing email which linked me to this "infographic."  I think it's a misinfographic - or graphics for the sake of graphics.  If you look at this graphic you would think that Corporate Accounting is the place to be for 'starting salaries.'   But the arrows mislead you.  They're saying that you would rather be in Public Accounting or Financial Services.  Is the entire population of Accounting and Finance only people in Corp Accounting, Public Accounting, and Financial Services?  This is important to know because you want to know if 2.2% is the average increase for all sectors, or just a simple average of the 2.0, 2.3 and 2.3 on the chart. 

Not to mention can you really accept a starting salary and be an in-demand specialist at the same time... 

If you're a manager, please don't use this to make decisions as important as how much you pay somebody. 

I guess I'm not a fan of infographic without a speaker standing beside it explaining it. ﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-xMeu6_AsEjM/UW7gSG1YorI/AAAAAAAAAm4/F45SSN8CBKU/w426-h395/Badinfographics.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/114133040010713743095/albums/5883915503844733905/5883915505348251794?authkey=CNHZusWe8J_3Lw</link><title>There seems to be a large number of folks out there who think that money is my only motivation for doing what I do. I find this rather amusing because if money was a driving factor for me then I’d be doing something very different indeed. 

Today I will talk about how I currently make money, why its not a motivating factor for me - and then cover some of the factors that do motivate me. 

If all I wanted was money, it would be a much much wiser decision for me to not leave corporate life and remain as a salaryman at either Amazon as Website Manager or Microsoft as Product Manager where I was earning about 30,000,000 yen per year (300,000 USD at today's rate). 
Compared to back then, my company now pays me 1,200,000 yen (12,000 USD) per year - less than what I pay my employees ^o^ 

Also, at the same time that Amazon gave me the job offer, I got an offer from eBay too. My recruiters got them both in a bidding war - the more they paid, the more the recruiter gets which is about 30% of my annual salary. eBay ended up offering much more but I chose Amazon. I felt I was more familiar with e-commerce rather than auctions - it was not the money that counted. 

If you are interested, you can read what life was like at Amazon and Microsoft in this post. 

The rest of this post can be read here &gt;&gt;&gt; http://buff.ly/11d6lJM﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-64H9GBJNgnM/Uafd-lCyEJI/AAAAAAABmy0/leY1S2ATN14/w426-h320/8887872454_b9d8b79b9e_b.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7111-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/what%20is%20the%20starting%20salary%20for%20a%20recruiter/photos/107823081868634858068/albums/5859525213453612625/5859525210091774002</link><title>Placements 2013: Median salary up by 9% at IIFT 
http://www.mbauniverse.com/article/id/6807/ 

In the final placements at IIFT Delhi, 74 recruiters visited the campus including Google, CRISIL, Citibank, Goldman Sachs, ITC, etc.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7111_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-8PaGnvTqk0c/UVE3Iiv3YDI/AAAAAAAABHk/Hog-MrSTJUM/w426-h237/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>