<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:49:12" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/106073502505833617615/albums/5706291751082055361/5706291753649880386</link><title>Oh When The Saint's.... 

So, I drove 6 hours, I worked for another 6 when I got here, and now I'm finally getting on to the computer to start getting my work in for the day. I'm back in the Big Easy, Home to Who Dat Nation for the next few days, and please believe one of those days will be spent reviewing the worlds most famous beignet's at Cafe Du Monde!! 

As for yesterday, it was a good game, and congratulations to Giant's fans everywhere... really the only people who can ever say they had Tom Brady and the Patriot's number. Eli may have just become a hall-of-famer, if you can believe that. Enjoy being the Champs New York, you definitely earned it in another great game! 

Oh, and did anyone see that M&amp;M's commercial?? Lol. That dance looked familiar! ;) 

So, I figured I would post me wearing Giant's Blue (or close enough to it) in honor of the occasion! 

Love you guys, but your girl has to get some sleep before my shoot tomorrow morning...﻿

Meer lezen (18 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-EsQeWha6MZA/TzDSHeEKvUI/AAAAAAABix4/W3R9A3Kfw2w/w426-h639/IMG_6762x.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/103493459351957813291/albums/5801753767837794289/5837801907270902866?authkey=CJuM75Xfk6e8VA</link><title>When it gets tough, remember this.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-zyF32OKhaUM/UQQJ55f65FI/AAAAAAAA_Kg/T2DOV5iHx-Q/w426-h239/Quote+-+Remember+that+guy.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/107383157816966336384/albums/5896561436710501457/5896561441610933954</link><title>The Illusion of Choice 
#infographic  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-M_ItI1LW0_8/UdTLY8t8JsI/AAAAAAAC_LM/VZdjUBBynnY/w426-h268/The%2BIllusion%2Bof%2BChoice.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/111285156314431541418/albums/5922930131769199617/5922930134993255890?authkey=CKXnyOby9qT2Jg</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_04_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ifufYvTWhmE/UjJ5k6W6vdI/AAAAAAACnIc/hkA7dDZJIMA/w426-h237/tumblr_msb9865FE81qhtknmo1_500.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/107982618909749811163/albums/5706106802785681201/5706106802117411186</link><title>*While watching the Super Bowl Last Night...* 

It was a fun game, I was here in the states watching it even though I'm Canadian... You Americans do like your football.... But I realized as the Giants are parading around collecting their speeches and trophies how many times the word " WORLD CHAMPIONS " were used. 

Umm... Last I checked only Americans play in the NFL... where's this world coming from? ;) 

*Update* I am shocked at how 150 people were able to comment on this and have a decent discussion, but as soon as it made What's hot people felt the need to start insulting other countries, other people commenting and make Extreme hate filled threats and remarks. Most things have been said in the comments already. Any hate speech will result in an immediately block.Behave.﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-XecRVE0b2cE/TzAp536mAXI/AAAAAAAAjjQ/gyY3NYrFCZs/w426-h273/worldamerica.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/114809488257853535663/albums/5659781463225459697/5659781469232776754</link><title>We are still the best in the game. New MUSIC tonight #SK StreetKing #9﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-KtMYJeEBVBU/TouVQmv1RjI/AAAAAAAABs8/fdAjVWodtn0/w426-h568/x2_89bd6fd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/108867109291590211266/albums/5988901798538166225/5988901801808013314?sqi=111905254708856017066&amp;sqsi=87521571-47e4-49e9-802b-1afa1d0faa1b</link><title>Finished My sketchy &lt;3 

It's NW as Satsuki from Kill la Kill 

Not sure if I should turn this into a full blown drawing or not o-o﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_08_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zaWF7gADCUI/UxzadUt2qAI/AAAAAAAAIos/a79ShMqcGZI/w426-h243/NW%2Bsatsuki.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/107430637753481876221/albums/5926161624633701297/5926161620841487298</link><title>Well hello there new trusty iPhone! ;)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-FfK20yQHgrU/Uj30mJPPW8I/AAAAAAAAXC0/3ZeajuUWq8E/w426-h577/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/106073502505833617615/albums/5705790175138914465/5705790175041826818</link><title>SUPERBOWL + FOOTBALL TALK 

So here we are. The final game of the football year. The biggest sporting event in America, and this one may be more hyped then any of the last three superbowls. 

Superbowl 42 was a classic. It gave us one of the single greatest catches in NFL history, it had an amazing finish, and was simply put, "David beating Goliath" The Giant's defeated the previously undefeated Patriots. Eli Manning walked off the hero, and Tom Brady walked off dejected. The dynasty was over. New England, who had made 3 superbowls in the previous 6 years, wouldn't make it again for the next three. The Giant's would go on to be a tough team to beat, but they wouldn't make it back either.... 

Superbowl 46: 4 years have passed since David Tyree's helmet out wrestled Rodney Harrison. Neither team has been back since the greatest upset in superbowl history. The Giant's come in as the hottest team in the league. They struggled, losing much more then they won to end the season... but just like everything else in NYC, it's a different story when the bright lights are on, and the stakes are raised. They made the playoffs by the skin of their teeth, but that was enough for this talented team to turn it up a notch. Behind the talents of Jason Pierre-Paul, Osi-Umen-whatever, and the rest of that extremely talented D-line, they defeated the favorite Packers, and they vanquished the best Defense in the league the week after they beat the best offense. I don't know a better resume than that. Eli comes in having the best year of his career, and the Giant's finally have a solid recieving corps to help him. They are a complete team, and playing like it these days... 

But across the field is the 3 time superbowl champions. The team of the decade. A future Hall of Fame Coach, Hall of Fame QB, and a team that defines the phrase "team first". They began the team introduction in the superbowl even. They are playing for the memory of the owners wife, and they have been almost untouchable most of the season. Tom Brady is playing lights out, Wes Welker set records, Rob gronkowski set records, and the two TE defense owned the G-men earlier in the season, even though Eli was the better QB that day... 

Interestingly awesome stat: In the past ten years, Tom Brady, Ben roethlisberger, or a Manning has played in 9/10 superbowls, and won 6... this will make it 10/11, with 7 wins between the 4 QBs... 

Prediction: I'll keep my prediction simple. A picture is worth a thousand words, and I found this one earlier today... Revenge is best served cold. 

NOW WHO'S WATCHING FOOTBALL WITH ME!?!?﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AKcTz1TdLpU/Ty8J7wJIMAI/AAAAAAABh70/-0QNBjWrZxo/w426-h694/426074_10151227185635144_391260230143_22384630_1600143668_n.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7121-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20is%20the%20man%20in%20the%20m%26m%20commercial/photos/113493854651753327245/albums/5810756137855356721/5810756140213599810</link><title>Due to a typo, an ad for the fourth-generation iPad claims the tablet is 0.37 millimeters thin. 

0.37 millimeters is about the same thickness as the lead in a mechanical pencil or 4 human hairs. 

We know Apple likes to tout the thinness of their devices, but they aren't that thin.  ;-) 

Read more: http://on.mash.to/XFOtGD﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7121_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-s6upvdPJOOk/UKPz7D3Z_kI/AAAAAAAAbBo/_tq9ntX5WZ8/w426-h266/ipad-thin.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>