<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:22:51" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/110255249160193387667/albums/5777996103227300945/5777996100441135106</link><title>\----------------------------   Hurricane Safe Destinations   ------------------------------ 

Hurricane-Safe Travel Destinations 
Hurricane season is upon us and anyone who has scheduled a late-summer vacation in the Southeast over the past few years knows how a hurricane can wreck havoc with your vacation plans, regardless of where you’re traveling. For 2010, we have complied a list of hurricane-safe destinations for you and your family to enjoy. Whiles most of these destinations are not a sure things, they have been among the safest of the past several years. Don't let the hurricane season spoil your travel plans this year! 
Hurricane-Safe Destinations ~ Pick Your Travel Destination Well 
OUR RECOMMENDED DESTINATIONS &amp; VACATION EXPERIENCES 
GO ON A CRUISE: 
The good thing about cruises is that they can usually sail around the worst of a storm. And today's ships are extraordinarily safe and with the advanced weather tracking available today, bad weather is something they can avoid. The downside is that the cruise line always reserves the right to reschedule port calls and change itineraries for weather-related reasons and therefore you may not get to visit the places you had hoped to. 
The big advantage of sailing during hurricane season is that prices tend to drop to their lowest point of the year.  Your best deals are during the fall months -- late August to mid December, so it's an attractive time to buy a cruise. And the reality is that statistically speaking the chances that your particular voyage is going to be affected by a hurricane are very slim. But it does happen, from time to time. The thing to bear in mind is that it is a possibility and to approach the cruise with the right attitude. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

POPULAR CRUISE DESTINATIONS: 
Caribbean 
Mexico 
Europe 
United States 
Australia and the South Pacific 
Africa, Asia, South America &amp; Indian Ocean Islands 
THE CARIBBEAN: 
When planning a trip to the Caribbean during hurricane season, it is good to know . 
that hurricanes are less likely the further south you go. The islands of Aruba, Bonaire, Curacao, Trinidad and Tobago, Barbados and St. Vincent, including the islands below them, are the least hit by hurricanes. However, as Grenada discovered in 2004 with Hurricane Ivan, never say never and keep in mind that hurricanes are unpredictable. If you still prefer to travel to the usual destinations, we recommend look for hotels and resorts that offers hurricane guarantees or something similar 
Antigua 
Antigua's secluded white beaches - among the most pristine in all the Caribbean - provide the ideal setting for a tropical paradise. The azure seas surrounding all sides of the island beckon you to the beaches, all 365 of them. 
Aruba 
Hurricane-free year round, the beaches and hotels of Aruba welcome those who travel for romance. 
Barbados 
Barbados offers all the things a Caribbean vacationer needs in a tropical paradise - coral shore beaches, crystal clear waters, a climate that's sure to delight, and for water sports enthusiasts, a dream come true. 
Bonaire 
Included in the "ABC" islands, along with Aruba and Curacao, Bonaire is a small island located in the southern Caribbean known for its pioneering role in the preservation of nature, in particular the preservation of the marine environment, and for its excellent scuba diving, snorkeling, and windsurfing, among other things. 
Curacao 
On Curacao, there's never a shortage of exciting things to do - with sailing or fishing, kayaking or windsurfing, shopping or dining, the options feel practically endless. 
Nevis 
Intoxicating natural beauty, sunny skies, warm waters, and sparsely peopled beaches combine in the sister islands of St Kitts &amp; Nevis to make them one of the most seductive spots in the Caribbean. 
St Kitts 
An uncrowded, unspoiled respite in the Caribbean, St. Kitts offers its natural beauty like a welcome mat for first-time and returning visitors alike. The island boasts pristine and gleaming shores surrounded by sparkling cobalt waters, plus many other facets to this impressive jewel of an island. 
St Lucia 
Rich in cultural history and natural beauty, the island nation of St Lucia offers a touch of everything you want in a Caribbean vacation. An unspoiled, tropical gem nestled in a chain of islands known as the Lesser Antilles, St Lucia traces its colorful history to long before colonial times, yet it has a legacy of over 400 years of European influence. 
St Maarten/St Martin 
Like well-suited counterparts, this striking dreamland offers two very distinct ad equally fabulous destinations on one island. The Dutch St. Maarten is a bustling haven, where surfers and divers head towards electrifying nightlife when the sun sets.     The French St. Martin provides a more low-key ambiance, where serene bays set the tone for relaxing feasts and peaceful strolls along moonlit shores. 
Trinidad &amp; Tobago 
Trinidad &amp; Tobago - two islands, one country. Two vacations in one - could you ask for a better deal? Lying just off the South American coast, this is the most culturally diverse of its peers, with a landscape and natural history as rich and varied as the rainbow faces of its many distinct heritages. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

MEXICO - (Central &amp; West Coast): 
Enjoy a Mexican beach getaway to fabulous resorts in Acapulco, Los Cabos, Mazatlan, and Puerto Vallarta. Experience great beaches and visit ancient cultures. Lounge on the beach and enjoy the pulsating Mexican nightlife. If you still prefer to travel to the usual destinations, we recommend look for hotels and resorts that offers hurricane guarantees or something similar. 
Acapulco 
The gorgeous beaches, romantic sunsets, and glamorous nightlife that attracted Hollywood's hottest celebrities in the 1950s are still very much a part of Acapulco today. This "Queen of Mexican Beach Resorts" is set around a crescent-shaped bay and framed by verdant mountains that plunge into warm, sapphire waters. 
Ixtapa/Zihuatanejo 
On the Gold Coast, the dynamic resort center of Ixtapa and the quaint fishing pueblo of Zihuatanejo are contrasting twins. One is bold, beautiful and full of action, and the other is a quiet wallflower, living a simple life on the outer edge of her sister's spotlight. Ixtapa is the most modern resort on Mexico's west coast, with half of its land protected as an ecological reserve. 
Mazatlan 
While other beach resorts in Mexico work hard to dazzle visitors with mega-resort excitement, the equation for a great vacation in Mazatlan is a simple one of fun, plus food, plus lots of world-class fishing. Mexico's largest West Coast port and the second largest coastal city combines affordable accommodations with seaside charm and plenty of ways to have fun in the sun. 
Mexico City Mexico City's historic center is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Aztec ruins, the continent's largest cathedral, and historic architecture make Mexico City an interesting place to visit. Mexico City is also a dangerous place to visit and security should be a major concern of anyone who visits the Mexican capital. 
Puerto Vallarta 
Spectacular beaches, great tanning weather and a fun city combine to make Puerto Vallarta an attractive destination. Its Bay of Banderas is the place to be, but touring the nearby jungles on horseback is also an attractive option. In addition, Puerto Vallarta is an area of Mexico that has attracted many talented artists and is known as one of the country's centers for the fine arts. 
Los Cabos 
To many travelers, Cabo has become the "place to be" in Mexico. Good beaches, great shoreline, golf, fishing, and wild nightlife combine to make the Cabo area an attractive destination for a variety of travelers. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
CENTRAL AMERICA: 

Enjoy a different kind of vacation experience...Central American style! Lounge on the beach, visit ancient archeological ruins and enjoy the pulsating island nightlife. Adventurous travelers will want to participate in one of the fabulous Eco-tours offered. 
Liberia, Costa Rica - (Costa Rica's western region)Liberia is the capital of the Guanacaste province and is fast becoming the new gateway to the sunny Guanacaste beaches. Over the past couple of years it has become more and more popular with tourists, just recently a new international airport in Liberia has opened up and many American airline carriers are now flying into Liberia. Liberia is very close to popular Tamarindo and its surrounding beaches and it is also becoming the preferred city to fly into if you are going to the new resorts in the Papagayo Gulf, only 30-40 minutes away. It is also very close to some popular and beautiful national parks. Parque Nacional Santa Rosa, Parque Nacional Rincon de la Vieja and Parque Nacional Guanasate are just to the north and are worth visiting. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
UNITED STATES: 

California 
Enjoy a Los Angeles getaway and include multi-day Disneyland® Resort Park Hopper® Bonus Tickets, or Universal Studios® Hollywood. Thrill to Pirates of the Caribbean at Disneyland® Park plus other exciting theme park attractions and entertainment. Or travel to San Francisco and experience the Golden Gate Bridge, Fisherman's Wharf and Chinatown.  Also See: 
Anaheim 
Los Angeles 
San Diego 
San Francisco 
Hawaii 
Hawaii is enchanting. Its beauty will stun you. Its floral scents will surround you. Its culture will fascinate you. Its legends will intrigue you. Its world-class resorts will pamper you, and you'll be treated as honored guests, as the "Spirit of Aloha" embraces you.  There are several Hawaii vacation packages, and hotels to choose from.  Day or night, flexible vacations options are available. 
Las Vegas 
Everywhere you look, from the Las Vegas Strip to the dazzling Freemont Street Experience, there's an incredible variety of things to see and do. Take a roller coaster ride around Manhattan skyscrapers.  Trek through space at warp speed. Visit the world's tallest Coke bottle, or the tallest observation tower in the United States. Take a chance with Lady Luck. Dine from buffet to gourmet. Swing into championship golf. Or relax beside a refreshing pool. These are just some of the many incredible experiences waiting for you in this remarkable desert playground.   Las Vegas is one of our top 5 hurricane-safe travel destinations. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
EUROPE:http://cmtravelonline.com/popular-destinations/go-europe 
Explore Italy, Ireland and the rest of Europe. Experience one of our European vacations our European tours. From our independent travel packages to European escorted tours, we feature only the best companies offering European travel and vacation packages.   The dream of European travel is easily turned into reality with our broad range of vacation packages across a continent of distinctive cultures. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
AUSTRALIA &amp; SOUTH PACIFIC: 
We invite you to experience the splendid diversity of Australia and South Pacific; from breathtaking beauty of the Great Barrier Reef to the vastness of the rugged Outback,  to the beautiful islands of Tahiti, Fiji, Samoa, and Cook Islands - the most romantic destinations in the world. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
AFRICA, ASIA, SOUTH AMERICA &amp; INDIAN OCEAN ISLANDS: 

Please visit Elite Travel Consulting.com or Dream Excursions.com for exceptional vacation experiences to these fine destinations. Your Elite Travel Consultant can customize virtually any itinerary to fit your specific needs. 
Destination information courtesy of Funjet Vacations, and Travel Impressions, our preferred vacation suppliers.﻿

Meer lezen (232 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-JBLozArcG0w/UC-Q1xhi2AI/AAAAAAAAAMc/t9n-_7p9X3o/w426-h237/hurricanesafe.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/111410703357000754962/albums/5846356166103663601/5846356167783000882?authkey=CMn7s9SBg9fpuAE</link><title>Longtime Lakers owner, Dr. Jerry Buss, passed away today at 5:55 am after a long illness. He was 80 years old. 

MORE: http://on.nba.com/133LohG 

Leave your condolences and favorite Dr. Buss memories in the comments below. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-b2Kk4XDLi9o/USJt9ZMeqzI/AAAAAAAARWQ/NBq6pI0fD1Q/w426-h240/buss_topstory.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/100193529331792590881/albums/5846854384468724401/5846854389059678818?authkey=CLy7xOvvm6enrgE</link><title>I am terribly excited about this purchase that I made today. 

Any vanity license plate ideas?   All I've got is THEOATWHEELS and that's stupid and too long. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_03_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-4700_5UXTGU/USQzFsFV8mI/AAAAAAAAa44/vrxFd83lWYo/w426-h350/Screen%2BShot%2B2013-02-19%2Bat%2B2.10.57%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/106332317776981377887/albums/5938929000810198481/5970971204212883490?sqi=112801523437501412730&amp;sqsi=561b4d4f-ce66-484c-be66-a62f15818802</link><title>Border between Mexico and United States 
Frontera entre México y Estados Unidos 
 メキシコ = アメリカ国境 
(2005) 
Blog: http://pillandia.blogspot.it/2009/02/blog-post_8974.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-lcaqP9t_EwE/Ut0mrLcyACI/AAAAAAAAOUU/Vr0UyKilPC4/w426-h284/CONFINE%2BMessico-Usa%25283%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/100355451043993388771/albums/5976688231980376609/5976688231117619346</link><title>Impressive storm system over the Central U.S. producing a wide variety of inclement weather, including ice and snow...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_06_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-BhUTAF0QEr4/UvF2R8UGAJI/AAAAAAAAc9o/xOXtLK8uj88/w426-h284/radar.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/115214861931726265762/albums/5874682465882869073/5874682470595056146?authkey=CNTcxJKP_sPXpwE</link><title>Location hypotheses of Atlantis. 

Location hypotheses of Atlantis are various proposed real-world settings for the legendary island of Atlantis, (Ἀτλαντὶς νῆσος) described as a lost civilization mentioned in Plato's dialogues Timaeus and Critias, written about 360 B.C. In these dialogues, a character named Critias claims that an island called Atlantis was swallowed by the sea in Last glacial period( about 9,200 years previously). According to the dialogues, this story was passed down to him through his grandfather, Dropides, who in turn got it from Solon, the famous Athenian lawmaker who got the story from an Egyptian sanctuary. Plato's dialogues locate the island in the Atlantic Pelagos "Atlantic Sea",[2] "in front of" the Pillars of Hercules (Ηράκλειες Στήλες) and facing a district called modern Gades or Gadira (Gadiron), a location that some modern Atlantis researchers associate with modern Gibraltar; however various locations have been proposed. 
*  North-West of Egypt: From Greece to Spain. 
Most theories of the placement of Atlantis center on the Mediterranean, influenced largely by the geographical location of Egypt from which the story allegedly is derived. 
\+ Thera (Santorini). 
The theory that Thera has been the site of the capital of Atlantis has been suggested by Angelos Galanopoulos in 1960.[3] 
Soon after the discovery of the Minoan civilization at Knossos on Crete by Sir Arthur Evans in 1900, theories linking the disappearance of this advanced empire with the destruction of Atlantis were proposed by K. T. Frost in 1913 and E. S. Balch in 1917. This theory was revived by Spyridon Marinatos in 1950 and P. B. S. Andrews in 1967.[4] More recent archaeological, seismological, and vulcanological evidence[5][6][7] (Recent arguments for Akrotiri being Atlantis have been popularized on television in shows such as The History Channel show Lost Worlds episode "Atlantis"[8][9]) has expanded the asserted connection of Crete, the island of Santorini, and the Minoan civilization with Plato's description of Atlantis. Evidence said to advance this idea includes: 
The Minoan palace and buildings discovered at the digs at Knossos on Crete and at Akrotiri on the island of Thera have revealed that the Minoans possessed advanced engineering knowledge enabling the construction of three- and four-story buildings with intricate water piping systems, advanced air-flow management, and earthquake-resistant wood and masonry walls. This level of technology was, it is said, far ahead of that found on mainland Greece at the time. 
Thera (also called Santorini) is the site of a massive volcanic caldera with an island at its center. Vulcanologists have determined that the island was engulfed by a volcanic eruption, the Thera eruption, around 1600 BC. The event, referred to as the Minoan eruption, was among the most powerful eruptions occurring in the history of civilization, ejecting approximately 60 km³ of material, leaving a layer of pumice and ash 10 to 80 meters thick for 20 to 30 km in all directions and having widespread effects across the eastern Mediterranean region.[10] Volcanic events of this magnitude are known to generate tsunamis and archaeological evidence suggests that such a tsunami may have devastated the coastal Minoan settlements on Crete.[7] Plato did not describe a volcanic eruption, although the events he described as "sunk by an earthquake" or "violent earthquakes, and only a flood (in singular)", could perhaps be intrepreted as consistent with such an eruption and the resulting tsunami.[11] 
Plato described quarries on Atlantis where "one kind of stone was white, another black, and a third red",[12] writing that these stones were quarried from the island and used in the construction. Rocks like this are found on Santorini.[citation needed] 
The center of the metropolis of Atlantis was described as being laid out in circular manner, surrounded by three circular concentric pits of seawater and two earth-rings, each connected to the sea by a deep canal. Docks for a large number of ships, with a causeway, were also mentioned. Scientists reconstructing the shape of the island prior to the eruption have concluded that there was a ring configuration with only one narrow entrance to a larger lagoon with islands inside, much as Plato described.[13] One fresco in the ruins of Akrotiri is believed to be a landscape of the city. It shows a large city in an island in the center of the caldera lagoon. 
The ancient Greek for "between" and "larger" are easily confused in transcription and translation, so "larger than Asia and Libya", might have originally read "between Asia and Libya",[citation needed]which is how Classical Greeks would have described Thera and Crete. 
\- Near Cyprus. 
It has been argued by Robert Sarmast, an American architect, that the lost city of Atlantis lies at the bottom of the eastern Mediterranean within the Cyprus Basin.[14] In his book and on his web site, he argues that images prepared from sonar data of the sea bottom of the Cyprus Basin southeast of Cyprus show features resembling man-made structures on it at depths of 1,500 meters. He interprets these features as being artificial structures that are part of the lost city of Atlantis as described by Plato. According to his ideas, several characteristics of Cyprus, including the presence of copper and extinct Cyprus Dwarf Elephants and local place names and festivals (Kataklysmos), support his identification of Cyprus as once being part of Atlantis. As with many other theories concerning the location of Atlantis, Sarmast speculates that its destruction by catastrophic flooding is reflected in the story of Noah's Flood in Genesis. 
In part, Sarmast[14] bases his claim that Atlantis can be found offshore of Cyprus beneath 0.9 mile (1.5 km) of water on an abundance of evidence that the Mediterranean Sea dried up during the Messinian Salinity Crisis when its level dropped by 2 to 3 miles (3.2 to 4.9 km) below the level of the Atlantic Ocean as the result of tectonic uplift blocking the inflow of water through Strait of Gibraltar.[15] Separated from the Atlantic Ocean, the Mediterranean Sea either partly or completely dried up as the result of evaporation. As a result, its formerly submerged bottom turned into a desert with large saline and brackish lakes. This area all was flooded when a ridge collapsed allowing the catastrophic flooding through the Straits of Gibraltar. However, Sarmast disagrees with mainstream geologists, oceanographers, and paleontologists[16][17] in arguing that the closing of the Straits of Gibraltar; the desiccation and subaerial exposure of the floor of the Mediterranean Sea; and its catatstrophic flooding has occurred "forty times or more times in its long and turbulent existence" and that "the age of each of these events is unknown."[18] In the same interview, he also contradicts what mainstream geologists, oceanographers, and paleontologists argue[16][17] in claiming that "Scientists know that roughly 18,000 years ago, there was not just one Mediterranean Sea, but three." However, he does not specify who these scientists are; nor does he cite peer-reviewed scientific literature that supports this claim. 
Marine and other geologists,[15][19] who have also studied the bottom of the Cyprus basin, and professional archaeologists completely disagree with his interpretations.[20] Investigations by Dr. C. Hübscher of the Institut für Geophysik, Universität Hamburg, Germany, and others of the salt tectonics and mud volcanism within the Cyprus Basin, eastern Mediterranean Sea, demonstrated that the features which Sarmast interprets to be Atlantis consist only of a natural compressional fold caused by local salt tectonics and a slide scar with surficial compressional folds at the downslope end and sides of the slide.[19] This research collaborates seismic data shown and discussed in the Atlantis: New Revelations 2-hour Special episode of Digging for the Truth, a History Channel documentary television series. Using reflection seismology, this documentary demonstrated techniques that what Sarmast interpreted to be artificial walls are natural tectonic landforms. 
Furthermore, the interpretation of the age and stratigraphy of sediments blanketing the bottom of the Cyprus Basin from sea bottom cores containing Pleistocene and older marine sediments and thousands of kilometers of seismic lines from the Cyprus and adjacent basins clearly demonstrates that the Mediterranean Sea last dried up during the Messinian Salinity Crisis between 5.59 and 5.33 million years ago.[15][19][21][22][23] For example, research conducted south of Cyprus as part of Leg 160 of the Ocean Drilling Project recovered from Sites 963, 965, and 966 cores of sediments underlying the bottom of the Mediterranean Sea at depths as shallow as 470, 1506, and 1044 meters (1540, 4940, and 3420 ft) below sea level. Thus, these cores came from parts of sea bottom of the eastern Mediterranean Sea that either lie above or at the depth of Sarmast's Atlantis, which lies at depths between 1460 and 1510 meters (4820 and 4950 ft) below mean sea level.[19] These cores provide a detailed and continuous record of sea level that demonstrates that for millions of years at least during the entire Pliocene, Pleistocene, and Holocene epochs that the feature that Sarmast interprets to be Atlantis and its adjacent sea bottom were always submerged below sea level.[21] Therefore, the entire Cyprus Basin, including the ridge where Sarmast claims that Atlantis is located, has been submerged beneath the Mediterranean Sea for millions of years.[17] Since its formation, the sea bottom feature identified by Sarmast as "Atlantis" has always been submerged beneath over a kilometer of water. 

\- Helike. 
A. Giovannini has argued that the submergence of the Greek city of Helike in 373 BC, i.e. while Plato was alive, may have been the inspiration for a totally fictional story about Atlantis.[24] The claim that Helike is the inspiration for Plato's Atlantis is also supported by Dora Katsonopoulou and Steven Soter.[25] 
\- Sardinia. 
In 2002 the Italian journalist Sergio Frau published a book, Le colonne d'Ercole ("Pillars of Hercules"), in which he states that before Eratosthenes, all the ancient Greek writers located the Pillars of Hercules on the Strait of Sicily between Sicily and Tunisia, while only Alexander the Great's conquest of the east obliged Eratosthenes to move the pillars at Gibraltar in his description of the world.[26] 
According to his thesis, the Atlantis described by Plato could be identified with Sardinia. He argues that a tsunami once hit Sardinia which destroyed the enigmatic Nuragic civilization and that the survivors migrated to the nearby Italian peninsula, founding the Etruscan civilization (which is now thought to have come from the Eastern Mediterranean). 
In April 2005, the theories of the Sergio Frau were debated at a conference organized by UNESCO in Paris. At the same time, an exposition of his findings was on display in the UNESCO building.[27] 
\- Sicily. 
The concept of the identification of Atlantis with the island of Sicily is the idea that the Italians were involved in the Sea Peoples movement (a similar story to Plato's account), that the name "Atlas" may have been derived from "Italos" via the Middle Egyptian language, and Plato's descriptions of the island and the city of Atlantis share several traits with Sicily and its Bronze Age culture.[28][29] 
\- Malta. 
Malta, being situated in the dividing line between the western and eastern Mediterranean sea, and being the home to the oldest man-made structures in the world, is considered a possible location of Atlantis both by some current researchers[30] and by Maltese amateur enthusiasts.[31] 
In Malta: Echoes of Plato's Island (2000), Anton Mifsud, Simon Mifsud, Chris Agius Sultana and Charles Savona Ventura catalogues the many archaeological sites and ancient remains in Malta that could be related to Atlantis.[32] 
In Malta fdal Atlantis (Maltese remains of Atlantis) (2002), Francis Galea writes about several older studies and hypotheses, particularly that of Maltese architect Giorgio Grongnet, who in 1854 claimed that the Maltese Islands are the remnants of Atlantis. 

* North-East of Egypt: From Middle East to the Black Sea. 
\- Middle East. 
Jaime Manuschevich argues that the real place of the mythical civilization is the territory that today corresponds to Israel and Sinai,[34] and that this region was an island in the Great Rift Valley,[35] surrounded by the Jezreel Valley on the north, the Dead Sea and Red Sea on the east and the Gulf of Suez and the Mediterranean on the west until 5600 BC. In addition, Manuschevich proposes that Atlantean civilization corresponds to the Natufian peoples, the first food-producing people, whose main political and harbor center was Jericho. These people lived in the region in the dates established by Plato (11,600 BC). 
\- Turkey. 
Peter James, in his book The Sunken Kingdom, identifies Atlantis with the kingdom of Zippasla. He argues that Solon did indeed gather the story on his travels, but in Lydia, not Egypt as Plato states; that Atlantis is identical with Tantalis, the city of Tantalus in Asia Minor, which was (in a similar tradition known to the Greeks) said to have been destroyed by an earthquake; that the legend of Atlantis' conquests in the Mediterranean is based on the revolt by King Madduwattas of Zippasla against Hittite rule; that Zippasla is identical with Sipylus, where Greek tradition placed Tantalis; and that the now vanished lake to the north of Mount Sipylus was the site of the city. 
\- Troy. 
The geoarchaeologist Eberhard Zangger has proposed the hypothesis that Atlantis was in fact the city state of Troy.[37] He both agrees and disagrees with Rainer W. Kühne: He too believes that the Trojans-Atlanteans were the sea peoples, but only a minor part of them. He proposes that all Greek speaking city states of the Aegean civilization or Mycenae constituted the sea peoples and that they destroyed each other's economies in a series of semi-fratricidal wars lasting several decades. 
\- Black Sea. 
German researchers Siegfried and Christian Schoppe locate Atlantis in the Black Sea. Before 5500 BC, a great plain lay in the northwest at a former freshwater-lake. In 5510 BC, rising sea level topped the barrier at today's Bosporus. They identify the Pillars of Hercules with the Strait of Bosporus.[40] They gave no explanation how the ships of the merchants coming from all over the world had arrived at the harbour of Atlantis when it was 350 feet below global sea-level. 
They claim Oreichalcos means the obsidian stone that used to be a cash-equivalent at that time and was replaced by the spondylus shell around 5500 BC, which would suit the red, white, black motif. The geocatastrophic event led to the neolithic diaspora in Europe, also beginning 5500 BC. 
In 2000, the Guardian reported that Robert Ballard, in a small submarine, found remains of human habitation around 300 feet underwater in the Black Sea off the north coast of Turkey. The area flooded around 5000 BC. This flood is also believed to have inspired the Biblical story of Noah's Ark known as the Black Sea deluge theory. 
Another candidate bordering the Black Sea, suggested by Hasan Umur in the 1940s, would be Ancomah, a legendary place near Trabzon. 
* Around Gibraltar: Near to the Pillars of Hercules. 
\- Andalusia. 
Andalusia is a region in modern day southern Spain which once included the "lost" city of Tartessos, which disappeared in the 6th century BC. The Tartessians were traders known to the Ancient Greeks who knew of their legendary king Arganthonios. The Andalusian hypothesis was originally developed by the Spanish author Juan de Mariana and the Dutch author Johannes van Gorp (Goropius Becanus), both of the 16th century, later by Jose Pellicer de Ossau y Tovar in 1673, who suggested that the metropolis of Atlantis was between the islands Mayor and Menor, located almost in the center of the Doñana Marshes,[42] and expanded upon by Juan Fernández Amador y de los Ríos in 1919, who suggested that the metropolis of Atlantis was located precisely where today are the 'Marismas de Hinojo'.[43] These claims were made again in 1922 by the German author Adolf Schulten, and further propagated by Otto Jessen, Richard Hennig, Victor Berard, and Elena Wishaw in the 1920s. The suggested locations in Andalusia lie outside the Pillars of Hercules, and therefore beyond but close to the Mediterranean itself. 
In 2005, based upon the work of Adolf Schulten, the German teacher Werner Wickboldt also claimed this to be the location of Atlantis.[44] Wickboldt suggested that the war of the Atlanteans refers to the war of the Sea Peoples who attacked the Eastern Mediterranean countries around 1200 BC and that the Iron Age city of Tartessos may have been built at the site of the ruined Atlantis. In 2000, Georgeos Diaz-Montexano published an article explaining his belief that Atlantis was located somewhere between Andalusia and Morocco.[45] An Andalusian location was also supported by Rainer W. Kühne in his article that appeared in the journal Antiquity.[46][47] Kühne's theory says: "Good fiction imitates facts. Plato declared that his Atlantis tale is philosophical fiction invented to describe his fictitious ideal state in the case of war. Kühne suggests that Plato has used three historical elements for this tale. (i) Greek tradition on Mycenaean Athens for the description of ancient Athens, (ii) Egyptian records on the wars of the Sea Peoples for the description of the war of the Atlanteans, and (iii) oral tradition from Syracuse about Tartessos for the description of the city and geography of Atlantis." According to Wickboldt, Satellite images show two rectangular shapes on the tops of two small elevations inside the marsh of Doñana which he hypothesizes are the "temple of Poseidon" and "the temple of Cleito and Poseidon".[48] On satellite images parts of several "rings" are recognizable, similar in their proportion with the ring system by Plato.[44] It is not known if any of these shapes are natural or manmade and archaeological excavations are planned.[49] Geologists have shown that the Doñana National Park experienced intense erosion from 4000 BC until 9th century AD, where it became a marine environment. For thousands of years until the Medieval Age, all that occupied the area of the modern Marshes Doñana was a gulf or inland sea-arm, but there was not even a small island with sufficient space to house a small village.[50][51][clarification needed] 
In 2011, a team led by Richard Freund claimed to have found strong evidence for the location[where?] in Doñana National Park based on underground and underwater surveys, and the existence of what they characterized as "memorial cities" rebuilt in Atlantis's image.[52][53] Spanish scientists have dismissed Freund's claims claiming that he was sensationalising their work. The anthropologist Juan Villarías-Robles, who works with the Spanish National Research Council, said "Richard Freund was a newcomer to our project and appeared to be involved in his own very controversial issue concerning King Solomon's search for ivory and gold in Tartessos, the well documented settlement in the Donaña area established in the first millennium BC" and described his claims as 'fanciful'.[54] 
Simcha Jacobovici, involved in the production of a documentary on Freund's work for the National Geographic Channel, stated that the biblical Tarshish (which he believes is the same as Tartessos) was Atlantis, and that "Atlantis was hiding in the Tanach". Aren Maeir, a professor of archeology at Bar-Ilan University said "a lot of people have made many crazy claims about Atlantis – it's one of those classic places where you have a lunatic fringe looking for all types of things. And Richard Freund is known as someone who makes ‘sensational’ finds. I would say that I am exceptionally skeptical about the thing, but I wouldn’t discount it 100% until I see the details, which haven’t been published as far as I know...every few years we hear something like this from him... And the fact that it's on National Geographic doesn’t mean much. Unfortunately, over the past years they’ve had many questionable programs." 
\- Spartel Bank. 
Two hypotheses have put Spartel Bank, a submerged former island in the Strait of Gibraltar, as the location of Atlantis. The more well-known hypothesis was proposed in a September 2001 issue of Comptes Rendus de l'academie des Sciences by French geologist Jacques Collina-Girard.[56] The lesser-known hypothesis was first published by Spanish-Cuban investigator Georgeos Díaz-Montexano in an April 2000 issue of Spanish magazine Más Allá de la Ciencia (Beyond Science), and later in August 2001 issues of Spanish magazines El Museo (The Museum) and Año Cero (Year Zero).[57] The origin of Collina-Girard's hypothesis is disputed, with Díaz-Montexano claiming it as plagiarism of his own earlier hypothesis, and Collina-Girard denying any plagiarism. Both individuals claim the other's hypothesis is pseudoscience.[57][58] 
Collina-Girard's hypothesis states that during the most recent Glacial Maximum of the Ice Age sea level was 135 m below its current level, narrowing the Gibraltar Strait and creating a small half-enclosed sea measuring 70 km by 20 km between the Mediterranean and Atlantic Ocean. The Spartel Bank formed an archipelago in this small sea with the largest island measuring about 10 to 12 kilometers across. With rising ocean levels the island began to slowly shrink, but then at around 9400 BC (11,400 years ago) there was an accelerated sea level rise of 4 meters per century known as Meltwater Pulse 1A, which drowned the top of the main island. The occurrence of a great earthquake and tsunami in this region, similar to the 1755 Lisbon earthquake (magnitude 8.5-9) was proposed by marine geophysicist Marc-Andrè Gutscher as offering a possible explanation for the described catastrophic destruction (reference - Gutscher, M.-A., 2005. Destruction of Atlantis by a great earthquake and tsunami? A geological analysis of the Spartel Bank hypothesis. Geology, v. 33, p. 685-688.) .[59] Collina-Girard proposes that the disappearance of this island was recorded in prehistoric Egyptian tradition for 5,000 years until it was written down by the first Egyptian scribes around 4000-3000 BC, and the story then subsequently inspired Plato to write a fictionalized version interpreted to illustrate his own principles. 
A detailed review in the Bryn Mawr Classical Review comments on the discrepancies in Collina-Girard's dates and use of coincidences, concluding that he "has certainly succeeded in throwing some light upon some momentous developments in human prehistory in the area west of Gibraltar. Just as certainly, however, he has not found Plato's Atlantis." 
\- Morocco. 
According to Michael Hübner, Atlantis core region was located in South-West Morocco at the Atlantic Ocean. In his papers[61][62][63] an approach to the analysis of Plato's dialogues Timaeus and Critias is described. By means of a hierarchical constraint satisfaction procedure, a variety of geographically relevant indications from Plato's accounts are used to infer the most probable location of Plato's Atlantis Nesos. The outcome of this is the Souss-Massa plain in today's South-West Morocco. This plain is surrounded by the High Atlas, the Anti-Atlas, the Sea of Atlas (Atlantis Thalassa, today's Atlantic Ocean). Because of this isolated position, Hübner argued, this plain was called Atlantis Nesos, the Island of Atlas by ancient Greeks before the Greek Dark Ages. The Amazigh (Berber) People actually call the Souss-Massa plain island. Of major archaeological interest is the fact that in the North-West of the Souss-Massa plain a large annular caldera-like geomorphologic structure was discovered. This structure has almost the dimensions of Plato's capital of Atlantis and is covered with hundreds of large and small prehistoric ruins of different types.[64] These ruins were made out of rocks coloured red, white and black. Hübner also shows possible harbour remains, an unusually geomorphological structure, which applies to Plato's description of roofed over docks, which were cut into red, white and black bedrock. These 'docks' are located close to the annular geomorphological structure and close to Cape Ghir, which was named Cape Heracles in antiquity. Hübner also argued, that Agadir is etymologically related to the semitic g-d-r and probably to Plato's Gadir. The semitic g-d-r means enclosure, fortification and sheep fold.[65] The meaning of enclosure, sheep fold corresponds to the Greek translation of the name Gadeiros (Crit. 114b) which is Eumelos = Rich in Sheep. 

* Atlantic Ocean: West. 
It has been claimed that when Plato wrote of the Sea of Atlantis, he may have been speaking of the area now called the Atlantic Ocean. The ocean's name, derived from Greek mythology, means the "Sea of Atlas". Plato remarked that, in describing the origins of Atlantis, this area was allotted to Poseidon. In Ancient Greek times the terms "Ocean" and "Atlas" both referred to the 'Giant Water' which surrounded the main landmass known at that time by the Greeks, which could be described as Eurafrasia (although this whole supercontinent was far from completely known to the Ancient Greeks), and thus this water mass was considered to be the 'end of the (known) world', for the same reason the name "Atlas" was given to the mountains near the Ocean, the Atlas Mountains, as they also denoted the 'end of the (known) world'. 
\- Azores Islands. 
One of the suggested places for Atlantis is around the Azores Islands, a group of islands belonging to Portugal located about 900 miles (1500 km) west of the Portuguese coast. Some people believe the islands could be the mountain tops of Atlantis. Ignatius L. Donnelly, an American congressman, was perhaps the first one to talk about this possible location in his book "Atlantis: The Antediluvian World".[67] 
The Azores are steep-sided volcanic seamounts that drop rapidly 1000 meters (about 3300 feet) to a plateau.[68] Cores taken from the plateau and other evidence shows that this area has been an undersea plateau for millions of years.[69][70] Ancient indicators, i.e. relict beaches, marine deposits, and wave cut-terraces, of Pleistocene shorelines and sea level show that the Azores Islands have not subsided to any significant degree. Instead, they demonstrate that some of these islands have actually risen during the Late and Middle Pleistocene. This is evidenced by relict, Pleistocene wave-cut platforms and beach sediments that now lie well above current sea level. For example, they have been found on Flores Island at elevations of 15-20, 35-45, ~100, and ~250 meters above current sea level.[71] 
Ignatius L. Donnelly also makes a connection to the mythical Aztlán. 

\- Canary Islands, Madeira and Cape Verde. 
The Canary Islands have been identified as remnants of Atlantis by numerous authors. For example in 1803, Bory de Saint-Vincent in his Essai sur les îles fortunées et l'antique Atlantide proposed that the Canary Islands, along with the Madeira, and Azores, are what remained after Atlantis broke up. Many later authors, i.e. Lewis Spence in his The Problem of Atlantis, also identified the Canary Islands as part of Atlantis leftover from when it catastrophically sank. 
Detailed geomorphic and geologic studies of the Canary Islands clearly demonstrate that over the last 4 million years, they have been steadily uplifted, without any significant periods of subsidence, by geologic processes such as erosional unloading, gravitational unloading, lithospheric flexure induced by adjacent islands, and volcanic underplating.[72] For example, Pliocene pillow lavas, which solidified underwater and now exposed on the northeast flanks of Gran Canaria, have been uplifted between 46 and 143 meters above sea level.[72] Also, marine deposits associated with lavas dated as being 4.1 and 9.3 million years old in Gran Canaria, ca. 4.8 million years old in Fuerteventura, and ca. 9.8 million years old in Lanzarote demonstrate that the Canary Islands have for millions of years undergone long term uplift without any significant, much less catastrophic, subsidence.[73][74] A series of raised, Pleistocene marine terraces, which become progressively older with age, on Fuerteventura indicate that it has risen in elevation at about 1.7 cm per thousand years for the past one million years. The elevation of the marine terrace for the highstand of sea level for the last interglacial period shows that this island has experienced neither subsidence nor significant uplift for the past 125,000 years.[75] Within the Cape Verde Islands, the detailed mapping and dating of 16 Pleistocene marine terraces and Pliocene marine conglomerate found that they have been uplifted throughout most of the Pleistocene and remained relatively stable without any significant subsidence since the last interglacial period.[76] Finally, detailed studies of the sedimentary deposits surrounding the Canary Islands have demonstrated, except for a narrow rim around each island exposed during glacial lowstands of sea level, a complete lack of any evidence for the ocean floor surrounding the Canary Islands having ever been above water. 

\- Northern Spain. 
According to Jorge Maria Ribero-Meneses,[79] Atlantis was in northern Spain. He specifically argues that Atlantis is the underwater plateau, known internationally as "Le Danois Bank" and locally as "The Cachucho". It is located about 25 kilometers from the continental shelf and about 60 km off the coast of Asturias, and Lastres between Ribadesella. Its top is now 425 meters below the sea. It is 50 kilometers from east to west and 18 km from north to south. Ribero-Meneses hypothesized that is part of the continental margin that broke off at least 12000 years ago as the result of tectonic processes that occurred at the end of the last ice age. He argues that they created a tsunami with waves with heights of hundreds of meters and that the few survivors had to start virtually from scratch.[80] 
Detailed studies[81] of the geology of the Le Danois Bank region have refuted the hypothesis proposed by Jorge Maria Ribero-Meneses that the Le Danois Bank was created by the collapse of the northern Cantabrian continental margin about 12,000 years ago. The Le Danois Bank represents part of the continental margin that have been uplifted by thrust faulting when the continental margin overrode oceanic crust during the Paleogene and Neogene periods. Along the northern edge of the Le Danois Bank, Precambrian granulite and Mesozoic sedimentary rocks have been thrust northward over Miocene and Oligocene marine sediments. The basin separating the Le Danois Bank from the Cantabrian continental margin to the south is a graben that simultaneously formed as a result of normal faulting associated with the thrust faulting.[81][82] In addition, marine sediments that range in age from lower Pliocene to Pleistocene, cover large parts of Le Danois Bank, and fill the basin separating it from the Cantabrian continental margin demonstrate that this bank has been submerged beneath the Bay of Biscay for millions of years. 
* Atlantic Ocean: North. 
\- Irish Sea. 
In his book Atlantis of the West: The Case For Britain's Drowned Megalithic Civilization (2003), Paul Dunbavin argues that a large island once existed in the Irish Sea and that this island was Atlantis. He argues that this Neolithic civilization in Europe was partially drowned by rising sea levels caused by a comet impact that caused a pole shift and changed the earth's axis around 3100 BC. 
\- Great Britain. 
William Comyns Beaumont believed that Great Britain was the location of Atlantis[86] and the Scottish journalist Lewis Spence claimed that the ancient traditions of Britain and Ireland contain memories of Atlantis. 
On December 29, 1997, the BBC reported that a team of Russian scientists believed they found Atlantis in the ocean 100 miles off of Land's End, Cornwall, Britain. The BBC stated that Little Sole Bank, a relatively shallow area, was believed by the team to be the capital of Atlantis. This may have been based on the myth of Lyonesse. 
\- Ireland. 
The idea of Atlantis being located in Ireland was presented in the book Atlantis from a Geographer's Perspective: Mapping the Fairy Land (2004) by Swedish geographer Dr. Ulf Erlingsson from Uppsala University. It hypothesized that the empire of Atlantis refers to the Neolithic Megalithic tomb culture, based on their similar geographic extent, and deduced that the island of Atlantis then must correspond to Ireland. Erlingsson found the similarities of size and landscape to be statistically significant, while he rejected his null hypothesis that Plato invented Atlantis as fiction.[88] 
Based on this result, the speculation was made that the capital of Atlantis could be connected with Newgrange, Knowth, and Tara, Ireland. As regards the sinking of Atlantis, it was suggested that it is a memory from another time and place, notably the Dogger Bank area. It was an island that sank in the North Sea about 6100 BC. While the world sea level rose gradually as the Ice Age ice sheets melted, there was a sudden sea level rise at this time due to the final drainage of Lake Agassiz. At about the same time a tsunami from the Storegga Slide is believed to have devastated the island in the manner described by Plato. (See also entry on North Sea below.) 
Other hypotheses place the location of Atlantis between Britain and France on the Celtic Shelf.[89] This hypothesis was first developed by Lewis Spence and has been recently revived by some oceanographers. 
\- North Sea. 
The North Sea is known to contain lands that were once above water; the medieval town of Dunwich in East Anglia, for example, crumbled into the sea. The land area known as "Doggerland", between England and Denmark, was inundated by a tsunami around 8200BP (6200BC), caused by a submarine landslide off the coast of Norway known as the Storegga Slide,[90] and prehistoric human remains have been dredged up from the Dogger Bank.[91] Atlantis itself has been identified besides Heligoland off the north-west German coast by the author Jürgen Spanuth,[92] who postulates that it was destroyed during the Bronze Age around 1200 BC, only to partially re-emerge during the Iron Age. Ulf Erlingsson hypothesized that the island that sank referred to Dogger Bank, and the city itself referred to the Silverpit crater at the base of Dogger Bank. A book allegedly by Oera Linda claims that a land called Atland once existed in the North Sea, but was destroyed in 2194 BC. 
\- Denmark. 
In his book The Celts: The People Who Came Out of the Darkness (1975), author Gerhard Herm links the origins of the Atlanteans to end of the ice age and the flooding of eastern coastal Denmark. 
\- Finland. 
Finnish eccentric Ior Bock located Atlantis in the Baltic sea, at southern part of Finland where he claimed a small community of people lived during the Ice Age. According to Bock, this was possible due to Gulf Stream which brought warm water to the Finnish coast. This is a small part of a large saga that he claimed had been told in his family through the ages, dating back to the development of language itself. The family saga tells the name Atlantis comes from Swedish words allt-land-is ("all-land-ice") and refers to the last Ice-Age. Thus in the Bock family saga it's more a time period than an exact geographical place. According to this the Atlantis disappeared in 8016 BC when the Ice-Age ended in Finland and the ice melted away. 
\- Sweden. 
In 1679 Olaus Rudbeck wrote Atland (Atlantica), where he argues that Scandinavia, specifically Sweden, is identical with Atlantis. According to Rudbeck the capital city of Atlantis was identical to the ancient burial site of Swedish kings Gamla Uppsala. 
* Americas. 
When Columbus returned from his voyage to the west, some historians of the period such as Francisco López de Gómara ,[95] writing in 1552 thought that what Columbus had discovered was the Atlantic Island of Plato. 
In 1556 Agustín de Zárate stated that the Americas was Atlantis which at one time began from the straits of Gibraltar and extended westwards to include North and South America[verification needed] and that it was as a result of Plato that the new continent was discovered. He also said it had all the attributes of the continent described by Plato yet at the same time mentioned that the ancient peoples crossed over by a route from the island of Atlantis. Zarate also mentions that the 9,000 "years" of Plato were 9,000 "months" (750 years).[96] 
This was also repeated and clarified by historian Pedro Sarmiento de Gamboa in 1572 in his "History of the Incas",[97] who by calculation of longitude stated that Atlantis must have stretched from within two leagues of the strait of Gibraltar westwards to include "all the rest of the land from the mouth of the Marañon (Amazon River) and Brazil to the South Sea, which is what they now call America." He thought the sunken part to be now in the Atlantic Ocean but that it was from this sunken part that the original Indians had come to populate Peru via one continuous land mass. He says that South America was also known by the name of the Isla Atlanticus. 
It first appeared as the Atlantic Island (Insula Atlantica) on a map of the New World by cartographer Sebastian Münster in 1540[98] and again on the map titled Atlantis Insula by Nicolas Sanson and son (1669) which identified both North and South America as "Atlantis Insula", the eastern part of the Atlantic Ocean as "Oceanus Atlanticus" and the western part of the Atlantic Ocean plus the Pacific Ocean as "Atlanticum Pelagus". This edition was further embellished with features from the Atlantis legend by his son Guillaume Sanson including the names of the ten kings of Atlantis with Atlas’ portion being in Mexico. Sanson's map supposedly showed what the earth looked like 200,000 years before there were any humans on it. 
\- South America. 
A hypothesis by author Jim Allen argues that Plato's description exactly fits South America with the island capital in what is now Bolivia because he describes a level rectangular-shaped plain which he said lay in the center of the continent, next to the sea and midway along the longest side of the continent.[100] He also described the capital city of Atlantis which was built on a small volcanic island and also called Atlantis. The city lay on the level rectangular plain, five miles from the sea and according to Plato the whole region was high above the level of the ocean sea, rising sheer out of the ocean sea to a great height on that side of the continent. Allen contends that the Altiplano region of Bolivia meets these characteristics. 
\- Cuba. 
Author Andrew Collins has advocated a Cuban connection to Atlantis in his book Gateway to Atlantis: The Search for the Source of a Lost Civilization. Collins supports his hypothesis with indirect historical and geographical evidence. He suggests Isle of Youth and the shallow sea bottom that surrounds it as a possible location for Atlantis.[101] 
Sonar images suggested to be a complex of submerged structures or a Cuban underwater city were recorded off the coast of the Guanahacabibes peninsula near the Pinar del Río Province in 2001. 
* Other locations. 
There have been suggestions for Atlantis to be placed outside of the Mediterranean Sea or the Atlantic Ocean. Such locations would tend to fall outside of the known world of the original sources of the legend. 
\- Antarctica. 
The theory that Antarctica was Atlantis was particularly fashionable during the 1960s and 1970s, spurred on partly both by the isolation of the continent, and also the Piri Reis map, which purportedly shows Antarctica as it would be ice free, suggesting human knowledge of that period. Charles Berlitz, Erich Von Däniken and Peter Kolosimo are some of the popular authors who made this proposal. 
More recently Rose and Rand Flem-Ath have proposed this in their book, When the Sky Fell; the theory was revised and made more specific in Rand's work with author Colin Wilson, in The Atlantis Blueprint (published in 2002). The second work theorized that Atlantis was to be found in Lesser Antarctica, near the coast of the Ross Ice Shelf. A geological theory known as "Earth Crust Displacement" forms the basis of their work. The Atlantis Blueprint uses both scientific and pseudoscientific (such as mere speculation and assumptions) means to back up the theory.[103] 
Charles Hapgood came up with the "Earth Crustal Displacement theory". Hapgood's theory suggests that Earth's outer crust is able to move upon the upper mantle layer rapidly up to a distance of 2,000 miles, placing Atlantis in Antarctica, when considering the movements of the crust in the past. It is to be noted that Albert Einstein was one of the few voices to answer Hapgood's theory. Einstein wrote a preface for Hapgood's book Earth's shifting crust, published in 1958. This theory is particularly popular with Hollow Earthers, and can be seen as a mirror of the Hyperborean identification.[104] In his book "Fingerprints of the Gods", author Graham Hancock argues for the Earth Crustal Displacement theory in general, and the Atlantis/Antarctica connection specifically, then goes on to propose archaeological exploration of Antarctica in search of Atlantis. 
What is now known about the Quaternary and Holocene history of Antarctica completely discredits any hypothesis about it being the location of Atlantis. Mapping and dating of the edges of the Antarctic ice sheet during the Last Glacial Maximum; mapping and dating of glacial erratics, tills, and striations within now ice-free areas; microfossils from post-glacial lake deposits; coring and analysis of glacial tills and marine sediments underlying the Ross and Wedell seas; coring and analysis of ice cores; and other research has accumulated an enormous amount of data that has disproved the various hypotheses that any sizable part of Antarctica was sufficiently ice-free and temperate in climate during the last 100,000 years and earlier to have supported any civilization.[105][106] This research soundly refutes Flem-Ath's proposal that lesser (West) Antarctica was ice-free and temperate prior to 9,600 B.C. (11,600 B.P.). 
\- Indonesia/Sundaland. 
The South China Sea north of Indonesia and Java Sea have been advocated as a site for Atlantis. Key to this argument that Sundaland was the location of Atlantis is that the Ocean of Atlantis refers to the ocean which encircles Eurasia and Africa, which was the historical understanding until the time of Christopher Columbus. Proponents of this idea claim that natives of Sundaland who fled the rising waters or volcanic explosions eventually had contact with Ancient Egyptians, who later passed the story onto Plato who gets some but not all of the details correct, including location and time period. The main advocate of this theory is the Brazilian professor of nuclear physics Arysio Nunes dos Santos.[110] 
During the Last Glacial Maximum, what is now known as the Sunda Shelf was the location of a large subaerial coastal plain that was part of Sundaland. During the Last Glacial Maximum, Sundaland extended northward from Indonesia to Borneo and northwestward to the coast of Southeast Asia.[111][112][113] Sundaland is quite tectonically stable lacking any known prehistory of any significant, much less cataclysmic, tectonic subsidence.[111][114] Numerous studies by petroleum and Quaternary geologists have found a complete lack of any evidence for any Neogene and Quaternary volcanic activity within the Sunda Shelf despite its proximity to Indonesia. 
Detailed studies[114][115] of late glacial and postglacial sea level rise for this part of the Sunda Shelf demonstrates that the first significant submergence of Sundaland by rising sea level occurred between 14,000 and 15,000 years ago. Periods of abrupt rise in sea level submerged a significant part of Sundaland beneath the South China Sea between 13,000 and 14,000 years ago. Between 14,300 and 14,600 years ago, a period of 300 years, sea level rose 16m (62 feet). Between 12,000 and 13,000 years ago, the submergence of Sundaland by rising sea level was relatively minor. A final period of rapid flooding of Sundaland by the South China Sea occurred between 11,000 to 12,000 years ago. The submergence of Sundaland during this period was minor in extent relative to the area submerged between 13,000 and 14,000 years ago. Evidence for any significant or cataclysmic submergence of Sundaland as the result of tectonic processes is completely lacking. 
\- North Pole. 
The professor of systematic theology at Boston University William Fairfield Warren (1833–1929) wrote a book promoting his belief that the original centre of mankind once sat at the North Pole entitled Paradise Found: The Cradle of the Human Race at the North Pole (1885). In this work Warren placed Atlantis at the North Pole, as well as the Garden of Eden, Mount Meru, Avalon and Hyperborea.[118] Warren believed all these mythical lands were folk memories of a former inhabited far northern seat where man was originally created.[119] 
Warren's identification of Atlantis with the North Pole was maintained by positioning Atlas in the far north by mapping out ancient Greek cosmology. Warren equated the primordial Titan Atlas of Greek mythology who supported the Heavens on his shoulders (or supported the earth on a pillar) to the Atlas described in Plato's dialogue Critias as the first ruler of Atlantis (Critias, 114a). In Warren's view, all the axis mundi or cosmic-axis of ancient legends (Yggdrasil, Irminsul and Atlas' pillar) had to be in the far north "at the top of the world": 
...To locate these in right mutual relations, one must begin by representing to himself the earth as a sphere or spheroid, and as situated within, and concentric with, the starry sphere, each having its axis perpendicular, and its north pole at the top. The pole-star is thus in the true zenith, and the heavenly heights centring about it are the abode of the supreme god or gods.[119] 
Warren noted how Homer, Virgil and Hesiod all placed Atlas or his world pillar at the "ends of the earth", meaning in his view the far northern arctic regions, while Euripides related Atlas to the Pole Star, so as he concluded: 
......in oldest Greek thought Atlas belongs at the North Pole, and it is only reasonable to locate the kingdom of Atlas in the same locality.[120] 
Therefore in Warren's view Atlantis sat in the far north, at the North Pole, since the Atlas in his ancient Greek cosmological mapping stood in the far northern zenith, under the Pole Star.﻿

Meer lezen (770 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ZiLc4tm66ec/UYcQlOQIUhI/AAAAAAAAOPA/4vDvBozTW3E/w426-h240/880x495_4249_Atlantis_2d_fantasy_illustration_atlantis_underwater_picture_image_digital_art.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/112765687963187722273/albums/5956197007306820401/5956197007930743698</link><title>Today's Trophy Estate Is Listed for only $20,800,000: www.sandiegorealestateflashreport.com 

Hello, 

It is an terrific Wednesday in San Diego with a high of 68 degrees. There are only 13 more shopping days until Christmas! Remember that the perfect family Christmas gift is the dream home you always have wanted. For sure, check out today's best new listings and read the entire Blog at: 

http://www.sandiegorealestateflashreport.com/ 

Here Are Today's Highlights. 

*Active MLS listings are 6,033 up 37.1%.  

*Closed sales YTD are 34,419 as compared to 33,891 last year.  

*The YTD average sales price for Single Family Homes is up 18.2% at $593,115.  

*The YTD average sale price for Condo/Townhouse is up 21.6% at $350,260.  

Today 's Best New "Luxury Listing"..... 

2120 Hickory Street, Mission Hills 92103 available for $1,950,000 with 4 bedrooms, 3.5 baths, 2 car attached garage, built in 1941 this wonderful historic home qualifies for Mills Act reduced property taxes! 

Prairie styled historic landmark, designated the S.H. Newell, JR spec house #1, built in 1916. Extra special extravagant moldings, superior woodwork and craftsmanship can be discovered throughout 

This Estate is meticulously renovated and retains Historical designation. 

Today's "Best Buy" New Listing..... 

Each day, I select what is the "most interesting" new listing and or "best buy" just listed on the market. Today, there are 1 Sold and 9 Active for the top 10 recent selections 

#1 today is 575 6th Avenue #604, Gaslamp 92101, listed for $599,000 with 2 bedrooms, 2 baths, 960 sq.ft. great city views in ALTA Downtown's most popular high-rise. 

Welcome to this great turn key ready Southeast Corner Unit in the ALTA downtown condominiums. This contemporary design is great for any type of lifestyle. The ALTA is located in the heart of the Gaslamp quarters where you are steps away from shopping, restaurants and entertainment. 

Don't miss the opportunity to own this gorgeous renovated home. 

Today's Most Interesting Real Estate News Article..... 

Concern Grows That Aging Home Equity Loans Threaten New "Wave Of Disaster" 

Nearly half of the nation’s outstanding second lien home equity lines of credit (HELOC) will amortize over the next several years, raising monthly payments and increasing the risk of a rash of new delinquencies that could result in new defaults and foreclosures. 

Lender Processing Services today joined Equifax in raising alarms about prospect that aging HELOC loans written in the final years of the housing boom could result in a huge number of defaults, creating a “wave of disaster.” Some 48 percent of outstanding second lien home equity lines of credit, which were originated between 2004 and 2006, will begin amortizing on their tenth anniversaries.. As the payments on these HELOCs become fully amortizing, many borrowers may see monthly payments increase. 

Read the complete story in today's Blog. 

Today's "Best First Time Buyer or Investment Property" Just Listed..... 

2757 Pikake Street, Chula Vista 92154 available for $379,000 with 4 bedrooms, 2.5 baths, 2 car attached garage, 2,159 sq.ft. and  large yard. 

Large move in ready property! No HOA or Mello Roos.This home has a spacious open floor plan with Kitchen Island perfect for entertaining. Recently remodeled with granite counters, stainless steel appliances, Tile flooring, recessed lighting and pre-wired for surround sound. 

This is a perfect home for a long term rental investment. Let's go look today. 

Today 's Trophy Estate..... 

This newly built gated beachfront home is located at 3 Kapalua Place in Lahaina, Maui, Hawaii is availablefor $20,880,000 

3 Kapalua Place maui beach house 

This is simply the most impressive house I have ever seen period! 3 Kapalua Place is a Maui beach house that is spectacular. The entire wall folds away to open the living room up to your private beach front. You get a beautiful infinity pool that looks over the Maui beach. It is a spectacular sight! 

See all the other photos for this fabulous estate in today's Blog. 

Thanks for reading today's news letter. 

If your ready to see some homes in person (that's when the real fun begins), I can easily set up some visits for you. Just let me know the best day and times. Or if you are still in search mode, no problem. I'm always happy to answer any questions you might have about particular homes or neighborhoods. Just email me and I'll get right back to you. 

For sure, enjoy your day! 

Sincerely, 

Tom 

PS. Register to receive my Buyer Commission Rebate towards your closing costs when buying a home with me as your agent! All you need to do is sign up to receive   daily updates for new listings that match your personal criteria. Here is the link to do so. 

http://www.ziprealty.com/registration/register_all.jsp?metro=sandiego&amp;referredByAgent=tfurino 

Tom Furino 
REALTOR (R), MBA 
ZipRealty, Inc. 
Licensed in CA, #01400489 
tfurino@ziprealty.com ﻿

Meer lezen (170 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-nBDk_RJzrjU/UqipnxX025I/AAAAAAAAQlk/AvY1kQDdvsI/w426-h237/3-Kapalua-Place-maui-beach-house-21.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/101202360136880934632/albums/5730181162617666097/5730181165290913602</link><title>NEW TOWNHOME PLAN WITH DOWNSTAIRS MASTER SUITE DEBUTS AT THE BUNGALOWS IN HUNTINGTON BEACH 
HUNTINGTON BEACH, CA – Just when it seemed like The Bungalows at Pacific Shores in Huntington Beach couldn’t get any better, Christopher Homes has introduced a brand-new townhome that offers the convenience of a downstairs master suite as well as the carefree lifestyle of attached-home living in a prime coastal setting just three blocks from the beach. 
Spanning approximately 2,137 square feet, The Bungalows’ new Residence Four is highlighted by dual master suites, including one on the first floor that makes stair-free living an everyday reality. The heart of the home is a free-flowing great room that opens to both a private courtyard and a covered front porch. The great room’s expanse continues into a gourmet island kitchen with walk-in pantry. A spacious loft or optional bedroom enhance the home’s versatility, and select versions of Residence Four feature a secluded third floor with bedroom, bath and loft that increases the total square footage to 2,595. 
Now selling Phase 4, The Bungalows has already won acclaim for its award-winning architecture, and Residence Four joins five other spacious two- and three-story attached townhome plans that have garnered those awards. They range from approximately 1,481 to 2,606 square feet, including two, three or four bedrooms and up to 4.5 baths. 
Each plan is uniquely designed for the needs of today’s families and single households, combining thoughtfully designed living space with today’s beach lifestyle. Enhancing their appeal are spacious gourmet kitchens and a variety of flex spaces, including a super loft spanning more than 500 square feet, a private master suite retreat or a multipurpose room. Creating a custom-like community ambiance, architecture includes a mix of Spanish, Andalusian, Plantation and Coastal styles. Prices currently start in the high $500,000s and range up to the low $800,000s. Residences Two, Three and Four offer both two- and three-story designs. The two-story homes are value-priced from the mid $700,000s. 
Sought-after appointments add style, convenience and value. Kitchens display the contemporary look of slab granite countertops, a choice of wood-stain or white Thermofoil cabinets, built-in Whirlpool® Gold® stainless steel appliances and 13”x13” ceramic tile flooring. Master baths maximize personal comfort with ceramic tile countertops and shower walls, clear-glass frameless shower enclosures and large walk-in closets. Architectural flair extends throughout the homes with uniquely designed passages, volume spaces, recessed lighting in select locations and even such striking touches as decorative glass block for light and privacy. 
The Bungalows offers an array of green living comforts: dual 13 SEER air conditioning and gas forced-air heating with pilotless ignition, Honeywell® programmable digital thermostat, Rinnai® tankless energy-efficient water heater, water-saving shower heads and faucets, energy-saving dual-pane Low-E glass insulating vinyl windows and complete exterior insulation. 
The Bungalows shares the private, gated environs of Pacific Shores with The Villas, where luxury soars to dramatic heights. Winner of two prestigious national awards, The Villas is a collection of three-story attached luxury courtyard homes spanning approximately 3,527 to 4,142 square feet, including four to five bedrooms, 4.5 to 5.5 baths, plus loft space for entertainment and parties and a three-car attached garage. Two of the plans are enhanced by a first-floor bedroom and adjoining bath, and architectural styles feature Coastal, Andalusian and Spanish designs. Prices start in the low $1 Millions. 
Renowned architects have compared The Villas to a custom-home community, noting the individual styling of each home’s exterior and such extraordinary refinements as gourmet island kitchens; ultra-spacious, fireplace-warmed great rooms; grand master suites with private decks; versatile lofts; crown molding in selected areas and optional elevators for unsurpassed convenience. 
The centerpiece of every Villas residence is an extra-spacious courtyard that will enable residents to share all the advantages of coastal living, from outdoor relaxation to al fresco entertaining. And each home is topped off with a third-floor bedroom suite that may be selected as an optional loft with wet bar in most plans. 
Touches of elegance extend throughout the homes, from Baldwin® SoHo® front door hardware and brushed nickel oval interior door knobs to Kohler® plumbing fixtures and ceramic-tile counters in all secondary baths. 
Kitchens achieve the perfect balance of style and convenience with slab granite countertops, including full backsplash, in a choice of five colors and materials; wood-stain raised-panel cabinets; under-cabinet lighting; and a complete collection of KitchenAid® stainless steel appliances, including 42” built-in refrigerator, 48” commercial-style six-burner gas range with griddle and self-cleaning double ovens, microwave oven with turntable and Energy Star Tall Tub multi-cycle dishwasher. 
Master suite baths feature such impressive extras as Kohler® soaking and jetted tubs with in-line heaters, hand-set ceramic-tile tub surround and shower walls, Caesarstone® countertops and 8” x 8” ceramic-tile flooring. 
Both The Bungalows and The Villas offer a variety of customizing opportunities, including upgraded cabinet stain finishes and door styles, upgraded granite and tile selections and such state-of-the-art technology as home theater, intercom, security alarm and central vacuum systems. At The Villas, optional Wolf® appliances are joined by such additional available upgrades as Sub-Zero® refrigerator/freezers and Bertazzoni® ranges. 
Pacific Shores sets the scene for close-to-home recreation at the community’s brand-new resort-style pool. The 60-foot-long heated pool offers residents the choice of chilling, sunbathing and exercising in a private setting or venturing the short three-block distance to surf and frolic in the waves at the nearby beach. 
As a money-saving benefit for buyers, the community of Pacific Shores has no Mello-Roos tax assessments, and as an added convenience, Pacific Shores is offering full broker cooperation. 
Residents of Pacific Shores will also enjoy an inviting two-acre public park and a prime location that is just minutes from Huntington Beach's vibrant downtown, which abounds with shops, restaurants and night life. Also nearby are the world-renowned Bolsa Chica Ecological Reserve, Huntington Central Park and Library and Huntington Beach's excellent public schools. 

Pacific Shores residents will also enjoy easy access to everything Orange County has to offer, including higher education at the University of California at Irvine, Goldenwest College, Orange Coast College; world-class shopping at South Coast Plaza and Fashion Island; major league sports at Angel Stadium and the Honda Center; and a full calendar of cultural presentations at Orange County’s Segerstrom Center for the Arts. 
Christopher Homes is an award-winning, private homebuilder with a long successful history of home building in the city of Huntington Beach. Over the past 14 years, Christopher Homes has developed neighborhoods encompassing more than 1,000 homes in Huntington Beach, including the Huntington SeaCliff neighborhoods of The Peninsula, The Bluffs, The Boardwalk, The Waterfront, St. Augustine I &amp; II and Peninsula Park. Christopher Homes also developed the SeaGate neighborhood and built its Bel Air homes. For the community of Pacific Shores, Christopher Homes has teamed with RPL, a national real estate investment company focused on residential land development. RPL offers extensive industry and market expertise, financial strength and a track record of proven success. Those advantages are a result of the organization’s dedication to operational excellence and the highest standards in business practices. Since 1995, the principals and affiliates of RPL have participated in the development of more than 87 residential communities located throughout 20 U.S. markets with a total capitalization exceeding $5.3 billion. 
To discover the new Residence Four at The Bungalows and tour gorgeous decorated models at both The Bungalows and The Villas at Pacific Shores, travel Pacific Coast Highway to Newland Street in Huntington Beach. Drive north on Newland, and Pacific Shores will be on the left. From the 405 Freeway, exit south on Beach Boulevard. Turn left on Pacific Coast Highway, left again on Newland Street and continue to Pacific Shores on the left. 
Models at both The Bungalows and The Villas are open daily from 10 a.m. to 6 p.m., and prospective buyers may obtain additional information, join the interest lists and download e-brochures by visiting www.pacificshoreshb.com. Further details are also available by calling The Bungalows sales information at 714-594-3254 and The Villas sales information at 714-960-2900. Home buyers can keep up to date on all the latest news and goings-on by visiting www.facebook.com/pacificshoreshb or follow them on twitter @pacificshoreshb.﻿

Meer lezen (148 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-quKIvlyguIo/T4WxaPfMf0I/AAAAAAAAAas/bQOUnDH4quA/w426-h285/bunglows.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/102871123574468799566/albums/5742405589473755889/5742405589096455618</link><title>"Pigeon Point Surf" , San Mateo County coast, south of San Francisco 

The iconic Pigeon Point lighthouse is just to the right, but sometimes it is good to exclude the icons in order to focus on the natural beauty that surrounds it! 
(Expand post for details, and click to see the big version!) 

Details 

Canon 5D 
Canon 17-40L @ 24 
0.2-second exposure @F13 
LEE soft ND grad (100x150mm) 0.9 + 0.9 ( 6 stops total) 
Lee foundation kit filter holder with Lee 77mm adapter ring 
ISO 100 
No polarizer 
RAW file processed with Capture One by Phase One 
TIFF file processed with Photoshop 
Small Slik Sprint mini II tripod 
Manfrotto 322RC2 pistol-grip ball head 

The Story 

I like going to this place to shoot the lighthouse, but even without the lighthouse it is a great place for photography. And this fact reminded me that sometimes it is good to shoot around the icon staring you in the face and concentrate on the other fine elements that surround you. For example, if you go to the Golden Gate Bridge, shoot the landscape without the bridge. Sometimes people don't even know where it is but they will see the beauty. 

Try it out! 

Before taking out the camera and tripod from the backpack, it is a good idea to study the beach and how the waves interact with the rock and sand. Choose one or two favorite places to emphasize, where the water motion grabs your eye. Here, I liked the curl of the distant waves as well as how the water flows over the foreground rocks. So I waited for both events to happen at the same time. Eventually it did, but I had to be hit by a few waves while I lifted the tripod above my head. 

Other stuff 

My pictures are featured on the front page of California Governor, Jerry Brown's website http://gov.ca.gov 

Resources 

I wrote a 325 eBook that describes exactly how I went about learning photography starting in 2006. I did not learn the usual way. I have studied the great masters of painting and hope to find that light in the real world. 

http://www.patricksmithphotography.com/Photography_Book.html 

A great weather mashup map of the world with local temperatures, weather and nice popups. See where it is hot and not! (Must wait for slow commercials first, but worth it!) 
http://www.wunderground.com/wundermap/ 
Google Earth 
http://earth.google.com/ 

Simply the best way to scout out locations that there is. You can see sun angles and pre-visualize light under lots of different conditions. Sometimes you can actually pre-compose your shots! This has saved me many thousands of vertical feet of climbing by avoiding spots with blocked views etc. 

Satellite imagery (choose 'National' for a local US region or use your fave website) 
http://www.wrh.noaa.gov/satellite/?wfo=mtr 

Tide charting and preditions: (chose your area in US, other countries have similar websites) 
http://tidesandcurrents.noaa.gov/tide_predictions.shtml?gid=235 

Wave Heights (I choose 'North Pacific from Global') 
http://polar.ncep.noaa.gov/waves/index2.shtml 

Or Here: 
http://www.opc.ncep.noaa.gov/shtml/RP1bw.gif 

Photos of every inch of the California coastline from a small plane. Excellent for close in detailed views. 

http://www.californiacoastline.org/ 

.﻿

Meer lezen (87 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-HF8xOPhbM-U/T7EfdW5P3cI/AAAAAAAAUEI/ynA7luZSZDw/w426-h266/061012-1078-PelicanCove.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7127-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/which%20cities%20surround%20long%20beach%20ca/photos/110180194324892840358/albums/5869303525804928017/5869303523766511490?authkey=CNnk0o2LxZ616QE</link><title>Gygaxian Democracy, Gamma Style!  Rules swiped from +Zak Smith, +Ramanan Sivaranjan, by way of +Joey Lindsey 

1\. ONE HEX PER COMMENT 
2\. Gamma World/Mutant Future/Post Apocalyptica. Think Kamandi, Thundarr the Barbarian, more than The Morrow Project.  Some suggestive icons have been added for ABC (atomic/bio/chemical) hazard hexes, but don't feel constrained. 
3\. We start at the top left (Hex 01 01) and go hex by hex south until it's done then move to the next column (Hex 02 01) 
4\. Hex descriptions should be short--2 sentences long maximum 
5\. You may add a 3rd sentence if you reference a hex that's already been written up in it. 
6\. You don't have to prove you're Grant Morrison or China Mieville in every damn hex. A map where every hex has a three-headed mechshark with teeth made from the remains of decayed galaxies is not actually helpful to anyone. "0101 Well. 3 crocodiles" is fine. 
7\. You don't have to prove you're the cutest, funniest motherfucker on G+ either. We know you are already, promise. Give us some gameables. 
8\. Hexes are 6 miles. Darker colors are higher elevations. 
9\. I'll probably post this somewhere public if it gets finished so if you wanna be anonymous, say that. 
10\. Put SETTLEMENTS, TOWNS, CITIES etc in bold. It'll make it easier to label the map when we're done. 
11\. FORMAT: +Ramanan Sivaranjan was so kind as to automate and webbify the last map. He has some suggestions : "I think it'd be cool if we all referred to other hexes constistently. For example, Hex 1122 or Hex 0103. It makes search for references easier. 
Punctuation after a hex number is fine, so long as people start their reference with the word "Hex". That way when i'm searching for stuff I don't end up turning 2000 GP into a link. Also you can bold your hexes if you like, since when I copy and paste those extra '*' won't show up." 
Starting all comments in a consistent manner would be the best. ... A perfect hex description: 
XXYY This is my description with a SETTLEMENT and some other junk in it and I mention Hex AABB and Hex CCDD. A second sentence, just because. 

#GygaxianDemocracy 
Rules obviously swiped from +Zak Smith 's last one.﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7127_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-uizz8E7DbH4/UXP0dT0NJ4I/AAAAAAAABRA/O9j7R97egiE/w426-h505/desertmap.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>