<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 16:07:54" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/113910389916975197051/albums/5828738635059288417/5829516254741913410?authkey=CKHqqbqyvavL8QE</link><title>The History of Yoga -Yoga is a very ancient practice that has gone through many transformations in its lifetime, most especially in the twentieth century.  All the popular modern schools of yoga in the West come from famous yoga gurus in India (and some from Western yogis too!)  Nowadays, there is a big focus on... - http://www.yourwellness.com/2013/01/the-history-of-yoga/-Yourwellness﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-sPORA_tUq8w/UOaaJchB30I/AAAAAAAAA3M/5dQbDyX_tUU/w426-h241/history-of-yoga.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/101350891103589775850/albums/5870162946023422689/5870162949659033618?authkey=CL_7kqb1u96OdA</link><title>History of yoga ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-j-YkS7GuVgw/UXcCGewWABI/AAAAAAAAAlc/NWHR2IjAVJo/w426-h285/67E61654-D7E0-4452-8063-6536524E26EA.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/110684609487455870785/albums/5961984808101772881/5961984811220319314</link><title>History of the Chakra System 
The chakras are inextricably linked with the science and practice of yoga. The word yoga means `yoke`. It is a system of philosophy and practice designed to yoke the mortal self to its divine nature of pure consciousness. The origin of yoga and earliest mention of the chakras goes back to the Vedas, meaning `knowledge`. To know more read: 
http://www.indianetzone.com/23/history_chakra_system.htm 

#yogaforhealth   #yogameditation #kundalini  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ampdSsrbs3w/Ur05mQ0PvFI/AAAAAAAABpU/njXuSyNqMrM/w426-h461/1+Kundalini.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/104320373488615338790/albums/5716823175865557201/5716823174179653954</link><title>History of Thai Yoga Massage 

The roots of traditional Thai Yoga Massage, called originally in Thailand “Nuad Phaen Boran” (which means: ancient healthful touch) reaches far back in history. 
The yoga poses e.g.: fish, plough, bridge used in the traditional Thai Massage and their terminology and characteristics of energy-lines are very similar to the Indian system of ayurveda and yoga. 
Read more..... 
www.yoga-thaimassage.com﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Wu00hohem8o/T1Y8Y0yzCUI/AAAAAAAAAHI/dNGYWg1RmzE/w426-h299/thai-massage.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/115313564053195734973/albums/5876342597731675377/5959906316470314258</link><title>Coming Soon: Yoga the Art of Transformation - As a lover of both yoga and art, nothing could make me happier than an exhibition about the art of yoga, so I guess I have nothing to complain about. On February 21, 2014 the Asian Art Museum in San Francisco will host the largest exhibition dedicated to the art and history of the practice and... - http://art-nerd.com/sanfrancisco/coming-soon-yoga-the-art-of-transformation/ on Art Nerd San Francisco﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-EfWmCBocKJc/UrXXN8fR5RI/AAAAAAAAJX8/59DpA1WYN1Q/w426-h241/1.001.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/101991289645798722989/albums/5839368037793870161/5839368037865983842?authkey=CIm0lMasuvDTwgE</link><title>Bhagavad Gita Discussion Group 
Facilitated by Krishnan 
Sunday, February 3 and Sunday, March 3 
11:30AM-12:45 PM * $20 each session 
Pre-registration requested and drop-ins welcome. 

The Bhagavad Gita, the Song of the Blessed One, is one of the most studied and translated texts in the history of world literature. It is considered the most important book in the evolution of Yoga. It is one of the most widely read and accessible storehouses of yogic wisdom and practice. It explores yoga along the paths of action, knowledge and devotion, taking us deeper into the experience of our own true Self. 

Krishnan is a scientist by training and has been a student of Vedanta and the Bhagavad Gita for 20 years. Over the last ten years he has been sharing his thoughts on the Gita and how we can increase the quality of our lives both at home and at the work place. He explains through discussions the Gita's benefits both in our lives and relationships. The Gita helps us unlock the door to "Successful and Effective Living". 

No prior experience necessary - just bring an open heart and inquisitive mind. We’ll begin each session with a brief recap of the preceding session to bring everyone up to speed. Bring your copy of the Bhagavad Gita, and a notebook and pen. 

For February and March, please read Chapter 2 verses 54-72﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-SuKwi6c1Y2k/UQmaSsnFj2I/AAAAAAAAATk/ihQSwLE2QBY/w426-h565/gita2.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/117947942334802441260/albums/5847651064021738513/5847651070358951618</link><title>At the beginning of summer, take a deep breath – relax into the serenity of New England’s coastal joys. Enjoy twice daily #yoga practice, #meditation, study of yoga philosophy on the theme of Gratitude, healthy food, time to explore the rich history of the area and lots of space for silence. 
http://bit.ly/YFMQ8W﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-UPJLT5jFVvw/UScHqpMtlsI/AAAAAAAABbU/fSSyeovq82Y/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/116401431644207428166/albums/5897525343099807937/5897525346054873058?authkey=CIm5zvLiyMmi_wE</link><title>July 12, 2013 5-6 p.m. History of Europe's Natural Salt Mines and their benefits - Informative Talk at The Salt Spa of Asheville - FREE (includes a 15 minute Halotherapy Mini Session) 

July 13, 2013 6-7 p.m. Halo Yoga Nidra at The Salt Spa of Asheville with Katherine Caldwell 

July 14, 2013 2-3 p.m. Halo Kundalini Yoga at The Salt Spa of Asheville with Bob Bauer 

All events require reservation, please call (828) 505 1838. 
More information at http://www.saltasiawellbeing.com/events.html ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/--Yl3DjkCoXE/Udg4Dkl2n-I/AAAAAAAAAIw/Zcwkwm3CM1g/w426-h320/History%2Bof%2BNatural%2BSalt%2BMines.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/107882929735168806241/albums/5839242144144557793/5839242148336240242?authkey=CLyTrLaJksuvyAE</link><title>history of yoga 
You may be looking interested to search for history of yoga, then just clixk on to this topmost health website and search for information in Yoga you want to gain. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-auartpYKMxo/UQkny9kSBnI/AAAAAAAAAFE/QHY_4QN_7AQ/w426-h328/dhyan.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7134-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/history%20of%20yoga/photos/105720822198691699633/albums/5872602386601299729/5872602388693010178?authkey=CIiS3oayztbJQA</link><title>History Of Yoga: 
The word yoga is Sanskrit for Yoke, or union. In the practice of yoga, we seek to create union between the mind and body. Yoga is the perfect example of holistic health because of this combination of mind and body. It is a systematic practice of physical exercise, breath control, relaxation, diet control, and positive thinking and meditation aimed at developing harmony in the body, mind, and environment. 

The eight limbs by Pathanjali are as follows: 
Yama: rules for successful living in society 
Niyama: techniques for managing and purifying self 
Asaana: posture techniques for physical and mental balance (what most people think of as yoga) 
Pranayama: breathing techniques for physical and mental balance 
Pratihara: techniques for detaching the mind from the senses for mental balance and calm 
Dharana: concentration techniques for mental balance and calm 
Dhyana: meditation techniques for mental balance and calm 
Samadhi: ultimate advanced meditation techniques and psychic procedures attained after regular practice for universal consciousness 
http://goo.gl/C9LTx﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7134_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-k8r8aQcMLa4/UX-swhUoRwI/AAAAAAAAArU/z4mid030cM8/w426-h240/Yoga.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>