<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:09:37" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5835144377378076369/5835144384814328370?authkey=CJDM-46JopT3CA&amp;sqi=114435503478132620253&amp;sqsi=a66eba73-90b9-4685-848f-83b25b96a1e0</link><title>Lance Armstrong’s Oprah Interview - A Hung Jury So what do people in Austin think of Lance now? The answer, of course, is that it’s complicated. 
http://www.bicycling.com/news/featured-stories/hung-jury 

The day after Lance Armstrong told Oprah Winfrey he used performance-enhancing drugs, I was on my way to the grocery store when a cycling friend forwarded me a story from Esquire, about Lance and Austin. The piece said the memorabilia decking the walls of the 24 Hour Fitness, where the author plays basketball, is now gone. 
While eating a bagel the following morning I listened to the award-winning, Austin-based NPR correspondent John Burnett reporting from Mellow Johnny’s. This isn’t just any bike shop, Burnett said; this one has a $14,000 carbon fiber bike. The shop's GM, Craig Staley conceded that, yes, Lance’s admission may affect T-shirt sales. 
A few hours later, I had coffee with a writer from the Sunday magazine of the Telegraph, a United Kingdom-based newspaper, who was seeking insight for a Lance-and-Austin piece. We chatted for an hour and as I said goodbye, he told me The London Times was in town doing a story as well. They both got scooped by the U.K.’s Independent, which ran a Lance and Austin piece on Saturday, that seemed to pull material from my own story, for Bicycling in 2009, called “The Local Lance.” (Oh yeah, the Guardian did a story too. Apparently, Brits love a scandal.) 
As the sun set, I played a round of disc golf with a friend who rides for the Livestrong development team and winters in Austin. It’s a shit-show out there, we agreed. He was grabbing a mid-ride coffee with a teammate two hours outside of town when a woman sitting at a nearby table approached them. Her husband was looking for sources to comment on Armstrong. Would they do an interview? They’re 21-year-old kids sponsored by the cancer foundation Lance founded. They declined. 
As Austinites went to work, rode their bikes, ate, everyone kept asking: What do you think of Lance? How do you like him now? Are you done with him, or will you still welcome him back? But just like with Lance himself, the answers are complicated. 
I have friends who vacation with Lance in Hawaii, and others whose pro-racing careers never fully blossomed largely because of the doping culture Lance helped perpetuate. I have friends in Austin who defend Lance because a loved one was stricken with cancer and received invaluable support from Livestrong. I have other friends, on Facebook, who call them apologists. 
I know people who know people who know a waitress or a bartender who claims Lance was an asshole at their establishment. I know other people who say Lance was pleasant and charming when he met them, and did you know he gave $100 gift cards to one of Austin’s chicest restaurants to every employee of Mellow Johnny’s, even the part-timers? When Lance randomly showed up on the Tuesday night group ride, we all thought it was pretty cool. (He didn’t contest the finish, we joked, because he knew he would lose.) But I don’t know how we would feel if he showed up now. 
I’ve heard some people say we should rename the $3.4-million dollar crosstown Lance Armstrong Bikeway—after all, Lance didn’t donate a penny to that project. I’ve heard other others say that Lance lending his name and official endorsement was enough, and that we can’t deny that Austin’s efforts to become more bike friendly have benefited from his fame. 
I’ve benefited, too. As a clean competitive cyclist, I hate dopers. But like every writer who’s covered Lance, I profited from the story. A decade ago, when I was 22, after making the breakaway with Lance in an early-season Austin race, I got invited to join him on a long group ride through the hills west of town. He asked me what I was studying. Journalism, I told him. That’s too bad, he said. Why? I asked. Journalists make a career out of tearing people down, Lance explained to me. 

Read More: http://www.bicycling.com/news/featured-stories/hung-jury 

#USADA   #Armstrong   #Oprah  ﻿

Meer lezen (68 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-uwtEwESCK7o/UPqY5u35KjI/AAAAAAABFB8/q1ZxEbK1FMA/w426-h306/ian-dille-lance-armstrong.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/100175498851595503678/albums/5833672033246040769/5833672038299524194?authkey=CMmZhs-1gsyCYw</link><title>Oprah Says Lance Armstrong 'Did Not Come Clean In The Manner' She Expected 

Oprah Winfrey has said Lance Armstrong did "not come clean in the manner I had expected" in their interview about the disgraced cyclist's doping history. http://huff.to/TXT7gF 

Armstrong sat down for an interview with Winfrey after a "tearful" confession to workers at the Livestrong Foundation he co-founded, where he is believed to have admitted to lying about his use of performance-enhancing drugs. 

"I think the entire interview was difficult for Lance Armstrong," Oprah told CBS This Morning. 

“Emotional doesn't begin to describe the intensity or difficulty Lance experienced during the interview. He brought it." 

Does Armstrong deserve our sympathy for a "difficult" interview? 

COMMENT for yes, +1 if you think he's simply a cheat...﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4i2sA9jhgLQ/UPVdz4r43GI/AAAAAAAABR4/uS_4HSVQX8o/w426-h237/photo-4.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/100175498851595503678/albums/5835151701611273345/5835151700617182050?authkey=CI3owfGN9_vyfA</link><title>Lance Armstrong Oprah Interview: Cyclist Says Lifetime 'Death Sentence' Undeserved 

By +Samuel Luckhurst 

Lance Armstrong told Oprah Winfrey he did not deserve the life ban "death sentence" imposed on him by the United States Anti-Doping Agency. 

In the second part of his interview in which he finally admitted to doping during his cycling career, the 41-year-old complained his penalty was harsh. 

"I got a death penalty and [other cyclists] got six months. Do I deserve this? I deserve to be punished but I’m not sure I deserve a death penalty." 

Read the full article here - http://huff.to/107MFmq 

Should Armstrong's lifetime ban be upheld? Thoughts in the COMMENTS below...﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-AQL82kb20iI/UPqfjkXNu2I/AAAAAAAABnQ/unW9M2BfA3o/w426-h257/PA-15572050.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/111460372243244520161/albums/5831497910675295745/5831497911332870594?authkey=CODj5LqFyaT5Ag</link><title>We've got some excellent Lance Armstrong Oprah specials on offer today. He's 4/9 to cry and 20/1 to jump up and down on the sofa... 

You can also have a punt on the number of times doping is said and the total number of times Armstrong says sorry. 

Get involved here: http://bit.ly/Sk12GL﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4XAgtiSwUfM/UO2kdCltmcI/AAAAAAAAAVM/mq4FcSYwiFk/w426-h284/Lance%2BArmstrong.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5834244690381442305/5834244693283006146?authkey=CPqi-ILatoCTIA</link><title>Oprah's interview of Lance Armstrong "LIVE" online 
http://www.oprah.com/own-oprahs-next-chapter/Lance-Armstrong-on-Oprahs-Next-Chapter 

\- Video: Oprah is interviewed on CBS about her Armstrong interview ("The biggest interview I've ever done.")  (CBS, 12:34) - http://www.cyclingfans.com/node/6788 

\- Oprah Winfrey's interview of Lance Armstrong, taped on Monday, is now scheduled to air over two nights due to the length of the interview (2.5+ hours) and a desire to broadcast as much of the interview as possible.  Armstrong has reportedly admitted to doping throughout his career and Winfrey has said she and her team were "mesmerized" by some of Armstrong's answers to her questions. (CBS/Washington Post)  There have been separate reports that Armstrong may testify against cycling officials alleged to have been complicit in the doping or cover-ups. (NY Times)  It would seem unlikely that Armstrong would get into much detail on that in the Oprah interview but we'll see. Part 1 of "Oprah and Lance Armstrong: The Worldwide Exclusive" will air Thursday, January 17 with Part 2 on Friday, January 18.  The interview will be broadcast on the OWN Network (Oprah Winfrey Network) and also streamed online worldwide each day at 9pm ET (3:00am CET).  If the interview is available On Demand after the broadcasts, I will post those here as well for you to watch at your leisure.  More info and a brief video teaser here. 

"Live" online streaming: Oprah and Lance Armstrong: The Worldwide Exclusive: 
Thursday, January 17 and Friday, January 18 
9:00pm ET (3:00am CET) 

oprah.com 
(Thursday and Friday at 9:00pm ET) 
(3:00am CET) 

#USADA   #Armstrong  ﻿

Meer lezen (33 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-c2HLcN46v94/UPdmoyvXZsI/AAAAAAABEvI/Pu5bw1OorJY/w426-h319/2005_dauphine_libere_lance_armstrong_discovery_channel_sallanches.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/105986449921389641226/albums/5834601855510703169/5834601855988565266?authkey=CKnGp8rby6iinQE</link><title>Get all the juicy details from the Lance Armstrong Oprah interview and visit our live coverage here. http://natpo.st/WbZMlY﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-jGL2Vo2mhso/UPireZgIhRI/AAAAAAAAT-I/_9jSBMzYFv0/w426-h319/1o3i8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/108776145893503034117/albums/5823271416475310865/5834788772274655666?authkey=CNKF7aHdwPn_hgE</link><title>Lance Armstrong Admits To Doping In Oprah Winfrey Interview | Photo- http://getmybuzzup.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/lance-and-oprah-528x350.jpg- 
Lance Armstrong Admits To Doping In Oprah Winfrey Interview 
Via NYDailyNews 
After more than a decade of angry denials and baseless lawsuits, Lance Armstrong finally acknowledged that performance-enhancing drugs fueled his ride to seven Tour de France victories, telling Oprah Winfrey in a much anticipated interview that he used EPO, testosterone, human growth hormone and other banned substances during his career. 
But the disgraced cyclist challenged some of the charges levied in the explosive U.S. Anti-Doping Agency report that was released in October, and his guarded and unpersuasive performance is unlikely to convince officials to rescind his lifetime ban from sports. 
Armstrong denied he was a drug kingpin and claimed he stopped doping in 2005 and competed clean in 2009 and 2010, after his comeback. He tried to paint himself as just another rider who was forced to use PEDs in order to compete in a grueling and drug-soaked sport. 
“I didn’t invent the culture, but I didn’t try to stop the culture, and that’s my mistake, and that’s what I have to be sorry for, and that’s what something and the sport is now paying the price because of that,” he added. “So I am sorry for that. I don’t think — I didn’t have access to anything else that nobody else did.” 
The U.S. Anti-Doping Agency had this to say about Lance’s confession: 
“Tonight, Lance Armstrong finally acknowledged that his cycling career was built on a powerful combination of doping and deceit,” USADA chief executive officer Travis Tygart said. “His admission that he doped throughout his career is a small step in the right direction. But if he is sincere in his desire to correct his past mistakes, he will testify under oath about the full extent of his doping activities.” 
Says Lance’s LIVESTRONG Foundation: 
“We at the LIVESTRONG Foundation are disappointed by the news that Lance Armstrong misled people during and after his cycling career, including us.” 
As for Lance and his view on his questionable behavior: 
“I had this exercise because I kept hearing I’m a drug cheat. I’m a cheat. I’m a cheater,” Armstrong said. “And I went in and just looked up the definition of cheat. . . . And the definition of cheat is to gain an advantage on a rival or foe that they don’t have. I didn’t view it that way. I viewed it as a level playing field.” 
Related articles 

Come Clean: Shady Lance Armstrong Keeps It Funky With Oprah About Doping And PEDs! 
Lance Armstrong Interview: Cyclist Confesses Doping To Oprah 
Lance Armstrong admits to doping in Oprah interview 
Armstrong admits doping: ‘I’m a flawed character’ 

by 
\- http://gd.is/4f4m44﻿

Meer lezen (52 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/--NkO1ML3T6k/UPlVeW7eUbI/AAAAAAAACzs/RWkqhUI8j9A/w426-h282/lance-and-oprah.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5831782161466290593/5831782167676432386?authkey=CJjd-ruXoMnpbA</link><title>Not a Comfy Couch Lance Armstrong’s appearance on Oprah could be must-see TV. Or it could be the last time we ever listen to him. 
By Joe Lindsey 

We all knew this day might come. 

Ever since Lance Armstrong got named as the subject of a federal criminal investigation, the possibility has lain tantalizingly in the distance that not only might Armstrong himself someday confess, but that his mea culpa would take place where all great secular Sacraments of Penance do: Oprah’s couch. 
It’s such a cliche that the talented duo at NY Velocity envisioned a Lance-couch appearance in As the Toto Turns. Back in May of 2011, that is (Oprah first appeared in Toto in 2008). 
So when Oprah’s PR machine churned out a press release Tuesday night that Armstrong would do his first interview since being stripped of his seven Tour de France titles, it immediately was the talk of the cycling world. Technically, the interview will be/was shot at Armstrong’s Austin home, but metaphorically, it’s still Oprah’s couch. 
“Oprah Winfrey will speak exclusively with Lance Armstrong in his first no-holds-barred interview,” read the first line of the press release, before going on to detail that subjects would include “the alleged doping scandal, years of accusations of cheating and charges of lying about using…drugs throughout his storied cycling career.” 
The use of “alleged doping scandal” should give you pause. While Armstrong was never charged in the criminal case, he has been banned for life in endurance sports and stripped of his titles in a legal proceeding built on 1,000 pages of evidence that yielded a verdict recognized by every relevant governing body in Olympic sports. We can drop the “alleged” bit now. 
But past that bit, which I’m sure the good legal team at OWN (or Lance) insisted on, is the troubling point that the show on which Armstrong will appear—”The Next Chapter“—is not exactly known for hard-hitting journalism. Some past guests include such controversial newsmakers as Fergie, Olympic gymnast Gabby Douglas, and the Biebs, of course. 
Also, this is not Oprah’s first disgraced-athlete rodeo. In 2009, she interviewed Marion Jones after her release from prison. Jones tearfully admitted in 2007 that she’d (unknowingly) used drugs. She repeated the claim to Oprah, who only lightly challenged it. If that’s any kind of blueprint for how Armstrong’s interview will go, that’s troubling. 

Read More: http://bicycling.com/blogs/boulderreport/2013/01/09/not-a-comfy-couch/ 

#USADA   #Armstrong   #USPS  ﻿

Meer lezen (45 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-B4TKm8EQ3aw/UO6m-7_PsAI/AAAAAAABEK4/3aJ4rnnJw6w/w426-h240/Lance%2BArmstrong%2BOprah%2BWinfrey%2BOprah%2527s%2BNext%2BChapter%2BSouth%2BAfrica.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/112352920206354603958/albums/5832903678928105793/5832903681276667986?authkey=CI2i2OaX3YDU8AE</link><title>10 Questions for Lance Armstrong: will Oprah dare to ask them? 
in case you lived under a rock: Oprah Winfrey will interview Lance Armstrong who has promised to answer all questions. 

Sunday Times Journalist and long-time critic of Lance Armstrong, David Walsh, has written an open letter to Oprah Winfrey, which includes ten questions for the disgraced cyclist. 

Earlier today on Twitter, Walsh indicated Oprah’s producer had spoken to him about the show, in which Armstrong will be interviewed by Oprah. 

And the journalist has since been moved to write the talkshow host a letter, containing questions directed at the American cyclist, which include: “Did you sue The Sunday Times to shut us up?” and “Do you regret how you treated Betsy Andreu, your former masseuse Emma O’Reilly and Greg LeMond?”. 

The news comes after reports suggested that Armstrong was set to admit to doping during the upcoming interview. Lance himself just tweeted: "I told her (Winfrey) to go wherever she wants and I'll answer the questions directly, honestly and candidly. That's all I can say" 

What would your question for Lance be?﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_09_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-WY7q8fEiDY0/UPKi_nuQaFI/AAAAAAAAYxc/pOAX8U605ok/w426-h443/david-walsh-4-481x500%255B1%255D.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7138-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lance%20armstrong%20oprah/photos/114875588593485801330/albums/5834819574206160097/5834819574260494354</link><title>Oprah's expensive mistake with the Lance Armstrong interview 

Oprah livestreamed her interview with Lance Armstrong at the same time it aired on her network, OWN. 

A certified #SocialTV win for OWN, right? Not so fast. 

The livestream was needlessly hindered by OWN's poor choice in live video players. 

Now, what if the network used a modern live stream tool, like Google+ Hangouts? Not only is the service free, and best of class, but here are 3 unique opportunities OWN missed out on: 

1\. Embed Everwhere. The Google+ Hangout player is essentially a YouTube player. That means a Hangout will embed and play anywhere a YouTube video will. 

Oprah's audience could have viewed the streaming video inside of a tweet, without having to click away. Or they could have viewed it on their mobile phones, live while on the go. 

OWN Ambassadors could have received the embed early and streamed the interview from their own blogs and social media profiles. 

The tool OWN used needs a special app to play on Facebook. A Hangout would have played just like a regular YouTube video would. 

And of course the video would have been made available on YouTube. Even if OWN does not want the content on YouTube in the long term, users are sure to search there anyway. Why not have an official presence on the largest video site in the world and the second largest search engine? 

#2 Real Time Reaction. The player OWN used allowed Facebook comments during the livestream. Most players can do that. With a Hangout OWN could have hosted a post-show video chat with to broadcast viewers' initial reactions. 

They could have gone the pro route and invited sports and legal pundits to weigh in. 

Our they could have featured fans of Lance to get the raw audience reaction. 

Either way, a video Hangout would have been a rich way to extend the conversation around the interview. 

#3. Better than free. I mentioned already that using a Google+ Hangout is free, while I'm sure the player OWN used cost thousands in fees. But for Oprah's network, a high profile Hangout like the Lance Armstrong interview could have been better than free. Google would have loved to participate in promotion of the event, since it would have meant a landmark use of their premier tool. 

Google used the weight of their homepage to promote a National Geographic Hangout, and Redbull's Space Jump benefited from heavy promotion on YouTube. I participated in a Hangout with Steven Spielberg that was simulcast on a huge Times Square billboard, thanks to Google. 

A creative use of Hangouts could have meant huge mounts of positive coverage in the tech and media press. The value of the earned media, combined with the elevated visibility from Google would have easily been valued in the 7 figure range. 

__ 

The Oprah Show was a pioneer in using Skype on television. Without their envelope pushing use of that tech, the producers of the show that I worked for would not have allowed me to experiment with #SocialTV as much as I did. I owe Oprah. 

Oprah's team could lead the television pack again if they duplicated their wise decision to use Skype, and upgraded their live stream player to Google+ Hangouts. 

(Want more #SocialTV analysis? Join the Drive Tune-In newsletter - http://drivetunein.com )﻿

Meer lezen (76 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7138_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-OK1WuQtSQRs/UPlxfRRK8BI/AAAAAAAAMjk/FMRrCWc2nQ4/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>