<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:23:23" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/113811492775425960680/albums/5819725566935594465/5819725566813157794?authkey=CLPf-6Tv9N6pOA</link><title>Brain research could play growing role in criminal justice system but must be used with caution. 

Neuroscientists seek to understand how the brain underpins our behaviour, thoughts and feelings. The law is also, of course, concerned with human behaviour, albeit for rather different reasons, so have the remarkable advances in neuroscientific research in the past 25 years made neuroscience increasingly relevant to the law? Legal interest in neuroscience is evident from several special issues of law reviews, and from the publication of such books as Michael Freeman’s Law and Neuroscience (OUP). In the US, a number of universities teach courses on the interface between neuroscience and the law, and the McArthur Foundation has invested several million dollars to fund research in this area. In the UK, the Royal Society has just published a report entitled Neuroscience and the Law as part of its ‘Brain Waves’ project. 

Much of this interest has focused on the criminal justice system – and the Royal Society’s report also emphasized criminal law. But neuroscience may also prove relevant to civil law – for example to issues of capacity and disability. It is not impossible that advances in functional brain imaging may, in the not too distant future, help to determine the level of pain someone is experiencing as a result of an injury. 

Within the criminal justice system, some have argued that neuroscientific research has already cast doubt on the idea of free will, and must therefore raise questions about the legitimacy of punishing people for actions over which they had no control. This might impact on a retributivist theory of punishment – but less so if punishment is justified on utilitarian or deterrent grounds. Nevertheless, in the US there has been a steady increase over the past few years in the number of cases where defense attorneys have sought to introduce neuroscientific (or genetic) evidence. Is ‘My brain (or my genes) made me do it’ a legitimate defense in a criminal trial? 

One issue where neuroscientific evidence might be relevant is the age of criminal responsibility. In England and Wales it is 10 – significantly lower than in most other European countries or than in many states of the US. Brain imaging studies have shown that the brain continues to develop throughout adolescence, with the prefrontal cortex, implicated in cognition, decision making and impulse control, not reaching maturity until the age of 20 or so. Such studies have also shown that there are huge individual differences in the rate of maturation of the brain. Does this imply that 10-year-olds should not be held fully responsible for their actions when they break the law? At the very least, it lends weight to the argument that English lawmakers need to show just why the age of criminal responsibility should be lower here than in other countries. 

It is essential, however, to sound a note of caution. Brain imaging studies have shown, for example, that there are often differences between the brains of people categorized as psychopaths or with anti-social personality disorder (who are disproportionately likely to commit violent crimes) and the more law abiding majority. Such differences have been found in the amygdala and orbitofrontal cortex and the connections between the two, but it needs to be stressed that these are average differences only – here as elsewhere differences within groups are often greater than any average difference between groups. Behavioural genetic studies have shown that men with the L allele of the MAOA gene and a history of childhood abuse are more likely to behave violently when adult. Does this really mean that the findings of a brain scan or of genetic screening should serve to reduce a convicted criminal’s sentence on the grounds that he could not help doing what he did? If psychopaths think, feel and behave differently from others, then of course these differences will be reflected in their brains. That is hardly sufficient to establish that the atypical nature of their brain was the inevitable cause of their criminal behavior. Not all men with the MAOA-L gene and a history of childhood abuse end up as violent criminals: in one large study, fewer than one third of such men had been convicted of a violent crime by the age of 26. 

Rather than such evidence serving to reduce a convicted criminal’s sentence, one could argue that if neuroscientific or genetic evidence has established that certain people are more likely than others to commit crimes, then it might be used to increase their sentence – or in decisions about release from prison or parole. Such decisions inevitably involve assessing the risk of reoffending, and risk assessment is a notoriously imprecise enterprise. It is simply not possible to predict with perfect accuracy that one prisoner will reoffend within a year of release from prison, and another will not. Unsurprisingly, those who have to make these decisions err on the side of caution: the 2003 Criminal Justice Act introduced the concept of indeterminate sentence for public protection, which allowed a judge not only to set a minimum prison sentence but also to require defendants to satisfy the authorities that they would not pose any threat if released at the end of this sentence. These measures were initially designed to detain a very small number of exceptionally dangerous criminals, but by March 2011 there were 6,550 people in prison under the terms of these provisions. Even if, as Ken Clarke has recently announced, these indeterminate sentences are abolished, the problem of risk assessment (in for example parole decisions) will not go away. It seems at least possible that neuroscientific or genetic evidence might be able to reduce the risk of getting these decisions wrong. 

The law is concerned to establish whether people are telling the truth. Is the witness who claims to have seen the defendant at the scene of the crime telling the truth? Is the defendant who protests his innocence in fact guilty? The polygraph, it is widely recognized, is not reliable enough to be used in a court of law. Might functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI), which can detect local changes in brain activity when people perform a particular task, do a better job? Several experiments have indeed shown differences in activity in certain regions of the brain, associated with cognitive effort and deciding between alternative responses, when students are asked to answer some questions truthfully and others with a lie. Emboldened by this success, two American scientists have set up commercial fMRI lie detector companies, Cephos and NoLieMRI. Neither has yet succeeded in persuading a court to accept their evidence – and there are good reasons to remain skeptical. At best, fMRI might sometimes be able to detect a difference between a witness who is telling the truth and another who deliberately lies. But there is good experimental evidence to suggest that it will not distinguish between a reliable witness and one who is honestly mistaken. By the same token it seems probable that a defendant who, under persistent questioning, has repeatedly protested his innocence might end up believing he is telling the truth even if he is not. Conversely, there is also evidence that if people are instructed to use countermeasures they can fool the brain imaging machine when lying. 

The law has a good record of taking science on board – the most obvious recent example being the use of DNA testing. There is no reason to doubt that it will do the same with neuroscientific evidence, and equally good reason to believe that neuroscience will provide some important revelations about human behaviour within the foreseeable future. But it is sensible, if boring, to end on a note of caution. It is all too easy to believe that the beautifully coloured images of the brain produced by fMRI show us the secrets of someone’s thoughts. They do not, and at present there are strict limits to what neuroscience can tell the law. That may change, but at this point, our priority needs to be to make sure that advances that may affect the law are communicated properly to legal professionals so that when it becomes appropriate, neuroscience is used in court to the benefit of all involved. 

By Professor Nicholas Mackintosh FRS, Department of Experimental Psychology at the University of Cambridge 

Professor Nicholas Mackintosh FRS is professor emeritus in the Department of Experimental Psychology at the University of Cambridge and chair of the working group that wrote the Royal Society’s report Brain Waves Module 4: Neuroscience and the Law. 

From: http://www.barristermagazine.com/article-listing/current-issue/brain-research-could-play-growing-role-in-criminal-justice-system-but-must-be-used-with-caution.html﻿

Meer lezen (145 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Q19f79Hb8U0/UMPRkZwoOaI/AAAAAAAAA7E/mkxYEVSX2fw/s426/Brain.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/102615066845810381812/albums/6005306027794299457/6005306032209477218</link><title>TEACHING ENGLISH IN GREECE 

jobs@anglo-hellenic.com 

We have vacancies for TEFL qualified teachers in a variety of locations in Greece for positions starting in September. Class sizes are small, with an average of 6 - 10 students in each class. Students are aged 10 – 17, at all levels from elementary to proficiency. Classes last for one or sometimes two hours, and for the older pupils there is a strong orientation towards exams such as the Cambridge FCE and CPE. Most classes have lessons fora total of three or four hours per week, so you will be teaching several different classes at all levels from elementary to proficiency. 

Teaching hours are 4 - 9 pm Monday to Friday. In addition to the hours spent teaching, you will also have to spend the proportionate amount of time planning lessons and correcting written work, making up a total workload of around 40 hours per week. You won't need to create your own materials, as each class will be working with a course book that provides all the activities and exercises for the lessons. The bulk of your preparation will consist of studying the materials in the course book and the accompanying teacher's guide, and planning how to do the lesson according to the needs of each group of students. 

This is a fixed term contract, but can be renewed from September to June each year. 

Qualifications: 

Applicants must have a degree (in any discipline), a TEFL certificate and speak English as their first language. Experience is not required. For citizens of the UK, Ireland or any other EU country, visas are not required. 

Remuneration: 

The salary is 813 euros per month gross, and free furnished accommodation is provided. 

To apply: 
Contact us via email at the address given on the job heading. 

To see other job postings, check this page out: http://www.teflcourse.net/tefl-jobs/ 
To see other job postings for Greece, check this page out: http://www.teflcourse.net/tefl-jobs/tefl-jobs-greece/  ﻿

Meer lezen (42 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Sn2zTYmmJtw/U1ciBNFbPmI/AAAAAAAAA_U/C8Xq72lQ7NY/w426-h320/Greece%2BAPR%2B14.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/107428266331359263265/albums/5715837772817420913/5715837773062405986</link><title>Can Economists Improve the Human Condition? 
By Paul Ormerod , 26 Oct 2009 
“Do you need math to study economics at university?” is a question I often get asked. Here is a cautionary tale for anyone who still has illusions about the relationship between the two disciplines. A friend of mine teaches economics at Cambridge, England. Recently she had a first year student who was very good indeed at math. So much so that he complained there wasn’t enough of it in his course. For his second year, he was sent on an exchange to the other Cambridge: the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Emails of an increasingly desperate nature began to whiz back to my friend across the Atlantic. The final one said simply: “Help! Please let me back home. There isn’t any economics in this course. It’s all math.” 

Things are not quite so bad in most places, but math is becoming increasingly pervasive in economics. Just for the record, at the right time among consenting adults, I too use math. There are both good and bad reasons for employing it in the service of economics. So far mainly the bad ones have prevailed. 

It wouldn’t matter much if policy makers didn’t take economics so seriously. Hardly anyone bothers about some of the lunacies in literary theory, for example. But economics matters and, at the frontiers of the discipline, a subtle but profound shift is taking place. Economics is starting to become more realistic, more rooted in institutions, in history, in the real world and, as a result, more useful. 

That is, in fact, how economics started off in the first place. Only then it wasn’t called “economics” but “political economy,” symbolizing the fact that economies do not exist independently of political systems and institutions. 

Economics is starting to become more realistic, more rooted in institutions, in history, in the real world and, as a result, more useful 
Adam Smith single-handedly founded the discipline of economics over 200 years ago, and his influence is profound even today. Yet his seminal book The Wealth of Nations contains no equations at all. Instead Smith uses carefully constructed arguments supported by a wealth of historical evidence. English stockbroker David Ricardo, author of On the Principles of Political Economy and Taxation (1817), is less well known – but the standard economic theory of trade is still based on his work. More than a century later, two figures from opposite ends of the political spectrum made wide-reaching contributions to economics. John Maynard Keynes was trained as a mathematician at Cambridge, switching later to economics. Friedrich Hayek, the intellectual inspiration for Thatcherism, had deep insights in psychology as well as in economics. Ricardo, Keynes, Hayek and a host of other key figures in economics studiously avoided math. Instead they used thoughtful arguments backed up by evidence. 

So how has math come to be so pervasive in economics, when so much was achieved without it? The worst reason is that the use of math makes economists feel like they are proper scientists. They suffer from deep “physics envy.” Physicists have to use math. (Try doing quantum physics in words.) And they are real scientists, who really have explained how lots of things really do work. So if we use math, that makes us real scientists, doesn’t it? Well, the logical error in this last sentence is pretty obvious. But it doesn’t stop the inner glow of satisfaction that most economists feel when they cover the page in mathematical symbols. 

So how has math come to be so pervasive in economics, when so much was achieved without it? 
There is a more serious and more damaging reason why math, or at least a particular kind of math, is used in economics. This is inextricably linked with the concept of “economic man.” Economics is essentially a theory about how individuals behave. And the standard theory not only assumes that individuals are self-interested, but that they behave like some sort of supercomputer – always gathering every bit of information relevant to a decision. These individuals then make the best possible decision out of all available options. Not just a good decision, but the very best. Or, as economists like to say, optimal. 

There is a whole branch of math devoted to optimal solutions: differential calculus. It is the ideal tool for a theory stating that individuals behave in a way optimal for them, given their tastes and preferences. So, for example, if you eat junk food and weigh 300 pounds as a result, or if you drink heavily and destroy your liver, or if you smoke and get cancer, hey, that’s your choice. You must have been making what you believed to be the best possible lifestyle choice for you, and calculus can prove it! 

This is still the basis for a lot of the economics taught in university. Yet, paradoxically, it has been precisely the use of math within economics that has undermined this view of the world. It’s also a reason why the subject is moving on dramatically. 

Math can be very useful in economics provided that we think of it simply as one tool among many. It is a tool that can assist us in logical thinking. It’s like another language – it can help us find our way around. 

Math can be very useful in economics provided that we think of it simply as one tool among many. 
Math has helped economists understand the implications of the economic man theory of behavior. After more than a century of research, economists determined that the theory is a marvelous intellectual construct, but a completely empty box. It has no testable implications. When economists say “demand curves slope downwards” or “people are paid what they are worth,” they have no theoretical basis for making these assertions. We cannot logically deduce from the theory of economic man behavior that either of these statements, both widely used by economists, are true. 

Pioneers like the 2001 Nobel laureates George Akerlof and Joseph Stiglitz moved the subject on in the 1970s. They realized something else was needed, so they abandoned the idea that people have perfect information when they make decisions. They developed the concept of “bounded rationality”: the idea that though we may try to make the best decision, we may not succeed due to a lack of vital information. So in a world of bound rationality, people who binge on junk food or smoke heavily are not necessarily seen as making the best possible decision for themselves. The work of Akerlof and Stiglitz was a huge step forward in making economics more realistic. 

Daniel Kahneman and Vernon Smith, the 2002 Nobel winners, made even bigger strides with their work. They actually went out into the world and conducted experiments to see how people really do behave. Observing and deducing just like real scientists! And they found that most of the time people don’t behave like the economic man at all. In his Nobel lecture, Kahneman stated: “The central characteristic of agents [people] is not that they reason poorly, but that they often act intuitively. And the behavior of these agents is not guided by what they are able to compute, but by what they happen to see at a given moment.” 

In other words, the whole concept of a rational, calculating economic man is being abandoned completely. The economic man theory postulates that people have all the relevant information to make the best possible decision. In this new approach people have – at best – imperfect information ... they stumble along, trying to make reasonable decisions, sometimes succeeding but often failing. 

“An economist who is only an economist cannot be a good economist.” 
The rules of behavior people use depend on the specific time and place. When the Soviet Union fell, for example, the policies forced on Soviet markets – based upon economic man – were disastrous. They led to theft and asset stripping on a stupendous scale and a massive fall in living standards. The policies failed to account for the fact that Russia and the other nations of the Soviet Union had little or no experience of how markets worked. Above all, they failed to take into account that in the West there are very few pure “free markets” – institutions, law, custom and practice all mediate the workings of markets. An outdated view of the world forced these tired policies on the Russians. 

The new approaches that have developed to replace the economic man, perhaps surprisingly, make economics much harder. Instead of just manipulating some equations, we have to think hard about what the relevant rules of behavior are in any particular context. And we have to restore the importance of institutions and history. In short, we have to restore the idea of political economy in a totally modern guise. Hayek is mistrusted by many, but there is a profound truth in his remark: “An economist who is only an economist cannot be a good economist.” 

All this makes economics more humble. Instead of claiming a completely general theory of behavior – applying to all people at all times in all places – economics is now much less grandiose. But ultimately, these changes will serve to make the discipline more realistic ... and potentially more powerful as a force for helping to understand and improve the human condition. 

Paul Ormerod studied economics at Cambridge University and did a postgraduate degree at Oxford. He is the author of The Death of Economics, Butterfly Economics and Why Most Things Fail. Download some chapters from his website, www.paulormerod.com. 

the creative destruction of neoclassical economics 
Deep in a recession and with scary ecological scenarios looming, now may be the ripest moment we’ll ever have to power-shift global capitalism onto a new path. Adbusters #85 asks economics students around the world to join the fight to revamp Econ 101 curriculums and challenge the endemic myopia of their tenured neoclassical profs. Go to KICKITOVER.ORG, read a few texts, download the Kick it Over Manifesto (and other posters) and whack them up in the corridors of your campus. Make sure your university is at the forefront of the paradigm shift from neoclassical to ecological economics now underway. 

http://www.adbusters.org/magazine/85/can-economists-improve-human-condition.html﻿

Meer lezen (186 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_03_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-R4iwxONkoi0/T1K8K7kk_2I/AAAAAAAAAK4/_KcYEebyr6c/w426-h507/economists3_royalblue_white.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/104181741037321372066/albums/5923168084865640881/5923168083704770162?authkey=CKuR3uDHxKuuRw&amp;sqi=107405100380970813362&amp;sqsi=ced8faf7-feb1-4909-a50f-4fb0a4402262</link><title>Lost in Google land. 

Last evening, while stumbling around Google's Cambridge office, I fell into a meetup of the Boston Security group.  Thinking I'd found my event, I had some pizza and proceeded to enjoy the attention of geeks who had not seen Glass and were totally enthralled with its potential. 

Akshat. the host asked me if I would say a few words to the Group.  After agreeing to speak, I realized I was in the wrong room, made my apologies and joined GDG for more pizza. 

Now, my prime goal last night was to sell the GDG Boston (google developers group) on attending the upcoming Hackathon. 

GDG group was twice the size and full of I/O attendess, Google coders and Googlers.  Not one asked about Glass but Steven the host did offer me a minute to speak about the hack.  I won't get into his forgetting to call me up to the front but it only took me a few minutes of boredom to pack up and move back to the security group where there was lively discourse and extreme interest in Glass. 

This is the #throughglass  photo I took while they focused on my Note 10.1 screencast.  We chatted about Glass in law enforcement, EMT and medicine.  Their topic was Android Security but they start with security news and I don't think there was one in the group wanting to give their finger print to Apple(NSA). 

At least 2 people from the group will be at my Hackathon and I'm sure to be leading a future meetup focused on wearable security. 

Why am I relating this story?  I'm an old time marketing, trade show, cold calling kind of guy.  I believe there are no problems, only opportunities and this mixed up night proves the point. 

We Explorers who embrace the opportunity, are in the unique position of Evangelist for the Glass platform.  Evangelist for Google.  As Evangelists we must be open to every possibility for market penetration, even when it comes from left field.  We and Google have absolutely no idea where Glass will find it's launch pad to stardom therefore we must openly seek any who ask  "what's it like?". 

And we evangelize gladly and without any thought of compensation.  We do it because never in the history of tech has there been such a door opener.  When wearing Glass at a networking event I truly feel like a networking god. 

Use Glass wisely.  Demo it even more wisely and let Glass open doors. 

For an experienced marketing guy, the stacks of business cards, new LinkedIn connection requests and speaking invites are more than enough compensation. ﻿

Meer lezen (49 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-2WMBUf4yg_Q/UjNR_WYnbnI/AAAAAAAAMMQ/WrXI_Dds1JE/w426-h313/20130912_185056_531_1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/114054103325052180233/albums/5820257793346712481/5820257797907224690?authkey=CPWxx9SXxYyS7QE&amp;sqi=107635984107923832068&amp;sqsi=89b6b8ba-e7b8-4663-ada0-7ab11bb03c84</link><title>There isn’t a hat stand in Roger Hunt’s office; but if there was, it would be full. 
Businessman, entrepreneur, Christmas tree grower, sheep farmer, scrap metal dealer and football club supporter . . . the CV is getting longer every year. 
“There’s a joke doing the rounds that the only person busier than me at Christmas is ‘Sion Corn’, old Father Christmas himself,” laughs Hunt. 
Pay a visit to his Christmas tree plantation overlooking the Tywi Valley and just up the road from Y Polyn restaurant and you’ll appreciate it isn’t so much a joke as a statement of fact. 
The joke is told in an accent which reveals his London and East England roots. 
The 60-year-old former chairman of Football League side Cambridge United has travelled a long way to put his new roots down near the National Botanic Gardens. 
“My football links can confuse many people,” said Hunt, who spends much of his spare time helping on the executive committee of Welsh Premier League side Carmarthen Town. 
“I can go to football dinners and it confuses the older generation. Some will mistakenly think I’m the same Roger Hunt who played in the England World Cup winning team of 1966. I wish! 
“We’re obviously two very different people, but it does get a laugh on occasions when people get confused.” 
Born in Folkestone and raised in London, Hunt now considers himself an adopted son of Sir Gar, Carmarthenshire. 
“I love the place and the people and it’s a great part of the world to live and work in.” 
Home for Hunt nowadays is Llwyndu Farm near the ‘Botanic’, a property once owned by the very sporting Williams family, showjumper Alun and brother Wyn, father of Paralympic discus medallist Claire Williams. 
“I’m in the process of renovating the farmhouse, who is another of my ‘projects’. It’s a slow process as there aren’t enough hours in the day, but we are getting there.” 
A short drive away lies Hunt’s Christmas tree plantation at Oaklands, which operates under the name Cymru Christmas Trees. 
The plantation has more than 10,000 Norway Spruce trees, all in different stages of development. 
“I specialise in Norway Spruce as it is a very popular variety, but I also supply other Welsh-grown potted varieties and Nordman trees. 
“Sustainability is key to the business and many of my customers, including some local councils and community organisations, return year after year. I reckon I plant at least a 1000 trees every year. The spotlight is very much on this being a sustainable crop. 
“If people want to return trees to me after Christmas, then they can do so for shredding. Over at Cwm Environmental in Nantycaws, they also provide a very good shredding service and throw in a free bag of compost if you recycle your tree with them.” 
Hunt is keen to preach the environmental message. Buying local is very important to Carmarthenshire and we should all do our bit to keep the carbon footprint down and run good sustainable businesses. 
Environmental matters are also at the heart of Hunt’s other business, Robinson Recycling, a leading South Wales scrap metal merchant, with a depot in Margam near Port Talbot. 
“We are one of the leading buyers of aluminium cans in South West Wales and we deal in all grades of ferrous of non-ferrous scrap metal. 
Hunt declared: I have always been focussed on recycling - even before it started to get the label ‘a green issue’. I think we should all be far more sustainable than we are. Recycling must be on the top of everyone’s agenda.” 
One of Hunt’s other hats is that of a sheep farmer. “We keep some Herdwick (Cumbrian) sheep on the farm, but the main flock is made up of Shropshire sheep,” he said. 
“The Shropshire sheep are a neat fit with the Christmas tree business as they are the only breed which can graze in and around Christmas trees. They are well fed and they also help to maintain the Christmas tree plantation. 
“The sheep can be a 24-hour job, especially during the lambing season between January and March. Sadly, that means I do miss out on one of the other passions of my life, football.” 
Hunt was running a scrap metal businesses in Cambridgeshire when he first joined Cambridge United in April, 1990. 
“Just six weeks later I was sat in the Royal Box at Wembley, watching Cambridge United bear Chesterfield 1-0 in the first ever play-off final at Wembley. Dion Dublin scored the winning goal. You can’t get much better than that and you can’t buy that sort of experience.” 
Hunt is philosophical about the rest of his Cambridge United experience. The club went into decline both on and off the field. Cambridge dropped out of the Football League and then went in administration. 
He reflected: “At about that time, my wife who was from Swansea, suggested moving to West Wales. It was a 500-mile commute to Cambridge to see football matches and attend board meetings, so not easy by any stretch of the imagination.” 
After Hunt finished his association with Cambridge, he was approached by Carmarthen Town President Jeff Thomas to help the Welsh Premier League side. 
“I have plenty of experience of the rough and tumble world of running a Football League club, so I try to bring some of that experience to bear in helping Carmarthen Town. 
“The club is well run by an enthusiastic team of people. Budgets are tight, but Carmarthen Town is a progressive club working very hard to nurture young talent in the community. 
“Football is one of my passions and I think it’s very important in life to care passionately about what you do. I try to carry that through in the different areas of my business life. Carmarthenshire is a great place and I am very fortunate to be running several businesses which bring me great delight.”﻿

Meer lezen (97 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-z64TJ2v6BXY/UMW1oVF1GHI/AAAAAAAAgsY/qzTMOJ8puLM/w426-h568/RogerHunt1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/108002872327122893818/albums/5728328101479595217/5728328097863029234</link><title>Allama Mohammad Iqbal 
The Poet of East 

BRIEF LIFE SKETCH 

Muhammad Iqbal (1877-1938) is one of the preeminent writers of the Indo-Pakistan subcontinent. Indeed, the attention he has received from numerous writers, translators, and critics from Western as well as Islamic countries testifies to his stature as a world literary figure. While his primary reputation is that of a poet, Iqbal has not lacked admirers for his philosophical thought. He has in fact been called “the most serious Muslim philosophical thinker of modem times.” The frequently used appellation of “poet-philosopher” is thus well deserved. The hyphen in the phrase is all-important: Iqbal’s poetry and philosophy do not exist in isolation from each other; they are integrally related, his poetry serving as a vehicle for his thought. Iqbal wrote poetry in Urdu and Persian, and several collections in each language exist. In the following page a life-sketch of Iqbal is followed by a brief treatment of some of the major themes and literary features of his poetry. 

*** 

Iqbal was born in Sialkot, in the present-day province of the Punjab in Pakistan, in 1877. He received his early education in that city, where one of his teachers was Mir Hasan, an accomplished scholar who commanded a knowledge of several Islamic languages. Mir Hasan gave Iqbal a thorough training in the rich Islamic literary tradition. His influence on Iqbal was formative. Many years later (1922), when the English governor of the Punjab proposed to the British Crown that Iqbal be knighted in acknowledgment of his literary accomplishments, Iqbal asked that Mir Hasan also be awarded a title. To the governor’s remark that Mir Hasan had not authored any books, Iqbal responded that he, Iqbal, was the book Mir Hasan had produced. Mir Hasan received the title of Shams al-’Ulama’ (“Sun of Scholars”). 
For higher education Iqbal went to Lahore (1895), where he enrolled in Government College, getting, in 1899, an MA in philosophy; he had already obtained a degree in law (1898). In Lahore, a major center of academic and literary activity, Iqbal soon made a name for himself as a poet. One of the teachers of Government College Iqbal admired most was Sir Thomas Arnold. Arnold, too, had great affection for Iqbal, he helped Iqbal in his career as a teacher and also encouraged him to undertake several research projects. When Arnold returned to England in 1904, Iqbal wrote a touching poem in which he expressed his resolve to follow Arnold to England. The very next year, in fact, Iqbal left for study at Cambridge. His choice of Cambridge was probably dictated by the fact that Cambridge was reputed for the study not only of European philosophy but also of Arabic and Persian. In his three years of stay abroad, Iqbal obtained a BA from Cambridge (1906), qualified as a barrister at London’s Middle Temple (1906), and earned a PhD from Munich University (1908). 
After returning to Lahore in 1908, Iqbal taught philosophy at Government College for a few years. In 1911 he resigned from government service and set up legal practice. Meanwhile he continued to write poetry in Urdu and Persian, Asrar-i Khudi (Persian) was published in 1915. Translated into English as The Secrets of the Self (1920) by Professor Reynold Nicholson of Cambridge, the book introduced Iqbal to the West. Asrar-i Khudi was followed by several other volumes: Rumuz-i Bikhudi (1918), Payam-i Mashriq (1923), Bang-i Dara (1924), Zabur-i ‘Ajam (1927), Javid Namah (1932), Musafir (1936), Zarb-i Kalim (1937), and Armaghan-i Hijaz (1938, posthumously). Iqbal wrote prose also. His doctoral thesis, The Development of Metaphysics in Persia, was published in 1908, and his Reconstruction of Religious Thought in Islam (with a 7th chapter added to the original set of six lectures, first published in 1930), in 1934. Many of Iqbal’s poetical works have been rendered into foreign languages, including English, German, Italian, Russian, Czechoslovakian, Arabic, and Turkish. His works have also spawned a vast amount of critical literature in many languages. 
Although his main interests were scholarly, Iqbal was not unconcerned with the political situation of the, country and the political fortunes of the Muslim community of India. Already in 1908, while in England, he had been chosen as a member of the executive council of the newly established British branch of the Indian Muslim League. In 1931 and 1932 he represented the Muslims of India in the Round Table Conferences held in England to discuss the issue of the political future of India. And in a 1930 lecture Iqbal suggested the creation of a separate homeland for the Muslims of India. Iqbal died (1938) before the creation of Pakistan (1947), but it was his teaching that “spiritually ... has been the chief force behind the creation of Pakistan.” He is the national poet of Pakistan. 

II 
A detailed discussion of the thematic and literary features of Iqbal’s poetry is not be undertaken here. A few general points may, however, be made. 
A reader of Iqbal’s poetry is struck by its sheer thematic variety. Iqbal was deeply interested in the issues that have exercised the best minds of the human race—the issues of the meaning of life, change and constancy, freedom and determinism, survival and progress, the relation between the body and the soul, the conflict between reason and emotion, evil and suffering, the position and role of human beings in the universe—and in his poetry he deals with these and other issues. He had also read widely in history, philosophy, literature, mysticism, and politics, and, again, his catholic interests are reflected in his poetry. 
Iqbal celebrates humanity, in more than one sense. On one level he shows broad acceptance for humanity. In “The Story of Adam”, the protagonist, Adam, plays a variety of roles-those of prophet, thinker, reformer, scientist, inventor, astronomer, martyr, and iconoclast. Adam in this poem is not simply a religious figure belonging to a certain tradition, but represents the whole of humankind. On another level, Iqbal takes pride in being human and has no desire to partake of the godhead of God. To be God is to have concerns and worries that would give one a headache, but to be human is to have that sweet pain called heartache. Humans can hold their heads high in view of their achievements in the world to which they were banished from paradise: if God has made the night, then humans have made the lamp, and if God has made deserts and mountains, then humans have made parks and meadows (“A Dialogue Between God and Man,”). Humans must, therefore, strive to be perfect qua humans, and that is a goal yet to be achieved. 
The theme of humanity is closely linked in Iqbal with that of khudi (literally, “selfhood”). Khudi is a complex thought in Iqbal. Broadly speaking, it represents the principle of the inner self with an urge to manifest itself Societies as well as individuals have khudi, and it is on the development or suppression of one’s or failure in the world depends, khudi that one’s success the khudi of slaves, for example, is moribund. 
Recognition, discovery, cultivation, and assertion of their khudi should, therefore, be the aim of humans. Iqbal’s critique of Muslim societies is predicated on the assumption that these societies have lost their khudi or have allowed it to become seriously impaired. The best way to understand Iqbal’s concept of khudi is by reading poems in which he discusses the subject. 
Perfection, or rather limitless perfection, is a frequently occurring motif in Iqbal’s poetry. “I seek the end of that which has no end,” says Iqbal in “The Houri and the Poet”, and, in the same poem: “From the spark I seek a star, from the star a sun.” Iqbal sees no end to human potentialities. He wishes humans to embark on a never-ending journey of discovery, and to this end emphasizes the importance of action. Constant action and perpetual movement are in fact the only guarantee of survival in the world. Nations fall behind when they cease to be dynamic and start preferring a life of idle speculation over one of purposive action. 
But the quest for perfection can give rise to irony. Irony, in fact, fills human life, for while they have been imbued with the desire to achieve perfection, humans have been denied the ability to achieve it in practice. The poems “Man”, “Solitude”, and “The Dew and the Stars” discuss several aspects of the irony of human life. The poem, “The Story of Adam,” though it ends on a more optimistic note, yet implies that it takes humans a long time to discover the most important secret of existence. 
“The heart has its reasons, of which reason is ignorant,” says Pascal. Iqbal, who frequently speaks of the conflict of the head and the heart, would agree, though he would add that while the conflict exists, it does not have to. More often than not it is reason (or the intellect) that belittles the heart (or intuition), but both are essential to a harmonious life; ideally, then, reason and the heart should cooperate rather than clash. 
Although he has wide-ranging interests, Iqbal essentially belongs to, and speaks from within, the Islamic tradition, employing, for his purposes, the historical, religious, philosophical, and literary resources of that tradition. A full appreciation of Iqbal requires an understanding of these resources, and the notes and commentaries in this volume elucidate Iqbal’s use of them. 
Iqbal held to the doctrine of art for life’s sake. Acutely aware of the problems of Muslim decadence and backwardness, Iqbal takes it upon himself to shake the Muslims of India and other countries out of their lethargy, urging them to take the path of progress, so that they can gain an honorable position in the polity of nations, He uses the medium of poetry to arouse socio-religious consciousness among Muslims. As a result, Islamic religious and social themes predominate in his poetry. But Iqbal’s vision of a revived religion is far from conservative. He is sharply critical of many of the institutions of historic Islam (of the institution of monarchy, for example), and his vision of a new world derives from the Islamic notions of egalitarianism and social justice. He rejects dogmatism in religion, advocates rethinking of the Islamic intellectual heritage, and stands for the establishment of a forward-looking community. But the conviction of art for life’s sake never allows Iqbal’s poetry to degenerate into bland or crass propaganda. The worldwide acclamation he has won is proof that Iqbal’s strength consists in writing purpose poetry of the highest artistic standards. 
Ultimately, however, the secret of the appeal of Iqbal’s poetry lies in the personality behind that poetry. Whether he is dealing with a broadly humanistic or a specifically Islamic theme, Iqbal views it from a unique perspective. Consider his boldly critical attitude toward certain aspects of the received tradition, an attitude reflected, for example, in the poems referred above. Unlike almost any other poet in the Islamic tradition, Iqbal enters into a dialogue with God, raising issues the orthodox would consider disturbing. He asks whether Adam’s expulsion from heaven has turned out to be Adam’s loss or God’s own; he challenges God to speak to him face to face rather than through messengers, and, noting the discrepancy between the boundlessness of human ambition and the limitedness of the resources put at humans’ disposal, he asks God whether His experiment involving Adam is to be taken seriously. Iqbal’s view of the role of Satan in the world is also highly intriguing and, as one would expect, highly unconventional (see “Conquest of Nature” and “Gabriel and Iblis”). 
A notable thing about Iqbal’s perspective is ambiguity, a typical modem quality. Especially when he is talking about metaphysical issues, Iqbal raises some difficult questions, without providing a single “valid” answer. In “Paradise Lost and Regained” the question whether Adam should have sinned or not (each scenario being theoretically defensible) is not answered by Iqbal. In “Gabriel and Iblis” we are left to wonder about Iqbal’s own view of Iblis’ self-justification. And in “Solitude” we cannot be certain why God smiles. 
In several places Iqbal talks about himself about his Eastern background and Western education, and the contradictions of his own personality; his conviction that his study of historic Islam had furnished him with certain valuable insights which he must share with his people; his hope that his message will spread across the Muslim world, and his apprehension that he will be misunderstood or appreciated for the wrong reasons. Here it may be added that the various attempts made to identify (or label) Iqbal as a Sufi or an orthodox Muslim, as a radical or a reactionary are wide of the mark because Iqbal is too large a figure to fit any narrow, procrustean category; he demands and deserves attention on his own terms. 

III 
Iqbal had a fine sense of the dramatic, and in his poetry he frequently employs dramatic techniques. Many of his poems are structured like a play, with the first half of the poem building a tension or conflict that is resolved, or raising a question that is answered, in the second half Examples are “Gabriel and Iblis”, “The Dew and the Stars”, “The Houri and the Poet” and “Fatimah bint ‘Abdullah”. Many poems are dialogues, with well-argued positions taken by the interlocutors (“A Dialogue Between God and Man”, “The Dew and the Stars”, “Reason and Heart” and “A Dialogue Between Knowledge and Love”; also the fables). Some poems are one-sided dialogues or monologues (“Give Me Another Adversary”, “The Falcon’s Advice to Its Youngster”). Again, Iqbal carefully weaves the “plot” of a poem, arousing the reader’s curiosity, dropping seemingly casual hints that turn out to be prophetic, providing flashback, and saving his masterstroke for the end. Two excellent examples are “The Night and the Poet” and “The Houri and the Poet”. 
Iqbal has some favorite images and motifs. The eagle is Iqbal’s favorite bird, and the tulip his favorite flower. We will here say a few words about the tulip. The tulip is a pretty flower, but, when it grows in the desert (Lala’-i sahra’), it combines strength with beauty, for it then represents the assertion of one’s self (khudi) in the face of hostile circumstances. The tulip owes its splendor not to an outside source but to the “scar” inside its heart, its glow being indigenous to it, as befits a flower with a khudi of its own. The tulip is thus a “model” for individuals and nations to follow. In one of his quatrains (“Freedom and Determinism and Philosophy of History”), speaking of the difficult circumstances that alone give birth to new nations, Iqbal says: “From mountains and deserts do nations arise.” Although Iqbal does not mention the tulip in this quatrain, it would not be far-fetched to suggest that, conceptually, Iqbal here has the desert tulip in mind. The cup-shaped flower suggests to Iqbal’s mind several analogies, and in one piece (“Locke, Kant, and Bergson,”) Iqbal, makes consistent use of the tulip image to describe and analyze complex philosophical ideas. It is in view of the deep significance of the flower in Iqbal’s poetry that I have chosen Tulip in the Desert as the title of my volume of translations (Mustansir Mir, Tulip in the Desert, Hurst and Company, London, 2000). The images of the eagle and the tulip illustrate how Iqbal adds to the native literary tradition or makes an innovative use of that tradition (the tulip). Another example in this connection is that of the moth. In Persian and Urdu poetry the moth represents the devoted and self-immolating lover. Like the moth, which keeps circling the light, the lover (a male) desires to stay close to the beloved (a female). But in Iqbal, typically, the moth often represent a reprehensible rather than a praiseworthy quality: the shining light it is in love with is not its own. The moth is to be contrasted with another, the firefly, which, though it has a weak light, can at least call this light its own. The firefly, in other words, is possessed of khudi, but the moth has no khudi. Iqbal often uses a series of images to convey a thought, producing a cumulative effect. In “Fatimah bint -Abdullah,” for example, he uses no fewer than four images to express the idea that, even in its present age of decadence, the Muslim Community can produce individuals of exceptional caliber: 

O that our autumn-stricken garden had 
A flower-bud like this! 
O that in our ashes would be found, O Lord, 
A spark like this! 
In our desert is hidden many a deer still. 
In the spent clouds lies dormant still 
Many a flash of lightning. 

Iqbal is capable of writing biting satire. Two examples are: “Give Me Another Adversary”, in which Satan argues that he deserves a better rival than Adam, and “Scorpion Land,” which criticizes slave mentality.﻿

Meer lezen (277 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-RHa-INDkO98/T38cDhYD0fI/AAAAAAAAACE/bkwUGvVHXfw/w426-h240/images.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/104005367575676950568/albums/5679269992176308017/5679269991658358002</link><title>Well, I did actually go get some running shoes this morning! Went to Up and Running in Cambridge, and was helped by Daryl. Glad I went early because, it got suddenly very busy as I was paying for the shoes. ( http://upandrunning.co.uk/index.php?left=shop&amp;main=cambridge# ) 

He analysed my run on the treadmill, and suprisingly I have an almost neutral running gait. He explained that despite my extra weight that I currently carry, my leg muscles are strong enough to keep my ankles from pronating as I pound the ground. 

I explained what I was after, my recent and not so recent health issues and injuries, and off he went into the store room to grab about as many boxes of shoes as one person can carry. Each one I tried I used on the treadmill, so I must have done about 5-8 minutes of running just this morning. For you experienced runners, thats just a warm up, but for me, thats more time running than I have done over the last 10 years... maybe 15!! And, much to my surprise, I didnt collapse afterwards, nor did it take me more than a few seconds to get my breath back. 

So, here they are, the shoes to get me running... or to knacker my knees, which ever happens first :)﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TU5be_XtVio/TtDR96RVBPI/AAAAAAAAACY/XMS8dhc4L5I/w426-h713/20111126_asics.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/104576893110209187122/albums/5957896177160952177/5957896180142370994</link><title>Yesterday it appeared that South and East of Roade, off A508 to M1 area, was being turned over for either cables or a development, including breaching the old Olney-Roade trackbed - bridge no longer over M1 of course, but some had mooted it to link at Roade with a new station as an alternative if Brackmills is lost. 

Meanwhile, Brackmills developments are coming a little unstuck 8000 people per day but no parking! - for example. Our BON Rail would enable 45 minutes via an extended Thameslink Airport-Campus from a Pan Europe + Israel audience... just what you want turning up and spending in our town centres minus a significant element of the traffic if all but less-than 10% bunged onto the so called 'public transport'. No, I'm not cynical, it is cynical, I believe systemically as a pattern it reduces national well-being. 

The systematic reductionising of the Local Planning Inspectorate and System, has let carte blanche creeping infill development with scant jobs, sewerage treatment, water supply, renewables, access to extra rail capacity 'included'. It, like the food banks, are part of a spectrum of scale to avoid the issue of proportionate to income and guzzle-power matters around 'fair taxation'. Meanwhile the lessons of such a liberalisation in Spain, need to be learnt, as needs-must change - nature of change more complicated, but when it turns up at the door, too late! 

http://www.thisismoney.co.uk/money/news/article-2148335/Fleeing-Costa-catastrophe-Thousands-hand-villa-keys-Spains-economy-teeters.html 

http://www.southnorthants.gov.uk/1551.htm 

http://www.universitiesuk.ac.uk/highereducation/Pages/UKcouldattractanextra126,000internationalstudentsovernextdecade-BritishCouncilreport.aspx#.Uq6osvRdW9Y 

In short I do believe there's a glaring gap in cynical approaches, beit captive of history/past associated images, comparison with poor performing bog standard (contrast London services) of Marston Vale leading to "not another one!" and yet HS2, televisual play-ons "it's a train... woo!" and no expense or 'can do' is spared, but Whitehall, whether true or false, will front it - we elect the Governor's Government, not our! But the Security Services may reflect that silencing, marginalising, ridicule are blunt instruments and counter-productive per se as they fail to grasp the systemic root issues, left undone as per Bedford-Cambridge x50 years - what can be done for HS2 isn't the same set of dynamics in 'can do' for Bedford-Cambridge, Northampton-Bedford-Cambridge... but for less cost and quicker delivery, latter not HS2 gives more for the well being of our country. The disproportionate weilding of demands to 'prove it' is akin to ask a postage stamp to account for all of Royal Mail - can't be done resource-wise, but duplicity of silencing, neutralising and countering, insists "it will not be done" and Thameslink and Northampton apart, allows development to breach trackbeds beyond reasonable route recovery. So if local, the result is either demolition or the kink in approaches to Sandy from Bedford and Cambridge 'S' on it's side, has to be the norm, as straighter urban corridor options are lost - Bedford-Hitchin North of A421 Bypass, another local example of spite-in-action masked behind 'day job-bification-al-ism' (a pseudo moral idea, with power, multi-practised rolled out and plural-randomised and taken as 'practice' = the translation of that word here!). 

I want to focus more on internals at BRTA and need others to take key positions and head up. Some have said they can't even if they wished as they must protect their I.D. at any cost... never had that in the Cold War did we?! 

Ps. On Stamford for ECML, an alternative could be Northallerton-Ripon-Harrogate-MML or GC Nottingham-Old Dalby-New Bit or upgrade via Oakham and walla Peterborough. New bit South to take from ECML direct, should look at South of Corby-Nene Valley and off South as a domestic alternative with 75mph average. HS2 bit, will not want a load of urban dense stations, otherwise 180mph and braking becomes 'expensive' and defeats the object of intent surely? 

Regards, 

Richard 

Mr Richard Pill: Land-line: 01234 330090/richard.selfemployed@yahoo.co.uk for employment related activity or see http://www.rpse.org.uk/ for any exploratories. Email richard24c@googlemail.com or richard.pill.1@facebook.com﻿

Meer lezen (79 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-pxViuHJ4x7o/Uq6zAnIK8LI/AAAAAAAABMI/raeEPNUov5M/w426-h301/The+Y.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/118046966811712598852/albums/5838770072091076209/5838770078948805922?authkey=CP6oiq_yvrfakQE</link><title>Restatement of History of Islam 
                                        Introduction  Part - II 
This pro-Saqifa tilt of the Orientalists has led them up a blind alley in which they cannot find answers for some fundamental questions in the history of Islam, and they find themselves caught, like the Sunni historians, in a net of paradoxes and contradictions. 
Many Sunni historians and many among the Orientalists have made a deliberate attempt to minimize the importance of the role played by Ali ibn Abi Talib in the story of Islam. They are, of course, entitled to their opinions and assumptions even if these are not attested by facts. In my presentation, I have made an attempt to place the emphasis on facts. In doing so, it has been my hope that the facts themselves would act as "judges". Since facts are impartial "judges," they can be counted upon to restore balance to the assessment of the roles played by the various protagonists in the history of nascent Islam. I have picked them up and have tried to string them, like pearls, into a "necklace", so that most of them can be seen in one place. 
History has no supreme court rendering verdicts; it has only fallible chroniclers. And yet, history can find its own supreme court or objective tribunal in the logic of facts. 
I have another and very pragmatic reason for depending upon facts. For writing the story of the early days of Islam, there are three primary sources, viz., Al-Qur’an al-Majid (the revealed book of Islam); the Hadith (the memorials of the attributed acts and sayings of Muhammad, as transmitted by a chain of informants or narrators); and the events as recorded by Arab historians. Out of these three, the first, i.e., the Qur’an, is acknowledged by all Muslims to be divine in origin. If a Muslim challenges the authority of Qur’an, he immediately becomes an apostate. But whereas the authority of Qur’an, as far as the Muslims are concerned, is inviolate, its verses are subject to varying and sometimes conflicting interpretations, and there is no such thing as a consensus on which or whose interpretation is right. The Hadith also suffer from a handicap; too many of them are spurious although there are some which are acknowledged both by the Sunnis and the Shias to be authentic. I have, therefore, made an attempt to be selective in quoting only those verses of Qur’an and only those Hadith (statements of the Prophet) in the interpretation of which the difference between the Sunnis and the Shias is minimal. But historical facts belong to an area in which there is not much room for disagreement. 
I have made very frequent use of quotations, both from classical and modern historians, in this book, often on the same subject or event. I have done so to present to the reader more than one point of view or more than one interpretation of the more important events. The same event seen from different angles appears different to different observers and is, therefore, subject to different interpretations. It is in the hope that the reader shares this opinion that I have tried, on many occasions, to let more than one historian tell the same story. "Let the professionals do the job," has been my motto in the restatement of most of the vital facts of the history of Islam. 
Another reason why I have presented testimony of the historians on such a vast scale, is to underpin my thesis with evidence, so that the reader, if he so wishes, may advert to sources which he may consider to be unimpeachable. 
It has been said that daring as it is to investigate the unknown, even more so it is to question the known. Many of the so-called "known facts" in the history of nascent Islam are little more than pious assumptions or even pious wishes which through persistent repetition by the long chain of the generations of Muslims, have acquired the "patina" if not the status of the "articles of faith". When I questioned some of the assumptions of many Muslims which are disguised as historical "truths", I noticed that they cannot withstand the scrutiny of critical analysis. The reader himself may, therefore, decide if he would cling to them or would accept truths some of which he might find extremely bitter and brutal. There are those people who are afraid of truth. Truth threatens their illusions, their favorite myths, and their assumptions. These latter, through long propinquity, have become so familiar to them that they feel it is safe and comfortable to live with them without the "intrusion" of truth. They equate truth with "insecurity." And yet, truth alone can bring them real security. Truth must be upheld at all costs, and by all, but especially, by the historians. Truth must be upheld even if it hurts a friend and benefits a foe. The first loyalty of the historian must be to truth, and nothing whatsoever must deflect him in its quest. 
The war of ideas and the conflict of opinions become even more interesting when the spotlight of investigation is turned away from philosophical concepts and abstract political doctrines to characters and personalities which played the key roles in the events under review. History springs to life with characterization; it becomes vibrant with sharply delineated characters who "make" events or act on them or react to them. They invest history with the "human interest" element, and the touch of drama. 
Whatever history is – accident, or inevitable causality, or the pressure of economic determinism, or the actions of strong leaders, or the result of forces nobody understands, or the collective aspirations of a people – whatever history is, the Arabs themselves see and interpret their own history more in terms of personal action than anything else. And they may be right. After all, as in every other area of endeavor, history is made by those who act. It consists, in the interaction, not of blind forces but of human beings. The conflicts of history are not between the abstractions of philosophy, economics or sociology but between human beings. It has been said that even in its most sociological moments, history cannot overlook the factor of human personality. The history of the first 23-years of the career of Islam which comprehends the entire ministry of Muhammad as the Messenger of God, is made, for the most part, next to himself, by the personal actions of his collaborator, Ali ibn Abi Talib. This is the testimony of history. But it is a testimony which many historians have consistently tried to conceal. It is to this testimony that I have tried to draw the attention of the readers of this book. 
But notwithstanding the past and present lopsidedness of Western historiography on Islam, there is new hope that historians of the future will make restitution for the omissions and failures of the historians of the past. All that they have to do is not to be tendentious, and not to accept blindly those interpretations and conclusions which have become the clichés of the history of Islam, but to rediscover truth for themselves through collation and examination of the evidence. 
In the introduction to the Cambridge History of Islam, Volume I, published by the University Press, Cambridge (1970), P.M. Holt, writes: 
"The study of Islamic history is now developing, many of the apparent certainties of the older Western historiography (often reflecting the assertions and interpretations of the Muslim traditional historians) have dissolved, and it is only gradually through detailed research that a truer understanding of the past may be attained." 
The certainties of the older Western historiography reflecting the assertions and interpretations of the Muslim traditional historians have not dissolved yet but let us hope that they will, and a truer understanding of the past will be attained in due course. 
An attempt to interpret the history of Islam, especially the history of its first century, is like stepping into a mine field; it's seething with controversy, diatribes and polemics, and one may approach it only extremely gingerly. Nevertheless, interpretation remains basic to the understanding of history. Without interpretation, history becomes a mass of uncoordinated information and a catalogue of "dead" events and dates unrelated to each other. Yet these "dead" events bounce back to life when effects are related to causes, and a concatenation of facts is established. A fact in correlation with other facts has historical significance; in isolation it may be meaningless. 
Even Einstein's Relativity is the understanding of the world not as a series of events but as relations. 
As stated above, there is a plethora of books on Islam but most of them are stereotypical interpretations of the story of its birth and growth, and its religious experience, just as handed down to their authors by the court historians of the government which was born in Saqifa, and its successor governments – the governments of Damascus and Baghdad. The story, however, has another side also. 
A principle of the ancient Roman law was audi alteram partem (in any dispute, hear the other side); or audiatur et altera pars (let the other side be heard). Concerted human action – which is called politics – is full of immense, heart-breaking tragedies that have damaged the lives of everyone on the planet. Most would have been averted had this law been heeded by all. 
This principle that in any dispute, both sides of the case should be heard – is entrenched in the legal systems of most nations, but most particularly in those of the United States and Western Europe. Thomas Jefferson was only paraphrasing this principle, without which there cannot be any justice, when he exclaimed: "For God's sake, let us freely hear both sides." The American and European students of Islam, in most cases, have heard only one side of its story; this book is an attempt to present the other side. It is with this intent that I deliver it to the judgment of its readers. 
From the cowardice which shrinks from new truth; 
From the laxness that is content with half-truth; 
From the arrogance that thinks it knows all truth; 
O God of Truth deliver us! 
Transliteration 
The system of transliteration employed in this book was devised with particular regard for simplicity. In most cases, those forms of spelling for names of persons and places have been used which are most familiar to Western readers, such as Qur’an, Muhammad, and Yemen in preference to Coran, Koran or Kuran, Mohammad, and al-Yaman. At the same time, some other forms of Western usage such as Moslems, Sunnites and Shi'ites have been discarded in favor of the simpler and more correct forms such as Muslims, Sunnis and Shias. 
The Arabic word for "son" is transliterated to conform with the Arabic spelling as ibn or bin, and both variants have been used. 
The words caliph and khalifa or caliphate and khilafat have been used interchangeably.﻿

Meer lezen (167 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-lUSBkkeEK3c/UQd6c6DsTSI/AAAAAAACpcg/5BQHboFpaPA/w426-h679/Quranpage.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7141-12"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/Cambridge%20must%20do/photos/115722829851477319854/albums/5886858768192945809/5886858771163312818?authkey=CLC6yc399bmBBQ</link><title>Leukippos Institute 

The future scientist will do coding and designing abstraction. Lab work is will be done by robots or outsourced..... 

A growing number of biotechnology companies employ a skeleton crew of managers and outsource hands-on science. 

Biotechnology: Virtual reality 
by 
Heidi Ledford 

"If Rosana Kapeller has her way, her company will develop treatments for scourges such as cancer, cardiovascular disease and diabetes. And it will do so with only 12 full-time employees and no wet labs. 
Kapeller shares a quiet office with eight colleagues at the headquarters of Nimbus Discovery in Cambridge, Massachusetts. The rest work from their homes in Missouri, Connecticut, Rhode Island and New York. This skeleton crew manages the company's operations and computer analyses; all hands-on experiments are outsourced to an international assembly of contract-research organizations (CROs). “It's a lot like managing a lab down the hall,” says Kapeller, the company's chief scientific officer. “But instead of down the hall, the lab's in China and we're using Skype.” 

Such is life at a 'virtual' biotechnology company, a lean, nimble model that is gaining popularity among cash-hungry start-ups. These companies consist of as few as one full-time employee who oversees a drug from preclinical development to tests in patients, all in the hands of outside contractors. 

To take advantage of this niche, scientists must have the management experience to run a remote team of researchers, and may need the financial backing to launch a company on their own. Aspirants should also be prepared for quick turnover with regard to projects and jobs: virtual start-ups are often designed to sell off individual projects — or the full company — to larger firms...." 

http://bit.ly/11mC7zX﻿

Meer lezen (35 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7141_12_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-5uYPmFFoOm0/UbJS3MoU8rI/AAAAAAAAO48/5xLQYOo60N0/w426-h594/nj7452-127a-i1.0.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>