<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:48:32" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/106047280557875175813/albums/5685720342467357281/5685720339343902210</link><title>Loud music can cause hearing loss: protect your hearing with these Vic Firth isolation headphones!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-DlEYeUafUfw/Tue8hj7OhgI/AAAAAAAAAKo/rZFALU5voWA/w426-h288/VF%2BHeadphones.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/107270281871345421799/albums/5997345517910760833/5997345527702374290</link><title>Bad Effects Of Using Earphones 
Now a days using earphones are very beneficial like when you are on journey,work you can listen to music without disturbing others.Most of the people will buy earphones because of its loud noise.They never consider the quality of that product.Earphones or headphones on music player or ipod reach noise similar to jet engines.They can produce sounds upto 120 decibels. 

Heavy noise may cause temporary deafness and also can damage coating nerve cells.If you feel you are loosing your hearing sense immediately consult your ENT, but very few people can identify it early. 

Bad Effects Of Using Earphones: 

Wearing headphones for an hour increases the bacteria  in your ear 700 times. 
Heavy noise may cause temporary deafness and also can damage coating nerve cells. 
Sharing or borrowing others earphones transfers someone's bacteria. 
Listening to music through earphones for a long time at a high volume can result hear loss. 
Prolonged use of earphones causes you tinnitus,hearing loss,pain &amp; infection.(impacts on the ear wax) 
Pain &amp; inflammation also occur when earphones are not fitted correctly.So better to buy which fits you correctly. 
Noise louder than 110 decibels is dangerous, researches show that it may lead to destruction of cells which causes severe damage to the nerves. 

Important Tips: 

Do not push your earphones too far to the ear canal. 
While removing earphones don't pull them harshly it may causes damage to ear drums. 
Clean your ears regularly to prevent infections.It is advised that use two drops of olive oil to remove the wax build up. 
Clean your earphones by using antibacterial solution into a warm water and soak the earphones for few minutes then wash it off with water and place the earphones on a paper towel to drain out the water and leave it to dry.﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-cu6EtBjpKj0/UzrZ-236R5I/AAAAAAADLNk/fPYOWSw-JIY/w426-h281/article-0-197F4A8F00000578-195_634x418.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/100106668466973455972/albums/5954342937456673377/5954342938592615186</link><title>The New York Health Department just launched a new campaign Warning of the Dangers of Listening To Loud Headphones. 
Exposure to acute or prolonged loud sounds can cause irreversible damage to the inner ear, resulting in hearing loss, tinnitus, or both problems. 
More info here http://www.nyc.gov/html/doh/html/pr2013/pr045-13.shtml﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-WDKykoIwgP0/UqITWu2rGxI/AAAAAAAAAd0/2Udz9M5963M/w426-h237/Hear+Today+Gone+Tomorrow.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/102173349122411290580/albums/5978034639152934241/5978034643108838386</link><title>Brain depends on vision to hear 

Engineers at the University of Utah discover the brain overrides what we hear based on what we see.  Even when we hear the correct thing, our visual senses will cause the auditory signal to be overridden.  This research was done with the context of speech, but it goes to show there is a lot to learn about how humans hear.  This indicates people with hearing loss can improve what they hear by reading lips. 
How does this relate to music played back through hi-fi gear?  It may or may not, but it would seem that how you hear depends in part to what you are looking at. Will watching TV or people watching while you are listening change your experience with gear?  It has been shown that people appearance plays a large role in being able to judge music competition winners, so it isn’t just all in the ears. 
How much does the look of your surroundings play a role in how you hear your gear?  The One Sense headphone might have been onto something, even if they didn’t know it since the headphone was designed for “the human need for periods of peace and tranquility.”  People say listening in the dark is the best way to truly experience audio playback. What do you think? 

http://theheadphonelist.com/brain-depends-on-vision-to-hear/﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ee4nbV8F-UA/UvY-1b17O_I/AAAAAAACVCA/bli9-b-qqmU/w426-h654/391f23e4bce3a8335524f595aebdd714.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/103260909450809151378/albums/5867635219350704321/5867635227479316466?authkey=CLn5iYDaj7DsPA</link><title>Aftershokz Bluez Bone Conducting Headphones 

Back in February, I had ordered myself the Aftershokz Bluez bone conduction headphones. Nearly 2 months later, a package arrived and much excitement ensued. I've been using the headphones pretty heavily over the past two weeks and thought I would share my experiences starting with what makes these headphones different than any other headphone on the market. 

What are bone conduction headphones? 
The Aftershokz bone conduction technology utilizes an open ear design by pumping vibrations through your cheek bone directly into your inner ear. The open ear design allows a listener to be aware of their surroundings and enjoy their music simultaneously. There are many use cases and environments where the open ear design is both suitable and desirable including the workplace, public and private settings, and even while working out. Each of these use cases I will cover in some detail. 

Connecting to Devices 
This is a very important feature for a Bluetooth headphone. Connecting the Bluez to my Nexus 4 was extremely simple and fast, taking all of about 5 seconds.There are two major uses for these headphones and those are media playback and phone calls. 
First, we have media playback. Media playback works just as expected. You launch your media application, hit play and enjoy your music. There is a media control on the headphones which pauses and resumes audio. It also works exactly as expected. One limitation however is that if you have not already initiated music from your phone, there doesn't appear to be a way to activate it solely from the headset. In fact, the headset appears to go into some sort of minimalist power saving mode when it is not receiving audio. This does wonders for the battery life, unfortunately it seems to cause some other technical issues. Specifically when it comes to voice dialing. 
Stock android uses Google’s own voice dialing app. I have found this app to be absolutely amazing in correctly translating speech to text. To initiate voice dialing from the headset, press and hold the phone button for about 2 seconds. In theory, this should activate the voice prompt. It is at this point that things get rocky. Even though the voice dialer is activated, there is no audible prompt. It took quite a bit of testing, but if you wait the correct amount of time for the prompt to finish before speaking then you can initiate a phone call via voice. This is a severe limitation that needs to be fixed. There is a way around this though. If you already have music playing and then initiate the voice dialer, the voice prompt will be audible. This method allows you to be able to navigate the voice dialer but also has it’s drawbacks. Mainly that the music you have playing does not suspend or even reduce in volume which can be both distracting and annoying. Additionally, the vibrations from the bone conducers seem to throw off the microphone making the voice dialer fail in translating speech. 

In the Office 
Like many people, while at work I like to listen to music. Mostly just to avoid the monotonous silence and key clicking from myself and everyone around me. I don't however, like it when I get startled by someone walking up behind me to ask a question. This is a problem I experience on a nearly daily basis when I am wearing my traditional Bose in ear headphones. Another problem I run into is when someone starts talking to me, I have to remove the headphones from my ears so that I can hear them clearer, and so I don't raise my voice unconsciously. 
With the open ear design, I have discovered that while listening to music, I can still hear people entering the room just as clearly as if I had not been wearing any headphones. I can also carry on a conversation without removing the headphones. Because my ear's are not blocked, I do not unconsciously compensate by raising the volume of my voice, and neither does the other person need to speak louder for me to hear. It is also entirely possible to continue a conversation without pausing the music, though I do find pausing the music to have a couple benefits. It's slightly less distracting for myself, and also more courteous to the person I am speaking to. 
One potential problem with listening to music while in a quiet environment is that the headphones have to be kept rather low or else there is "leakage", meaning that other people can hear your music and it might distract them. That being said, I was able to set my volume at a comfortable and audible level far below where the leakage occurred. This is more a problem for people who prefer their music on the louder side. 

In Public 
Over the weekend I went grocery shopping. There are always lots of people at the grocery store, and it is always quite noisy. I've never enjoyed wearing headphones in public since being aware of my surroundings is very important especially in crowded areas. The open ear design allowed me to keep track of my surroundings and still listen to my music. I did have to turn the volume up a bit otherwise the music would get overpowered by the surrounding noise. This did cause one problem, and that is that the louder music made it more challenging to understand what people were saying. However, I could still identify that a person was speaking where as with regular headphones I would have been completely unaware. 
In regards to the leakage problem I mentioned above, I did not notice it being an issue in public even with the louder volume setting. It seems that louder ambient noise counteracts the leakage. I tested this very scientifically... by holding out the headphones about 2 feet from my head and not hearing anything from the headphones.  (+1 for science!) 

In Private 
In my home, I often have music and podcasts playing from my computer speakers to break up the silence.  For 2 days I decided to use my headphones instead of my computer speakers. It worked out quite well. I kept the volume at about the same level as when I am in the office. It is during this time that I focused more on the quality of the audio. The details regarding quality are in the ”Sound Quality” paragraph down below. The portability of the headphones was very enjoyable. I could walk from one end of my apartment all the way to the other and not lose connection nor did I experience sound degradation. Keep in mind that my apartment is not overly big, so I would except the range not to cover an apartment or house that is significantly larger than mine. The nice thing about this portability is that my music never disappeared whereas right now if I have music playing on my computer speakers, it gets harder to hear the further away I get. 

Running Test 
  Over the weekend I went for a 4 mile run and for the first time in years I wore headphones, the Aftershokz Bluez. I was extremely happy with the results of this test. It was a slightly windy day and there was traffic along all the roads I ran on. To begin, I had to turn my volume up closer to the levels used while out in public. After setting the volume to a comfortable level I could hear both my music, and the noises around me very clearer. I could hear cars passing, dogs barking, and more. I could even hear the guy washing his car around the corner before I saw him. This was a major success. My main worry about wearing headphones while running or cycling is the lack of awareness to one’s surroundings. With the Aftershokz, I did not feel like I was putting myself in that situation. A few days later I went for another run and listened to a podcast. Again, I had no difficulty listening both to the podcast speakers, and the world around me simultaneously. 

Phone Calls 
I don’t make or receive many phone calls, however I do like my headphones to have the capability of answering and making calls should the event occur. I currently use the Bose in ear headphones which have a built in microphone. It’s works pretty well in a pinch but I can’t wear them in the car and I really don’t like being wired to my phone. I also the have Bose Bluetooth earpiece 1st generation which I absolutely love and would constantly have in my ear while driving or out in public. The Bose Bluetooth does not support media however, and even if it did it is a closed ear design. Enter Aftershokz... This headset has media and phone controls, while being wireless and leaving my ears open. Pretty much the perfect solution. 
So how does it compare? There is a difference in sound quality which I will cover in the next paragraph. But the basic idea is that the Bose appears to have slightly higher quality in both the speaker and the microphone. But neither difference is significant enough to render the Aftershokz undesirable. The comfort level is very similar and probably comes down to a personal preference. The Bose have an in ear design which is extremely comfortable compared to other ear pieces, while the Aftershokz have a band that wraps around the back of the head. Neither of them bother me, but I will point out that I notice the Aftershokz more than I notice the Bose. In fact there are many times I completely forget I am wearing my Bose. Forgetting I am wearing the Aftershokz does happen as well, but seemingly less often. 

Sound Quality and Comfort 
So how can a device with no speakers compare to the traditional sound producing devices? Surprisingly well. But it’s not perfect. When I first put on the Aftershokz and began playing music, I genuinely believed my ear’s were just picking up the sound from the “speakers” of the device, and that it wasn't doing what it claimed. Then I tried a little test by putting in ear plugs. I am no longer a skeptic. It truly is sending sound directly to your inner ear. In fact it wasn't until I did this that I noticed just how much sound quality was being lost. 
Without any earplugs, it is very easy to hear the mid range of music, and while you can still hear the highs and the lows, they are not nearly as prominent. The exception is if you turn up the headphones very loudly, then the highs and lows become much more prominent. Under normal volume conditions however, the open ear design seems to let these 2 ranges escape the confines of the ear, or perhaps the ambient noise overrides it. Either way, it is significant enough to be noticed if you are really listening to the music as was the case for my ”In Private” scenario above. For the casual listener, the runner, the office worker, the grocery shopper,  or the many other scenarios where music is not the focus of the moment, the loss in quality is barely noticed. 
As per comfort, I found the form factor of the Aftershokz slightly annoying at first. It  continuously slipped and took me a bit of time adjusting the strap to find the right fit. That being said, after I found the right fit it has been extremely comfortable. I have been wearing this for about 8-10 hours a day nearly every day and often forget it is even there. Over the weekend I was at a tech conference and wore it from about 6 am to 11 pm. It’s surprisingly comfortable. During my run I only had to adjust it once, which I think is pretty reasonable considering all the impact motion that running causes. 

The Good 
There are many really great things about this technology. I think the biggest selling point for me would be the open ear design. It’s flexibility to let you wear it and still be completely aware of your surrounding without removing the device is a huge advantage over traditional headphones. The price is extremely competitive for a Bluetooth headset and microphone, especially considering the uniqueness of the technology. The battery life is very good. On several occasions I have drained my phone and my headphones still had power. 

The Less Good 
The Aftershokz do fall short in a couple respects when compared to traditional headphones. The most painful shortcoming is the way it handles hands free voice dialing. The loss in sound quality and the leakage of sound at higher volumes are also problems, but depending on how loud you like your music and how strongly you care about the sound quality in a Bluetooth headphone this may or may not be an issue.﻿

Meer lezen (210 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_05_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BIUb_iv-vTg/UW4HJr15F_I/AAAAAAAAI6w/AipRRWL5JF8/w426-h239/aftershock1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/114862810589780495557/albums/5944442191243723857/5944442195184822754</link><title>From the Desk of "Whadid-He-Say...? 

Being hard of hearing has its own set of obvious challenges.  What adds X10 to that challenge is there not being a device or medical procedure to improve it. 

I suffer Tinnitus as a side effect of Chemo Therapy.  Cisplatin is well-known for being a cancer-killing drug but it also trashes the hearing of those who have to take borderline-lethal doses. 

My mom suffered from Meniere's disease  Disease the last half of her life and hard, loud ringing was always present for her.  Even though she wore hearing aids, all they really did was amplify the "noise".  It's hard to explain to someone not affected and many people can lose patience with those of us displaying this malady. 

I finally got through to Diane,...no matter how hard I tried to explain it...she insisted on calling me from two rooms away when I had absolutely no chance of hearing her.  She didn't like the fact that I would shush her during TV shows as well.  She didn't understand how one added noise to my environment made everything jumbled.  I explained to her this way and now she understands. 

This is what I hear when I watch TV with no ambient sound" 

https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B2bdSLJMw_v1YXA1ck54eFFmN0k/edit?usp=sharing 

This is what I hear when just one other voice or noise is added to my environment: 

https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B2bdSLJMw_v1SXZOSnYwMlIxMG8/edit?usp=sharing 

And yeah, it sucks but it beats my alternatives. 

http://tinyurl.com/6ovndjz﻿

Meer lezen (33 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-EhzbglZnqq0/Un7mrnfVqeI/AAAAAAAAfVw/G86qkhJNKLM/w426-h240/deaf.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/107635094329792651474/albums/5824378810572839329/5824378812077537058?authkey=CPvZ05fBwuD-hgE</link><title>Why hello there Doomsday preppers. Must be awkward, eh? 

So, this morning, I woke up ignorantly wondering about the 'inner voice' of those born deaf and the imaginations and dreams of those born blind. Ignorantly, because it's so easy to assume that everyone thinks, imagines and dreams exactly the way I do, which is obviously not so. This led to thoughts on language and its importance in self-reflection and expression. Even as I type this, I can hear the words in my head, in my voice, with my accent and intonations. I can picture exactly what I'm going to wear today and cross reference it to my shoes and accessories. I can read +Jessica Turner's post and flip my accent so I'm reading it in her Aussie one. 

I did the right thing and googled my wakening thoughts and am as a result even more ignorant if that's possible. Just trying to wrap my mind around language and consciousness and someone thinking in braille or sign language or a feeling-voice I can't comprehend is proving difficult. The more I learn, the less I know proves itself once again. 

If forced to choose, would you choose sight or hearing? 

The following was said by Helen Keller, born blind and deaf: "The problems of deafness are deeper and more complex, if not more important, than those of blindness. Deafness is a much worse misfortune. For it means the loss of the most vital stimulus--the sound of the voice that brings language, sets thoughts astir and keeps us in the intellectual company of man." 

If forced to choose, would you choose sight or hearing? 

Image: Because Zombies.﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-eVnZgksXXh4/UNRZq7MxdyI/AAAAAAAA_8o/w9x87mc-M70/w426-h261/333556_9376033_lz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/111218007346771477342/albums/6004998246120673185/6004998249455735394</link><title>BAD EFFECTS OF USING EARPHONES - 
We feel that how awesome or beneficial earphones may seem. But, they still have their downside. 

Hearing Loss: 
One of the main side effects of listening to loud music is hearing loss. According to Dr. Brian Fligor, the director of Diagnostic Audiology at Boston Children's Hospital, people who listen to music at volumes exceeding 90 decibels, can suffer temporary loss of hearing. Sounds in this range can eventually cause permanent hearing loss, especially to teenagers who wear their earphones for long periods of time. 

Decibel Ranges: 
Decibels are the measurement of loudness. If you listen to music at a restrained volume, then you don't have to worry. However, if you listen to music at the highest volume possible might want to consider the following warnings. If you listen to your music using earphones at 85 decibels, you can get permanent hearing loss if you listen up to eight hours a day. At 88 decibels, you can get the same result at just four hours of listening time. Now for the painful truth, you can lose your hearing in just 15 minutes if you listen at 100-105 decibels. 

Ear Infections: 
Since earphones are made for two ears, it is quite inevitable that people share them. According to the Manchester Evening News, regular use of earphones can enhance the growth of harmful bacteria, and sharing or borrowing earphones may just cause the transfer someone else's bacteria to your ears. Research leader, Dr. Chiranjay Mukhopadhyay, advises everyone to avoid sharing earphones. If it cannot be helped, sanitize them before using. 

Tips and Warnings: 
Do not use earphones that are inserted directly into your ear canals because, even though they can make the music sound better, they enhance the chances of hearing loss will also increase. You should also try taking 5-minute breaks every hour. This will help your ears recover from being bombarded by concentrated sound waves. Last but not least, if you can use speakers at a moderate level instead, then do so because they will disperse the sound waves and not cause as much direct damage to your ear drums. 

PLEASE SHARE WITH EVERYONE﻿

Meer lezen (40 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-qZLLk_2nQ_Q/U1YKF4-m0mI/AAAAAAAAFPk/LXJjbXUcecg/w426-h388/10155365_486939781432736_3959601799963206165_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/113513382671152284499/albums/5877847710386627297/5877847707558520130?authkey=CIPZ88azodSkXQ</link><title>DID YOU KNOW? Ear buds are more likely to cause hearing damage than headphones that sit over the ear as they can also be up to 9 dB...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_sx5QF-8lm0/UZJPWQzepUI/AAAAAAAAAMw/QE-iChw0bYk/w426-h237/24rb7.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7144-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/can%20headphones%20cause%20hearing%20loss/photos/115648103846482447145/albums/5977181386930011553/5977181390950382418?sqi=116668312022536853330&amp;sqsi=dd5ae20f-1ca6-4350-9a56-445d86e40c6b</link><title>A FRIENDLY REMINDER 

What are the Effects of Hearing Music Through Earphones? 

[Take time to read...] 

If you enjoyed listening to your favorite music with high volume, actually there is research that says that it has a positive impact. According to research conducted at the University of Manchester, there is evident that the greater the sound of music that we hear, the greater our pleasure. It is caused by the vestibular system, which is responsible for balance but also cause vibration. When the sound wave is sent, it also sent a positive message to the brain. According to researcher Neil Todd, it is the influence of primitive acoustic sense we are connected with basic desires such as sex or hunger. 

But do not forget, that the high volume to hear music also has a negative impact quite dangerous to the health of our ears. The negative impact will be felt quite diverse as echo ears until the inability to hear and as yet known how to prevent it. 

The fact there is said that the sound power of the clubs and rock concerts could reach up to 125 decibels. Though, mild strength voice for adults only 25 to 40 decibels, while for children 20 to 40 decibels. Strength of the heaviest sounds that are still quite safe for the human ear is 90 decibels. Figures 85 decibels for eight hours is still considered safe, but if it increases up to 88 decibels, we should prune up to half an hour. Besides the danger hear loud music in clubs or rock concerts, there are also dangers posed by the listening habits of portable music players, such as MP3 players and I-pod are wearing earphones or headphones. These habits can also make ear injury. Based on research, It will be devastating when using earphones for five hours a week, this can cause permanent damage to the ear. The impact is not going to be felt in the near future, but one day listening skills can be lost. Even according to nine researchers from committee on emerging and newly indentified health risk of hearing loss due to too often listen to music with earphones will be felt in the mid of 20s. 

Although quite a lot of negative impacts gained from high-volume to hear music, there is still many people ignore the impact that it receives, because the music will make brain cells more stimulated so that it can eliminate the tedium and boredom from routine. Therefore, if we love to hear high-volume music is better to use a special ear protectors can reduce the music volume without ruining the sound quality. Or if love to hear music through earphones, we should choose a design that is safe and able to block some sound output without lowering quality. 

Source: bit.ly/1eq36H4﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7144_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BIyNl2LeORM/UvM2zn2sO1I/AAAAAAAAasA/lSYRP-Fj8Qs/w426-h319/1798518_695842153788374_1207455510_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>