<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:59:14" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/100697624494719030243/albums/5925418208205266865/5925418216018236338?authkey=CLCD1NOfiv7qswE</link><title>Why do leaves change color every fall? 

Answer: http://to.ehow.com/16iMmrq 

[Hint: Carbohydrates--turns out trees love 'em just as much as we do.]﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Nap3nIH1GJ0/UjtQeSdlU7I/AAAAAAAAMZE/FVaR-M4EZPE/w426-h415/1002610_10151737707066026_251388513_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/102179825788477461360/albums/5784710148169329905/5784710148500030418</link><title>Why do leaves change colors in fall? A handy infographic. http://bit.ly/Tigyl8 
#nature   #photosynthesis   #fallcolors  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-skrYoxeDipg/UEdrOznxA9I/AAAAAAAAAcw/L37cgbvFz5A/w426-h852/why%2Bdo%2Bleaves%2Bchange%2Bcolors-infographic***b.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/106613472282175348979/albums/5656253748469147201/5656253747304701794</link><title>AUTUMN COLORS 

I love the colors of autumn leaves. But why do leaves change color in the fall? There are 3 main pigments in the leaves. 

CHLOROPHYLL 

The color of leaves in spring and summer is green, because of a pigment known as chlorophyll. Chlorophyll is the power-station in the leaves, where light energy is converted to chemical energy. The light absorbed by chlorophyll supplies the energy used by plants to transform carbon dioxide and water into oxygen and carbohydrates (type of sugar). Chlorophyll is not a stable compound. To maintain the amount of chlorophyll in their leaves, plants continuously synthesize it. The synthesis of chlorophyll in plants requires sunlight and warm temperatures. 

CAROTENE 

Another pigment found in the leaves of many plants is carotene, which appears yellow. Carotene is a much more stable compound than chlorophyll. Carotene persists in leaves even when chlorophyll has disappeared. When chlorophyll disappears from a leaf, the remaining carotene causes the leaf to appear yellow. 

ANTHOCYANINS 

A third pigment in leaves are anthocyanins. The light reflected by leaves containing anthocyanins appears red. The color produced by these pigments is sensitive to the pH of the cell sap and the reaction also requires light. If the sap is quite acidic, the pigments impart a bright red color, if the sap is less acidic, its color is more purple. 

CHANGES IN THE FALL 

During summer chlorophyll causes the leaves to appear green. The shortening days and cool nights of autumn trigger changes in the tree. The production of chlorophyll in the leaf declines, and the green color of the leaf fades. If the leaf contains carotene, as do the leaves of birch and hickory, it will change from green to bright yellow as the chlorophyll disappears. In some trees, as the concentration of sugar in the leaf increases, the sugar reacts to form anthocyanins. These pigments cause the yellowing leaves to turn red. Red maples, red oaks, and sumac produce anthocyanins in abundance and display the brightest reds and purples in the autumn landscape. Autumn colors is greatly influenced by the weather. Bright sunshine also destroys chlorophyll and enhances anthocyanin production. Dry weather, by increasing sugar concentration in sap, also increases the amount of anthocyanin. So the brightest autumn colors are produced when dry, sunny days are followed by cool, dry nights. The only pigments that remain are tannins, which are brown.﻿

Meer lezen (49 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-jQcMp7mu48w/Tn8M0KeRn2I/AAAAAAAAAQ0/_Z3hNLTGi7I/w426-h237/tnemes_20101011_0239p.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/101209194359473019649/albums/5936233902802621729/5936233905766938306?sqi=101202846634554139673&amp;sqsi=122a6bb5-76bc-4697-a281-765f457c1bd8</link><title>There are leaves that do not fall as hard as the wind, there are moments, people and deeds that do not forget, even if forgetting is a law of nature.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-fRPWhJMikTU/UmG9SSjeNsI/AAAAAAAAcSg/P2FJG1G2bg8/w426-h284/1379781_422509877854121_86748404_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/107911807758392215627/albums/5940189432726885777/5940189440490272434</link><title>Do you want some beautiful Fall leaves.....to eat that is?!  I made some for you! 
http://asweetbaker.com/fall-leaf-sugar-cookies/ 
#cookies   #sugarcookies   #Fall   #leaves  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-_fQcOotJRu4/Um_K0try9rI/AAAAAAAACHs/SCA2oAYIkCw/w426-h639/Fall-Leaf-Sugar-Cookies3.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/110970845904049786016/albums/5938338023030592593/5938338028801890354</link><title>Did you know fall leaves contain nutrients that help your garden grow? Or that they help boost water retention which is great for a dry lawn? 

+houzz put together a great guide to reusing your leaves this fall to help your landscaping. 

http://goo.gl/C1TJm7 

Do you reuse your leaves, burn them, or toss them in the trash? 

#fall   #fallleaves   #landscaping  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-D5GDoPPIocA/Umk2-XruGDI/AAAAAAAABeY/gryx98ySa-c/w426-h281/fall_leaves.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/117556009102039073349/albums/5755022618709040689/5755022619137739858</link><title>My life is like autumn leaves 
Do you go to fall to the ground turned into yellow 
Lost into the wind crumbles 
I do not come on my love﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-tZHP5P7Utek/T93ylKgLDFI/AAAAAAAAAvw/xTwTizhf8K0/w426-h341/4ys0iz1cz9mt5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/101934872474396213977/albums/5942821527774961937/5942821533796703714</link><title>Do you know why leaves change color in the fall? Read the answer here: &lt;del&gt;-&lt;/del&gt;&gt; http://bit.ly/1ffrzfl #biology #botany #ecology #wyzantanswers﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-RuHKC-8c_Mo/UnkkstV-neI/AAAAAAAAAyw/Z9qA2BYeZBo/w426-h638/fall%2Bleaves.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/114570895856760708794/albums/5930238207842769361/5930238208925453010</link><title>Leaves are falling already! Do you have a plan for Fall season maintenance for you home? Here are just a few helpful tips and steps to follow for cleaning, maintaining and repairing gutters yourself. 

Read more here &gt;&gt;&gt; http://goo.gl/f4YdOd 

#diyproject   #DIY   #repair   #fallseason  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-RctkYzqwc4U/UkxwOzRzStI/AAAAAAAAB-c/STieK31E4hg/w426-h283/campus-handyman-leaves-in-gutters-columbus-ohio-state-maintenance-provider.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7146-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20do%20leaves%20fall/photos/107771181372242547518/albums/5943878594851198849/5943878596646588594</link><title>Fall Leaves 

The first ever body painting I did was in this style. It was a test image to get my first full gig. I've since painted it multiple times. 

Back when I produced this image, I often applied superimposed imagery as backgrounds. Now, I prefer to keep things as true to life as possible. 

If I were to do this over, I would definitely photograph her on location. 

www.RoustanBodypaint.com﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7146_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-FejEXRxQtx4/UnzmF3Uq0LI/AAAAAAAAc10/15gSxAThIjA/w426-h605/4.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>