<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:08:35" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/118241394497978714287/albums/5808548614037379185/5808548620034085202</link><title>Is Breast Cancer Being Over-diagnosed? 

Breast cancer screening review in UK concludes mammography benefits outweigh harms. 

Read more at: http://www.1-800-oncologist.com/news-article/breast-cancer-screening-review-uk-concludes-mammography-benefits-outweigh-harms﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-B8fueq2G4dc/UJwcMeW3kVI/AAAAAAAABF0/coK7JPf7dWs/w426-h237/awoman.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/117203888618988736001/albums/5805807650617114465/5805807660253374066</link><title>Debating the merits of breast screening 

An independent review has cast doubt about the merits of breast cancer screening, recognising it saves lives but acknowledging also that it often triggers unnecessary treatment. 

The independent review panel, commissioned by the government and the charity Cancer Research UK, does recommend that screening, which saves around 1,300 lives every year, should continue, but stresses that about 4,000 other women, as a result of having a mammography, undergo unnecessary treatment for a cancer they were previously unaware of and which actually would do them no harm in their lifetime. The review does say that many cancers, picked up by screening, are tiny and slow growing and never get to the stage of affecting a person’s health. 

National cancer director Sir Mike Richards says the government is now looking at the leaflet which invites women in for screening and is considering rewording it so that women can make their own decisions and weigh up the advantages and disadvantages of being screened. 

The panel, led by Sir Michael Marmot, estimated that screening reduced the risk of dying from breast cancer by 20% and prevented 43 deaths in every 10,000 women screened. However, it also found that of those 10,000 women, an average of 681 cancers would be diagnosed of which 129 would be over-diagnosed - in other words picking up previously undetectable tumours which do not present a risk to that individual woman’s health. 

One leading critic of screening is Professor Peter Gøtzsche, who says the numbers of advanced cancers has not been reduced as a result of screening and, with this being one of the reasons why screening was introduced in the first place, questions should be asked as to what is the point of putting so many women through it. However, three leading breast cancer charities have praised the review for adding clarity to the debate and says it should reassure women that breast screening can be beneficial though they warned that women should always have access to clear and balanced information so they are in a position to make a choice as to their future. 

You can read our other news stories here: http://www.winstonsolicitors.co.uk/allnews﻿

Meer lezen (38 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TEzACzW1Lws/UJJfTnek5nI/AAAAAAAAAb8/0xkDCjUouN8/w426-h342/iStock_000008895431Medium.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/103430773410928392958/albums/5818560714291092289/5818560720017198210</link><title>This is a clear mini-review of the fundamental problems of cancer. The authors describe two methods of dormancy and make a case for decades of undiagnosed breast cancer. 

Read this review and sign up to receive Breast Cancer: Targets and Therapy journal (free): http://www.dovepress.com/dormancy-in-breast-cancer-peer-reviewed-article-BCTT﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-TVVtEoE8D-M/UL-uJZSqjII/AAAAAAAAAaw/WdM0D92WP2k/w426-h345/Untitled-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/102050635894370230017/albums/5940124463168968017/5940124463826841394</link><title>During the last few days of Breast Cancer Awareness Month I will review facts/figures and possible signs/symptoms to look out for. Nothing here is medical advice. If you have any signs or symptoms or are unsure about what you may have found please see your healthcare provider. Early detection is the best cure. If you are over 40 please get a mammogram every year and take someone with you. If you have a family history of breast cancer please be seen much sooner. 

3.) ANY NIPPLE DISCHARGE—PARTICULARLY CLEAR DISCHARGE OR BLOODY DISCHARGE 

It is also important to note that a milky discharge that is present when a woman is not breastfeeding should be checked by her doctor, although it is not linked with breast cancer. 

#allpinkallmonth #PINK #PINKtober #breastcancerawareness #thinkpink #fightlikeagirl #savethetatas #ihatecancer #ihatebreastcancer #mammograms #aworldwithoutcancerisaworldwithmorebirthdays #susangkomen #breasthealth #squeezetheboobies #whenpinkisjustacoloragain﻿

Meer lezen (18 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XnS1On58VB8/Um-PukwBrzI/AAAAAAAAKwU/1EMh9hTMmdQ/w426-h317/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/118241394497978714287/albums/5855630888318337329/5855630886663018386?authkey=CM22zenx087i8QE</link><title>Does HRT Cause Breast Cancer or Not? 

Women used to rely on hormonal replacement therapy (HRT)​ to calm the discomforts of menopause. Then a study linked HRT to breast cancer, and everything changed. 

A recent review questioned the conclusions of studies linking HRT and breast cancer. The researchers cited study flaws, biology and time as part of their reasoning. 

According to the reviewers, there’s not enough evidence to support or reject the claim that HRT causes breast cancer. A noted breast cancer expert disagrees. 

Read more at: http://www.1-800-oncologist.com/news-article/breast-cancer-study-conclusions-linking-hrt-and-breast-cancer-questioned 

#breastcancer   #HRT   #cancer   #disease   #oncology   ﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DkuJLSG6rc4/UUNhRFda15I/AAAAAAAACV4/scxEwpKk-S0/w426-h237/ladyshorthairs.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/114230165101521664137/albums/5994382074771426113/5994382076106306210</link><title>#Dartmouth researchers at its Norris Cotton Cancer Center have compiled a review of the role that information gathered through genetic testing plays in the diagnosis and treatment of breast cancer. The paper entitled "Personalized Therapy for Breast Cancer" was accepted on March 17, 2014, for publication in Clinical Genetics. The paper discusses targeted therapies, new biomarkers, and the quality of commercially available testing methods. 
Learn more: http://cancer.dartmouth.edu/about_us/newsdetail/65978/ #cancer #breastcancer ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-2tSY0nCf0Kc/UzBSvRZI8qI/AAAAAAAAAbI/GFP2Unwa7N8/w426-h284/breastcancerresearch.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/100177140109550749246/albums/5936156751860050161/5936156758230946754</link><title>Scientists have created a new technique for the treatment of breast cancer that may spare healthy tissue in the body. The new treatment involves injection of therapeutics via the nipple. Because breast cancer most commonly originates in the milk ducts, this targeted method would spare healthy regions of the body. 

“Local delivery of therapeutic agents into the breast, through intra-nipple injection, could diminish the side effects typically observed with systemic chemotherapy—where the toxic drugs pass through all of the tissues of the body,” said Dr. Silva Krause, one of the researchers behind the experiment, “It also prevents drug breakdown by the liver, for example, which can rapidly reduce effective drug levels.” 

Silva says she and her colleages have been utilizing a new technique involving the injection of a nanoparticle-based therapeutic that inhibits a gene that drives breast cancer formation. 

“This targeted treatment was shown to prevent cancer progression in mice that spontaneously develop mammary tumors, [and] is currently in review in Science Translational Medicine.” Said Silva 

This study was published to JoVe, the Journal of Visualized Experiments. See the press release for the video: 

http://www.jove.com/about/press-releases/74/sparing-the-body-breast-cancer-treatment-via-nipple-injection﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-t_eLEaz_4aI/UmF3Htlj08I/AAAAAAAAAYs/W1SWzaV5QkQ/w426-h768/images.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/110360704593329082086/albums/5762172234260441361/5762172235060701650</link><title>Review articles: 

BET domain co-regulators in obesity, inflammation and cancer. 

Bromodomain proteins are chromatin 'readers' which recruit chromatin-regulating enzymes, including 'writers' and 'erasers' of histone modification to target promoters and to regulate gene expression. Conventional wisdom held that complexes involved in chromatin dynamics are not 'druggable' targets. However, small molecules that inhibit bromodomain and extraterminal (BET) proteins have been described. Article discusses the implications for small molecule epigenetic targeting of chromatin networks in cancer. Examples include the first-generation BET-specific inhibitor JQ1 that proved to be highly effective against NMC (NUT midline carcinoma) xenografts in mice and promoted both growth arrest and differentiation of NMC cells in vitro. While JQ1 is not selective for any of the BET bromodomains (BRD 2, 3, 4, BRDT), there are other bromodomain containing proteins (e.g., ATAD2) that have no small molecule inhibitor available. Epigenetic inhibitors for non-BET bromodomain proteins are sought for applications, such as breast and prostate cancer. 

Nature Reviews | Cancer 2012 Jun 22;12(7):465-77 | doi: 10.1038/nrc3256﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_08_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-7R5wx0OZHbo/T_dZHlVpadI/AAAAAAAAALg/w93lEwoNa_I/w426-h306/BET%2Binhibitors.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/100329139366567921157/albums/5714999980707388097/5714999979883637426</link><title>You can’t pick your parents, but you can pick your weapons – 5 foods, spices, and drinks to give breast cancer the boot 

1\. Brassica vegetables. Cabbage, broccoli, Brussels sprouts, and other members of the Brassica family come packed with a cancer-fighting compound called indole-3-carbinol (I-3-C), which helps detoxify the “bad” estrogens. A study in the journal Cancer Research concluded that Chinese women who consumed lots of Brassica vegetables significantly reduced their breast cancer risk. Because of their high immune-boosting sulfur content, these veggies often get a smelly reputation. But even your most finicky eater will devour Brussels sprouts in garlic and olive oil or faux-tatoes (mashed cauliflower). 

2\. Green tea. A study in the journal Integrative Cancer Therapies concluded green tea could help prevent breast cancer recurrence in early-stage cancers. That’s because it comes loaded with antioxidants, including EGCG, which can block several enzymes cancer cells need to reproduce and flourish. Green tea also has a calming reputation thanks to the amino acid theanine, which can lower stress hormones. Enjoy green tea hot or cold, but drink it often. 

3\. Curcumin. Turmeric is a popular spice in Middle Eastern dishes like curry that lends an orange pigment. Curcumin, the primary antioxidant in turmeric, offers numerous health benefits including reduced inflammation and liver detoxification. A study in the journal FEBS Letters showed curcumin can trigger apoptosis in cancer cells. To get these benefits, sprinkle turmeric liberally on your food and supplement with Meriva-SR or Meriva-500 from Thorne Research, which offer a highly absorbable therapeutic amount of curcumin. 

4\. Wild fish and fish oil. Omega 3 fatty acids, prevalent in wild salmon and other fish, support optimal cell membrane fluidity and reduce inflammation. A study in the journal Biochemical and Biophysical Research Communications showed fish oil prevents cancer cell metastasis, increasing the rate that cancer cells die off and slowing tumor growth. If you don’t regularly eat fish, you can get therapeutic amounts of omega 3s with Omega Plus from Thorne Research. Flaxseeds and chia seeds, which also offer omega 3s, provide a nutty boost to your morning protein smoothie. 

5\. Nuts. Raw almonds, walnuts, and pecans come loaded with Vitamin E, which studies show inhibit the growth of human breast cancer cells. Nuts also come packed with immune-boosting minerals like selenium as well as fiber. A study in the journal Cancer Causes Control found women who ate higher amounts of fiber and nuts during adolescence reduce their risk for breast disease. Researchers concluded nuts are an ideal way to prevent breast cancer. 

Sources: 
Choudhuri T, et al. Curcumin induces apoptosis in human breast cancer cells through p53-dependent Bax induction. FEBS Lett. 2002 Feb 13;512(1-3):334-40 

Fowke JH, et al. Urinary isothiocyanate levels, brassica, and human breast cancer. Cancer Res. 2003 Jul 15;63(14):3980-6. 

Mandal CC, et al. Fish oil prevents breast cancer cell metastasis to bone. Biochem Biophys Res Commun. 2010 Nov 26;402(4):602-7. 

Seely D, et al. The effects of green tea consumption on incidence of breast cancer and recurrence of breast cancer: a systematic review and meta-analysis. Integr Cancer Ther. 2005 Jun;4(2):144-55. 

Su X, et al. Intake of Fiber and Nuts during Adolescence and Incidence of Proliferative Benign Breast Disease. Cancer Causes Control. 2010 July; 21(7): 1033–1046.﻿

Meer lezen (64 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AqKJwcXlLUU/T0_CM8xUKrI/AAAAAAAAADA/lLTIEe12uNQ/w426-h283/Brassica%2Bveg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7147-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/breast%20cancer%20review/photos/106403167086053809814/albums/5930930117491315841/5930930118221180946</link><title>Celebrating and honoring the life of Judy, my best friend who passed to breast cancer and honoring these courageous women for sharing their voice and partnering to help make a difference! Excited to present "A Champion's Guide To Thriving Beyond Breast Cancer" - Book Signing and Screen Show. Please join us at 6:30pm Sat Oct 5th at: Hilton Garden Inn - 8270 N. Tamiami Trail, Sarasota, Fl 34243. 
Thank you Connie Hicks for your generous review of latest book. Now available in your favorite bookstores and http://janetimueller.com/ 

"The book was absolutely inspiring and motivating. As a breast cancer survivor, it touched and encouraged my soul to the core. I felt God all over and throughout your book. Definitely much more than a book-it's a life-changer for so many I'm sure. You are such a blessing" - Connie Hicks﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7147_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-3R86vKbNFZ0/Uk7lhOQ9MBI/AAAAAAAAAbU/uEsh7YLFfM8/w426-h523/IMG_1189.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>