<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:30:00" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/110348757624119773251/albums/5986505710659441729/5986505707199817330?sqi=104191988121507435081&amp;sqsi=544704b7-5e28-4e4f-80af-1d9ce5451ef1</link><title>Hey could anyone help me with the name or location of this small vatican like place where the Nuns were taking care of these pig-like people. &amp; by pig-like that means they had the exact pig face features, long pig ears, even hoofed shaped feet. &amp; it was found out that these ill-genetics were the offsprings of the Nuns having mated with the Priest. Later on thru-life, was it St. Peter or St Frances who had one of these kids that was kept hidden beneath the vatican, thru one of the secret underway passages..? 
From these marked people is where the pig latin had came from... If you're one to know hope this could refresh your memory. I just need the very name or location of the lil small town like vatican. 
Thanks in Advance."﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-UzC_tnHMcq0/UxRXOQt-ZnI/AAAAAAAAEXE/JGGTbLZM-D4/w426-h634/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/107130247487186913773/albums/5702396273635213377/5702396271040737106</link><title>BIOGRAPHY Google Search - Nelio Guerson Music Download 
google search | nelioguersonmusicdownload 

Google Search 
The Google homepage 
http://www.google.com (Original) 
https://www.google.com (Secure Version) 
Commercial? Yes 
Type of site Search engine 
IPv6 support Yes, by arrangement or ipv6.google.com 
Registration Optional 
Available language(s) Multilingual (124) 
Owner Google 
Created by Sergey Brin and Larry Page 
Launched September 15, 1997 (1997-09-15) 
Alexa rank 1 (July 2011) 
Revenue From AdWords 
Current status Active 

Google Search or Google Web Search is a web search engine owned by Google Inc. and is the most-used search engine on the Web. Google receives several hundred million queries each day through its various services. The main purpose of Google Search is to hunt for text in webpages, as opposed to other data, such as with Google Image Search. Google Search was originally developed by Larry Page and Sergey Brin in 1997. 

Google Search provides at least 22 special features beyond the original word-search capability. These include synonyms, weather forecasts, time zones, stock quotes, maps, earthquake data, movie showtimes, airports, home listings, and sports scores. (See below: Special features). There are special features for numbers, including ranges (70..73), prices, temperatures, money/unit conversions ("10.5 cm in inches"), calculations ("3*4+sqrt(6)&lt;del&gt;pi/2"), package tracking, patents, area codes, and language translation of displayed pages.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;The order of search results (ghits for Google hits) on Google's search-results pages is based, in part, on a priority rank called a "PageRank". Google Search provides many options for customized search (see below: Search options), using Boolean operators such as: exclusion ("-xx"), inclusion ("+xx"), alternatives ("xx OR yy"), and wildcard ("x * x").&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;The frequency of use of many search terms have reached a volume that they may indicate broader economic, social and health trends. Data about the frequency of use of search terms on Google (available through Google Adwords, Google Trends, and Google Insights for Search) have been shown to correlated with flu outbreaks and unemployment levels and provide the information faster than traditional reporting methods and government surveys.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In June 2011, Google has introduced "Voice Search " and "Search by Image" features for allowing the users to search words by speaking and by giving images.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Contents &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1 Search engine &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.1 PageRank&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.2 Search results&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.3 Non-indexable data&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.4 Google optimization&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2 Functionality &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.1 Search syntax&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.2 Query expansion&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.3 "I'm Feeling Lucky"&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.4 Rich Snippets&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.5 Special features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.6 Search options&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.7 Error messages &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.7.1 January 2009 malware bug&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.8 Doodle for Google&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.9 Google Caffeine&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.10 Encrypted Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3 Instant Search &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3.1 Negative reception&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3.2 Censorship&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;4 Features &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;4.1 June 2011 redesign&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;5 Google +1&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6 Adding the +1 button &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.1 Interface features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.2 Media features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.3 Navigation bar design&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.4 Google logo size reduction&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.5 Move of links&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7 International &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7.1 Languages&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7.2 Domain names&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;8 Search products&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;9 Energy consumption&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt; &lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search engine PageRank&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's rise to success was in large part due to a patented algorithm called PageRank that helps rank web pages that match a given search string. When Google was a Stanford research project, it was nicknamed BackRub because the technology checks backlinks to determine a site's importance. Previous keyword-based methods of ranking search results, used by many search engines that were once more popular than Google, would rank pages by how often the search terms occurred in the page, or how strongly associated the search terms were within each resulting page. The PageRank algorithm instead analyzes human-generated links assuming that web pages linked from many important pages are themselves likely to be important. The algorithm computes a recursive score for pages, based on the weighted sum of the PageRanks of the pages linking to them. PageRank is thought to correlate well with human concepts of importance. In addition to PageRank, Google, over the years, has added many other secret criteria for determining the ranking of pages on result lists, reported to be over 200 different indicators. The specifics of which are kept secret to keep spammers at bay and facilitate Google maintain an edge over its competitors globally.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search results&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The exact percentage of the total of web pages that Google indexes is not known, as it is very difficult to accurately calculate. Google not only indexes and caches web pages, but also takes "snapshots" of other file types, which include PDF, Word documents, Excel spreadsheets, Flash SWF, plain text files, and so on. Except in the case of text and SWF files, the cached version is a conversion to (X)HTML, allowing those without the corresponding viewer application to read the file.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Users can customize the search engine, by setting a default language, using the "SafeSearch" filtering technology and set the number of results shown on each page. Google has been criticized for placing long-term cookies on users' machines to store these preferences, a tactic which also enables them to track a user's search terms and retain the data for more than a year. For any query, up to the first 1000 results can be shown with a maximum of 100 displayed per page. The ability to specify the number of results is available only if "Instant Search" is not enabled. If "Instant Search" is enabled, only 10 results are displayed, regardless of this setting.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Non-indexable data&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Despite its immense index, there is also a considerable amount of data available in online databases which are accessible by means of queries but not by links. This so-called invisible or deep Web is minimally covered by Google and other search engines. The deep Web contains library catalogs, official legislative documents of governments, phone books, and other content which is dynamically prepared to respond to a query.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google optimization&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Since Google is the most popular search engine, many webmasters have become eager to influence their website's Google rankings. An industry of consultants has arisen to help websites increase their rankings on Google and on other search engines. This field, called search engine optimization, attempts to discern patterns in search engine listings, and then develop a methodology for improving rankings to draw more searchers to their client's sites.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search engine optimization encompasses both "on page" factors (like body copy, title elements, H1 heading elements and image alt attribute values) and Off Page Optimization factors (like anchor text and PageRank). The general idea is to affect Google's relevance algorithm by incorporating the keywords being targeted in various places "on page", in particular the title element and the body copy (note: the higher up in the page, presumably the better its keyword prominence and thus the ranking). Too many occurrences of the keyword, however, cause the page to look suspect to Google's spam checking algorithms.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google has published guidelines for website owners who would like to raise their rankings when using legitimate optimization consultants.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;It has been hypothesized, and, allegedly, is the opinion of the owner of one business about which there has been numerous complaints, that negative publicity, for example, numerous consumer complaints, may serve as well to elevate page rank on Google Search as favorable comments. The particular problem addressed in The New York Times article, which involved DecorMyEyes, was addressed shortly thereafter by an undisclosed fix in the Google algorithm. According to Google, it was not the frequently published consumer complaints about DecorMyEyes which resulted in the high ranking but mentions on news websites of events which affected the firm such as legal actions against it. There has also been a Google toolbar for use on many internet browsers.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Functionality &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Image of definition link provided for many search terms.Google search consists of a series of localized websites. The largest of those, the &lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt; site, is the top most-visited website in the world. Some of its features include a definition link for most searches including dictionary words, the number of results you got on your search, links to other searches (e.g. for words that Google believes to be misspelled, it provides a link to the search results using its proposed spelling), and many more.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search syntax&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's search engine normally accepts queries as a simple text, and breaks up the user's text into a sequence of search terms, which will usually be words that are to occur in the results, but one can also use Boolean operators, such as: quotations marks (") for a phrase, a prefix such as "+", "&lt;/del&gt;" for qualified terms, or one of several advanced operators, such as "site:". The webpages of "Google Search Basics" describe each of these additional queries and options (see below: Search options). Google's Advanced Search web form gives several additional fields which may be used to qualify searches by such criteria as date of first retrieval. All advanced queries transform to regular queries, usually with additional qualified term. 

Query expansion 
Google applies query expansion to the submitted search query, transforming it into the query that will actually be used to retrieve results. As with page ranking, the exact details of the algorithm Google uses are deliberately obscure, but certainly the following transformations are among those that occur: 

Term reordering: in information retrieval this is a standard technique to reduce the work involved in retrieving results. This transformation is invisible to the user, since the results ordering uses the original query order to determine relevance. 
Stemming is used to increase search quality by keeping small syntactic variants of search terms. 
There is a limited facility to fix possible misspellings in queries. 
"I'm Feeling Lucky"Google's homepage includes a button labelled "I'm Feeling Lucky". When a user types in a search and clicks on the button the user will be taken directly to the first search result, bypassing the search engine results page. The thought is that if a user is "feeling lucky", the search engine will return the perfect match the first time without having to page through the search results. However, with the introduction of Google Instant, it is not possible to use the button properly unless the Google Instant function is switched off. According to a study by Tom Chavez of "Rapt", this feature costs Google $110 million a year as 1% of all searches use this feature and bypass all advertising. 

On October 30, 2009, for some users, the "I'm Feeling Lucky" button was removed from Google's main page, along with the regular search button. Both buttons were replaced with a field that reads, "This space intentionally left blank." This text faded out when the mouse was moved on the page, and normal search functionality is achieved by filling in the search field with the desired terms and pressing enter. A Google spokesperson explains, "This is just a test, and a way for us to gauge whether our users will like an even simpler search interface." Personalized Google homepages retained both buttons and their normal functions. 

On May 21, 2010, the 30th anniversary of Pac-Man, the "I'm Feeling Lucky" button was replaced with a button reading the words "Insert Coin". After pressing the button, the user would begin a Google-themed game of Pac-Man in the area where the Google logo would normally be. Pressing the button a second time would begin a two-player version of the same game that includes Ms. Pacman for player 2. This version can be accessed at google.com as a permanent link to the page. 

Rich Snippets 
On 12 May 2009, Google announced that they would be parsing the hCard, hReview, and hProduct microformats and using them to populate search result pages with what they called "Rich Snippets". 

Special features 
Besides the main search-engine feature of searching for text, Google Search has more than 22 "special features" (activated by entering any of dozens of trigger words) when searching: 

weather – The weather conditions, temperature, wind, humidity, and forecast, for many cities, can be viewed by typing "weather" along with a city for larger cities or city and state, U.S. zip code, or city and country for smaller cities (such as: weather Lawrence, Kansas; weather Paris; weather Bremen, Germany). 
stock quotes – The market data for a specific company or fund can be viewed, by typing the ticker symbol (or include "stock"), such as: CSCO; MSFT; IBM stock; F stock (lists Ford Motor Co.); or AIVSX (fund). Results show inter-day changes, or 5-year graph, etc. This does not work for stock names which are one letter long, such as Citigroup (C) or Macy's (M) (Ford being an exception), or are common words, such as Diamond Offshore (DO) or Majesco (COOL). 
time – The current time in many cities (worldwide), can be viewed by typing "time" and the name of the city (such as: time Cairo; time Pratt, KS). 
sports scores – The scores and schedules, for sports teams, can be displayed by typing the team name or league name into the search box. 
unit conversion – Measurements can be converted, by entering each phrase, such as: 10.5 cm in inches; or 90 km in miles 
currency conversion – A money or currency converter can be selected, by typing the names or currency codes (listed by ISO 4217): 6789 Euro in USD; 150 GBP in USD; 5000 Yen in USD; 5000 Yuan in lira (the U.S. dollar can be USD or "US$" or "$", while Canadian is CAD, etc.). 
calculator – Calculation results can be determined, as calculated live, by entering a formula in numbers or words, such as: 6*77 +pi +sqrt(e^3)/888 plus 0.45. The user is given the option to search for the formula, after calculation. The calculator also uses the unit and currency conversion functions to allow unit-aware calculations. For example, "(3 EUR/liter) / (40 miles/gallon) in USD / mile" calculates the dollar cost per mile for a 40 mpg car with gas costing 3 euros a liter. The caret "^" raises a number to an exponent power, and percentages are allowed ("40% of 300"). There is also some debate as to Google's calculation of 0^0. Many mathematicians believe that 0^0 is undefined but Google's calculator shows the result as 1. 
numeric ranges – A set of numbers can be matched by using a double-dot between range numbers (70..73 or 90..100) to match any positive number in the range, inclusive. Negative numbers are treated as using exclusion-dash to not match the number. 
dictionary lookup – A definition for a word or phrase can be found, by entering "define" followed by a colon and the word(s) to lookup (such as, "define:philosophy") 
maps – Some related maps can be displayed, by typing in the name or U.S. ZIP code of a location and the word "map" (such as: New York map; Kansas map; or Paris map). 
movie showtimes – Reviews or film showtimes can be listed for any movies playing nearby, by typing "movies" or the name of any current film into the search box. If a specific location was saved on a previous search, the top search result will display showtimes for nearby theaters for that movie. 
public data – Trends for population (or unemployment rates) can be found for U.S. states &amp; counties, by typing "population" or "unemployment rate" followed by a state or county name. 
real estate and housing – Home listings in a given area can be displayed, using the trigger words "housing", "home", or "real estate" followed by the name of a city or U.S. zip code. 
travel data/airports – The flight status for arriving or departing U.S. flights can be displayed, by typing in the name of the airline and the flight number into the search box (such as: American airlines 18). Delays at a specific airport can also be viewed (by typing the name of the city or three-letter airport code plus word "airport"). 
package tracking – Package mail can be tracked by typing the tracking number of a Royal Mail, UPS, FedEx or USPS package directly into the search box. Results will include quick links to track the status of each shipment. 
patent numbers – U.S. patents can be searched by entering the word "patent" followed by the patent number into the search box (such as: Patent 5123123). 
area code – The geographical location (for any U.S. telephone area code) can be displayed by typing a 3-digit area code (such as: 650). 
synonym search – A search can match words similar to those specified, by placing the tilde sign (~) immediately in front of a search term, such as: ~fast food. 

Search options 
The webpages maintained by the Google Help Center have text describing more than 15 various search options. The Google operators: 

OR – Search for either one, such as "price high OR low" searches for "price" with "high" or "low". 
"-" – Search while excluding a word, such as "apple &lt;del&gt;tree" searches where word "tree" is not used.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;"+" – Force inclusion of a word, such as "Name +of +the Game" to require the words "of" &amp; "the" to appear on a matching page.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;"*" – Wildcard operator to match any words between other specific words.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Some of the query options are as follows:&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;define: – The query prefix "define:" will provide a definition of the words listed after it.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;stocks: – After "stocks:" the query terms are treated as stock ticker symbols for lookup.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;site: – Restrict the results to those websites in the given domain, such as, site:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.acmeacme.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;. The option "site:com" will search all domain URLs named with ".com" (no space after "site:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;allintitle: – Only the page titles are searched (not the remaining text on each webpage).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;intitle: – Prefix to search in a webpage title, such as "intitle:google search" will list pages with word "google" in title, and word "search" anywhere (no space after "intitle:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;allinurl: – Only the page URL address lines are searched (not the text inside each webpage).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;inurl: – Prefix for each word to be found in the URL; others words are matched anywhere, such as "inurl:acme search" matches "acme" in a URL, but matches "search" anywhere (no space after "inurl:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The page-display options (or query types) are:&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;cache: – Highlights the search-words within the cached document, such as "cache:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt; xxx" shows cached content with word "xxx" highlighted.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;link: – The prefix "link:" will list webpages that have links to the specified webpage, such as "link:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;" lists webpages linking to the Google homepage.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;related: – The prefix "related:" will list webpages that are "similar" to a specified web page.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;info: – The prefix "info:" will display some background information about one specified webpage, such as, info:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;. Typically, the info is the first text (160 bytes, about 23 words) contained in the page, displayed in the style of a results entry (for just the 1 page as matching the search).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;filetype: – results will only show files of the desired type (ex filetype:pdf will return pdf files)&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Note that Google searches the HTML coding inside a webpage, not the screen appearance: the words displayed on a screen might not be listed in the same order in the HTML coding.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Error messages&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Some searches will give a 403 Forbidden error with the text&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;"We're sorry... ... but your query looks similar to automated requests from a computer virus or spyware application. To protect our users, we can't process your request right now. We'll restore your access as quickly as possible, so try again soon. In the meantime, if you suspect that your computer or network has been infected, you might want to run a virus checker or spyware remover to make sure that your systems are free of viruses and other spurious software. We apologize for the inconvenience, and hope we'll see you again on Google."&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;sometimes followed by a CAPTCHA prompt.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt; &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's Server Error pageThe screen was first reported in 2005, and was a response to the heavy use of Google by search engine optimization companies to check on ranks of sites they were optimizing. The message is triggered by high volumes of requests from a single IP address. Google apparently uses the Google cookie as part of its determination of refusing service.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In June 2009, after the death of pop superstar Michael Jackson, this message appeared to many internet users who were searching Google for news stories related to the singer, and was assumed by Google to be a DDoS attack, although many queries were submitted by legitimate searchers.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;January 2009 malware bug &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;A screen-shot of the error of January 31, 2009.Google flags search results with the message "This site may harm your computer" if the site is known to install malicious software in the background or otherwise surreptitiously. Google does this to protect users against visiting sites that could harm their computers. For approximately 40 minutes on January 31, 2009, all search results were mistakenly classified as malware and could therefore not be clicked; instead a warning message was displayed and the user was required to enter the requested URL manually. The bug was caused by human error. The URL of "/" (which expands to all URLs) was mistakenly added to the malware patterns file.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Doodle for Google&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Main article: Google logo&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;On certain occasions, the logo on Google's webpage will change to a special version, known as a "Google Doodle". Clicking on the Doodle links to a string of Google search results about the topic. The first was a reference to the Burning Man Festival in 1998, and others have been produced for the birthdays of notable people like Albert Einstein, historical events like the interlocking Lego block's 50th anniversary and holidays like Valentine's Day.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google Caffeine&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;In August 2009, Google announced the rollout of a new search architecture, codenamed "Caffeine". The new architecture was designed to return results faster and to better deal with rapidly updated information from services including Facebook and Twitter. Google developers noted that most users would notice little immediate change, but invited developers to test the new search in its sandbox. Differences noted for their impact upon search engine optimization included heavier keyword weighting and the importance of the domain's age. The move was interpreted in some quarters as a response to Microsoft's recent release of an upgraded version of its own search service, renamed Bing. Google announced completion of Caffeine on 8 June 2010, claiming 50% fresher results due to continuous updating of its index. With Caffeine, Google moved its back-end indexing system away from MapReduce and onto BigTable, the company's distributed database platform. Caffeine is also based on Colossus, or GFS2, an overhaul of the GFS distributed file system.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Encrypted Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;In May 2010 Google rolled out SSL-encrypted web search. The encrypted search can be accessed at &lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;encrypted.google.com&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Instant Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google Instant, an enhancement that displays suggested results while the user types, was introduced on September 8 2010. One concern is that people will select one of the suggested results instead of finishing their request, and that such a practice could cause bias toward familiar businesses or other search terms. Pornographic or otherwise offensive search terms are excluded from the suggested results. The instant feature appears only on the basic Google site and not specialized iGoogle pages. Google expects Google Instant to save users 2 to 5 seconds in every search, which they say will be collectively 11 million seconds per hour. Search engine marketing pundits speculate that Google Instant will have a great impact on local and paid search.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In concert with the Google Instant launch, Google disabled the ability of users to choose to see more than 10 search results per page. Instant Search can be disabled via Google's "preferences" menu, but autocomplete-style search suggestions now cannot be disabled. A Google representative stated, "It's in keeping with our vision of a unified Google search experience to make popular, useful features part of the default experience, rather than maintain different versions of Google. As Autocomplete quality has improved, we felt it was appropriate to have it always on for all of our users."&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Negative reception&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Many users have reported being unable to save the Instant Search "off" setting in their Google preferences.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Censorship&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The publication 2600: The Hacker Quarterly has compiled a list of words that are restricted by Google Instant. These are terms the web giant's new instant search feature will not search. Most terms are often vulgar and derogatory in nature, but some apparently irrelevant searches including "Myleak" are removed.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;June 2011 redesignIn late June of 2011, Google introduced a new look to the Google home page in order to boost the use of the Google+ social tools.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google +1+1 helps people discover relevant content aimed to increase Google search result status offering a status to show people know and trust the content. When a signed-in Google user is searching, Google search result snippet will show an annotation with the names of the user's connections who've +1'd your page.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Adding the +1 buttonA small script is added before the closing header tag containing the Google Plus One Java Script and then on the website page position the button is added with &lt;g:plusone&gt;&lt;/g:plusone&gt;. Additional to this there is button sizes which are small (15px), medium (20px), standard (24px) and large (60px). A reference to a website URL can also be for example:&lt;/del&gt; &lt;g:plusone size="medium" href="WEBSITE URL"&gt;&lt;/g:plusone&gt;. 

Interface features 
Simple white background with time-to-time changes in the title, “Google” with a special historic day or to celebrate a certain day. 
Top bar has web, image, videos, maps, news, shopping, Gmail, and more. 
Voice search on Google Chrome like how you can use voice search on your phone. 
When you sign onto your Google account, you have a history of all the searches that you have done with that specific account. (only when your logged in) 
Google Instance, which instantly brings up what you are typing for example, if you are looking for “Google”. As soon as you type G and O the word Google will come up so it saves you time like a short cut. 

Media features 
Share your own picture to the world. You can upload your own picture. 
Image search with optional settings such as size, color, type, and sorting. 
Video search that is connected to YouTube. Also with optional setting such as duration, time, quality, also other sources that is related to the topic that you are searching. 

Navigation bar design 
One of the major changes was replacing the classic navigation bar with a black one. Google's digital creative director Chris Wiggins explains: "We're working on a project to bring you a new and improved Google experience, and over the next few months, you'll continue to see more updates to our look and feel." The new navigation bar has been negatively received by a vocal majority. 

Google logo size reduction 
The new design also has a reduced size logo. 

Move of links 
Links for advertising, business partners and company information pushed to the bottom edges of the browser. 

International 
Google is available in many languages and has been localized completely or partly for many countries. 

Languages 
Afrikaans 
Akan 
Albanian 
Amharic 
Arabic 
Armenian 
Azerbaijani 
Basque 
Belarusian 
Bemba 
Bengali 
Bihari 
Bosnian 
Breton 
Bulgarian 
Cambodian (Khmer) 
Catalan 
Cherokee 
Chichewa 
Chinese (Simplified) 
Chinese (Traditional) 
Corsican 
Croatian 
Czech 
Danish 
Dutch 
English (United Kingdom) 
English (United States) 
Esperanto 
Estonian 
Faroese 
Filipino 
Finnish 
French 
Frisian (West) 
Galician 
Georgian 
German 
Greek 
Guarani 
Gujarati 
Hausa 
Haitian Creole 
Hawaiian 
Hebrew 
Hindi 
Hungarian 
Icelandic 
Igbo 
Indonesian 
Interlingua 
Irish 
Italian 
Japanese 
Javanese 
Kannada 
Kazakh 
Kinyarwanda 
Kirundi 
Korean 
Kurdish 
Kyrgyz 
Laotian 
Latin 
Latvian 
Lingala 
Lithuanian 
Luganda 
Luo 
Macedonian 
Malagasy 
Malay 
Malayalam 
Maltese 
Maori 
Marathi 
Mauritian Creole 
Moldavian (Romanian) 
Mongolian 
Montenegrin 
Nepali 
Norwegian 
Norwegian (Nynorsk) 
Occitan 
Oriya 
Oromo 
Pashto 
Persian 
Polish 
Portuguese (Brazil) 
Portuguese (Portugal) 
Punjabi 
Quechua 
Romanian 
Romansh 
Runyakitara 
Russian 
Scots Gaelic 
Serbian 
Serbo-Croatian 
Sesotho 
Setswana 
Shona 
Sindhi 
Sinhalese 
Slovak 
Slovene 
Somali 
Spanish 
Sundanese 
Swahili 
Swedish 
Tajik 
Tamil 
Tatar 
Telugu 
Thai 
Tigrinya 
Tonga 
Tshiluba 
Turkish 
Turkmen 
Twi 
Uighur 
Ukrainian 
Urdu 
Uzbek 
Vietnamese 
Welsh 
Xhosa 
Yiddish 
Yoruba 
Zulu 

The interface has also been made available in some languages for humorous purpose: 

Bork, bork, bork! 
Elmer Fudd 
Hacker 
Klingon 
Pig Latin 
Pirate 

Domain names 
Main article: List of Google domains 
In addition to the main URL Google.com, Google Inc. owns 160 domain names for each of the countries/regions in which it has been localized. 

Search products 
Main article: List of Google products 
In addition to its tool for searching webpages, Google also provides services for searching images, Usenet newsgroups, news websites, videos, searching by locality, maps, and items for sale online. In 2006, Google has indexed over 25 billion web pages, 400 million queries per day, 1.3 billion images, and over one billion Usenet messages. It also caches much of the content that it indexes. Google operates other tools and services including Google News, Google Suggest, Google Product Search, Google Maps, Google Co-op, Google Earth, Google Docs, Picasa, Panoramio, YouTube, Google Translate, Google Blog Search and Google Desktop Search. 

There are also products available from Google that are not directly search-related. Gmail, for example, is a webmail application, but still includes search features; Google Browser Sync does not offer any search facilities, although it aims to organize your browsing time. 

Also Google starts many new beta products, like Google Social Search or Google Image Swirl. 

Energy consumption 
Google claims that a search query requires altogether about 1 kJ or 0.0003 kW·h.﻿

Meer lezen (737 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-H9ZYpSI-Dp0/TyL7MiflL1I/AAAAAAAAFS4/F81C747tRjA/w426-h237/Google-Music-Player-Logo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/110172490080527198738/albums/5801454721590596081/5801454724826709922</link><title>Genetically engineered micro-piglets make good pets (according to this article) 

&lt;snip&gt; the latest British fad in genetically engineered family pets - micro-piglets...Micro-piglets only grow to about 14" tall as adults, about the size of a medium-sized dog. They are very clean, easily house-trained, and love being held and petted. Jane Croft, a breeder of micro-piglets, says that micro-piglets will even "talk" to their owners (in Pig Latin?) and sit on their laps while they watch TV. Because their genetic makeup is combined by a mixture of several different breeds of pigs, micro-piglets are usually less bothersome for people with allergies, who might not be able to own a dog. They can also be trained to use a litter box.&lt;/snip&gt; 

source: http://www.buzzle.com/articles/these-little-piggies-are-like-family.html﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-sPhIGQq6-Ew/UILoVbXOv6I/AAAAAAAAC3I/OCObVxTD65k/w426-h411/335865-29514-0.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/113289985037799561231/albums/5954838185139138529/5954838182609928162?authkey=CKi7henM2_6Zew&amp;sqi=108841949284509753148&amp;sqsi=e045e62c-b8f2-4ba9-86cd-c9a394911768</link><title>Heyo 

Name Finn 
Sex Male 
Age 12 (debut) 
13 (as of "Mystery Train") 
14 (confirmed by Pen Ward, possibly until "Earth &amp; Water") 
15 (possibly as of "Earth &amp; Water," assuming he is the exact same age as Flame Princess, current age) 
Species Human 
Occupation Hero 
Adventurer 
King (formerly in "The Silent King") 
Wizard (formerly in "Wizard") 
Marceline's Henchman (formerly in "Henchman") 
Relatives 
[Expand] 
Jake (adoptive brother) 
Click "expand" for full list 
Introduced in Animated short (Pen) "Slumber Party Panic" (Finn) 
Voiced by Zack Shada (Pen) 
Jeremy Shada (Finn) 
Jonathan Frakes (adult Finn)[1] 
Finn (full title: Finn the Human, known as Finn Mertens in the Farmworld timeline and formerly as Pen in the original short) is the main protagonist of the series Adventure Time. 

Contents[show] 
Background 

Margaret finds Finn and adopts him. 
As shown in "Memories of Boom Boom Mountain," Finn appears to have been abandoned in the woods during infancy. He reveals that he made "boom boom" (Finn's word for defecation) on a large leaf, fell on it, and lay there crying until Joshua and Margaret (Jake's parents) rescued him from the wilderness to raise him alongside Jake, who becomes like a brother to him (as such, Jermaine is also Finn's adoptive brother). In "Memory of a Memory," a baby Finn is seen singing a song in the bathroom of what appears to be Joshua and Margaret's house. In "Henchman," when Finn is asked about his parents, he says Jake told him that he came from a cabbage, in jest. In "Susan Strong," Finn states that he knows nothing of his human parents or any other humans. 

Status as the last human 
Finn is the only confirmed human in the Land of Ooo. In the episode "Her Parents," Lady Rainicorn's dad says he thought humans were extinct. This lends new significance to his title "Finn the Human," as his humanity may be unique in Ooo. 

Up until "Susan Strong," Finn believes he has never met another human. Finn becomes morose and "soul-searchy" when he thinks about it. In the same episode, Finn encounters Susan Strong. Even though the other members of Susan's tribe of Hyoomans were revealed to be mutants, Susan's identity as a human or mutant is left ambiguous. In "Beautopia," it may be true that Susan is also a human, but it was not confirmed. The businessmen are also likely humans, but their minds have been damaged by being frozen for so long, and they talk like zombies. They also have boils all over their face, which may also be a result of being frozen. 

Other "human" characters (such as Penny, Phil or the Old Man Henchman) have been confirmed by the show's creator, Pendleton Ward, to be mutants or humanoids.[2][3] According to Pendelton Ward's FAQ page,[4] even Finn is mutated in some way. 

Fionna is also a human, although she is just a character in Ice King's fan fiction. Ice King was formerly a human, as shown in "Holly Jolly Secrets Part II." 

Moe, creator of BMO was also human but as he grew old, some of his functions were run by machines leaving only his skin and hair human. He is still now classified as a humanoid, since he is a human-like being that lives in the land of Ooo. 

Appearance and equipment 

Pen, Finn's original art design 
Finn is a 15-year-old human. He is roughly five feet tall. He has several missing teeth because he bites trees and rocks among other things.[5] 

Although his eyes typically lack detail and appear as small black dots due to a minor mutation,[6] they are shown to have color in the episode "The Enchiridion!," when Finn is tried by the Dark Magician. His left eye is green while his right eye is blue, characteristic of the genetic condition heterochromia. (However, as stated by lead character designer Andy Ristaino on Spring, "That was a special occasion. The heterochromatic effect was a byproduct of him being hypnotized by that guardian dude." Andy confirmed that Finn's eyes are blue.[7] 

Hair 

Finn has blonde hair which is first seen in "To Cut a Woman's Hair," where Finn removed his hat, and long, golden locks of hair flowed out. His hair had a glowing sheen and extended his body length, until he cut it off and gave it to the Tree Witch. His hair subsequently began to regrow, as shown in "Mortal Folly," "Heat Signature," "Apple Thief," "Beautopia," "No One Can Hear You," "Another Way," "Beyond this Earthly Realm," "Gotcha!," "You Made Me," "Who Would Win," "The Hard Easy," "The Lich," "Jake the Dog," and "All the Little People." In "Another Way," Finn's hair nearly touched his shoulders, and later in "Beyond this Earthly Realm," Finn's hair was shown to have grown past his shoulders. In "Gotcha!," Lumpy Space Princess saw an illusion of Finn with hair reaching his waist. Finn's hair is also seen in "You Made Me" when he blocks the blast from Lemongrab which caused his hat to rip off. A few strands of his hair also came out in "Who Would Win" after Finn got repeatedly beaten by Jake and they were evident throughout the majority of the episode. It makes an appearance in "The Hard Easy," having roughly the same length as in "Beyond this Earthly Realm." In "The Lich," Finn pulled off his hat showing it seemed a bit longer than in its appearance in "The Hard Easy." In the episode "Davey," Finn has shaved off almost all of his hair for the second time so he could disguise as 'Davey'. In "Little Dude," it started to grow again. In "The Great Bird Man," Finn's hair seems to be growing longer again. In "A Glitch is a Glitch," his hair is the same length from when it was first shown. In "Puhoy," Finn, as an adult, grew facial hair. His hair could also be seen in "Jake Suit." In "Love Games," his hair appears to be the same length it was in "You Made Me." In "Dungeon Train," it was a bit shorter than in "Love Games." 

Clothing 
Main article: Finn's hat 
Finn wears a white hat with two "ears" sticking out on top. The hat is inspired by a character called Bueno, a bear that appears in comics made by Pendleton Ward, the creator of Adventure Time. Consequently, Finn's hat is bear themed; coincidentally the Hyoomans wear animal themed hats as well. This might be a hint that humans in the Land of Ooo wear animal hats to fit in the society. Finn's hat covers his entire head except for his face. He also wears a light-blue T-shirt (or as he would call it, baby blue "boy-style"), denim shorts, a green circular backpack, rolled-down white socks, and a pair of black shoes. In "Ocean of Fear," his footwear appears to be black booties with white cuffs. In "It Came from the Nightosphere," Finn had a small pocket sewn onto his shirt that he carried Jake in. It appeared again in "Davey" for Finn to steal the keys from the guards and where he can hide Jake in when he broke out of Jail. When he is in the Ice Kingdom, he occasionally wears a yellow sweater, but has also recently worn his pink sweater made by Princess Bubblegum. In "In Your Footsteps," the Bear wears Finn's clothes, which may mean that Finn has multiple sets of the same outfit, along with multiple hats. However, in "Little Dude," when Finn's hat comes to life and is set free, Jake tells Finn, "OK, let's go skin an evil bear," which may imply that Finn only has one hat, or only had one hat left. 

He wears white briefs that made an appearance in "City of Thieves" when Penny stole his trousers at the end of the episode. In "Who Would Win," he was shown to wear a different pair with red elastic. 

Finn sleeps in red footie pajamas that have appeared in many episodes, but in the animated short, he sleeps in a red sleeping bag in his regular clothes. In the series, the sleeping bag is beige. 

Weapons 
Main article: Finn's swords 
Although Finn has wielded a number of weapons, he originally favored a gold sword. As of the episode "Mystery Train," Finn is shown using a new sword with a pink/silver blade and a red, twisted "root" handle. (Finn's original sword was destroyed by a black hole in "The Real You.") Along with his new root sword, his green backpack has a new side strap that can hold the sword while Finn is walking. In the episode "Dad's Dungeon," Finn and Jake ventured into Joshua's dungeon, which was built by Joshua to toughen Finn up. In the dungeon, Finn retrieves Jake's family sword, which has replaced the root sword as his primary weapon. Overall, Finn is known to have three main swords: a golden sword, a root sword, and the demon blood sword. However, this sword was snapped in half by Finn in "Play Date." It is unknown what sword Finn currently uses. They are a number of other swords seen being used by Finn, but it seems that he had not kept them. 

Main article: Finn's crossbows 
In "Conquest of Cuteness," Finn was shown to have a crossbow. He used a different one in "The New Frontier," although it appears he is not as successful as with one of his swords. 

Personality and character traits 
Though at times violent and aggressive, Finn is a brave and righteous hero. He has a very strong sense of responsibility and gets upset when he is unable to help others. He seems to be somewhat overprotective of his friends; such as when Tree Trunks almost got killed in the episode "Tree Trunks" and Jake in "The New Frontier." He is almost physically incapable of doing anything evil or unjust, and will struggle greatly against doing such things, as seen in several episodes such as "City of Thieves," "Mortal Recoil," "The Eyes," and "The Enchiridion!" Even though he acts like a normal boy, Finn acts like a gentleman when it comes to ladies. As revealed in "Davey," despite his heroic nature, he also takes a liking to a "normal life" without any recognition or praise for being a hero. 

Finn is shown to be a fearless thrill-seeker and enjoys putting himself in the midst of danger simply because he enjoys a challenge. However, as illustrated in "Ocean of Fear," Finn has an unexplained phobia of the ocean, or thalassophobia, despite the fact that he can effortlessly come into contact with any other body of water. While he portrays himself as a rough and tough hero, Finn has a tender side capable of love and compassion, as shown by his boyhood crush on Princess Bubblegum and his brotherly relationship with Jake. However, Finn seems to hate romance movies and kissing because in "Go With Me," he actually vomits during a kissing scene in a movie. However, at the end of "Dream of Love," Finn was not grossed out by Tree Trunks and the Pig kissing. Finn's growth in accepting romance and physical love is also demonstrated when he willingly kisses Princess Bubblegum in "Too Young" and his latest ex-girlfriend, Flame Princess, in "Burning Low." 

Finn's aspirations to be a great hero makes him somewhat of a moral sheriff in the Land of Ooo, as he is willing to help and protect any innocent person or creature. Finn appears to be somewhat simple-minded, seeing that he gets a lot of conflicting emotions when it is unclear whether something is good or evil (exemplified by his dealings with Marceline in the episode "Henchman"). 

Many aspects of Finn's personality are shrouded in mystery. In the episode "Rainy Day Daydream," it was shown that Finn believes "imagination is for turbonerds who can't handle how kick butt reality is," showing Finn not only accuses imagination users as "turbonerds" and believes life is fantastic. Finn then refused to use his imagination until he had to reactivate Jake's "bombastic personality" in his imagination land, (which was just a basic gray and white empty plane hinting that Finn is not very imaginative, but that was contradicted in "Power Animal" when the gnomes harnessed the energy from Finn's imagination) which was inhabited with a few dainty creatures such as Bellamy Bug. Finn's imagination was than powerful enough to effect the real world (like Jake's but to a lower degree) and turn on Jake's imagination. 

Finn can also be very stubborn; such as in "Memories of Boom Boom Mountain," "Wizard," "Dungeon" "Rainy Day Daydream," and especially in "Another Way." Finn can also be easily tricked, as in "The Eyes" when Jake convinced him that the giant hawks would take the horse to a land of sunshine and love stuff and take care of him. He can get overly angry and yell as in "Trouble in Lumpy Space" and "Tree Trunks," but he immediately feels guilt and remorse and apologizes when he can. Finn prefers to do work and not take the easy way out ("Business Time" and "The Real You"). 

While Finn is shown to be a courageous warrior, he is also shown to have several fears. In "Another Way" and "King Worm," he is shown to have a fear of clowns. Also in "King Worm" he is shown to have a fear of Bubblegum calling him too young, and he also fears the return of the Lich, or possibly just the Lich himself. He is also shown to fear the Ghost Lady ("King Worm," and "The Creeps") and the ocean ("King Worm," and "Ocean of Fear"). However despite all this Finn is a a really kind and selfless person always putting the safety of others above his own. Jake also says that "he is a good kid with a kind heart" a trait which is true and that Finn has throughout the whole series. 

Abilities 
Physical 

Finn's first sword 
Finn is proficient in several forms of combat, including hand-to-hand combat, magic, and swordsmanship. He can jump very high and is exceptionally strong and agile for a boy of his age. Despite his age and appearance, Finn seems to be quite strong and athletic; he can be seen wrestling full-grown Marauders, the large grass ogre Donny, and a general variety of monsters and creatures several times his size. Finn is also capable of lifting up Princess Bubblegum, as shown in "Mortal Recoil" when he picks her up and puts her in her bed, and capable of lifting up Marceline as seen in "Daddy's Little Monster." In addition, he was able to lift a tree and hit the giant spider Barb with it in "Web Weirdos." In "Another Way," Finn was able to run around carrying a giant cyclops' eye. Lastly, in "Dad's Dungeon," when he stabbed the Evil Monster in the eye, he was able to lift him up slightly off the ground and flip him into the pit. Being the size it is, the giant Evil Monster should have weighed at least a couple of tons, thus showing how strong Finn is. He also can make his arms and legs bend in inhuman ways, as during the Science Dance and when he uses "spaghetti limbs" (waving his arms and legs, which Jake can also do). In "The New Frontier," it is shown that Finn can make fire only with his hands. Finn is very tolerant to pain as shown in "No One Can Hear You" when the stag broke his legs; he just says, "whatever." Also, in "The Lich," he was able to break the Enchiridion on his knee. He even tries to teach Jake how to do pain tolerance in "Jake Suit," when he says," just pretend like every bruise is a hickey from the universe." Finn seems to have impeccable balance, as he was able to balance himself on two wheels in his wheelchair in the episode "No One Can Hear You." However, he refers to it as "skills." One of Finn's weaknesses is Short-Cone monochromancy (tendency to see the colors green and red as gray), as shown in "Red Starved." 

Mental 
Finn has the ability to mentally fight psychic abilities. The first time was against the Lich. The second time was against Goliad, as he was constantly able to manipulate his thoughts in order to avoid revealing the plan to defeat Goliad, allowing Princess Bubblegum to create Stormo. Finn can focus for a very long time as shown in "Still" when he spends hours telepathically summoning an Astral Beast. As demonstrated in "The Creeps," Finn can lock unwanted memories in "the vault," which is later seen in "King Worm." However, this is a normal human ability which is activated if the scene the person had witnessed is too traumatizing for them. Finn has the ability to read and write, and he can also do simple math. 

Creative 
Besides combat, Finn has displayed many other impressive abilities in handicraft. He has some origami skills, as shown in "Ricardio the Heart Guy," in which he makes Princess Bubblegum a paper crane, as well as in "Marceline's Closet," in which he makes a paper airplane. In addition to that, Finn is shown to be able to construct a sculpture (of the Candy Kingdom) from his saliva, which was also made for Princess Bubblegum in "The Real You." Finn is also somewhat gifted at constructing simple machines, such as the catapult in "The Witch's Garden." 

Musical 
Finn enjoys singing; after swallowing a tiny computer, he gained the ability to Auto-tune his voice on command, although he can sing without Auto-tune as well. Apparently, Finn can also play the flute, demonstrated in "Prisoners of Love," in which he played a short lick before javelin-throwing it at Ice King. Unfortunately, the flute fell apart before it could hit him, so Finn is not seen playing the flute again except as Farmworld Finn at the end of "The Lich" and near the climax of "Finn the Human" when he shoves it into Tromo's nose. He is also very good at beat boxing as seen in "It Came from the Nightosphere" and "What Was Missing." In "Gut Grinder," Finn tries to play Jake's viola, but Jake says he stinks. Jake even imitates his foot prints and said "I'm Finn the Human, and I stink at viola." However, during "Death in Bloom," Finn panicked over what instrument to pick, supposedly because he could not play any of them, and settles for sleigh bells. In the episode "Go With Me," Finn is seen playing the lute. In "Daddy's Little Monster," he is seen playing the tambourine. 

Miscellaneous 
Finn is very good at playing a video game called Adventure Master, which he and Jake play on BMO from time to time. He can also spit very long distances, as demonstrated in "Evicted!," when he spits on Marceline, in "My Two Favorite People," when he spits on Tiffany's face, and in "Web Weirdos," when he spits at birds flying overhead, while suspended upside down on a giant spider web. In "Dungeon," one of the trials that Jake says Finn would have breezed through is a spitting competition against a goblin-like creature. In "Burning Low," Finn is shown to be able to spit water incredibly high into the air. In "Who Would Win," Finn showers Jake with an abnormal amount of saliva through spitting. As seen in "Frost &amp; Fire," Finn normally writes with his right hand, but he can write and draw with both hands and occasionally at the same time. He additionally handles his sword with his right hand. Suggesting he may be ambidextrous, able to use both hands with equal skill. 

Temporary 
Finn and Jake gained magical abilities in the episode "Wizard," but they have never used those abilities in any other episode. Pendleton Ward later revealed on his Spring that all of the magic Finn and Jake gained in that episode was contained in their robes, which were destroyed.[8] Likewise, in "The Chamber of Frozen Blades," Finn and Jake gain ice-ninja skills, but it is unlikely they will use them again because, according to Adam Muto, "They didn't have enough time to commit the incantations and hand positions to memory."[9] Finn seems to speak Latin (as evidenced in "Morituri Te Salutamus,") although this may be caused by the magical powers of Fight King's arena. In "Daddy's Little Monster," for the first time, he becomes an antagonist by wearing the Nightosphere amulet, although it is only temporary. 

Fighting Style 
Finn is an aggressive hand-to-hand combatant, combining some forms of martial arts or his amazing swordsmanship skills. Finn prefers overpowering his opponents but when he has to, he is quick enough to understand an opponent's weakness or using his environment to win a fight. 

Cooking 
Finn isn't seen cooking very often because Jake cooked most of the meals they eat. However, in "In Your Footsteps" it mentioned and shown he makes Finn Cakes. 

Age 
Finn was 12 years old at the start of the series and is progressively growing older realistically.[10] As of "Mystery Train," he turned 13 years old. Finn is shown going through puberty throughout the series. This is seen whenever when he is screaming - his voice cracks. Finn's voice is noticeably deeper at 13 than it was at age 12, as a result of his voice actor aging. Episodes with early production codes have Finn with a very childlike voice such as "The Enchiridion," "Prisoners of Love," "Evicted," and "Ricardio the Heart Guy." 

In an interview in early 2012 (at the end of season three), Pen Ward stated that Finn is 14. 

After the episode "Earth &amp; Water," it was revealed that Flame Princess was 15 years old. Assuming that they were both the same age (In Incendium, Flambo and Jake stated that she was Finn's age), Finn would be 15 by now. 

Relationships 
Main article: Finn's relationships 
Disguises and alternate forms 
Older/Pillow world 
In the episode "Puhoy," Finn travels to a realm full of pillows where he starts a new life, becoming an adult and elder. 

Adult 

Elder 

Death Bed 

Add a photo to this gallery 
Lute suit 

Lute Finn 
In the episode "Go With Me," Finn is shown wearing a lute suit provided by his friend Jake in his attempt to convince Princess Bubblegum to go to the movies with him. It is also shown later in the same episode when he tries to get Marceline to go to the movies with him. 

Magic Fist 

Magic Fist Finn 
Magic Fist is the alter-ego of Finn and Jake that first appeared in "Wizard Battle." He is not a real wizard; he only entered Wizard Battle to save Princess Bubblegum from having to kiss Ice King for the prize was a kiss from her on the lips. He wore a blue eye mask, an electric-green hood, and a large red robe. Finn was the head, while Jake was the body. See the gallery section for more images. 

Cat Finn 

Finn was turned into a cat by the Grand Master Wizard when Finn had forfeited the Wizard Battle; however, Finn was able to break out of it, enraged by Abracadaniel deciding to take the kiss from Princess Bubblegum. 

Prince Hotbod 

Prince Hotbod Finn 
In the episode "The Creeps," Finn wears a black tuxedo ending in a split tail with blue trimming on the collar, a matching blue bow tie, a gray vest, a brown and tan fox mask over his characteristic hat, and brown "fancy gloves." 

Giant Foot Finn 

In the episode "Freak City," Finn is turned into a foot by Magic Man posing as a beggar. As a foot he has great difficulty moving at first, and only musters the effort to make himself fall over. Finn becomes depressed at his physical handicap while Jake tries to make him realize that being a foot is a blessing. Finn is unconvinced, and later in the episode he becomes motivated to return to his original body after discovering that Magic Man has turned many people into body parts as well. After creating Super Freak and seemingly defeating Magic Man, Magic Man restores Finn and the rest of the freaks to their original bodies. 

Zombie Finn 

Zombie Finn's appearance 
Zombie Finn looks like Finn, and apparently appeared in "Slumber Party Panic." Zombie Finn appears when the zombies break the barricades, in the bottom left corner of the first window to be broken open. Zombie Finn also appears in the Adventure Time game, Rhythm Heroes. In the game, Finn appears as a zombie just like in "Slumber Party Panic." He seems to be controlled by Marceline in the game, and he is next to two other zombies, a cupcake and a candy heart. 

Lumpy Finn 
Lumpy Finn 
In the episode "Trouble in Lumpy Space," Finn turns into a Lumpy Space person to give the antidote to Jake so that he can return back to his normal body. 

By doing this, he turns into a Lumpy Space person as well. Lumpy Finn hates Lumpy Jake. 

Demonic Finn 

Demonic Finn 
In "Daddy's Little Monster," Finn puts on the Nightosphere amulet to rescue Jake and Marceline from the Nightosphere. This causes him to transform into a huge, monstrous, demonic form similar to Hunson Abadeer. Afterwards, he tried to pull Jake and Marceline back in. He is reverted to his original form by Hunson himself. 

Paper plate demon Finn 

Paper plate Finn 
To sneak into the Nightosphere in the episode "Daddy's Little Monster," Finn disguises himself by putting on his red pajamas, cutting a paper plate and putting it on his face, and taping forks to his hat. 

Hug Wolf Finn 

Wolf Finn 
In the episode "Hug Wolf," Finn is hugged by the Alpha Hug Wolf on a full moon, causing him to transform every night into a Hug Wolf himself. When he is in this form, he must go on a hugging spree to fulfill his hug lust. When he awakens each morning after being in this form, he has no memory of the night. When a Hug Wolf, Finn's hands and feet are heart-shaped, he has shaggy gray fur, and he wears torn clothing. He is cured when he hugs the Alpha Hug Wolf, curing her as well. 

Jake's shadow 

In the episode "Princess Cookie," Finn dresses in a black bodysuit and pretends to be Jake's shadow in order to get into the grocery store and take out the Chocolate Chips. 

Alternate Universe Finn (Finn Mertens) 
Main article: Farmworld Finn 
In the episodes "Finn the Human" and "Jake the Dog" Finn is shown with a pointed nose, wide eyes, a robotic arm, and a blue sweater instead of a blue shirt. He became like this because of the wish that Prismo granted him. He is reverted when Jake makes his own wish. 

Davey 
In the homonymous episode, Finn disguised himself as 
Finn disguised as Davey "Davey" in an attempt to hide from his followers. This eventually evolves into his own character, possibly hinting Finn temporarily developed a multiple personality disorder. 
Shoko 
Main article: Shoko 
In "The Vault," it is revealed that the weird amorphous ghost lady that has seemingly been haunting him was Shoko, his former self in a past life that got horribly mutated. Finn completes her dying wish, by returning Princess Bubblegum's amulet that Shoko had stolen. 

Trivia 
In the Cartoon Network Live Action Promo "What Time Is It?" Finn is portrayed by Christopher Kramme. 
In Legends of Ooo, it is seen that Finn has a telescope which he uses to spy on Princess Bubblegum. 
Finn has only shown to be afraid of six things: 
Being too young and/or being rejected by his loved ones, seen throughout the series, revealed in "King Worm" 
The ocean (thalassophobia), as seen in "Ocean of Fear" 
Ghost Lady, as seen in "The Creeps" (conquered) 
The Lich, as seen in "Mortal Folly" 
Jake dying, as seen in "The New Frontier" 
Clowns (coulrophobia), as seen in "Another Way" 
Finn is technically still the King of the Goblins; the goblins believe his scapegoat, Whisper Dan, to be him. 
Finn has a fictional female counterpart: Fionna. 
One of Finn's catch-phrases is being "all about" something. In "Freak City," Finn says he is "frickin' all about sugar." Yet, he also explains that he is even more "all about feeding hobos." In "The Real You," Finn shouts "I'm all about stupid!" 
In "Dad's Dungeon," it is revealed that Finn cries rarely; only in such devastating situations, such as death or heartbreak. 
Finn and Jake frequently use math terms as catch-phrases and at times censors for curse words. However, they are shown to be terrible at math as confirmed in the episode "Slumber Party Panic." (Examples of these words include: mathematical, rhombus, algebraic and math). This has seemingly been abandoned as the show progresses. 
Finn's favorites have been stated throughout the series. 
Finn's favorite color is baby blue "boy style," as revealed in "The Silent King." 
Finn's favorite food is meatloaf, as stated in "Still" and later confirmed in "Jake Suit." 
Finn's favorite song sounds like an alternative version of "Itsy Bitsy Spider." 
When Finn is wearing his doctor suit in "His Hero," he has three Scientific Parasites in his pockets. 
In "Jake vs. Me-Mow," Finn carries his adoptive mother's music box in his pack and knows her lullaby by heart. 
Stormo is a creation partially made from Finn's DNA from the episode "Goliad." 
Flame Princess is Finn's first and former girlfriend. Jake referred to Princess Bubblegum as Finn's ex-girlfriend in "In Your Footsteps," but Finn replied that they "never went steady." 
It appears that Finn is the only character so far who ages consistently. 
In the beginning of the series, Finn's voice is more high pitched, but later near the latest episodes, Finn's voice is a bit deeper from puberty. 
There is a secret GPS implanted on Finn's ear by Princess Bubblegum, as stated in "Lady &amp; Peebles." 
Finn refers to Flame Princess as his girlfriend for the first time in "Puhoy." 
Each alternate form of Finn has a prosthetic limb, a mechanical right arm. Finn can be seen with one in "Finn the Human," "King Worm" and "Puhoy." In The Vault Finn's former self, Shoko, also is given a prosthetic limb. 
Besides Tree Trunks' pies, Finn also likes Wildberry Princess' meat pies. 
Finn likes to make lists to remember things, like in "The Real You" and "Five Short Graybles." 
Finn might be tolerant to high/extreme temperatures, as seen in the episode "Jake Suit" when Jake dipped his head in lava. This may be because he is already accustomed to heat from his relationship with Flame Princess. 
Finn's hat remotely resembles that of "Maxwell" in Scrbblenauts. 
Finn has deuteranomaly (tendency to see the color green as red); as shown in "Red Starved," he perceived a large emerald as being a ruby. 
In "Dungeon Train" Jake says Finn is about 5' tall. 
Cultural references 
Finn McCool was an adventurer and hero of Irish mythology. "Finn" is actually a nickname meaning "blonde." 
Production notes 
In the original short, Finn was named "Pen." 
In Issue 9, it is revealed that Finn had been called "Pen" in the original short because of his love for pens. A future Finn then takes his red sleeping bag when him and Jake leave to help Lady Rainicorn, also leaving a note of advice telling Finn to use his real name. This, however, is most likely non-canon. 
In the pilot, Finn is voiced by Zack Shada. However, in the series, he is voiced by Zack's younger brother, Jeremy Shada. 
Jeremy Shada can make Finn's voice crack when asked during episode recording to better represent his youth and growth. 
In the original storyboard of "The Lich," it is revealed that Finn's father was "unlawfully" brought to a crystal-like dimensional prison a few years ago. It keeps the most dangerous criminals from other dimensions and Finn's father still fights them. However, since this was not shown in the final project, it may not be canon. 
Appearances in other media 
Finn and Jake appeared four times on the series MAD. See References in other media for a detailed description. 
Finn appears as a playable character on Cartoon Network's TKO where his special moves are Look Out Below (when Jake falls on your opponent) and Sidekick Swing (when Finn grabs Jake's paw and Jake swings him at the opponent) and his super move is when Jake falls onto the opponent with an axe. 
Finn, Jake, Princess Bubblegum, Lady Rainicorn, Ice King, Stanley the watermelon, and the Reaper are characters in the game FusionFall, in which the player helps Finn save two princesses, get shirts from Stanley, and train with Finn in the petting zoo (Generator Rex). 
Like most of the main characters, Finn is an Exosuit in the game Project Exonaut. His suit is in the "Banzai Squadron" (red) faction. 
There is a licensed Halloween costume of Finn. 
In the popular Facebook game called "Pet Society," there is a Finn Costume labeled, "Odessey Boy Costume." 
Finn is a playable character in the game FusionFall Heroes. 
Finn and Jake make a cameo appearance in the Futurama episode "Leela and the Genestalk." 
Finn has a playable kart in the Cartoon Network app, Formula C Cartoon; it is one of the free karts given to the player at the beginning. 
A child in a Finn costume appeared in the Halloween episode of South Park. 
Finn and Jake had a balloon depicting them in the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade for 2013. 
Gallery 

﻿

Meer lezen (655 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QrbyOn4YD28/UqPVxullv-I/AAAAAAAAAZY/7vwIRef1Ivw/w426-h428/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/114963786071989905755/albums/5752947948744944721/5752947946075029266</link><title>Oil Lamp Pigs (Organize Relay Gems) 

LE MANISULLA CITTA 
Hands Over the City 
“Yes, the city spreading that way per the Urban Development plan.” 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hands_Over_the_City 
IL Generale Della Rovere, Roberto Rossellini  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_della_Rovere 
There are things one does with-out realizing one is doing wrong …. 

…. Penniless …. because I sold every-thing in order to live …. How can we forget these suffer-ings …. anxieties …. fears ?” “…. Put the lights out ….” 

“…. About this organization I have absolute urgent need to know every detail ….” 

“You say you know my past and present activities perfectly ….” “Knowing that, do you really think I can spy for you?” ~ OPEN CITY; Roberto Rossellini  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rome,_Open_City 
“You have the chance to earn what I promised you: freedom and a reward ….” 

“…. In Genoa you told me I was to be a decoy for the ducks. Now you want me to be the rifle too ….” 

ban·quet (băng'kwīt) n. 1. An elaborate and sumptuous repast. 2. A ceremonial dinner honoring a particular guest or occasion. &lt;del&gt;v. banqueted, -queting, -quets. -tr. To entertain at a ban-quēt. -intr. To partake of a banquet; to feast. [Old french, diminutive of banc, bench from Germanic. See bheg&lt;/del&gt; in Ap-pendix.*] -ban'quet·er n. 

ban·quette (băng-kĕt) n. 1. Military. A platform lining a trench or parapet wall where soldiers may stand when firing . 2. Southern U.S. A sidewalk. 3. A long upholstered bench, either placed against or built into a wall. 4. Any ledge or shelf, as on a buffet. [French, from Provencal banqueta, diminutive of banca, bench, from Germanic. See bheg- in Appendix*] 

Indo-European Roots 
ghedh- To unite, join, fit. 1. Lengthened o-grade form *ghōdh- in Germanic *gōdaz, “fitting, suitable,” in Old English gōd, good: GOOD. 2. Germanic *gadurī, “in a body,” in Old English tōgᴂdere (tō, To), together: TO-GETHER. 3. Germanic *gadurōn, “to come or bring together,” in: a. Old English gad( e)rian, to gather: GATHER; b. Middle Dutch gaderen, to gather: (FORGATHER), GARBOARD. 4. Ger-manic *gad- in Old English gᴂdeling, com-panion, comrade: GAD¹. [Pok. ghedh- 423.] 

ghei-¹. To propel, prick. 1. Suffixed and ex-tended o-grade form *ghoidh-ā in Germanic *gaidō, goad, spear, in Old English gād, goad: GOAD. 2. Suffix form *ghei-s- perhaps in nasalized zero-grade form *ghi-n-s in Sanakrit hiṁsati, he injures: AHIMSA. (3. Old English gār, spear, which in the case of its derivative OSCAR has accidentally been referred to this root, belongs to ghaiso-, which itself perhaps has some connection with ghei-¹.) [Pok. 1. ghei- 424.] 

ghei-². Theoretical base of *ghiem-, *ghyem-, winter. 1. From *ghyem-, in Latin hiems, winter: HIEMAL. 2. Suffixed zero-grade form *ghim-ri-no in Latin hībernus, pertaining to winter: HIBERNACULUM, HIBERNATE. 3. Suf-fixed zero-grade form *ghim-ar-ya, “female” animal one year (winter) old,” in Greek khim-aira, she-goat: CHIMERA. [Pok. 2. ghei- 425.] 

ghēi-, To yawn, gape. 1. Variant form *ghyā-in: a. nasalized form *ghyi-n-ā- in Germanic *ginōn in Old English ginan, ginian, geonian, to yawn: YAWN; b. Latin hiāre, to gape, be open: HIATUS, DEHISCE. 2. Suffixed variant form *ghə-smn in Greek khasma, yawning gulf, chasm: CHASM. 3. Suffix variant form *ghə-n in Greek khainein, to gape: ACHENE. 4. Labial extensions: a. Old Norse gap, chasm: GAP; b. Old Norse gapa, to open the mouth: GAPE; c. Old Norse geispa, to yawn: GASP. 5. Germanic *gil- in Old Norse gil, ravine, chasm: GILL³. 6. Germanic *gīr-, vulture (&lt; “voracious or yawning bird”), in Old High German gīr, vulture: LAMMERGEIER. [Pok. 2. ghē- 419.] 

gheis-, Used of the emotion of fear or amaze-ment (original part of speech uncertain). Suf-fixed o-grade form *ghois-dho- in Germanic *gaistaz, a ghost, in: a. Old English gāst, ghost: GHOST, AGHAST, BARGHEST, GHASTLY; b. Old High German geist, ghost: POLTERGEIST; c. Old English denominative gᴂstan, to scare: GAST. [Pok. gheis- 427] 

ko-. Stem of demonstrative pronoun meaning “this.” I. Variant form *ki-. 1. Germanic *hi-in: a. Old English he, he: HE¹; b. Old English him, him: HIM; c. Old English his, his; his; d. Old English hire, her: HER; e. Old English hit, it: IT; f. Old English heonane, from here: HENCE. 2. Suf-fixed form *ki-tro- in Germanic *hi-thra- in Old English hider, hither: HITHER. 3. Suffixedform *ki-s in latin cis, on this side of: CIS-, II. Variant form *ke-. 1. Prefixed form *ghi-ke (*ghi-, demonstrative particle; see ghe-) in Latin hic, this: ENCORE. 2. Preposed in ke-etero- (*e-tero-, a second time, again; see i-) in Latin cēterus, the other part, that which re-mains: ET CETERA. 3. Latin &lt;del&gt;ce (see nu&lt;/del&gt;). III. Attributed by some to this root (but more likely of obscure origin) is Germanic root *hind-, behind. 1. Old English hindan, behind: HIND¹. 2. Old English bihindan, in the rear, behind (bi, at, BY): BEHIND. 3. Old High German hintar, behind: HINTERLAND. 4. Ger-manic derivative verb *hindrōjan, to keep back, in Old English hindrain, to check, hinder: HIN-DER¹. [Pok. ko- 609.] 

Ossobuco 
Italian for “bone with a hole”, a reference to the marrow hole at the center of the cross-cut veal shank. The braising liquid is usually a combination of white wine and meat broth flavored with vegetables. 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ossobuco 
Crème brûlée 
Also known as burnt cream, crema catalana, or Trinity cream is a dessert consisting of a rich custard base topped with a contrasting layer of hard caramel. The caramel may be formed directly on top of the custard, immediately before serving. To do this, sugar is sprinkled onto the custard, then caramelized under a broiler/salamander, with a butane torch …. It is usually served cold in individual ramekins. 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cr%C3%A8me_br%C3%BBl%C3%A9e 
Can we believe what we see with our own eyes? 
“.... It's not (usually) the fault of our eyes, but our brains. What matters is not so much seeing as interpretation. And we interpret the world with brains that evolved to use vision to help us survive. That is why seeing arose at all. Evolution has honed our brains to exploit the reflective and refractive qualities of objects in the Sun's light, and we rely on a number of innate assumptions of how the world works: we expect that this wall is in shadow, or that building looks small because it is far away. Create an image that challenges these assumptions and we are misled. ~ SEEING THROUGH ILLUSIONS; Richard L. Gregory  http://ukcatalogue.oup.com/product/9780192802859.do 
“ …. Out of all the male migicians of the Golden Dawn era, Crowley was by far the most “Witchy” of the high migicians. He openly explored the shadow through sexuality and topics found too taboo, both profane and sacred by the society around him …. ” ~ The Temple of High Witchcraft, Ceremonies, Spheres and The Witches Qabalah.  http://www.llewellyn.com/product.php?ean=9780738711652 

Germed A Sheppard 
Presently through the rising mists we caught sight of Enzeli, a large village of squalid huts standing near the water's edge. 

The mis-er-able fever stricken inhabitants came running down to the landing-place to greet us, begging for coppers and quinine, a drug which appears to be considered a great luxury in this “malarious” locality. ~ Persia: The Awakening East, William Penn Cresson  http://books.google.com/books/about/Persia.html?id=bYhCAAAAIAAJ﻿

Meer lezen (140 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-RryuKYOCTek/T9aTrTEdfxI/AAAAAAAAAk0/0ns496_a5_0/w426-h320/PhilaArt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/118135535337532829792/albums/5983171885861274977/5983171891365295602</link><title>What should the EU do to help us out of the crisis? What are the rights of EU citizens and how do they affect people's lives? What Europe do we want in 2020? Join Commission Vice-President Viviane Reding tomorrow at 18:00 CET in Barcelona to debate the future of Europe. Ask your questions online using #eudeb8 and #RedingBCN . 

Watch it live here: http://europa.eu/!Nm69qj 

See our Citizens' Dialogue Pinterest board http://bit.ly/1f3srAZ 
#barcelona   #catalunya   #cataluña   #catalonia   #spain  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-xUhjEmOfUIk/Uwh_Io7uNfI/AAAAAAAAdKg/hHjB1jkw-zA/w426-h415/1620569_652477661466384_1401937874_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/111474406259561102151/albums/5671154171034870657/5671154167905518162</link><title>Rant of the Week #studentwriting Earlier this week, I wrote to someone I know on my campus who recently took a job at our campus Writing Center (http://www.ou.edu/writingcenter/). I used this as an excuse to ask about something I have asked about before and which to continues to be a big problem for me: I need a professional-quality online writing assessment to use as a diagnostic for my students' writing mechanics (spelling, punctuation, sentence structure). A good diagnostic tool could allow both the students and me to identify their problem areas right at the start of the semester. Moreover, the students could re-take the online assessment periodically to get a measure of their own progress in gaining the skills they lack. Right now, I have had to invent a diagnostic of my own (http://onlinecourselady.pbworks.com/w/page/44024314/proofreading), but it is time-consuming - it takes about 15-20 hours for me to mark in the first week (I start every semester with 90-100 students). This diagnostic does give me valuable information and is a good basis for interacting with the students, but it is not something I can do repeatedly during the semester, and of course it is also not a professional-quality diagnostic. It is homemade. 

So, I got a response from the Writing Center director. She told me that what I need to do is to use peer review software. This response made me feel very frustrated. Not only does this recommendation not meet my needs in any way whatsoever, but it also showed that this question is not even on the agenda of things that they are thinking about at the Writing Center. In other words: I feel totally alone at my school in what I am trying to do in grappling with writing mechanics, even though I know all faculty who assign written work to their students must be seeing the same problems that I am. 

Peer review is GREAT. I use it a lot - every week, in fact, both for student blogs and also for student projects. The problem is that my students are not capable of helping each other with writing mechanics. Out of all my students this semester, I would say that there are 5 who are fully competent in writing mechanics - but that does not mean they can help others. Instead, they are like fluent native speakers, unconsciously applying all the rules of the language but not consciously aware of those rules in order to be able to help others to apprehend them (ask a native speaker of English to tell you something about word order in English questions or about sequence of tense in indirect statement and you'll see them be amazed at the weirdness of the rules they actually do use, unconsciously, every day). 

Meanwhile, the Writing Center provides no online references or guidance of any kind for the problems with writing mechanics that almost every student faces. Yes, there are citation guides for APA, MLA, Chicago style and APSA. Yes, there is an abundant supply of anti-plagiarism propaganda. Yet there are no online resources to give students immediate, expert help with writing mechanics. There's not even a link to the Purdue OWL. Nothing that even acknowledges the problems students have with writing mechanics. Sure, you can make an appointment and come in for a session with a writing tutor - but one-on-one sessions like that are probably the least effective way to remediate problems with punctuation, for example. To be honest, I'm not all that confident that the writing tutors are trained to provide that kind of help (i.e. they fall into the "native speaker" category I mentioned above - great at unconsciously applying the rules themselves, but untrained at explaining the rules to others). Those kinds of problems are ideally suited for computer-mediated instruction, yet we offer nothing at all. Not even worksheets online. I have to do it all myself (a new work in progress here: http://writingwithaesop.blogspot.com/). For better or worse, I personally find all this stuff fascinating and am motivated to try to find my own solutions - but most faculty are not. Moreover, I am not really trained in this, except insofar as my professional training is in foreign language instruction, which admittedly helps a lot. I know that MY STUDENTS DESERVE BETTER. Why are there no professional-quality online resources available at my school to help me with basic sentence-level writing instruction? 

Instead, we have… TURNITIN. If you look at the Writing Center website, you would conclude that plagiarism is a huge problem, worthy of our constant vigilance. You would also conclude that there are apparently no students who have problems with writing mechanics. Yet I would say just the opposite is true: very few students plagiarize, but almost every single student has some kind of problem with writing mechanics, and many students have problems that are both numerous and serious. In addition, I would guess that poor writing skills contribute to the plagiarism problem, such as it is. From personal experience, I have seen that students who are not confident in their writing skills are in fact more tempted to copy-and-paste than students who are confident in their writing abilities. 

So, here's my conclusion for this week's rant: I would argue that basic writing skills are a far far FAR bigger problem than plagiarism on my campus. I am still waiting for someone… anyone… at my school to say so in public and to do something about it.﻿

Meer lezen (86 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_07_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-bbwYWj26Ryc/TrP8qyx8AlI/AAAAAAAA5c4/ZVaOxkYcHIQ/w426-h507/contractions.GIF</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/117787341870748981032/albums/5948510057582359009/5948510062264857634</link><title>It's been a terrific day! Thank you for referring us. We love hearing from people we can help. http://www.720media.com/services/ 

Reminder: tomorrow night is cstweetup at Sparrow Hawk Cookware from 5-8pm. Beer provided by Pikes Peak Brewing and goodies from Piglatin Truck Ltd and Orchard Ovens Bakery. Will be fun! #ColoradoSprings #socialmedia  #networking #creativity #colorado ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-fO3X2teZjOs/Uo1aYpQiNCI/AAAAAAAACYc/nwZEK53AlKE/w426-h284/colorado%2Bsprings%2Bweb%2Bdesign%2Bcreate%2Bbanners%2Bonline%2B720media.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/111068530907531663814/albums/5767259255956412993/5767259253216086178</link><title>North African Crested Porcupine (Hystrix cristata) - The name “porcupine” is derived from the Latin word for “quilled pig”. These hazardous-looking animals are however, a rodent species (more closely related to a rat or mouse than a pig). The African crested porcupine (Hystrix cristata) is the largest of the porcupine species, and can weigh up to 60 pounds. Rodents have teeth that grow continuously throughout their lives so they must constantly chew or eat to help keep them at a manageable length.  Porcupines are herbivores and include many fruits, berries and even flower blossoms in their diet. This species will also eat stems, roots, bark and even will chew on bones to keep their teeth from overgrowing. African crested porcupines have a range that extends from Morocco to Egypt and are normally found in forests and grassland habitats. They are a terrestrial, burrowing species with powerful claws designed for digging shallow holes amongst the roots and rocks for shelter. The crested porcupine is a master at evading predators. When threatened, they stomp their feet, click their teeth, and shake the small hollow quills on their rear to mimic a rattlesnake’s rattle.  The longer quills on their backs are also a defense mechanism and have small hook-like structures on the shaft hat make them very difficult to remove.  Contrary to popular belief, porcupines do not have the ability to “shoot” their quills off of their bodies.  Instead, they raise their sharp quills and move backwards into predators to enable the quills to become painfully embedded in their predator’s face and body. The Palm Beach Zoo’s African crested porcupine Priscilla is featured in the zoo’s Wild Things Show weekdays at 1:00 PM and at Noon on weekends. Please make it a “point” to see the show and “sharpen” your knowledge on this unique species!﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-eLZoBkYEfL8/UAlrvAuHiKI/AAAAAAAAAKA/BJXSQLuXcPI/w426-h326/african-crested-porcupine.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7153-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/pig%20latin%20help/photos/107130247487186913773/albums/5803346514636330129/5803346519930907218</link><title>GOOGLE &amp; GOOGLE Inc. 
http://google-news-blogger.blogspot.com/p/google.html 

Google 
Google Inc. 
Type Public 
Traded as NASDAQ: GOOG FWB: GGQ1 
NASDAQ-100 Component 
S&amp;P 500 Component 
Industry Internet, Computer software 
Founded Menlo Park, California, U.S. 
(September 4, 1998) 
Founder(s) Larry Page, Sergey Brin 
Headquarters Googleplex, Mountain View, California, United States 
Area served Worldwide 
Key people Eric Schmidt 
(Executive Chairman) 
Larry Page 
(Co-founder &amp; CEO) 
Sergey Brin (Co-Founder) 
Products See list of Google products. 
Revenue US$ 37.905 billion (2011) 
Operating income US$ 11.632 billion (2011) 
Profit US$ 9.737 billion (2011) 
Total assets US$ 72.574 billion (2011) 
Total equity US$ 58.145 billion (2011) 
Employees 53,546 (2012) 
Subsidiaries AdMob, DoubleClick, Motorola Mobility, On2 Technologies, Picnik, YouTube, Zagat 
Website Google.com 
References: 
Google Inc. (NASDAQ: GOOG) is an American multinational corporation which provides Internet-related products and services, including internet search, cloud computing, software and advertising technologies. Advertising revenues from AdWords generate almost all of the company's profits. 
The company was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while both attended Stanford University. Together, Brin and Page own about 16 percent of the company's stake. Google was first incorporated as a privately held company on September 4, 1998, and its initial public offering followed on August 19, 2004. The company's mission statement from the outset was "to organize the world's information and make it universally accessible and useful" and the company's unofficial slogan is "Don't be evil". In 2006, the company moved to its current headquarters in Mountain View, California. 
Rapid growth since incorporation has triggered a chain of products, acquisitions, and partnerships beyond the company's core web search engine. The company offers online productivity software including email, an office suite, and social networking. Google's products extend to the desktop as well, with applications for web browsing, organizing and editing photos, and instant messaging. Google leads the development of the Android mobile operating system, as well as the Google Chrome OS browser-only operating system, found on specialized netbooks called Chromebooks. Google has increasingly become a hardware company with its cooperation with major electronics manufacturers on its high-end Nexus series of devices and its acquisition of Motorola Mobility in May 2012, as well as the construction of fiber-optic infrastructure in Kansas City as part of the Google Fiber broadband Internet service project. 
Google has been estimated to run over one million servers in data centers around the world, and process over one billion search requests and about twenty-four petabytes of user-generated data every day. 
As of October 2012 Alexa listed the main U.S.-focused google.com site as the Internet's second most visited website, and numerous international Google sites as being in the top hundred, as well as several other Google-owned sites such as YouTube and Blogger. Google also ranks number two in the BrandZ brand equity database. The dominant market position of Google's services has led to criticism of the company over issues including privacy, copyright, and censorship. 

Contents 
1 History 
1.1 Financing and initial public offering 
1.2 Growth 
1.3 Acquisitions and partnerships 
1.4 Google Data Centers 
2 Products and services 
2.1 Advertising 
2.2 Search engine 
2.3 Productivity tools 
2.4 Enterprise products 
2.5 Other products 
3 Corporate affairs and culture 
3.1 Employees 
3.2 Googleplex 
3.3 Easter eggs and April Fools' Day jokes 
3.4 Philanthropy 
3.5 Network neutrality 

History 

Main article: History of Google 

Google's original homepage had a simple design, since its founders were not experienced in HTML, the language for designing web pages. 
Google began in January 1996 as a research project by Larry Page and Sergey Brin when they were both PhD students at Stanford University in California. 
While conventional search engines ranked results by counting how many times the search terms appeared on the page, the two theorized about a better system that analyzed the relationships between websites. They called this new technology PageRank, where a website's relevance was determined by the number of pages, and the importance of those pages, that linked back to the original site. 
A small search engine called "RankDex" from IDD Information Services designed by Robin Li was, since 1996, already exploring a similar strategy for site-scoring and page ranking. The technology in RankDex would be patented and used later when Li founded Baidu in China. 
Page and Brin originally nicknamed their new search engine "BackRub", because the system checked backlinks to estimate the importance of a site. 
Eventually, they changed the name to Google, originating from a misspelling of the word "googol", the number one followed by one hundred zeros, which was picked to signify that the search engine wants to provide large quantities of information for people. Originally, Google ran under the Stanford University website, with the domains google.stanford.edu and z.stanford.edu. 
The domain name for Google was registered on September 15, 1997, and the company was incorporated on September 4, 1998. It was based in a friend's (Susan Wojcicki) garage in Menlo Park, California. Craig Silverstein, a fellow PhD student at Stanford, was hired as the first employee. 
In May 2011, the number of monthly unique visitors to Google surpassed 1 billion for the first time, an 8.4 percent increase from May 2010 (931 million). 
Financing and initial public offering 

Google's first production server. Google's production servers continue to be built with inexpensive hardware. 
The first funding for Google was an August 1998 contribution of US$100,000 from Andy Bechtolsheim, co-founder of Sun Microsystems, given before Google was even incorporated. Early in 1999, while still graduate students, Brin and Page decided that the search engine they had developed was taking up too much of their time from academic pursuits. They went to Excite CEO George Bell and offered to sell it to him for $1 million. He rejected the offer, and later criticized Vinod Khosla, one of Excite's venture capitalists, after he had negotiated Brin and Page down to $750,000. On June 7, 1999, a $25 million round of funding was announced, with major investors including the venture capital firms Kleiner Perkins Caufield &amp; Byers and Sequoia Capital. 
Google's initial public offering (IPO) took place five years later on August 19, 2004. At that time Larry Page, Sergey Brin, and Eric Schmidt agreed to work together at Google for 20 years, until the year 2024. The company offered 19,605,052 shares at a price of $85 per share. Shares were sold in a unique online auction format using a system built by Morgan Stanley and Credit Suisse, underwriters for the deal. The sale of $1.67 billion gave Google a market capitalization of more than $23 billion. The vast majority of the 271 million shares remained under the control of Google, and many Google employees became instant paper millionaires. Yahoo!, a competitor of Google, also benefited because it owned 8.4 million shares of Google before the IPO took place. 
Some people speculated that Google's IPO would inevitably lead to changes in company culture. Reasons ranged from shareholder pressure for employee benefit reductions to the fact that many company executives would become instant paper millionaires. As a reply to this concern, co-founders Sergey Brin and Larry Page promised in a report to potential investors that the IPO would not change the company's culture. In 2005, however, articles in The New York Times and other sources began suggesting that Google had lost its anti-corporate, no evil philosophy. In an effort to maintain the company's unique culture, Google designated a Chief Culture Officer, who also serves as the Director of Human Resources. The purpose of the Chief Culture Officer is to develop and maintain the culture and work on ways to keep true to the core values that the company was founded on: a flat organization with a collaborative environment. Google has also faced allegations of sexism and ageism from former employees. 
The stock's performance after the IPO went well, with shares hitting $700 for the first time on October 31, 2007, primarily because of strong sales and earnings in the online advertising market. The surge in stock price was fueled mainly by individual investors, as opposed to large institutional investors and mutual funds. The company is now listed on the NASDAQ stock exchange under the ticker symbol GOOG and under the Frankfurt Stock Exchange under the ticker symbol GGQ1. 
Growth 
In March 1999, the company moved its offices to Palo Alto, California, home to several other noted Silicon Valley technology startups. The next year, against Page and Brin's initial opposition toward an advertising-funded search engine, Google began selling advertisements associated with search keywords. In order to maintain an uncluttered page design and increase speed, advertisements were solely text-based. Keywords were sold based on a combination of price bids and click-throughs, with bidding starting at five cents per click. This model of selling keyword advertising was first pioneered by Goto.com, an Idealab spin-off created by Bill Gross. When the company changed names to Overture Services, it sued Google over alleged infringements of the company's pay-per-click and bidding patents. Overture Services would later be bought by Yahoo! and renamed Yahoo! Search Marketing. The case was then settled out of court, with Google agreeing to issue shares of common stock to Yahoo! in exchange for a perpetual license. 
During this time, Google was granted a patent describing its PageRank mechanism. The patent was officially assigned to Stanford University and lists Lawrence Page as the inventor. In 2003, after outgrowing two other locations, the company leased its current office complex from Silicon Graphics at 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway in Mountain View, California. The complex has since come to be known as the Googleplex, a play on the word googolplex, the number one followed by a googol zeroes. The Googleplex interiors were designed by Clive Wilkinson Architects. Three years later, Google would buy the property from SGI for $319 million. By that time, the name "Google" had found its way into everyday language, causing the verb "google" to be added to the Merriam Webster Collegiate Dictionary and the Oxford English Dictionary, denoted as "to use the Google search engine to obtain information on the Internet." 
Acquisitions and partnerships 
See also: List of mergers and acquisitions by Google 
Since 2001, Google has acquired many companies, mainly focusing on small venture capital companies. In 2004, Google acquired Keyhole, Inc. The start-up company developed a product called Earth Viewer that gave a three-dimensional view of the Earth. Google renamed the service to Google Earth in 2005. Two years later, Google bought the online video site YouTube for $1.65 billion in stock. On April 13, 2007, Google reached an agreement to acquire DoubleClick for $3.1 billion, giving Google valuable relationships that DoubleClick had with Web publishers and advertising agencies. Later that same year, Google purchased GrandCentral for $50 million. The site would later be changed over to Google Voice. On August 5, 2009, Google bought out its first public company, purchasing video software maker On2 Technologies for $106.5 million. Google also acquired Aardvark, a social network search engine, for $50 million, and commented on its internal blog, "we're looking forward to collaborating to see where we can take it". In April 2010, Google announced it had acquired a hardware startup, Agnilux. 
In addition to the many companies Google has purchased, the company has partnered with other organizations for everything from research to advertising. In 2005, Google partnered with NASA Ames Research Center to build 1,000,000 square feet (93,000 m2) of offices. The offices would be used for research projects involving large-scale data management, nanotechnology, distributed computing, and the entrepreneurial space industry. Google entered into a partnership with Sun Microsystems in October 2005 to help share and distribute each other's technologies. The company also partnered with AOL of Time Warner, to enhance each other's video search services. Google's 2005 partnerships also included financing the new .mobi top-level domain for mobile devices, along with other companies including Microsoft, Nokia, and Ericsson. Google would later launch "AdSense for Mobile", taking advantage of the emerging mobile advertising market. Increasing its advertising reach even further, Google and Fox Interactive Media of News Corporation entered into a $900 million agreement to provide search and advertising on popular social networking site MySpace. 
In October 2006, Google announced that it had acquired the video-sharing site YouTube for US$1.65 billion in Google stock, and the deal was finalized on November 13, 2006. Google does not provide detailed figures for YouTube's running costs, and YouTube's revenues in 2007 were noted as "not material" in a regulatory filing. In June 2008, a Forbes magazine article projected the 2008 YouTube revenue at US$200 million, noting progress in advertising sales. In 2007, Google began sponsoring NORAD Tracks Santa, a service that follows Santa Claus' progress on Christmas Eve, using Google Earth to "track Santa" in 3-D for the first time, and displacing former sponsor AOL. Google-owned YouTube gave NORAD Tracks Santa its own channel. 
In 2008, Google developed a partnership with GeoEye to launch a satellite providing Google with high-resolution (0.41 m monochrome, 1.65 m color) imagery for Google Earth. The satellite was launched from Vandenberg Air Force Base on September 6, 2008. Google also announced in 2008 that it was hosting an archive of Life Magazine's photographs as part of its latest partnership. Some of the images in the archive were never published in the magazine. The photos were watermarked and originally had copyright notices posted on all photos, regardless of public domain status. 
In 2010, Google Energy made its first investment in a renewable energy project, putting $38.8 million into two wind farms in North Dakota. The company announced the two locations will generate 169.5 megawatts of power, or enough to supply 55,000 homes. The farms, which were developed by NextEra Energy Resources, will reduce fossil fuel use in the region and return profits. NextEra Energy Resources sold Google a twenty percent stake in the project to get funding for its development. Also in 2010, Google purchased Global IP Solutions, a Norway-based company that provides web-based teleconferencing and other related services. This acquisition will enable Google to add telephone-style services to its list of products. On May 27, 2010, Google announced it had also closed the acquisition of the mobile ad network AdMob. This purchase occurred days after the Federal Trade Commission closed its investigation into the purchase. Google acquired the company for an undisclosed amount. In July 2010, Google signed an agreement with an Iowa wind farm to buy 114 megawatts of energy for 20 years. 
On April 4, 2011, The Globe and Mail reported that Google bid $900 million for six thousand Nortel Networks patents. 
On August 15, 2011, Google announced that it would acquire Motorola Mobility for $12.5 billion subject to approval from regulators in the United States and Europe. In a post on Google's blog, Google Chief Executive and co-founder Larry Page revealed that Google's acquisition of Motorola Mobility is a strategic move to strengthen Google's patent portfolio. The company's Android operating system has come under fire in an industry-wide patent battle, as Apple and Microsoft have taken to court Android device makers such as HTC, Samsung and Motorola. The merger was completed on the 22 May 2012, after the approval of People's Republic of China. This purchase was made in part to help Google gain Motorola's considerable patent portfolio on mobile phones and wireless technologies to help protect it in its ongoing patent disputes with other companies, mainly Apple and Microsoft and to allow it to continue to freely offer Android. In order to expand its social networking services, Google plans to purchase Silicon Valley start up Meebo. 
On June 5, 2012 Google announced it acquired Quickoffice, a company widely known for their mobile productivity suite for both iOS and Android. Google plans to integrate Quickoffice's technology into its own product suite. 
Google Data Centers 
Google Inc. currently owns and operates 6 data centers across the U.S., plus one in Finland and another in Belgium. On September 28, 2011 the company has announced to build three data centers at a cost of more than $200 million in Asia (Singapore, Hong Kong and Taiwan) and has already purchased the land for them. Google said they will be operational in one to two years. 
Products and services 

See also: List of Google products 
Advertising 
In 2011, 96% of Google's revenue was derived from its advertising programs. For the 2006 fiscal year, the company reported $10.492 billion in total advertising revenues and only $112 million in licensing and other revenues. Google has implemented various innovations in the online advertising market that helped make it one of the biggest brokers in the market. Using technology from the company DoubleClick, Google can determine user interests and target advertisements so they are relevant to their context and the user that is viewing them. Google Analytics allows website owners to track where and how people use their website, for example by examining click rates for all the links on a page. Google advertisements can be placed on third-party websites in a two-part program. Google's AdWords allows advertisers to display their advertisements in the Google content network, through either a cost-per-click or cost-per-view scheme. The sister service, Google AdSense, allows website owners to display these advertisements on their website, and earn money every time ads are clicked. 
One of the disadvantages and criticisms of this program is Google's inability to combat click fraud, when a person or automated script "clicks" on advertisements without being interested in the product, which causes that advertiser to pay money to Google unduly. Industry reports in 2006 claim that approximately 14 to 20 percent of clicks were in fact fraudulent or invalid. Furthermore, there has been controversy over Google's "search within a search", where a secondary search box enables the user to find what they are looking for within a particular website. It was soon reported that when performing a search within a search for a specific company, advertisements from competing and rival companies often showed up along with those results, drawing users away from the site they were originally searching. Another complaint against Google's advertising is its censorship of advertisers, though many cases concern compliance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. For example, in February 2003, Google stopped showing the advertisements of Oceana, a non-profit organization protesting a major cruise ship's sewage treatment practices. Google cited its editorial policy at the time, stating "Google does not accept advertising if the ad or site advocates against other individuals, groups, or organizations." The policy was later changed. In June 2008, Google reached an advertising agreement with Yahoo!, which would have allowed Yahoo! to feature Google advertisements on its web pages. The alliance between the two companies was never completely realized due to antitrust concerns by the U.S. Department of Justice. As a result, Google pulled out of the deal in November 2008. 
In an attempt to advertise its own products, Google launched a website called Demo Slam, developed to demonstrate technology demos of Google Products. Each week, two teams compete at putting Google's technology into new contexts. Search Engine Journal said Demo Slam is "a place where creative and tech-savvy people can create videos to help the rest of the world understand all the newest and greatest technology out there." 
Search engine 
Main article: Google Search 

On February 14, 2012, Google updated its homepage with a minor twist. There are no red lines above the options in the black bar, and there is a tab space before the "+You". The sign-in button has also changed, it is no longer in the black bar, instead under it as a button. 
Google Search, a web search engine, is the company's most popular service. According to market research published by comScore in November 2009, Google is the dominant search engine in the United States market, with a market share of 65.6%. Google indexes billions of web pages, so that users can search for the information they desire, through the use of keywords and operators. Despite its popularity, it has received criticism from a number of organizations. In 2003, The New York Times complained about Google's indexing, claiming that Google's caching of content on its site infringed its copyright for the content. In this case, the United States District Court of Nevada ruled in favor of Google in Field v. Google and Parker v. Google. Furthermore, the publication 2600: The Hacker Quarterly has compiled a list of words that the web giant's new instant search feature will not search. Google Watch has also criticized Google's PageRank algorithms, saying that they discriminate against new websites and favor established sites, and has made allegations about connections between Google and the NSA and the CIA. Despite criticism, the basic search engine has spread to specific services as well, including an image search engine, the Google News search site, Google Maps, and more. In early 2006, the company launched Google Video, which allowed users to upload, search, and watch videos from the Internet. In 2009, however, uploads to Google Video were discontinued so that Google could focus more on the search aspect of the service. The company even developed Google Desktop, a desktop search application used to search for files local to one's computer (discontinued in 2011). Google's most recent development in search is its partnership with the United States Patent and Trademark Office to create Google Patents, which enables free access to information about patents and trademarks. 
One of the more controversial search services Google hosts is Google Books. The company began scanning books and uploading limited previews, and full books where allowed, into its new book search engine. The Authors Guild, a group that represents 8,000 U.S. authors, filed a class action suit in a New York City federal court against Google in 2005 over this new service. Google replied that it is in compliance with all existing and historical applications of copyright laws regarding books. Google eventually reached a revised settlement in 2009 to limit its scans to books from the U.S., the UK, Australia and Canada. Furthermore, the Paris Civil Court ruled against Google in late 2009, asking it to remove the works of La Martinière (Éditions du Seuil) from its database. In competition with Amazon.com, Google plans to sell digital versions of new books. On July 21, 2010, in response to newcomer Bing, Google updated its image search to display a streaming sequence of thumbnails that enlarge when pointed at. Though web searches still appear in a batch per page format, on July 23, 2010, dictionary definitions for certain English words began appearing above the linked results for web searches. Google's algorithm was changed in March 2011, giving more weight to high-quality content possibly by the use of n-grams to remove spun content. 
Productivity tools 
In addition to its standard web search services, Google has released over the years a number of online productivity tools. Gmail, a free webmail service provided by Google, was launched as an invitation-only beta program on April 1, 2004, and became available to the general public on February 7, 2007. The service was upgraded from beta status on July 7, 2009, at which time it had 146 million users monthly. The service would be the first online email service with one gigabyte of storage, and the first to keep emails from the same conversation together in one thread, similar to an Internet forum. The service currently offers over 7600 MB of free storage with additional storage ranging from 20 GB to 16 TB available for US$0.25 per 1 GB per year. Furthermore, software developers know Gmail for its pioneering use of AJAX, a programming technique that allows web pages to be interactive without refreshing the browser. One criticism of Gmail has been the potential for data disclosure, a risk associated with many online web applications. Steve Ballmer (Microsoft's CEO), Liz Figueroa, Mark Rasch, and the editors of Google Watch believe the processing of email message content goes beyond proper use, but Google claims that mail sent to or from Gmail is never read by a human being beyond the account holder, and is only used to improve relevance of advertisements. 
Google Docs, another part of Google's productivity suite, allows users to create, edit, and collaborate on documents in an online environment, not dissimilar to Microsoft Word. The service was originally called Writely, but was obtained by Google on March 9, 2006, where it was released as an invitation-only preview. On June 6 after the acquisition, Google created an experimental spreadsheet editing program, which would be combined with Google Docs on October 10. A program to edit presentations would complete the set on September 17, 2007, before all three services were taken out of beta along with Gmail, Google Calendar and all products from the Google Apps Suite on July 7, 2009. 
Enterprise products 

Google's search appliance at the 2008 RSA Conference 
Google entered the enterprise market in February 2002 with the launch of its Google Search Appliance, targeted toward providing search technology for larger organizations. Google launched the Mini three years later, which was targeted at smaller organizations. Late in 2006, Google began to sell Custom Search Business Edition, providing customers with an advertising-free window into Google.com's index. The service was renamed Google Site Search in 2008. 
Google Apps is another primary Google enterprise service offering. The service allows organizations to bring Google's web application offerings, such as Gmail and Google Docs, into its own domain. The service is available in several editions: a basic free edition (formerly known as Google Apps Standard edition), Google Apps for Business, Google Apps for Education, and Google Apps for Government. Special editions include extras such as more disk space, API access, a service level agreement (SLA), premium support, and additional apps. In the same year Google Apps was launched, Google acquired Postini and proceeded to integrate the company's security technologies into Google Apps under the name Google Postini Services. 
Additional Google enterprise offerings include geospatial solutions (e.g., Google Earth and Google Maps); security and archival solutions (e.g., Postini); and Chromebooks for business and education (i.e., personal computing run on browser-centric operating systems). 
Other products 

Galaxy Nexus, the latest "Google phone" 
Google Translate is a server-side machine translation service, which can translate between 35 different languages. Browser extensions allow for easy access to Google Translate from the browser. The software uses corpus linguistics techniques, where the program "learns" from professionally translated documents, specifically UN and European Parliament proceedings. Furthermore, a "suggest a better translation" feature accompanies the translated text, allowing users to indicate where the current translation is incorrect or otherwise inferior to another translation. 
Google launched its Google News service in 2002. The site proclaimed that the company had created a "highly unusual" site that "offers a news service compiled solely by computer algorithms without human intervention. Google employs no editors, managing editors, or executive editors." The site hosted less licensed news content than Yahoo! News, and instead presented topically selected links to news and opinion pieces along with reproductions of their headlines, story leads, and photographs. The photographs are typically reduced to thumbnail size and placed next to headlines from other news sources on the same topic in order to minimize copyright infringement claims. Nevertheless, Agence France Presse sued Google for copyright infringement in federal court in the District of Columbia, a case which Google settled for an undisclosed amount in a pact that included a license of the full text of AFP articles for use on Google News. 
In 2006, Google made a bid to offer free wireless broadband access throughout the city of San Francisco along with Internet service provider EarthLink. Large telecommunications companies such as Comcast and Verizon opposed such efforts, claiming it was "unfair competition" and that cities would be violating their commitments to offer local monopolies to these companies. In his testimony before Congress on network neutrality in 2006, Google's Chief Internet Evangelist Vint Cerf blamed such tactics on the fact that nearly half of all consumers lack meaningful choice in broadband providers. Google currently offers free wi-fi access in its hometown of Mountain View, California. 
In 2010, Google announced the Google Fiber project with plans to build an ultra-high-speed broadband network for 50,000 to 500,000 customers in one or more American cities. On March 30, 2011, Google announced that Kansas City, Kansas would be the first community where the new network would be deployed. In July 2012, Google completed the construction of a fiber-optic broadband internet network infrastructure in Kansas City, and after building an infrastructure, Google announced pricing for Google Fiber. The service will offer three options including a free broadband internet option, a 1Gbit/s internet option for $70 per month and a version that includes television service for $120 per month. 
In 2007, reports surfaced that Google was planning the release of its own mobile phone, possibly a competitor to Apple's iPhone. The project, called Android, turned out not to be a phone but an operating system for mobile devices, which Google acquired and then released as an open source project under the Apache 2.0 license. Google provides a software development kit for developers so applications can be created to be run on Android-based phones. In September 2008, T-Mobile released the G1, the first Android-based phone. More than a year later on January 5, 2010, Google released an Android phone under its own company name called the Nexus One. 
Other projects Google has worked on include a new collaborative communication service, a web browser, and even a mobile operating system. The first of these was first announced on May 27, 2009. Google Wave was described as a product that helps users communicate and collaborate on the web. The service is Google's "email redesigned", with realtime editing, the ability to embed audio, video, and other media, and extensions that further enhance the communication experience. Google Wave was previously in a developer's preview, where interested users had to be invited to test the service, but was released to the general public on May 19, 2010, at Google's I/O keynote. On September 1, 2008, Google pre-announced the upcoming availability of Google Chrome, an open source web browser, which was then released on September 2, 2008. The next year, on July 7, 2009, Google announced Google Chrome OS, an open source Linux-based operating system that includes only a web browser and is designed to log users into their Google account. 
Google Goggles is a mobile application available on Android and iOS used for image recognition and non-text-based search. In addition to scanning QR codes, the app can recognize historic landmarks, import business cards, and solve Sudoku puzzles. While Goggles could originally identify people as well, Google has limited that functionality as a privacy protection. 
In 2011, Google announced that it will unveil Google Wallet, a mobile application for wireless payments. 
In late June 2011, Google soft-launched a social networking service called Google+. On July 14, 2011, Google announced that Google+ had reached 10 million users just two weeks after it was launched in this "limited" trial phase. After four weeks in operation, it had reached 25 million users. 
Corporate affairs and culture 

Then-CEO, now Chairman of Google Eric Schmidt with Sergey Brin and Larry Page (left to right) in 2008. 
Google is known for having an informal corporate culture. On Fortune magazine's list of best companies to work for, Google ranked first in 2007, 2008 and 2012 and fourth in 2009 and 2010. Google was also nominated in 2010 to be the world’s most attractive employer to graduating students in the Universum Communications talent attraction index. Google's corporate philosophy embodies such casual principles as "you can make money without doing evil," "you can be serious without a suit," and "work should be challenging and the challenge should be fun." 
Google uses various tax avoidance strategies. Consequently, out of the five largest American technology companies it pays the lowest taxes to the countries of origin of its revenues. This is accomplished partly by licensing technology through subsidiaries in Ireland, Bermuda, the Bahamas and the Netherlands. 
Employees 

New employees are called "Nooglers," and are given a propeller beanie cap to wear on their first Friday. 
Google's stock performance following its initial public offering has enabled many early employees to be competitively compensated. After the company's IPO, founders Sergey Brin and Larry Page and CEO Eric Schmidt requested that their base salary be cut to $1. Subsequent offers by the company to increase their salaries have been turned down, primarily because their main compensation continues to come from owning stock in Google. Before 2004, Schmidt was making $250,000 per year, and Page and Brin each earned a salary of $150,000. 
In 2007 and through early 2008, several top executives left Google. In October 2007, former chief financial officer of YouTube Gideon Yu joined Facebook along with Benjamin Ling, a high-ranking engineer. In March 2008, Sheryl Sandberg, then vice-president of global online sales and operations, began her position as chief operating officer of Facebook while Ash ElDifrawi, formerly head of brand advertising, left to become chief marketing officer of Netshops, an online retail company that was renamed Hayneedle in 2009. On April 4, 2011 Larry Page became CEO and Eric Schmidt became Executive Chairman of Google. In July 2012 Google's first female employee, Marissa Mayer left Google to become Yahoo's CEO. 
As a motivation technique, Google uses a policy often called Innovation Time Off, where Google engineers are encouraged to spend 20% of their work time on projects that interest them. Some of Google's newer services, such as Gmail, Google News, Orkut, and AdSense originated from these independent endeavors. In a talk at Stanford University, Marissa Mayer, Google's Vice President of Search Products and User Experience until July 2012, showed that half of all new product launches at the time had originated from the Innovation Time Off. 
In March 2011, consulting firm Universum released data that Google ranks first on the list of ideal employers by nearly 25 percent chosen from more than 10,000 young professionals asked. Fortune magazine ranked Google as number one on its 100 Best Companies To Work For list for 2012. 
Googleplex 
Main article: Googleplex 

The Googleplex, Google's original and largest corporate campus 

Google Mountain View campus garden 

Google Mountain View dinosaur 'Stan' 
Google's headquarters in Mountain View, California is referred to as "the Googleplex", a play on words on the number googolplex and the headquarters itself being a complex of buildings. The lobby is decorated with a piano, lava lamps, old server clusters, and a projection of search queries on the wall. The hallways are full of exercise balls and bicycles. Each employee has access to the corporate recreation center. Recreational amenities are scattered throughout the campus and include a workout room with weights and rowing machines, locker rooms, washers and dryers, a massage room, assorted video games, table football, a baby grand piano, a billiard table, and ping pong. In addition to the rec room, there are snack rooms stocked with various foods and drinks, with special emphasis placed on nutrition. Free food is available to employees 24/7, with paid vending machines prorated favoring nutritional value. 
In 2006, Google moved into 311,000 square feet (28,900 m2) of office space in New York City, at 111 Eighth Avenue in Manhattan. The office was specially designed and built for Google, and it now houses its largest advertising sales team, which has been instrumental in securing large partnerships. In 2003, they added an engineering staff in New York City, which has been responsible for more than 100 engineering projects, including Google Maps, Google Spreadsheets, and others. It is estimated that the building costs Google $10 million per year to rent and is similar in design and functionality to its Mountain View headquarters, including table football, air hockey, and ping-pong tables, as well as a video game area. In November 2006, Google opened offices on Carnegie Mellon's campus in Pittsburgh, focusing on shopping related advertisement coding and smartphone applications and programs. By late 2006, Google also established a new headquarters for its AdWords division in Ann Arbor, Michigan. Furthermore, Google has offices all around the world, and in the United States, including Ann Arbor, Michigan; Atlanta, Georgia; Austin, Texas; Boulder, Colorado; Cambridge, Massachusetts; New York City; San Francisco, California; Seattle, Washington; Reston, Virginia, and Washington, D.C. 

Google's NYC office building houses its largest advertising sales team. 
Google is taking steps to ensure that its operations are environmentally sound. In October 2006, the company announced plans to install thousands of solar panels to provide up to 1.6 megawatts of electricity, enough to satisfy approximately 30% of the campus' energy needs. The system will be the largest solar power system constructed on a U.S. corporate campus and one of the largest on any corporate site in the world. In addition, Google announced in 2009 that it was deploying herds of goats to keep grassland around the Googleplex short, helping to prevent the threat from seasonal bush fires while also reducing the carbon footprint of mowing the extensive grounds. The idea of trimming lawns using goats originated from R. J. Widlar, an engineer who worked for National Semiconductor. Despite this, Google has faced accusations in Harper's Magazine of being an "energy glutton", and was accused of employing its "Don't be evil" motto as well as its very public energy-saving campaigns as an attempt to cover up or make up for the massive amounts of energy its servers actually require. 
Easter eggs and April Fools' Day jokes 
Main article: List of Google's hoaxes and easter eggs 
Google has a tradition of creating April Fools' Day jokes. For example, Google MentalPlex allegedly featured the use of mental power to search the web. In 2007, Google announced a free Internet service called TiSP, or Toilet Internet Service Provider, where one obtained a connection by flushing one end of a fiber-optic cable down their toilet. Also in 2007, Google's Gmail page displayed an announcement for Gmail Paper, allowing users to have email messages printed and shipped to them. In 2008 Google announced Gmail Custom time where users could change the time that the email was sent. In 2010, Google jokingly changed its company name to Topeka in honor of Topeka, Kansas, whose mayor actually changed the city's name to Google for a short amount of time in an attempt to sway Google's decision in its new Google Fiber Project. In 2011, Google announced Gmail Motion, an interactive way of controlling Gmail and the computer with body movements via the user's webcam. 
In addition to April Fools' Day jokes, Google's services contain a number of easter eggs. For instance, Google included the Swedish Chef's "Bork bork bork," Pig Latin, "Hacker" or leetspeak, Elmer Fudd, Pirate, and Klingon as language selections for its search engine. In addition, the search engine calculator provides the Answer to the Ultimate Question of Life, the Universe, and Everything from Douglas Adams' The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy. Furthermore, when searching the word "recursion", the spell-checker's result for the properly spelled word is exactly the same word, creating a recursive link. Likewise, when searching for the word "anagram," meaning a rearrangement of letters from one word to form other valid words, Google's suggestion feature displays "Did you mean: nag a ram?" In Google Maps, searching for directions between places separated by large bodies of water, such as Los Angeles and Tokyo, results in instructions to "kayak across the Pacific Ocean." During FIFA World Cup 2010, search queries like "World Cup", "FIFA", etc. caused the "Goooo...gle" page indicator at the bottom of every result page to read "Goooo...al!" instead. Typing in 'Do a barrel roll' in the search engine will make the page do a 360° rotation. 
Philanthropy 
Main article: Google.org 
In 2004, Google formed the not-for-profit philanthropic Google.org, with a start-up fund of $1 billion. The mission of the organization is to create awareness about climate change, global public health, and global poverty. One of its first projects was to develop a viable plug-in hybrid electric vehicle that can attain 100 miles per gallon. Google hired Dr. Larry Brilliant as the program's executive director in 2004 and the current director is Megan Smith. 
In 2008 Google announced its "project 10100" which accepted ideas for how to help the community and then allowed Google users to vote on their favorites. After two years of silence, during which many wondered what had happened to the program, Google revealed the winners of the project, giving a total of ten million dollars to various ideas ranging from non-profit organizations that promote education to a website that intends to make all legal documents public and online. 
In 2011, Google donated 1 million euros to International Mathematical Olympiad to support the next five annual International Mathematical Olympiads (2011–2015). Google is not a sponsor of the main Olympics, but through clever use of Google doodles on their main page, they are able to create consumer confusion on the issue. On July 2012, Google launched a "Legalize Love" campaign in support of gay rights worldwide. 
Network neutrality 
Google is a noted supporter of network neutrality. According to Google's Guide to Net Neutrality: 
Network neutrality is the principle that Internet users should be in control of what content they view and what applications they use on the Internet. The Internet has operated according to this neutrality principle since its earliest days... Fundamentally, net neutrality is about equal access to the Internet. In our view, the broadband carriers should not be permitted to use their market power to discriminate against competing applications or content. Just as telephone companies are not permitted to tell consumers who they can call or what they can say, broadband carriers should not be allowed to use their market power to control activity online. 
— 
On February 7, 2006, Vint Cerf, a co-inventor of the Internet Protocol (IP), and current Vice President and "Chief Internet Evangelist" at Google, in testimony before Congress, said, "allowing broadband carriers to control what people see and do online would fundamentally undermine the principles that have made the Internet such a success."﻿

Meer lezen (787 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7153_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-2pzJKOth9t4/UImg6ZT7KlI/AAAAAAAAG5s/w6rZ1dTQz4c/w426-h237/Google-Music-Player-Logo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>