<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 16:33:48" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/114528586908817727732/albums/5774065732774431985/5774065740262423570</link><title>What is a MOOC? 

MOOCs (massive, open, online classes) are a hot topic -- they've generated a lot of experimentation, press, venture capital, etc.  When my colleagues ask what it is all about, I point them to these quick resources: 

1\.  Peter Norvig, The 100,000-student classroom.  This is a six-minute TED talk describing the MOOC Norvig and a colleague taught at Stanford along with some of the principles that guided the course design.  (http://bit.ly/TdipF7) 

2\.  A twenty minute audio interview of George Siemens, a professor at Athabasca University.  Siemens was one of the first to teach a MOOC.  (He may have coined the term).  He describes his decentralized approach to MOOC design and, like Norvig, focuses on the need and opportunity for pedagogical research.  (http://bit.ly/P4mxYP) 

3\. A twenty minute 
4\.  Two blog posts that give a sense of the video production process at Udacity, a visible, venture funded startup: 

*  Katy Reichelt, video editing manager at Udacity: Video editing and the learning process (http://bit.ly/OXzzG2) 

*  John Regehr, Associate Professor of Computer Science at the University of Utah describes the Udacity production process from the point of view of a teacher.  (http://bit.ly/O0K3pT) 

Disclaimer -- these are all presentations by enthusiasts.  I've written several posts on MOOCs in the last year or so (http://bit.ly/JMplY2), and see a lot of potential, but there remain many unanswered questions. 

Gripe -- this post is ugly.  I sure wish Google Plus had a few simple formatting tools like bullet lists and links. 

#mooc   #edreform #pedagogy #bonkopen #educause     #digitalliteracy   #edtech  ﻿

Meer lezen (36 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BkMOJdEBPd0/UCGaMs4YPBI/AAAAAAAAP98/oXUbDue4Ksg/w426-h540/mooc.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/114528586908817727732/albums/5777263594481217137/5777263601109188370</link><title>Coursera students find plagiarism in peer-graded essays 
http://bit.ly/NH7YsM 

Automated grading of things like multiple choice tests and short programs has allowed MOOCs to scale.  Coursera hopes that peer grading will do the same for essays, but this article in the Chronicle of Higher Education reports dozens of plagiarism incidents in one of their courses. 

If students plagiarize in Coursera's non-credit courses, they will be more likely to plagiarize in for-credit courses.  Is the solution to impose penalties for plagiarizm?  For example, if a peer reports an  incident of plagairism, the case could be reviewed by a faculty member and if the claim were upheld some sanction applied.  The faculty review process would add cost, but it might help. 

#education #edtech #highereducation #digitalliteracy   #mooc  ﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uabx2OlLmEk/UCz2os3oPxI/AAAAAAAAQW0/_QKLkDwg5Ys/w426-h609/plagiarism.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/111634746643816111742/albums/5971259935591671889/5971259942741932258</link><title>Sage mir, wie Du moocst / lernst / arbeitest / sprichst und ich sage dir, wer du bist. 

Senhor Floh: "Ist das Leben ein ständig ablaufender 'massive open online + offline course - ein moooc?" 

Dona Biene: Klar, das Leben ist ein MOOC-Marktplatz, aber nur nicht zu sehr anpassen und wir brauchen auch keine 'stinkenden Abzeichen.' 
(Zu 'stinking badges' siehe Video unter Link 1). 
Marken / Brandzeichen brauchen wir hingegen. 
Wir dürfen nämlich den beschrittenen Weg und uns nicht aus den Augen verlieren und wir müssen uns zusammentun. 
Wir brauchen Zusammenarbeit (13). 
Ansonsten gilt es, zu entschleunigen. 
Was wollen wir uns auch ständig beweisen? 

Senhor Floh: "Ich möchte wieder gesund sein und zu arbeiten beginnen!" 
"Ich möchte versuchen, wieder zu arbeiten und ich möchte es allen Mitarbeitern so angenehm wie möglich machen." 

Dona Biene: Ist das der richtige Weg? 

Senhor Floh: "Wenn ich in eine andere Umwelt käme, dann könnte etwas beginnen, das besser ist." 

Dona Biene: Ist das wahr? 
Ist das nicht ein Flüchten? 

Senhor Floh: "Gute Frage!" 
"Umschulen oder sich in einer anderen Firma bewerben ist ab einem gewissen Alter nicht mehr so leicht. Da fallen die Ergebnisse negativ aus." 

Dona Biene: Sind Sie da nicht falsch programmiert? 
Wahrscheinlich haben Sie mit 40 Jahren auch schon gedacht, dass Sie für die Diskothek zu alt sind? 
Sie sollten sich umprogrammieren. 
Ha! Jetzt lachen Sie sogar erstmals! 

Senhor Floh: "Wenn man ganz gute Qualifikationen hat, bekommt man schneller eine gute Arbeit. Als Durchschnittsmensch sind die Chancen sehr gering." 

Dona Biene: 
Glauben Sie das wirklich? 
Sind die Chancen für Arbeitsmöglichkeiten vielleicht mit denen zum Absatz von Wohnungen vergleichbar? 
Können Sie leichter eine Luxuswohnung verkaufen oder eher eine etwas einfachere Wohnung in normaler Lage? 

Senhor Floh: "Was ist dann richtig? Soll ich mich jetzt jung und wie eine Luxuswohnung fühlen? Also, schön wäre es." 

Dona Biene: Gut, dann tun Sie es doch. 
Allerdings gehen Sie, wenn Sie sich dann zu sehr verwöhnen lassen oder in die Passivität verfallen oder alles für sich machen lassen, am wahren Leben vielleicht vorbei. 

Senhor Floh: "Also normale Arbeit und wenig Lohn oder qualifizierte Tätigkeit und keine Anstellung?" 

Dona Biene: Sie könnten sich im privaten Bereich gewissermaßen als 'Luxuswohnung' fühlen. 
Das bedeutet, sich über MOOCs oder Fernkurse weiterzuqualifizieren oder einfach zu lernen, was Ihnen Spaß macht. 

Senhor Floh: "Sich nur privat mit einer Luxuswohnung vergleichen?" 

Dona Biene: Nicht zu sehr. Da dürfen Sie sich wahrscheinlich nicht verändern und müssen nur schön sein,  nach Geld riechen und ständig wird an Ihnen herumgesaugt und gewischt. 
Das ist Ihnen natürlich völlig fremd. Sie sind ein Schaffer und Selbermacher. Aber sind Ihre Ansprüche an sich selbst vielleicht etwas zu hoch? 

Senhor Floh: "Die Probleme entwickeln sich durch die Meinungsverschiedenheiten. Einer will es besser haben als der andere. Da ging es schon in der Steinzeit mit den Machtkämpfen los.So ist das doch! Gerecht oder ungerecht ..." 

Dona Biene: Das Problem ist also der Mensch. Also das eigene Ich. 
Ich muss nicht meine Mitmenschen verändern. Deren Umerziehung findet statt, wenn ich mich selbst verändere. 
Es gilt sich selbst umzuprogrammieren, wobei ich das Flüchten nicht aus dem Kopf verjagen würde. Was sollte man in Ihrem Fall umprogrammieren? 

Senhor Floh: "Was soll ich umprogrammieren? In welche Richtung? Einen Hinweis vielleicht?" 

Hm ... 

Senhor Floh: "Gut! Das muss ich mir jetzt mehrmals durch den Kopf gehen lassen in den nächsten Tagen. Das Thema müssen wir erweitern, da bin ich mir sicher. Ich muss mich nicht anpassen und einfügen?" 

Dona Biene: Nein, Sie sind eine einzigartige Marke. 
Sie dürfen sich selbst feiern. 
Sie dürfen sich in Ihrem persönlichen Logo sonnen. 
Sie können an sich / Ihrem Logo herumprobieren, aber nicht am Mitarbeiter, Chef oder Lebenspartner. 
Solche Dinge und Aufklärungsversuche an denen überlassen Sie der Gewerkschaft bzw. der Partnerberatung. Sie kommen sonst in Teufelsküche und werden selbst zum Teufelsbraten. 

Senhor Floh:  "Ein Vorgesetzter sagte, ich solle mir gut überlegen, was ich sage, denn ich sei ersetzbar." 

Dona Biene: 
Natürlich! Der Vorgesetze auch. 
Trotzdem sind Sie etwas Besonderes. 
Dem Grundgedanken Ihres 'Ichs' / Ihres Logos sollten Sie treu bleiben. 
Abgesehen davon, wer will sich schon völlig neu erfinden? 
Auch Padre Alfonso Maria Parentes (2, 3) blieb als Musiker seinem Gesang und seinem Logo treu. Er trägt weiterhin seine Ordenstracht und wechselte lediglich den Orden. 

Senhor Floh: "Ich singe gerne, aber Kapuzinermönch? Nein!" 

Dona Biene: 
Müssen Sie nicht. 
Wenn Sie sich nach Ihrem eigenen Bauchgefühl richten, dann finden Sie Ihren passenden Weg mit ihrem unverwechselbaren Logo. 

Senhor Floh: "Ich möchte meine Umwelt anders erleben." 

Dona Biene: 
Ihre Umwelt erleben Sie neu und die Sie auch. 
Die aus Ihrer Einmaligkeit und ihrer Flexibilität heraus entstehende Innovation ist mächtiger als Ihr Wissen. 
(Zu "Innovation is more powerful than knowledge"  siehe Link 6 und 7). 

Senhor Floh: "Natürlich kann auch einiges schief gehen. Es muss nicht ..." 

Dona Biene: 
So ist es! Nach einem Unglück (9) ist keiner, was er vorher war. 
Das Leben ist ein Tanzboden zum Ausprobieren von neuen Verhaltensweisen.. 
Man kann sich natürlich auch verschämt und aus Furcht verkriechen und im Bett sterben. 
Wichtig ist das Gefühl, nicht alleine zu sein, dass da jemand sich sorgt und einen gern hat. (9  12). 

Senhor Floh: "Ich reise so gerne und war gerne mit dem Mountainbike unterwegs, um andere Leute - vielleicht neue Freunde - zu treffen. Jetzt bin ich ein durch meine Mitmenschen verunsicherter Mensch." 

Dona Biene: Reisen und Veränderungen sind selten tödlich. 
Sie fördern vielmehr die seelische und geistige Gesundheit, weil sie etwas in Bewegung bringen. Manche Menschen haben die besten Einfälle übrigens auf Reisen (siehe Link 4). 

Senhor Floh: "Ich muss meinem Leben wieder eine Bedeutung geben. Wenn man in ein fremdes Land kommt, versucht man zuerst die Sprache gut zu sprechen und sich völlig anzupassen, um nur nicht aufzufallen." 

Dona Biene: Eine Bedeutung gab sich Ijad Madisch mit seinem Mashup eines sozialen Media-Netzwerks für Mediziner und Forscher und durch die Verwirklichung seines Gedankens 'Give meaning to data.' (siehe Link 5) 
Sie hingegen besitzen Bedeutung allein aufgrund Ihres Interesses an Fremdsprachen und der Art Ihrer empathischen Kommunikation. Sie fallen schon auf, weil Sie besser der deutschen Sprache mächtig sind als mancher Deutsche. 
Ich selbst mag übrigens den Reiz des Auffallens und Rollenspiels. Allein mit meinem Namen, da bin ich ein lebendes Warnzeichen und jeder denkt "gleich sticht die Biene." 

Senhor Floh:  "Ich weiß, aber wer Sie länger kennt ...." 

Dona Biene: Der weiß, dass mich Honig und Worte beflügeln. 
Mr. Profitt sagt übrigens "The more flexible that people are about language use, then probably the more they thrive.” 
(Mr. Profit, siehe Link 8) 

_____________________________ 
(1) No stinking badges 
(1) We don't need no stinking badges! 
(2) Padre Alfonso Maria Parente - Che giorno sarà 
(2) Padre Alfonso Maria Parente - Che giorno sarà - Sanremo 2000.m4v 
(3) Cura, Senhor (Padre Alfonso Maria Parente) 
(3) http://letras.mus.br/padre-alfonso-maria-parente/1553762/ 
(4) Outfittery Co-Founder: "I Have My Best Ideas On Planes" 
(4) http://www.inspiredby-dld.de/ 
(5) Give meaning to data (Ijad Madisch) 
(5) https://plus.google.com/111634746643816111742/posts/8Apz1MgUhcX 
(6) DLD 14 in München und Bloggertreffen am Busbahnhof in München. 
(6) https://plus.google.com/111634746643816111742/posts/iHZesg7VFvs 
(7)"innovation is more powerful than knowledge" DLD14 - Annotate My Brand (Jean-Claude Biver, Angela Missoni, Mahbod Moghadam, Massimo Redaelli) 
(7) http://dld.co/videos/PQAhZRkUsng 
(8) "The more flexible that people are about language use, then probably the more they thrive.” (Mr. Profit) / Language by the Book, but the Book Is Evolving 
O.E.D.’s New Chief Editor Speaks of Its Future 
(8) http://www.nytimes.com/2014/01/22/books/oeds-new-chief-editor-speaks-of-its-future.html?smid=tw-nytimes&amp;_r=0 
(9) Sei anwesend! / Do be there! 
(9) http://www.nytimes.com/2014/01/21/opinion/brooks-the-art-of-presence.html?src=me&amp;module=Ribbon&amp;version=context&amp;region=Header&amp;action=click&amp;contentCollection=Most%20Emailed&amp;pgtype=article 
(10) Die Macht der Verletzlichkeit 
(10) http://diegoerelebt.wordpress.com/2012/09/24/uber-verletzlichkeit-scham-und-die-courage-unvollkommen-zu-sein-brene-brown/ 
(11) TEDx TALK – Brene Brown: Die Macht der Verletzlichkeit (Dez. 2010 
(11) )http://www.ted.com/talks/brene_brown_on_vulnerability.html 
(12) EDx TALK – Brene Brown: Auf die Scham hören (März 2012) 
(12) http://www.ted.com/talks/lang/de/brene_brown_listening_to_shame.html 
(13) Are MOOCs designed to be solo activities? Is Collaboration Key in a MOOC? 
(13) http://linkis.com/learningmoocs.com/KyLGS 
_________________________ 
#mooc   #MMC13   #elearning   #Sprache      #digitale_bildung     #Psychotherapie     #dld14  ﻿

Meer lezen (226 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-CBjn6hzUyPg/Ut4tR-Sm-OI/AAAAAAAAGGM/jmxvI0FIdWA/w426-h568/2014-01-19+16.17.07.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/110038350445855508357/albums/5935688462047722209/5935688461698298786</link><title>It's not an accident that three of the five fastest growing cities are in Texas. It's more like destiny. Our new issue explores why the Lone Star state is America's destiny. Find it on newsstands Friday. 

Read a preview: http://ti.me/1gmFV1w 

(Photo-illustration by Sarah Illenberger for TIME)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-W7Hz4njVyf8/Ul_NNRDpc6I/AAAAAAAAqqQ/VE9JxA-lj04/w426-h566/1101131028_600.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/115918140590477023459/albums/5957972490877233473/5957972491722595186</link><title>Paper-Planes Machine 
This will be highly used on Fridays﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_05_thumb.gif">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-MQ8i8eocwEg/Uq74ah6sm3I/AAAAAAAAsA8/75ZdfO_vmZs/w426-h240/rxmc8y4.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/101062611634442190772/albums/5935415082974369889/5845884439324304402</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-mw-Pq_N0U4Q/USDA7LvopBI/AAAAAAAAuRw/EuNRlCgaRjk/w426-h281/daphne%2Bkoller%2B7.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/114528586908817727732/albums/5739066320762366433/5739066326293563714</link><title>Many models for online learning 

Online schools are springing up all over, and there are many variations on the theme. It will be fascinating to see which models survive. Here are some examples: 

Calstate online (calstateonline.net): Charge tuition and grant degrees. Self-sustaining non-profit. 

edX (http://www.edxonline.org/): Free for now, but will they one day offer certificates for a fee? Large cash endowment, but what happens when that runs out? 

The Khan Academy (http://www.khanacademy.org/): Free forever? Contract with school districts? Foundation support. 

Udacity (http://www.udacity.com/) and Coursera (https://www.coursera.org/): Venture backed university spin offs are free for now, but investors will want income in the future. 

NPTEL, the National Program on Technology Enhanced Learning, (http://nptel.iitm.ac.in/): Produced by the Indian Institutes of Technology. Government funded and free. 

Open University (http://www.open.ac.uk/): Grants degrees and charges tuition (discount for UK students). 

Open University Learning Space (http://openlearn.open.ac.uk/): Free online courses from 1-20 hours long from the Open University and the BBC. 

Note that while US entries in the online education marketplace have been getting a lot of attention, this is a global phenomenon and there are excellent universities -- like the Open University in the UK and the Indian Institutes of Technology -- in many nations.﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_07_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-JPkLs8z4AvE/T6VCarkiSUI/AAAAAAAACrk/c-Qw9V4fy68/w426-h308/onlineuniversities2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/116726325327075260175/albums/5956490552828857105/5956490556136082818</link><title>QUESTION OF THE DAY: What free stuff on the internet should everyone be taking advantage of? 

I'll combine everything later and make one resource for everyone, so plus all the stuff you like so it gets added. 

#questionoftheday 

Let me know if you would like to be added to the QotD notification circle﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-T6eJK27kGhQ/Uqm0mhp1zYI/AAAAAAAByg0/hLqJUg6zerg/w426-h240/original.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/111474406259561102151/albums/5979243730027061217/5979243730332917682</link><title>I fail to understand why something like this needs to be a face-to-face workshop. It will meet 12:00 - 1:15 p.m.February 25, March 4, March 11, March 25 - so, right there, with the fixed days/times, they have probably eliminated 90% of their potential audience. Meanwhile, the announcement itself does not even contain a link to the "Information Literacy Competency Standards for Higher Education." 
I just don't get it: on the one hand, we are supposed to be teaching our students about how to make good use of the Internet (that is the theme of this workshop)... but our Center for Teaching Excellence acts like we live in a face-to-face world. If we really want to convey to our students how best to use the Internet, shouldn't we model Internet use (HYPERLINKS for example) in our own communications...? 
Sigh. Maybe someday my school will discover the Internet. For real. 
The only link, literally the one and only link, in this email which I just received is ... an email link for the email address of the organizer of the workshop. 
Oh, and there is a Register Now button for the face-to-face workshop. Of course. ﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_09_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-b9RCZ-cF7DE/UvqKfkv5n7I/AAAAAAAA_44/-xu3PhqEOFY/w426-h441/Screen%2Bshot%2B2014-02-11%2Bat%2B3.38.43%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7155-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/ted%20talk%20mooc/photos/115768532033761132465/albums/5997791246024094545/5997791250157150930</link><title>Join MakingComics.com CEO Patrick Yurick, EIC Devin Larson, and Gutter Talk Host Adam Greenfield as we cover the second week of content available through the “Get A Grasp!” course. 

Guest panelists for this week include: 

Mark Waid – Thrillbent, Incorruptable, Daredevil, Hulk, etc. 
Bizhan Khodabendeh – Little Black Fish 
Lee Cherolis – Little Guardians 
Ted Washington – Puna Press 
Aaron Conley – Sabretooth Swordsman 
Ulises Farinas – Judge Dredd Artist 

Each week MakingComics.com brings you an exciting new installment of our famous Gutter Talk podcasts in conjunction with content being released on our MOOC “Get A Grasp!”. To interact with guests visit http://makingcomics.appspot.com and enroll in this massive open online course (it’s free! EVERYTHING IS FREE with Get A Grasp!) Registration closes on March 22nd so enroll now. 

Gutter Talk 1 “Grasping The Pitch”: http://tinyurl.com/guttertalk1 
Gutter Talk 2 “World Building” http://tinyurl.com/guttertalk2 
Gutter Talk 3 “Setting Achievable Goals” http://tinyurl.com/guttertalk3 
Gutter Talk 4 “Making The Pitch” http://tinyurl.com/guttertalk4﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7155_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-NP6FJdeEDYs/UzxvXUaQItI/AAAAAAAAAaw/JcQki_Jy0kk/w426-h335/Week2_fwesite.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>