<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:34:56" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/107508786997767901955/albums/5949229058128316289/5949229057470302674?sqi=117695051214010077934&amp;sqsi=cb52afac-0779-4c93-aea0-b623269e6528</link><title>The helicopters land on the White House grounds. 
Liz Carpenter, executive assistant to Johnson: "Again, there was a battery of newspaper people. The Secret Service man motioned to Mrs. Johnson's car in front of the White House, and the president said to me, 'Stay with Lady Bird and help her all you can.' 
"I got into the car, and we started driving through the night to The Elms (the vice president's official residence), rolling up the window so we could talk. Both of us were well aware of what dreadful thing had happened and the difficult days ahead - made even more difficult because this had occurred in the home state of the vice president. 
"And I said to her, 'It's a terrible thing to say, but the salvation of Texas is that the governor was hit.' 
"And she said, 'Don't think I haven't thought of that. I only wish it could have been me.' " 
Houston PR man Jack Valenti is among those who accompany Johnson after their landing on the south grounds of the White House.﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-aqrN_cmKoZI/Uo_oTrHzCdI/AAAAAAAAO00/mMQEqdTpnic/w426-h471/JFKLBJCONNALLY.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/116852308918354172806/albums/5708515014549776257/5708515018454062066</link><title>Residence of Baaghee President 

Vice covered as how it should me.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-F7tbjOAmlhU/Tzi4Kg3v0_I/AAAAAAAABHM/LPeiii7cwbE/w426-h320/396236_10151276698350107_585465106_23059459_1268935299_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/107655690851381052200/albums/5934361675000490529/5934361673118007474?sqi=107414335085606228412&amp;sqsi=59584e6a-24a4-4095-a68b-485dbdc1ea85</link><title>Zoomed iPhone 5s pic of deer on the grounds of the vice president's residence ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-exmJlclGtl4/UlsWgAbkQLI/AAAAAAAASkg/v9j2xanyjnU/w426-h568/IMG_2364.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/113603800432750245212/albums/5765050513017683873/5765050513074739666</link><title>"UPA renominates Hamid Ansari for vice president" 

Incumbent Hamid Ansari will be the United Progressive Alliance (UPA) candidate in the vice presidential election, Congress president Sonia Gandhi announced here today.Making the announcement at the UPA leaders' meeting, Gandhi said that Ansari has presided over the Rajya Sabha as its chairman with dignity. 
She said the UPA is honoured to nominate Ansari for "second term as vice president of India". 

The UPA meeting was held at the residence of Prime Minister Manmohan Singh and was attended by leaders of the constituents of the alliance. 

Ansari was elected vice president in 2007 and his term will come to an end on Aug 10. 

Election for the vice president's post are scheduled on Aug 7. Last date for filing nominations is July 20.﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-aoZtoo-3E9U/UAGS5agA2dI/AAAAAAAAABg/mEF9FkT12nc/w426-h320/921101472hamid_ansari_20070806.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/106955629541341378521/albums/5966079690595624065/5966079691502488978</link><title>#Priyanka gets active in #Congresspolitics, holds meeting at #Rahul’s residence   http://goo.gl/ZKa5Eh #PriyankaGandhi has suddenly become active in #Congress #politics, holding an #importantmeeting with #partyleaders at her brother and #Congress vice-president #RahulGandhi’s residence.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-sbXY8piyENw/UsvF3qmtjZI/AAAAAAAAGH4/WXaaKeHNIJk/w426-h320/Priyanka-Gandhi400x300.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/113662445126048769965/albums/5836035794244895793/5836035799539812434?authkey=CIefnqHCgNGLRw</link><title>The White House 
In 2007, it was ranked second on the American Institute of Architects list of "America's Favorite Architecture". 

The White House is the official residence and principal workplace of the President of the United States. Located at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue Northwest, Washington, D.C., the house was designed by Irish-born James Hoban,[1] and built between 1792 and 1800 of white-painted Aquia Creek sandstone in the Neoclassical style. It has been the residence of every U.S. president since John Adams. When Thomas Jefferson moved into the house in 1801, he (with architect Benjamin Henry Latrobe) expanded the building outward, creating two colonnades that were meant to conceal stables and storage.[2] 
In 1814, during the War of 1812, the mansion was set ablaze by the British Army in the Burning of Washington, destroying the interior and charring much of the exterior. Reconstruction began almost immediately, and President James Monroe moved into the partially reconstructed Executive Residence in October 1817. Construction continued with the addition of the South Portico in 1824 and the North in 1829. Because of crowding within the executive mansion itself, President Theodore Roosevelt had all work offices relocated to the newly constructed West Wing in 1901. Eight years later, President William Howard Taft expanded the West Wing and created the first Oval Office which was eventually moved as the section was expanded. The third-floor attic was converted to living quarters in 1927 by augmenting the existing hip roof with long shed dormers. A newly constructed East Wing was used as a reception area for social events; Jefferson's colonnades connected the new wings. East Wing alterations were completed in 1946, creating additional office space. By 1948, the house's load-bearing exterior walls and internal wood beams were found to be close to failure. Under Harry S. Truman, the interior rooms were completely dismantled and a new internal load-bearing steel frame constructed inside the walls. Once this work was completed, the interior rooms were rebuilt. 
Today, the White House Complex includes the Executive Residence, West Wing, East Wing, the Eisenhower Executive Office Building -- the former State Department, which now houses offices for the President's staff and the Vice President -- and Blair House, a guest residence. 
The Executive Residence is made up of six stories—the Ground Floor, State Floor, Second Floor, and Third Floor, as well as a two-story basement. The term White House is regularly used as a metonym for the Executive Office of the President of the United States and for the president's administration and advisers in general. The property is a National Heritage Site owned by the National Park Service and is part of the President's Park. 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_House﻿

Meer lezen (43 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-cnYNXvP79dY/UP3Do5gIiFI/AAAAAAAAGg0/upK79BrZGY8/w426-h316/WhiteHouseSouthFacade.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/108290752985682488534/albums/5997926242399775489/5997926244450170578</link><title>Embarrassment for Rahul Gandhi as Amethi SDM rejects residence proof application 

http://zeenews.india.com/news/general-elections-2014/embarrassment-for-rahul-gandhi-as-amethi-sdm-rejects-residence-proof-application_922000.html 

 In a major embarrassment for the Congress, its vice president Rahul Gandhi's application for proof of residence in his parliamentary constituency Amethi has been rejected by the Sub Divisional Magistrate of the area, reports said on Thursday.   #myvote2014﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-XlGfb2pzhwc/UzzqJBVx9tI/AAAAAAABOJc/seQs0nnLDMY/w426-h245/rahul-540310.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/110877871709290597487/albums/5886852451515845553/5886852456344436066?authkey=CPfV3_H2pZTJCQ</link><title>Villa Melzi was built back in 1810 as a summer residence of Francesco Melzi d'Eril, Vice President of the Italian Napoleonic Republic. The villa is a perfect example of Neoclassical style, while the gardens are an English inspired corner of heaven. 
More photos: http://www.travelocafe.com/2013/06/villa-melzi-gardens-bellagio-lake-como.html 
#LakeComo #Italy #Bellagio #nature #gardeninginspiration   ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-z0PD9DcZWKQ/UbJNHoGLvWI/AAAAAAAAWLw/QQUVhz-ih9M/w426-h284/Gardens%2Bof%2BVilla%2BMelzi%252C%2BBellagio%2B27.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/103145429239923145864/albums/5737741807264825137/5737741808717131170</link><title>A labour delegation led by Pt. Ram Swaroop Jaanbaz today called on Haryana Chief Minister, Mr Bhupinder Singh Hooda at his New Delhi residence and gave him greetings of Labour Day(1St. May). 

Chandigarh, May 1- A labour delegation led by Pt. Ram Swaroop Jaanbaz today called on Haryana Chief Minister, Mr Bhupinder Singh Hooda at his New Delhi residence and gave him greetings of Labour Day(1St. May). The delegation included Vice-President of Pradesh Congress Committee Labour Cell, Mr Parvesh Tyagi and Secretary Mr Rakesh Tyagi, besides Daya Ram Sharma, Yograj Sharma, Sangram Singh, Hari Parkash and others. They thanked Mr Hooda for the labour friendly policies of his Government. 

Mr Hooda said that Haryana Government is committed to the welfare of labour class. Minimum wages for labour in Haryana are maximum as compared to other states. The credit for peaceful industrial atmosphere in the state goes to hardworking labour also, besides the policies of the Government, he said. 

Mr Hooda was also presented a memento on this occasion.﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-IewIJWtGAn0/T6CNxnF97aI/AAAAAAAAC1A/2IBO7AKO-eo/w426-h374/CM%2B02.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7165-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/vice%20president%20residence/photos/109201681846030076792/albums/5901210579017353905/5901210582563798946</link><title>July 16, 1790 – U.S. President George Washington signed the Residence Act, selecting a new permanent site along the Potomac River for the capital of the United States, which later became Washington, D.C. ... Wikipedia \- "he Residence Act of 1790, officially titled An Act for establishing the temporary and permanent seat of the Government of the United States, is the United States federal law that settled the question of locating the capital of the United States, selecting a site along the Potomac River. The federal government was located in New York City at the time the bill was passed and had previously been located in Philadelphia, Annapolis and several other settlements. 

The question of where to locate the capital was raised in 1783. Numerous locations were offered by the states to serve as the nation's capital, including: Kingston, New York; Nottingham Township in New Jersey; Annapolis; Williamsburg, Virginia; Wilmington, Delaware; Reading, Pennsylvania; Germantown, Pennsylvania; Lancaster, Pennsylvania; New York City; Philadelphia; and Princeton; among others. The Southern states refused to accept a capital located in the North, and vice versa. Another suggestion was for there to be two capitals. Congress approved a plan in 1783 for a capital on the Potomac, near Georgetown, in Maryland, and another capital on the Delaware River; this plan was rescinded the following year. ..." 

more: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Residence_Act﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7165_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4Tk-_LnxyTQ/UeVPwkZ9v6I/AAAAAAACHCs/A9r-ANj4fOQ/w426-h684/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>