<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:43:51" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/113018212081050297710/albums/5735594540056123441/5735597072816989762</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Gk2XaGoRr2E/T5jvJjQG5kI/AAAAAAAAAFg/l1YrAjZ2fJk/w426-h320/IMG-20120426-01026.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/113018212081050297710/albums/5735595637224402513/5735595637284678354</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MnAb7o7OqQU/T5jt1_eiKtI/AAAAAAAAAEo/d0_rvSgEOz8/w426-h568/IMG-20120426-00999.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/100631810155377056526/albums/5680484152657832001/5680484157357041234</link><title>Aluminium extrusion with CNC punched ventilation slots 

This aluminium extrusion has been sawn to length and then CNC punched on our Titan CNC punch press. Each extrusion is held in a special jig and fed under the turret and punched with the correct rectangular tools to create the ventilation pattern seen below. This method of manufacturing is much faster and cheaper than maching the slots in a milling machine. 

For more example of CNC punching on our Titan please click below: 
http://www.vandf.co.uk/titan-cnc-punching/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-jVbubc6O1jk/TtUiPp-AJlI/AAAAAAAAAgc/GwHzVvfznws/w426-h320/aluminium%2Bextrusion.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/115807480993720684891/albums/5841574356591012897/5841574362127978402?authkey=CLS49amRvcjR1gE</link><title>QATALUM SIGNSALUMINUM SUPPLY CONTRACTS WITH QATARI DOWNSTREAM BUSINESSES 
Qatalum – the Qatari aluminium smelter – has announced the signing, on 29th January, of supply contracts with ALUNOOR and Qatar Aluminium Extrusion, for the sale of premium aluminium, The signing of the contracts took place at the Qatalum office at Mesaieed. 
Qatalum was represented by CEO Tom Petter Johansen and Deputy CEO Khalid Mohammed Laram; ALUNOOR was represented by Mr. Jassim Abdul Noor, Owner and General Manager; and Qatar Aluminium Extrusion was represented by Chairman Mr. Abdul Rahman Al Ansari. 
The total volume of both contracts is approximately ten thousand tonnes for 2013 - of which close to 800 metric tonnes will be delivered monthly. Although a small amount by global downstream standards, the significance of the contracts is in the pioneering of a downstream aluminium industry in Qatar, exemplifying the support and cooperation between Qatalum and such downstream industries. 
Deliveries to local customers started in mid-2012 on a trial basis during both the customers’ ramp-up operations and to test the product at their facilities. The excellent quality of Qatalum products was appreciated by both customers, thus current contracts represent a long-term commitment for supply from Qatalum. 
The two companies who have signed these supply contracts have varied expertise and market focus. ALUNOOR has two broad profiles, in industry and construction, making up 20 and 80 per cent of its work, respectively. In construction, it produces windows, doors, metal curtains and building exteriors. In industrial production, ALUNOOR makes products for other factories to use in the manufacturing process, such as mechanical devices and various high-end precision equipment. 
Qatar Aluminium Extrusion Company is an expert in aluminium extrusion and is involved in production of various products for domestic and business use. 
Qatalum CEO Tom Petter said: “Encouraging the local aluminium downstream industry is a key priority and commitment at Qatalum. The contracts signed today represent the beginning of implementing such commitment towards Qatalum’s participation in developing local industry in Qatar. ”Qatalum premium quality products and location represent huge opportunities for developing aluminium downstream industries in Qatar. The demand for aluminium is obviously there. 
Khalid Laram, Qatalum’s DCEO added, “Qatalum is ideally located to meet the growing demand for aluminium products based on strong strategic fundamentals. With these supply contracts, we are seeing an exciting future in downstream Qatari industry. We at Qatalum are proud to be instrumental in developing this in Qatar”. 
Khalid Laram added: “We expect that Qatalum should be able to supply the local Qatari market with their needs for the coming years. This is an exciting time for us, and these contracts are part of Qatalum's policy in encouraging other companies to become involved in the downstream industry related to aluminium in Qatar especially after Qatalum received ISO 9001/2008 certificate and ISO/TS 16949:2009 certificate for high quality products which allows our Aluminium to be used in the automotive industry”.﻿

Meer lezen (51 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-eqDpF2_wOD8/URFw7q-qz6I/AAAAAAAAAm0/oIdo-5W7vzI/w426-h237/1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/115807480993720684891/albums/5990239973153223905/5990239975825011778</link><title>Qatalum celebrates first year with local clients 

The first year of successful local sales reinforces Qatalums commitment to supply the local downstream market with premium aluminium. 

Abdul Noor and Qatar Aluminium Extrusion signed their first permanent contract with Qatalum for our premium aluminium products in January 2013. In recognition of a successful year of exclusive sales, Qatalum celebrated the milestone by hosting a small dinner for its local clients. 

“It’s an honour for us to have Abdul Noor and Qatar Aluminium Extrusion as our clients. They represent the beginning of a potentially large local downstream market for Qatalum and our team in the Sales and Marketing team are doing our best to meet this requirements as the need arises,” said Saeed Al-Marri, Qatalum’s Marketing and Sales Manager.﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-RQq9ETMiRVI/UyGbhTZk9EI/AAAAAAAACbw/hD0COj1tAnc/w426-h237/photo%2B1%2BSM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/113018212081050297710/albums/5735596146085455201/5735599380509398770</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-7b0JjpjgG1U/T5jxP4E2lvI/AAAAAAAAAHI/ovRwRwhquyk/w426-h320/Ngoro-20111123-00587.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/113018212081050297710/albums/5735594540056123441/5735594537993150498</link><title>Profile Untuk High Risk Building﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-qxtT07tN33w/T5js2ATAoCI/AAAAAAAAAEM/wBzm0WnC0Ac/w426-h320/IMG-20120426-01012.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/115807480993720684891/albums/5854077799481047649/5854077800617049874?authkey=CP6utf2B7cnd3AE</link><title>Support and cooperation between Qatalum and downstream Aluminium industries in Qatar 

On the 27th of February 2013 a technical seminar was hosted by Marketing and Sales to inform local customers on the virtues of aluminium. 
The seminar took place in the Al-Zubara meeting room and focused on broadening the audience’s technical knowledge. Together with the Qatalum Marketing and Sales Department, also present were Roar Orsund, Casthouse Manager and Christian Stette, EI Manager who gave presentations on their respective topics: ‘Aluminium Alloys’, ‘Extrusion Metallurgy’ and ‘End Use of Aluminium’. 
The seminar was attended by production managers and senior technical staff from Qatalum’s local customers, Qatar Aluminium Extrusion, and Abdul Noor Aluminium Extrusion Factory. They exchanged valuable information related to alloys, products, quality, and markets. 
The presentations and discussions were followed by a visit to the Qatalum casthouse. 
After the seminar, Manjunath N. Rao, acting General Manager of Qatar Aluminium Extrusion Company (QLAX) said, “The event was extremely beneficial to our staff and operation. I am particularly impressed by Qatalum’s advanced casting technology.” 
Qatalum’s business objective for such an event is to enhance and create a healthier customer supplier relationship which will result in an increase in Qatalum’s local sales.﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/--9huxpkwE_I/UT3cvlFHfxI/AAAAAAAAAvE/PQ63QWts0rE/w426-h237/Local%252520Customer%252520Event%2525201-470.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/116403146004026488069/albums/5846719365866422177/5846719365670832866</link><title>Liquid aluminium 710 degrees celcius, extrusion ingot. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-4w7Bu6jLg5E/USO4SSw1CuI/AAAAAAAAAb0/YN27ofX1VOM/w426-h240/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7167-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/aluminium%20extrusion/photos/115807480993720684891/albums/5957567641933719233/5957567644009051986</link><title>Qatalum offers conversion service to regional customers 

In its efforts to add value to its customers, through the conversion service package, Qatalum is able to satisfy its clientele, improve its customer relationships and generate a positive casthouse gross margin. 

Beginning January 2014, Qatalum will take clean process scrap retrieved from its customer’s process back to reclaim a casthouse product of the same quality as a conversion service initiated by Qatalum’s Marketing and Sales department. The result is to establish a long-term relationship with its customers and make Qatalum the preferred provider of casthouse value added products in GCC. 

The conversion service fee includes transportation both ways and the logistical particulars are currently being solved. The competitive rate offered to Qatalum’s local clients, Qatar Aluminium Extrusion, and Abdul Noor Aluminium Extrusion Factory has resulted in a very positive longstanding outcome. The service to other clients in the GCC is under evaluation. 

It stands to be noted that the arrangement is not one of recycling which allows for third part intervention into the loop, often resulting in a mix-in with other materials and a reduction of value of the material, of which will be downgraded. As this is Qatalum’s own metal to begin with there is no degradation. 

Therefore, the casthouse can utilise its extra capacity and the cold metal helps in bringing the temperature in the furnaces down unlike when using hot metal from Reduction which is at a higher temperature. 

According to Saeed Al-Marri, Marketing and Sales Manager, Supply Chain Group, “Customer satisfaction anchors Qatalum’s Marketing and Sales strategy. Adding value to our sales enables Qatalum to create a future of opportunities for a viable downstream industry in Qatar in which Qatalum can play a leading role.”﻿

Meer lezen (34 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7167_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Iry3JqTl19s/Uq2INSqFN1I/AAAAAAAACC0/5meSnk1xQbQ/w426-h248/Untitled.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>