<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:16:48" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/114863801824334157938/albums/5943523929719122353/5943523936926030674?sqi=101996609942925099701&amp;sqsi=9b30e14a-ca6e-48c5-9376-f108acf5e411</link><title>One of the possible side effects of a severed spinal cord is a person’s inability to sense when their bladder is full or control over its release. By wrapping electrodes round the bundles of nerves that still exist near the bladder and connecting it to the spinal cord, researchers managed to allow a rat with a severed spinal cord to control its bladder again. 

There are still many steps before this technology can go inside humans. The device may be small enough to fit in a human, but the equipment needed to process the information is still far too large for people to carry around with them. If scientists can make this smaller (and scientists are pretty good at making electronics smaller) then it will be a great leap forward in the well-being of those with spinal injuries. 

http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-24834374﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-wXgSSf0II1g/Unujh86B21I/AAAAAAAACSQ/-XsgZGwevXQ/w506-h526/rat+brown+norwegian%28NHGRI%29+cropped.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/111571652882578786524/albums/5986521966830475505/5986521970351312002</link><title>Just for your #baby : Gruesome abortionist severed spinal cords of living babies after they were born alive 
Abortion is an uncomfortable subject for most Americans but the time has come, thanks to details emerging from a murder trial in Philadelphia, for the country to have a national conversation that is not about a "woman's right" or a "man's mandate" but about life itself, and specifically, what it should mean to be born alive in America. 

This long-overdue conversation has become necessary due to allegations surrounding the gruesome nature of Dr. Kermit Gosnell's abortion practice in a metropolis that is still, though laughingly, referred to as the "city of brotherly love." 

Gosnell, who is currently on trial for murdering as many as seven newborns over the course of his decades-long career, has not yet been convicted by a court for things he is accused of doing. But based on testimony thus far, if he is even guilty of some of those things, he is clearly a sick man in a sick industry that is in dire regulatory need - and I just don't say, "We need more regulations" very easily, as my readers know. 

Follow Us On Social Media Channels : 
#Web Site :   http://www.evegym.com 
#Twitter    :           https://twitter.com/eveegym #Facebook  :        https://www.facebook.com/evegym #YOUTUBE :  http://www.youtube.com/evegym 
#Google   +   :  https://plus.google.com/+Evegym/posts﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Vd4KCG9C3BM/UxRmA5rcjII/AAAAAAAAN-A/ApRVjrvAwKM/s506/11.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/111480413428119678209/albums/5780101418234877553/5780101419627790866</link><title>Scientists Clear Path to the Fountain of Eternal Youth 
http://goo.gl/1vcPK 
Researchers have discovered an efficient and totally safe method to turn adult blood cells "all the way back to the way [they were] when that person was a 6-day-old embryo." The discovery could be the key to cure the incurable—from heart attacks to severed spinal cord to cancer—and open the door, some day, to eternal youth. 

How It Works 
Using electrical pulses, the researchers opened holes in the membrane of blood cells extracted from a patient's spinal cord. They used these tiny holes to inject plasmids loaded with four genes, programmed to make the cells revert to a primitive state. After the plasmids completed their function, they cultivated the cells with irradiated bone-marrow cells. Seven to 14 days later, the cultivated cells magically turned to embryonic stem cells.﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-l4f_hGJ9NLA/UDcLneqlQhI/AAAAAAAB-zs/hqgiMv8erHY/w506-h285/scientists-clear-a-path-to-the-fountain-of-eternal-youth.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/101701263979248309987/albums/5748846747703502337/5748846749452330546</link><title>Spinal Cord Regeneration? 

Wearing a robotic harness, paralyzed rats have been made to walk again, according to a new study—albeit with an oddly upright, humanlike gait and while stimulated by judicious jolts of electricity and chemicals. 

It's the first time severely injured spinal cords have been reawakened, say researchers, who add that the technique might hold some promise for disabled people. 

First, neuroscientist Grégoire Courtine and his team severed the spines of 27 rats, leaving some tissue intact but no direct nerve connections—and therefore no way for the animals to control their hind legs. 

A week later the researchers put 17 of the rats on a sort of physical therapy regimen and began administering chemical injections and electric stimulation directly to the rodents' spinal cords. The remaining ten rats, used as a control group, received no treatment. 

http://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2012/05/120531-paralyzed-rats-walk-science-spinal-cords-health﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-yzJROeCEtL0/T8gBqPFD5jI/AAAAAAAAAOQ/mK8nhS_C3LU/w506-h380/paralyzed-mice-walk-again-science_54205_600x450.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/103258540708963344616/albums/5946636177103553057/5946636177059547842</link><title>Jessica Pressler and her five siblings were in a car with their dad when a tire blew and their van rolled. Jessica severed her spinal cord and lost the use of her legs. 

On Saturday, a rally will be held in Collierville supporting the 12-year-old, who is now adjusting to life in a wheelchair. She is inspiring -- learning a new way of life with a smile and a sense of humor. 

More information about Jessica -- and how you can help -- coming up TONIGHT at 6 p.m. 

More: http://buff.ly/1auXp6b﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-rIaV7wAkVtk/UoayGK4fCsI/AAAAAAAABJY/MK50xhXx4YA/w506-h284/f185eae5-47c1-4ecc-ac4a-3a3c503edd60</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/116633256261935341657/albums/5749037540845912401/5749037541373537506</link><title>これだったらずっと寝てる方がいいわ。 

An undated handout photo provided by the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (EPFL) May 31, 2012, shows a researcher observing a rat walking on its hind legs during an experiment at the Center for Neuroprosthetics and Brain Mind Institute in Ecublens. Rats with spinal cord injuries and severe paralysis are now walking thanks to researchers lead by Professor Gregoire Courtine at EPFL. Published in the June 1, 2012 issue of 'Science' magazine, the results show that a severed section of the spinal cord can make a comeback when its own innate intelligence and regenerative capacity is awakened. According to lead author Gregoire Courtine, it is yet unclear if similar rehabilitation techniques could work for humans, but the observed nerve growth hints at new methods for treating paralysis. REUTERS/EPFL/Handout (SWITZERLAND - Tags: SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY SOCIETY HEALTH) ﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-qsFV2WESqKk/T8ivLyX0bOI/AAAAAAAAD7k/jcKPOjMOHwk/w506-h337/%E3%83%80%E3%82%A6%E3%83%B3%E3%83%AD%E3%83%BC%E3%83%89+%281%29.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/102281416163557901093/albums/5848912616066219905/5848912621365193218?authkey=CNK1kpKJktzNZg</link><title>Scientists behind groundbreaking research that enabled rats with severed spines to run again after two weeks have outlined their plans for human trials. 

The technology brings fresh hope to sufferers of spinal cord injuries, and the team say they hope the first humans could be implanted with the technology within months. 

(Daily Mail: goo.gl/yQfk6) 

#ScienceEveryday   #spinalcordinjury   #electricalstimulation   #NeuroScience  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Ta9tZtHfTiU/USuDCk7FagI/AAAAAAAANas/atpS2Utf__k/w506-h433/tumblr_mirv126RkD1rog5d1o1_r1_500.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/112677783382674926842/albums/5863134149733680929/5863134153973722290?authkey=CPe7jpizm8_ZRQ</link><title>Apr 4, 1968: 
Dr. King is assassinated 

Just after 6 p.m. on April 4, 1968, Martin Luther King Jr. is fatally shot while standing on the balcony outside his second-story room at the Lorraine Motel in Memphis, Tennessee. The civil rights leader was in Memphis to support a sanitation workers' strike and was on his way to dinner when a bullet struck him in the jaw and severed his spinal cord. King was pronounced dead after his arrival at a Memphis hospital. He was 39 years old.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-7Kch9gkHaWs/UV4JcuYQbLI/AAAAAAAABoY/q6s-_YG1DRQ/s506/Martin-Luther-King-Jr-9365086-2-402.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5994627340374696241/5994627346528766946</link><title>Autopsy Confirms Texas Cop Killed Student for Being Sarcastic, With 5 Shots in Back at Close Range http://b4in.org/p1CK 

A Texas college student died from a gunshot wound to his back after making a sarcastic remark to the campus police officer who killed him. 

23-year-old Cameron Redus was shot five times at close range by Cpl. Christopher Carter, a University of Incarnate Word police officer, during a traffic stop in the early hours of December 6th 2013, near the San Antonio campus. 

KENS-TV report that the autopsy performed the following day showed Redus, a student at the private Catholic university, was shot in the back, left eye, upper chest, left elbow, and right hip. 

According to the medical examiner, the bullet that was “the most immediately lethal” entered the student’s back, severed his spinal cord, hit a major blood vessel in his chest, and became lodged in the sac surrounding his heart. The autopsy also found that the gunshot wound to his eye could also have been fatal. 

The autopsy noted a number of wounds around the student’s neck, but found such contusions could have occurred when Redus was thrown to the ground or by a nearby gunshot wound. 

A toxicology report found that Redus’ blood-alcohol content was 0.155, nearly twice the legal limit for driving in Texas, and a separate test conducted using vitreous fluid from the student’s eye showed a higher 0.186 level. 

Redus also tested positive for trace amounts of tetrahydrocannabinol, the active component in marijuana. 

More http://b4in.org/p1CK﻿

Meer lezen (27 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-qXJbMQ5-hgo/UzExz46wi-I/AAAAAAAAfec/MrtRltm-n08/w506-h281/Cameron+Redus.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7173-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/%20severed%20spinal%20cord/photos/115202563351778582675/albums/6001060943409965265/6001060949783548338</link><title>A horrific accident nearly robbed 3-year-old Zakkary Smith of his life and left him paralyzed from the neck down. 

Zakkary was strapped into his booster seat when a car driven by an elderly man ran a red light and slammed into their vehicle. 

Though Zakk never suffered any direct impact, he experienced a kind of super whiplash called internal decapitation that severed his skull from his spine, stretching the spinal cord. 

He’s now entered in a contest sponsored by the National Mobility Equipment Dealers Association to win a wheelchair-accessible vehicle and he needs your vote. 

“Like” and “Share” to show your support for little Zakkary! 

Full story: http://abc7.ws/1n136Rl﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7173_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-acLS3o4T2-c/U0gNI4tREbI/AAAAAAAAjlo/lUZZSYKZJPQ/w506-h284/ht_zakk_mom_sr_140410_16x9_992.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>