<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7189">judiciary act 1789</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:19:38" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/113127374166684973080/albums/5782302181377118385/5782302184471558978</link><title>The authority for requiring this Oath arises under Article VI of the Constitution of the United States "... all executive and judicial Officers, both of the United States and of the several States, shall be bound by Oath ... ";  and the Judiciary act of 1789, 1 Stat 23, Sec. 3:  1 Stat 23 Sec. 3: 

SEC.  3.  And be it further enacted, That the members of the several State legislatures, at the next sessions of the said legislatures, respectively, and all executive and judicial officers of the several States, who have been heretofore chosen or appointed, or who shall be chosen or appointed before the first day of August next, and who shall then be in office, shall, within one month thereafter, take the same oath or affirmation, except where they shall have taken it before; which may be administered by any person authorized by the law of the State, in which such office shall be holden, to administer oaths.   And the members of the several State legislatures, and all executive and judicial officers of the several States, who shall be chosen or appointed after the said first day of August, shall, before they proceed to execute the duties of their respective offices, take the foregoing oath or affirmation, which shall be administered by the person or person, who by the law of the State shall be authorized to administer the oath of office;  and the person or persons so administering the oath hereby required to be taken, shall cause a record or certificate thereof to be made, in the same manner, as, by the law of the State, he or they shall be directed to record or certify the oath of office 

The requirement for taking this oath, and that this is still current law is evidenced by 5 U.S.C. § 3331. Oath of office. 
Origin: United States Statute, Title XIX, Sec. 1756 - Sec. 1759: [2 July, 1862 c. 128v. 12 p. 502] 

The statutes did not change their meanings when the laws were codified, and a construction is necessary: 

To wit: (From United States Statutes at Large Revised Statutes) 
TITLE XIX. PROVISIONS APPLICABLE TO SEVERAL CLASSES OF OFFICERS. 1873 -1874; 

“Sec. 1756. Every person elected or appointed to any office of honor or profit, either in civil, military, or naval service, excepting the President and the persons embraced by the section following, shall, before entering upon the duties of such office, and before being entitled to any part of the salary or other emoluments thereof, take and subscribe the following oath: “ I, A B, do solemnly swear (or affirm) that I have never voluntarily borne arms against the United States since I have been a citizen thereof; that I have voluntarily given no aid, countenance, counsel, or encouragement to persons engaged in armed hostility thereto; that I have neither sought, nor accepted, nor attempted to exercise the functions of any office whatever, under any authority or pretended authority, in hostility to the United States; that I have not yielded a voluntary support to any pretended government, authority, power, or constitution within the United States, hostile or inimical thereto. And I do further swear (or affirm) that, to the best of my knowledge and ability, I will support and defend the Constitution of The United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic; that I will bear true faith and alleg-iance to the same; that I take this obligation freely, with-out any mental reservation or purpose of evasion, and that I will well and faithfully discharge the duties of the office on which I am about to enter. So help me God.” 

[ Section 1757 is repealed] (Alternate Oath for Confederate Officers) 

“Sec. 1758.The Oath of office required by either of the two preceding sections may be taken before any officer authorized either by the laws of the United States, or by the local municipal law, to administer oaths, in the State, Territory, or District where such oath may be administered. [See § 2617.]” 

“Sec. 1759. The oath of office taken by any person pursuant to the requirements of section seventeen hundred and fifty-six or of section seventeen hundred and fifty-seven, shall be delivered in by him to be preserved among the files of the House of Congress, Department, or court to which the oath is made may appertain.” 

“Sec. 1760. No money shall be paid from the Treasury to any person acting or assuming to act as an officer, civil, military, or naval, as salary, in any office when the office is not authorized by some previously existing law, unless such office is subsequently authorized by law.” … 

“Sec. 1762. No money shall be paid or received from the Treasury, or paid or received from or retained out of any public moneys or funds of the United States, whether in the Treasury or not, to or by or for the benefit of any person appointed to or authorized to act in or holding or exercising the duties or functions of any office contrary to sections seventeen hundred and sixty-seven to seventeen hundred and seventy, inclusive; nor shall any claim, account, voucher, order, certificate, warrant, or other instrument providing for or relating to such payment, receipt, or retention, be presented, passed, allowed, approved, certified, or paid by any officer, or by any person exercising the functions or performing the duties of any office, or exercising or performing the duties of any office or place of trust under the United States, for or in respect to such office, or the exercising or performing the functions or duties thereof. Every person who violates any part of the provisions of this section shall be deemed guilty of a high misdemeanor, and shall be imprisoned not more than ten years, or fined not more that ten thousand dollars, or both.”﻿

Meer lezen (96 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-aM_qth5vCGA/UD7dM2lke0I/AAAAAAAAAaI/Lb7_DNvGV4Q/w426-h407/Judge_Imposter.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/113630612440279083293/albums/5892219013922170401/5892219019978204146?authkey=CPTRyYvdl-LrJw</link><title>Elizabeth Warren Warns That The Supreme Court Is Becoming ‘A Subsidiary’ Of The Chamber Of Commerce 

Then it could also be said the Robert's Supreme Court is an extension of ALEC and Americans should do something about this...keep reading. 

Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) used her remarks at the 2013 American Constitution Society for Law and Policy National Convention to warn that the Supreme Court is being captured by interests representing America’s biggest corporations: 

ake a look at the win rate of the Chamber of Commerce. According to the Constitution Accountability Center, the Chamber moved from a 43 percent win rate during the very conservative Berger Court to a 56 percent win rate under the very conservative Rehnquist court. And now they are at a 70 percent win rate under the Roberts Court. Follow this pro-business trend to its obvious conclusion and you will end up with a Supreme Court that’s a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Chamber of Commerce. 

The Chamber of Commerce is the nation’s largest business lobby. In 2012, it spent over $100 million on lobbying, according to OpenSecret.com. Aligned with the dark money “social welfare” non-profits of the Koch brothers and Karl Rove, the Chamber helped raise and spend about one billion dollars to influence the 2012 elections. 

But elections are far less reliable an investment than focusing on the courts. 

“All told, the Chamber of Commerce has filed a whopping 18 amicus briefs this Term – just below its record number of 21 in October Term 2010,” according to Doug Kendall and Tom Donnelly of the Constitution Accountability Center. “Overall, the Court will likely decide 76 cases this Term, meaning that the Chamber will have participated in roughly 24 percent of the Court’s decided cases.” 

Conservative Justices side with the Chamber 82 percent of the time. 

The cases that matter to the Chamber aren’t generally the high-profile cases about civil rights, but rather quiet victories that swing justice in favor of corporations. They seek to defeat clean energy requirements and make it more difficult for consumers to file class action lawsuits — and they usually win. 

Warren says that fighting back against the corporate takeover of the highest court in the land will not be easy. 

“We are up against a conservative movement that for 30 years, since President Reagan, has dedicated itself to packing the courts with pro-business, anti-regulation conservative allies,” she said. “They are tough and they prepared.” 

The fight begins, she said, with speaking out about what’s going on in the courts.  The future of the Affordable Care Act, the Voting Rights Act and the country depend on it. 

http://www.nationalmemo.com/elizabeth-warren-warns-that-the-supreme-court-is-becoming-a-subsidiary-of-the-chamber-of-commerce/ 

So let's speak out. When there is threat of impeachment, even arrogant and corrupt justices historically clean up their shit, so to speak. So, make lots and lots of citizen noise; enough to wake up your senators. 

The current Roberts Court regularly hands down anti-democratic decisions based on 5-4 partisan divides, undermining any credibility that the Court speaks for beliefs with any partisan difference from other political branches. 

Pushing for Termed Appointments v. Current Life Terms 

Since 1970, Supreme Court justices have been staying on the Court for longer than ever before, which means that they are not accountable to current popular understandings of constitutional meaning. Vacancies on the Court are opening up much less frequently than in the past, which means that the democratic instillation of public values on the Court is occurring more irregularly. All of this combines to undermine the Court’s ability to reflect the country’s political values and thereby damages its democratic legitimacy. 

Furthermore, when vacancies do occur they tend to be packed together, such that a number of years will pass without any openings and, suddenly, two, three, or even four seats may open up within the space of a few years, followed by another long period without any vacancies. When this happens, the party in power at that particular time will be able to make a disproportionate impact on the political values of the Supreme Court. The result is invariably that the Court will no longer accurately reflect the country’s political values. 

Without more regular and frequent appointments, the Court becomes too far removed from democratic control and popular understandings of constitutional meaning. Indeed, the problem of democratic unaccountability is the primary reason cited by scholars for reconsidering life tenure. 

Calling the judiciary “America’s home-grown aristocracy” because of the privileged position of judges, there is a realistic notion of a life-tenured elite that decides the most basic constitutional rights and freedoms of the people which is fundamentally inconsistent with the needs of a democratic republic. Due to the lack of strong checks on their actions, the life-tenured judges act contrary to “the obvious republican grain of the rest of the Constitution” and that they are improperly liberated “from their role as agents of the people.” Obviously, the life-tenure provision makes Justices imperious and unaccountable to democracy, attaining an intolerable level of autocracy that is essentially out of touch with the typical citizen’s concerns” as their rulings impact important fundamental rights. 

Life tenure is obviously a “dubious policy” that must be abolished. The system of life tenure thus poses a danger to our democratic form of government. Without regular and frequent vacancies, the public and political branches are deprived of their one constitutionally-provided method of ensuring that the Supreme Court accurately reflects the popular understanding of what the Constitution requires. 

See: Term Limits for the Supreme Court: Life Tenure Reconsidered 

Steven G. Calabresi 
Northwestern University - School of Law 

James Lindgren 
Northwestern University - School of Law 

Harvard Journal of Law and Public Policy, Vol. 29, No. 3 
Northwestern Public Law Research Paper No. 07-24 

Abstract: 
In June 2005, at the end of its October 2004 Term, the U.S. Supreme Court's nine members had served together for almost eleven years, longer than any other group of nine Justices in the nation's history. Although the average tenure of a Supreme Court Justice from 1789 through 1970 was 14.9 years, for those Justices who have retired since 1970, the average tenure has jumped to 26.1 years. Because of the long tenure of recent members of the Court, there were no vacancies on the high Court from 1994 to the middle of 2005. We believe the American constitutional rule granting life tenure to Supreme Court Justices is fundamentally flawed, resulting now in Justices remaining on the Court for longer periods and to a later age than ever before in American history. 

This trend has led to significantly less frequent vacancies on the Court, which reduces the efficacy of the democratic check that the appointment process provides on the Court's membership. The increase in the longevity of Justices' tenure means that life tenure now guarantees a much longer tenure on the Court than was the case in 1789 or over most of our constitutional history. 

Moreover, the combination of less frequent vacancies and longer tenures of office means that when vacancies do arise, there is so much at stake that confirmation battles have become much more intense. Finally, as was detailed in a recent article by Professor David Garrow, the advanced age of some Supreme Court Justices has at times led to a problem of "mental decrepitude" on the Court, whereby some Justices have become physically or mentally unable to fulfill their duties during the final stages of their careers. 

In this Article, we call for a change to the life tenure rule for Supreme Court Justices. To resolve the problems of life tenure, we propose that lawmakers pass a constitutional amendment pursuant to Article V of the Constitution instituting a system of staggered, eighteen-year (or less) term limits for Supreme Court Justices. The Court's membership would be constitutionally fixed at nine Justices, whose terms would be staggered such that a vacancy would occur on the Court every two years at the end of the term in every odd-numbered calendar year. Every one-term President would thus get to appoint two Justices and every two-term President would get to appoint four. Our proposal would not apply to any of the nine sitting Justices or to any nominee of the President in office when the constitutional amendment is ratified. Moving to a system of eighteen-year terms for Supreme Court Justices would restore the norms in this country that prevailed on the Court between 1789 and 1970, when vacancies occurred about once every two years, and Justices served an average of 14.9 years on the Court. We recommend that the country recommit itself to the tenure practices that held for Supreme Court Justices for most of our history. 

Number of Pages in downloadable PDF File: 110 

http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=701121﻿

Meer lezen (180 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-xXWj6kQd50I/UcVd-viZ4_I/AAAAAAABcwU/DLhYZ7ah3Bs/w426-h678/I%2BFUCKING%2BHATE%2BTHIS%2BGODDAMN%2BMOTHER%2BFUCKING%2BCOUNTRY%2BGODDAMN%2BYOU%2BMOTHER%2BFUCKER%2BOBAMA%2BYOU%2BSHOULD%2BBE%2BDEAD%2BFUCKER.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/109276020821138262473/albums/6003278143693894193/6003278149397859698</link><title>TO: Robert Miller 
Governor of the State of Nevada 

TO: Bruce Babbitt 
Secretary of the Interior 

TO: Michael Espy 
Secretary of Agriculture 

TO: Jim Baca, Director 
Bureau of Land Management 

TO: David Unger, Acting Chief 
U.S. Forest Service 

SUBJECT: PUBLIC LAND AND OTHER MATTERS RELATED THERETO 
Gentlemen: 

INTRODUCTION 
My name is Dick Carver, I am a Nye County Commissioner, member of the Nevada State Land Use Planning Advisory Council, a member of the Consumer Advisory Panel to Sierra Pacific Power Company, past member of the Nevada State Conservation Commission, past member of the United States Department of Interior Bureau of Land Management Battle Mountain District Advisory Council, a conservationist, and a second generation rancher here in Smoky Valley, Nye County, Nevada. There are two more generations living on the Carver Ranch today, my son and my grandchildren. My ranch does not have any dependency on public lands for grazing, nor do I have any mining claims on public land today. 

The Carver family has a long history involving the use of the public lands. The Carver family was in the cattle business when they came from Missouri to California in 1850. They drove 800 head of cattle from the Salt Lake area to Hangtown (Placerville), California, to supply beef for the miners of the California Gold Rush. The Carver family was the first family of non-hispanic, non-native American settlers to graze cattle on the public lands in what is now Yosemite National Park, including Yosemite Valley and Tuolumne Meadow. In 1869, because of drought, the Carvers moved their cattle south along the west slope of the Sierra Nevada mountains to the Kern River area, where they continue to operate today on public lands. 

Because of my "deep roots" in the public lands issue, and as a Nye County Commissioner, taking the oath of office to uphold the Constitution and laws of the United States and the Constitution and laws of the State of Nevada, I am addressing the above- mentioned topic. 

These views are my own and as a Nye County Commissioner, but may or may not be the views of the Board of Nye County Commissioners. I am addressing the most critical issue before us today; 

WHO OWNS THE PUBLIC LANDS IN NEVADA? 
POINTS OF INTEREST 
1\. The United States Federal Government, Department of the Interior, and the Department of Agriculture are now regulating and managing certain public lands within the borders of the State of Nevada. 

2\. The United States Federal Government, Department of the Interior, Bureau of Land Management (BLM) is in the process of developing a new Tonopah Resource Management Plan (RMP). "The purpose of the Tonopah RMP is to provide the BLM direction to manage its natural resources in the Tonopah Resource Area." (Draft Tonopah Resource Management Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, p 1-1). 

3\. The United States Federal Government, Department of the Interior, and the Department of Agriculture have presented "a proposal to improve management of rangeland ecosystems and the administration of livestock grazing on public lands." "As the nation's principal conservation agency, the Department of Interior has responsibility for most of our nationally-owned public lands and natural resources." (Rangeland Reform '94). 

4\. After a thorough review of the United States Constitution, and the intent and concerns of the framers of the United States Constitution, it does not contain any authorization for the Federal Government of the United States to own, hold, or exert its dominion over any public lands except for whatever land it needs for its own governmental purpose as specified. Furthermore, the United States Government is authorized to acquire such needed land in any of the several states, by purchase, providing it shall be with the consent of the legislature of the state involved, and for those purposes specified. Article 1, Section 8, Clause 17, of the United States Constitution, hereafter referred to as 1.8.17). 

5\. The State of Nevada legislature has granted certain cessions to the United States Federal Government pursuant to 1.8.17 in Nye County as follows: The land for the Post Office and Federal building in Tonopah (NRS 328.270 and NRS 328.280), the Federal acquisition of land required by the Department of Defense or Atomic Energy Commission. (Appendix B PART A - State Constitutional Provisions and Statutes of General Effect Relating to the Acquisition of Legislative Jurisdiction by the United States, for Nevada, found in Report of the Interdepartmental Committee for the Study of Jurisdiction over Federal Areas within the States, Part I, The Facts and Committee Recommendations Submitted to the Attorney General and Transmitted to the President, April 1956, pages 175-178). 

6\. The Nevada Revised Statutes clearly limit federal jurisdiction over the land in Nevada. 

NRS 328.075 (2) STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
Federal jurisdiction over land to which this state has not ceded its jurisdiction is limited to carrying out governmental purposes authorized by the Constitution of the United States, and federal jurisdiction over lands held for other purposes is limited to that exercisable by an ordinary proprietor under the laws of this state. (my emphasis added). 

7\. The conclusion submitted to the Attorney General of the United States, the Honorable Herbert Brownell, Jr. and transmitted to President Eisenhower in 1956 by The Interdepartmental Committee for the Study of Jurisdiction over Federal Areas within the States is as follows: 

1\. "In the usual case there is an increasing preponderance of disadvantages over advantages as there increases the degree of legislative jurisdiction vested in the United States." 

2\. "With respect to the large bulk of federally owned or operated real property in the several states and outside of the District of Columbia, it is desirable that the federal government not receive, or retain, any measure whatever of legislative jurisdiction, but that it hold the installations and areas in a proprietorial interest status only, with the legislative jurisdiction remaining in the several states." (Id 70, Part I). 

8\. The intent of the framers of the Constitution of the United States was to guarantee to each of the states sovereignty over all matters within its boundaries except for those powers specifically granted to the United States as agent of the state. (NRS 321.596(4)). (my emphasis added). 

9\. The certain public lands mentioned in my first point of this letter are in fact public lands that belong to and are under the jurisdiction and control of the State of Nevada. 

NRS 321.5973 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
Public lands and minerals are property of the State; rights and privileges under Federal laws to be preserved; administration of land to conform with Treaties and Compacts. 

1\. Subject to existing rights, all public lands in Nevada and all minerals not previously appropriated are the property of the State of Nevada and subject to its jurisdiction and control. 

2\. Until equivalent measures are enacted by the State of Nevada, the rights and privileges of the people of the State of Nevada under the National Forest Reserve Transfer Act (16 U.S.C. 471 et seq. ), the General Mining Laws (30 U.S.C. 21 et seq. ), the Homestead Act (43 U.S.C. 161 et seq. ), the Taylor Grazing Act (43 U.S.C. 315 et seq. ), the Carey Act (43 U.S.C. 641 et seq.), and the Public Rangelands Improvement Act (43 U.S.C. 1901 et seq. ), and all rights of way and easements for public utilities must be preserved under administration by the state. 

3\. Public lands in Nevada which have been administered by the United States under international treaties or interstate compacts must continue to be administered by the state in conformance with those treaties or compacts. (Added to NRS by 1979, 1976). 

10\. On the public lands owned by Nevada, there is a split estate or other private property rights (i.e., water rights, minerals, grazing rights, timber rights, access rights, etc.). These rights must be recognized and are by state law. 

NRS 321.5973(1) STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"Subject to existing rights, all public lands in Nevada and all minerals not previously appropriated are the property of the State of Nevada and subject to its jurisdiction and control." 

11\. The following discusses the administration of the public lands within the State of Nevada. 

NRS 321.5977 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
Objectives in administering public lands. The public lands of Nevada must be administered in such a manner as to conserve and preserve natural resources, wildlife, artifacts, prehistoric sites and artifacts, paleontological resources and to permit the development of compatible public uses for recreation, agriculture, ranching, mining and timber production and the development, production and transmission of energy and other public utility services under principles of multiple use which provide the greatest benefit to the people of Nevada. (Added to NRS by 1979, 1365; A 1981, 323 ). 

12\. Nye County, as a governmental subdivision of the State of Nevada, is responsible for public lands management in cooperation with the State of Nevada on public lands within -the borders of Nye County. Nye County has a Policy Plan for Public Lands which was developed with the cooperation of the State of Nevada (NRS 321. 640-770) and approved by the Nye 

County Board of Commissioners on April 3, 1985. Nye County has been in the process of updating this plan. I have been holding any further action on this plan until I could research who owns the public lands. 

In conclusion, unless evidence can be produced to the contrary, Nye County in cooperation with the State of Nevada, is the public land management authority within the borders of Nye County on all public lands with the exception of those lands pursuant to 1.8.17 of the United States Constitution. 

ISSUES 
To understand clearly how this conclusion was drawn, one must look back over the past history of the public lands. These lands at one time were called "public domain." We have to go back even further into the past, back to the original thirteen colonies (1783), where there was no "public domain" as we later came to know it. When the thirteen colonies became free sovereign states, all the land within the border of each state was either privately owned or belonged to that state. There was no central government, and each unit was a complete independent sovereign state or small nation unto itself. In the states that were created out of the Northwest Territory, lands not privately owned were called waste or unappropriated lands. 

The book "Golden Fleece in Nevada" written by Judge Clel Georgetta states "In 1780, the Continental Congress adopted a resolution requesting the thirteen original states to surrender to the central government (the Confederation) all the lands they claimed in the territory west of their original boundaries to the Mississippi, so such lands could be sold to private interests for money to pay off the debt incurred by the Revolutionary War, and then the area would be divided into new states to be admitted into the Confederation on the same basis as the original states." (@ 151). 

Judge Georgetta continues "The thirteen independent sovereign states were first joined together in a Federal Union known as 'The Confederation' and in 1781 ratified 'The Articles of Confederation and Perpetual Union.' Those Articles contain the following words: 

Article II. Each state retains its sovereignty, freedom and independence, and every power, jurisdiction and right, which is not by this confederation expressly delegated to the United States in Congress assembled. Article IX. ...provides also that no state shall be deprived of territory for the benefit of the United States. (Id 150). 

There can be no doubt that the purpose of guaranteeing each state its complete sovereignty was to waylay all fear of joining the organization. It was those words of guaranty in the Articles that the various states joined the 'Confederation' in order to form a Central Government to perform certain functions for all the states as a group. It was to be a central government with very limited power." (Id 151). 

"The transfer of the dominion of the central government comprised of the land west of the Appalachian Mountains to the Mississippi became known as 'the Northwest Territory.' In 1787, the Continental Congress created, by the Articles of Confederation, passed a legislative act which came to be known as 'the ordinance of 1787' pertaining to the Northwest Territory. It contained these words": 

"Section 13 ...to provide also for the establishment of states, and permanent government therein, and for their admission to a share in the Federal Councils on an equal footing with the original states." 

"Article V ...and whenever any of said states shall have sixty thousand free inhabitants therein, such state shall be admitted, by its delegates, into the Congress of the United States, on equal footing with the original states, in all respects whatsoever..." (Id 152, 153). 

"In view of the fact that the Articles of Confederation did not contain any provision for the Central Government to own, hold, or control any public land, it was considered that the Central Government - 'The Confederation' - held these lands in trust for the states that would be later created in the area." (Id 152). "Since this was a legislative act adopted by the Continental Congress before the United States Constitution was adopted, there seemed some doubt that it continued to be in full legal effect. Therefore, after the new Constitution was in effect, the Congress of the United States, created by the Constitution, reenacted the ordinance of 1787 in its exact words." (Id 152). 

To insure the continuation of "the Articles of Confederation" and those of "the Ordinance of 1787", the Constitution of the United States which became effective on March 4, 1789 contains Article VI, Section 1 (hereafter referred to as 6.1). 

6.1 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"All debts contracted and engagements entered into before the adoption of this Constitution shall be as valid against the United States under this Constitution as under the Confederation." 

The United States operates under the numerous restrictions of the Constitution. No matter what Congress or the States might wish to do, they have to stay within the boundaries of the Constitution. This is why the framers are credited with the invention of a new kind of republic based on "Constitutional Supremacy." This makes the "supremacy clause" the cornerstone of the whole American political structure." (The Makings of America, ~. Cleon Skousen @657). 

The "Supremacy clause" Article VI, Section 2 (hereinafter referred to as 6.2) recognized both the supremacy of the United States Constitution and laws, and the supremacy of the State Constitution and laws. 

6.2 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"This Constitution, and the laws of the United States which shall be made in pursuance thereof; and all treaties made or which shall be made, under the authority of the United States, shall be the supreme law of the land; and the Judges in every state shall be bound thereby, any thing in the Constitution or laws of any State to the contrary notwithstanding." 

The purpose of the supremacy clause was to prevent the States &gt;from invading those areas which had been specifically delegated to the federal government. The framers were equally concerned with the possibility of the federal branches of government invading the supreme authority retained by the States or trying to acquire exclusive domination of areas in which there was joint jurisdiction. Either case involved the ugly word 'usurpation,' which all of the Framers so vigorously warned against. (Id 657- 658 The Makings of America, Skousen J. "The word supreme means no more than this - that the Constitution and laws made pursuant thereof, cannot be controlled or defeated by any other law...the State, as well as individuals, are bound by these laws; but the laws of Congress are restricted to a certain sphere, and when they depart from this sphere, they are no longer supreme or binding." (Id 659, Skousen citing Hamilton). 

The misconception of the Supremacy Clause is "that Congress has supreme power." Congress has only those powers granted by the Constitution. The evidence is clear that "the laws of the United States shall be made according to the Constitution of the United States and shall be supreme." Another reading is that "the Constitution expressly confines this supremacy to laws made pursuant to the Constitution of the United States." 

"This Constitution as the powers therein granted, is constantly to be the supreme law of the land... It is not the supreme law in the exercise of a power not granted. It can be supreme only in cases consistent with the powers specially granted, and not in usurpation." (Id 659, Skousen citing Davie). 

6.2 (lST PART) STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"This Constitution, and the laws of the United States which shall be made in pursuance thereof; and all treaties made or which shall be made, under the authority of the United States, shall be the supreme law of the land;..." 

Given the most casual reading of this part of the provision clearly demonstrates that it is talking about the supremacy of the laws of the United States made pursuant to the United States Constitution. 

6.2 (2ND PART) STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"...and the judges in every state shall be bound thereby, any thing in the constitution or laws of any state to the contrary notwithstanding." 

Again, "even the most casual reading of this part of the provision clearly demonstrates that it is talking about the state constitution, not the national Constitution." This supremacy is with the States. (The Makings of America, Skousen @ 662). 

The United States Congress was not granted the power to make state law pursuant to state constitution. Only the state can make laws pursuant to the state constitution. The United States Constitution," when adopted, will become a part of our state constitution; and the latter must yield to the former only in those cases where power is given by it. It is not to yield to it in any other case whatever..." (Id 659, Skousen citing Iredell). 

Thus, I conclude that there are two supremacies, that of the United States Constitution and that of the State Constitution. State supremacy is "auxiliary" (Id 663) to the supremacy of the laws made pursuant to the United States Constitution. Powers not delegated in the United States Constitution to Congress are reserved to the States or to the people through the Tenth Amendment to the United States Constitution. 

The Tenth Amendment, "powers retained by the states and the people," clearly strengthens my position that the powers granted to Congress through the Constitution of the United States by the people are limited, and all other powers are retained by the states or the people. 

This amendment was adopted to reassure the people that the national government would not swallow up the states. It confirms that the states or the people retain all powers not qiven to the national government, (The Worldbook Encyclopedia CI-CZ Volume 4, page 798). (my emphasis added) 

TENTH AMENDMENT STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"The powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the states, are reserved to the states respectively, or to the people." 

This brings us to the "powers granted to Congress." The enumerated powers delegated to Congress are clear. Congress shall have the exclusive power to make ALL federal laws, and that those laws would pertain only to the powers enumerated in the Constitution. (The Making of America, Skousen @ 252). From reading the intent of the framers of the Constitution, we begin to see how much they had suffered from war and what they had learned from their bitter experience with the weak constitutional structure of the Articles of Confederation. In 1787, "they sat in solemn contemplation of the powers they were not willing to admit they must relinquish to a central government. Many of those powers were volatile and dangerous - open to abuse." (Id 371). The framers therefore tried to incorporate into the Constitution the necessary checks and balances so that if these powers were abused, there would be peaceful remedies available to protect the people and preclude the necessity of going to war to regain their rights. "One of the most important reasons the States united was to promote their mutual defense. Spelling out the war powers was, therefore, a highly significant segment of the Constitution." (Id 439). The enumerated powers of Article 1, Section 8, Clauses 11-16 are considered the war powers. One of the war powers, Article 1, Section 8, Clause 14 (hereinafter referred to as 1.8.14) has the word land in it. 

1.8.14 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
1.8.14, "To make rules for the government and regulation of the land and naval forces." 

This power clearly does not have anything to do with public lands, but refers to land forces (i.e., United States Army) and naval forces. "This provision gave the Congress the right to dictate the specific rules and regulations under which the land and naval forces of the United States would operate. This is a very important provision. The Constitution made the President the commander in chief, but it gave the Congress the power to lay down the regulations and restrictions under which, he would be required to operate." (The Makings of Amer!ca, Skonsen @ 449). 

It is also interesting to note that following the "war power" provisions 1.8.11-16, the next enumerated power 1.8.17 gives Congress the AUTHORITY to set up a ten square mile restricted area for the seat of government, to be exclusively under the control of the Congress, (Id 456) for Congress should have a permanent, secure location. The individual States had failed to protect Congress in the past. 1.8.17 also gives the Congress the AUTHORITY to exercise complete jurisdiction over lands and facilities for defense of the nation which it purchased with consent of the state legislatures for the purposes specified. Here, in this provision, is still the concern of war, and is the only enumerated power that mentions land.. 

1.8.17 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"To exercise exclusive legislation in all cases whatsoever over such district (not exceeding ten square miles) as may, by cession of particular states and the acceptance of Congress, become the seat of government of the United States and to exercise like authority overall places purchased, by the consent of the legislature of the state in which the same shall be, for the erection of forts, magazines, arsenals, dockyards, and other needful buildings." 

1.8.17 is very clear that the people of the States empowered Congress to exercise complete jurisdiction and authority over all lands or facilities purchased within a state, providing it shall be with the consent of the legislature of that state. Such lands shall be used for the "erection of forts, magazines, arsenals, dock yards, and other needful buildings." Nowhere does Congress have enumerated power to exercise complete jurisdiction and authority over state owned public lands within the borders of Nevada. "It was assumed that as soon as a new teople of that state would acquire title to every acre of land other than a very small percentage granted to the federal government for the erection of forts, magazines, arsenals, dock yards, and other needful buildings." (The Making of America Skousen @ 458). (my emphasis added). 

"The consent requirement of 1.8.17 was intended by the framers of the Constitution to preserve the State's jurisdictional integrity against federal encroachment. The federal government cannot, by unilateral action on its part, acquire legislative jurisdiction over an area within the exterior boundaries of a state." (Report of the Interdepartmental Committee for the study of Jurisdiction over Federal Areas within the States. Part II @ 46, 47). 

Article 1, Section 8, Clause 18 (hereafter referred to as 1.8.18), which is called an "implied power" (The Making of America Skousen @ 778) gives the Congress the AUTHORITY to pass any other laws needed to implement the provisions of the Constitution. It does not delegate additional powers. "The Constitution had enumerated all the powers which the government should have, but did not say how they were to be exercised. This clause explained how they were to be exercised." (Id 459-460 Skousen citing Nicholas). 

1.8.18 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"To make all laws which shall be necessary and proper for carrying into execution, the foregoing powers, and all other powers vested by this Constitution in the government of the United States or any department or officer thereof." 

We have reviewed Article I, the Legislative Branch which includes the powers granted to Congress, Section 8. There is Article II that is the Executive Branch, and Article III, the Judicial Branch, the three branches divide the powers of the United States government. This division, called the separation of powers, is designed to prevent any branch of the government from becoming too powerful. 

Next there is Article IV, much of this article was taken word for word from the old Articles of Confederation. This Article is "the relation of the states to each other". (The World Book Encyclopedia CI-C2 @ 798M). This is another section of the United States Constitution that deals with land, lands that are to become states. This is the section that will be referred to as the statehood section, Article IV, Section 3 (hereinafter referred to as 4.3). At the time the United States Constitution was formed and adopted, remember that the Confederation held the Northwest Territory in trust for the establishment of states. Also remember that "the Articles of Confederation" and "the Ordinance of 1787" were valid under the new consiitution, 6.1. The question of how the new central government was going to form and admit new states in the future, beyond the original 13 states, had to be addressed. This is how and why Article IV, Section 3, Clause 1 (hereinafter referred to as 4.3.1) was inserted into the United States Constitution (my emphasis added). 

4.3.1 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
New states may be admitted by the Congress in the Union; but no new states shall be formed or erected within the jurisdiction of any other state; nor shall any state be formed by the junction of two or more states, or parts of states, without the consent of the legislatures of the states concerned, as well as of the Congress. 

Now that we see how the Constitution covers property in the future, what about the existing property that the government held from the original 13 states? How was Congress going to dispose of the lands pertaining to the Northwest Territory and any other property that the original 13 states had ceded to the Confederation, and recognized by the new Constitution in 6.1. 

This is how and why Article IV, Section 3, Clause 2 was inserted into the Constitution. 
4.3.2 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"The Congress shall have powers to dispose of and make all needful rules and regulations, respecting the territory belonging to the United States; and nothing in the Constitution shall be construed to prejudice any claim of the United States, or of any particular state." (my emphasis added). 

The Supreme Court has decided this "property clause" pertains only to a certain territory at the time the Constitution was adopted and was considered to only last until the territory was made into states, and the debt was paid. Thereafter, the only power Congress was to have was to be one of the enumerated powers of 1.8 of the United States Constitutions. The statehood article surely would not have given Congress unlimited power to make any laws necessary and proper over whatever Congress wanted to do. This would have defeated the limiting powers of 1.8 of the United States Constitution and would also make it impossible to determine the exact powers retained by the states in the Tenth amendment. 

Others consider this "property clause" as pertaining to a territory and property before it becomes a state, as when a state is admitted, all property is granted to the state on an equal footing with the original thirteen states. 

It is true that Article 4, Section 3, Clause 2 of the Constitution states the Federal Government shall have power to make rules and regulations respecting "the territory or other property belonging to the United States." What did those words refer to? "...other property belonging to the United States" no doubt referred to its "forts, magazines, arsenals, dock yards, and other needful buildings" specifically listed in Article 1, Section 8, Clause 17. What did the word "territory" refer to? According to various debates among early American Statesmen, it referred to the lands west of the Appalachian Mountains which the central government had accepted from the original states to be held in trust until new states could be created and admitted to the Union as full sovereign states on an equal basis with the original states, which owned and had full dominion over all lands within their borders. (Golden Fleece in Nevada, Clel Georgetta, Judge @153). 

The Framers of the Constitution could have enumerated other powers in 1.8 of the Constitution that could have included the authority for the federal government to own, manage and control all public lands. The enumerated powers delegated to Congress limits the control of land. The management and control of certain public lands were clearly retained by the states through the Tenth Amendment. 

There were many lengthy debates in Congress on issues dealing with public lands. Senator Hendricks made one while speaking of the ordinance of 1787: "this union is in theory formed of sovereign, equal people and independent states. In the older members of this Confederation, the federal government sets up no claim to the waste and unappropriated lands, has no land office, derives no revenue from the sale of land. The ordinance contemplated the public lands as belonging to new states, after their admission in the union... As a further inducement to the new states to join the Confederation the ordinance stipulated that they should be admitted into the union... on an equal footing with the original states in all respects whatever, and the Constitution in substance of the same policy, provides that all engagements entered into before the adoption of the Constitution shall be as valid against the United States, under the Constitution as under the Confederation so that the Articles of Confederation, the Acts of Cessions, the ordinance of 1787 and the Constitution itself, form a perfect and harmonious chain of policy - the grand object of which was the union and equality of the states. Then Mr. President, if at all correct in this view, it may well be asked by what means have the new states been. deprived of their equality of the right of soil... The public lands should be ceded to the states in which they lie because their present condition is not warranted by the letter of the Constitution of this government... Its powers are carefully enumerated and specified. I deny, sir, the limits of the states, except for the purpose designated by the Constitution such as forts, magazines, arsenals, dockyards and other needful buildings, and to enable Congress to hold lands even for these purposes, the consent of the legislature of the states is declared to be necessary by the expressed language of the Constitution..." (Id 154, 155). 
As one can see, waste or unappropriated lands, later public domain, and still later, public lands were always a concern and discussed, but their ownership and control were retained by the states through the 10th amendment to the Constitution. We definitely do not want to overlook treaties, because they are also "supreme law of the land." 

A PORTION OF 6.2 STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"...and all Treaties made, or which shall be made, under the Authority of the United States, shall be made the supreme Law of the Land..." 

Earlier, we mentioned the importance of "the ordinance of 1787." Let us now discuss a treaty between Mexico and the United States. It should be pointed out that there are several treaties of great importance to the public lands issue between 1787 and 1848 (i.e., Louisiana Purchase, etc.). 

In 1848, by the Treaty of Guadaloupe Hidalgo, Mexico ceded to the United States the vast southwest. "The states of California, Arizona, Nevada, Utah, and parts of New Mexico, Colorado, and Wyoming were carved out of this combination of purchase and treaty. This treaty contains an interesting section: ...shall be formed into free, sovereign, and independent states and incorporated into the Union of the United States as soon as possible, and the citizens thereof shall be accorded the enjoyment of all the rights, advantages, and immunities as citizens of the original states..." (Golden Fleece in Nevada, Judge Georgetta @ 165). This is very interesting because we are now talking about the very land that is to become the state of Nevada. 

What is an independent sovereign state as one of the original thirteen states? It is a state that retains its sovereignty, freedom and independence, and every power, jurisdiction and right, which is not expressly delegated to the United States Congress by the Constitution and shall not be deprived of territory for the benefit of the United States. (The articles of confederation, and 6.1 of the United States Constitution). 

It is also very interesting to note that "when the original states became free sovereign states, all the land within the border of each state was to be either privately owned, or belong to the state." (Golden Fleece in Nevada, Judge Georgetta @ 150). Nevada cannot be a free sovereign state, as the original thirteen states, unless all the lands within its borders are either privately owned or belong to the state except those pursuant to 1.8.17. This is why the Federal Government must purchase, with the consent of the state legislature, land for specified purposes. The land belongs to the state, this was the intent of the framers of the United States Constitution and is the limit placed upon the federal government today. 

It is important to look at how Nevada became a state. On March 21, 1864, Congress passed an act called "The Enabling Act." 

THE ENABLING ACT STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
A part of Section 1: "Enable the people of the Territory of Nevada to form a Constitution and State Government and for the admission of such State into the Union on an Equal Footing with the original States in all respects whatsoever." 

So, again, we have the same intent as the Treaty of Guadaloupe Hidalgo of 1848 - free sovereign state as the original thirteen states. 

SECTION 4, CLAUSE 3 OF "THE ENABLING ACT" STATES AS FOLLOWS: 
"That the people inhabiting said territory do agree to declare that they forever disclaim all right and title to the unappropriated public lands lying within said territory, and that the same shall be and remain at the sole and entire disposition of the United States..." 

Let's get a clear reading and understanding of this part of-"The Enabling Act." The United States Congress was the only one that could pass an act to allow the people of the Nevada Territory to form a Constitution and State Government and to admit this Territory into the Union as a state. (4.3.1 U.S. Constitution). The people of the Nevada Territory had no authority to pass this act. Research has shown that first, the people of the Territory of Nevada had to give up all their "interest" in the unappropriated lands of the Nevada territory to the Congress of the United States so Congress could pass said lands to the State of Nevada upon acceptance of Nevada into the Union. Then Nevada would become a free sovereign state as the original thirteen states relating to land. 

If the unappropriated public lands referenced in "The Enabling Act'' were not passed from Congress to the new state of Nevada and Congress held these lands in the name of the Federal Government, it would be a "violation of the United States Constitution as these lands are not pursuant to 1.8.17 of the U.S. Constitution." (Golden Fleece !n Nevada,- Judge Georgetta @ 168). Remember that the Constitution limits what the federal government can own; it does not grant unlimited ownership to the federal government. It would also be a violation of: 

a. The Congressional Act of 1834 which provided any land held by the federal government within a new state would be held in trust for the state until it could pass into private hands. 

b. The Treaty of Guadaloupe Hidalgo of 1848, as Nevada would be denied the right of a free sovereign as an original state in all respects whatsoever. 

And it would be a breach of trust, and void President Lincoln's proclamation where he said, "...do hereby declare and proclaim that the said State of Nevada is admitted into the Union on an equal footing with the original states." 

The Constitution of the United States provides the basis of government. It divides the powers and duties between the federal and state governments, limiting the power of the federal government, and the states retaining all other powers. 
AUTHORITIES 
Judicial review is the method used to answer basic questions as to what the Constitution means in case of dispute, and confirms the state and national governments with their constitutiona1 limits. (The Worldbook Encyclopedia, U-V, Volume 20, page 83). 

Review of some authorities from court cases relevant to the public lands issue. 

"When the state of Alabama was admitted to the Union, one of the requirements laid down by the federal government was that the state must relinquish claim to all public lands within its borders. The compact between the United States and the state of Alabama provided that the people of Alabama forever disclaimed all right or title to the waste or unappropriated lands lying within the state and that the same would remain at the sole disposal of the United States. That is almost the same wording we have in the Nevada 'Enabling Act."' (Golden Fleece in Nevada, Judge Georgetta @ 158). 

"Later there was a dispute over the legal effect of such a compact. One party contended the federal government was the out- and-out owner of the land and had complete jurisdiction and sovereignty over it. The other party contended the federal government had no power under the Constitution to hold land in Alabama after it became a state." (Id 158). 

"The dispute finally reached the Supreme Court of the United States in the case of: POLLARD V. HAGEN, 44 U.S., (3 How), 212 (1845) 11 Law Ed. 565. Fact: Pollard claimed the land in the City of Mobile under a patent issued by an act of Congress." (Id 158). "Hagen claimed the land by a chain of title through the state of Alabama going back to a 'Spanish Grant.' At the time Alabama was admitted to the Union as a state, this land was under the Mobile River, a navigable stream." (Id 158). 

"The United States Supreme Court held Alabama had the same jurisdiction over navigable rivers, and the soil under them as the original thirteen states had. The compact (Enabling Act) through which Alabama became a state contained the provision 'that the people of Alabama forever disclaimed all right or title to the waste or unappropriated lands lying within the state, and that the same should remain at the sole disposal of the United States. The United States Supreme Court held that provision was in violation of the United States Constitution and was therefore void.'" (Id 158). (my emphasis added) 

The misconception about the "Enabling Act" of Alabama and Nevada, is that the people of the State of Alabama disclaimed all riight and title to waste or unappropriated lands after statehood, where in Nevada the people of the Nevada territory (before statehood) disclaimed all right and title to unappropriated public lands in the Nevada Territory. There is a very big difference. Could it be that the Nevada disclaimer (Enabling Act) is being interpreted as being the people of the STATE of Nevada rather than the people of the territory of Nevada? There is no constitutional provision for the people of a territory to discard the sovereignty and equal footing of a future state. The people of the territory of Nevada were only giving up their interest at that time to the unappropriated public lands. 

NEVADA V. UNITED STATES 512 F. Supp. 166 (1981). 
The State of Nevada brought an action alleging that the Federal Land Policy and Management Act (FLPMA) of 1976 was unconstitutional. The question of ownership of the public lands was not asked. The court entered judgement for defendants that the FLMPA was constitutional. The Ninth Circuit affirmed the lower court decision and referenced that this case does not involve a claim to title of land. The Ninth Circuit upholding the lower court decision, "The federal government owns approximately 88 percent of the land within the borders of the state of Nevada, according to the uncontroverted allegation of the state in this case... Nevada agrees that this case does not involve the claim of title to land... Any further challenges to actual or anticipated federal action with respect to federally held land will arise in a different legal and historical context from that surrounding the 1964 moratorium which prompted this suit. " (699 F 2d 486- 488, Judge Schroeder, Ninth Circuit). 

"The purposes of the cessions of unappropriated lands to the federal government was for the land to be sold, and the proceeds applied to paying the public debt incurred in the Revolutionary War." "...[t]he United States never held any right to the vacant lands in any of the new states except temporarily to execute the trusts created by the original states in their deeds of cession of their western lands to the federal government. 'Both of these deeds of cession stipulated, that all the lands within the territory ceded, and not reserved or appropriated to other purposes, should be considered as a common fund for the benefit of all the United States, to be faithfully and bona fide deposed of for that purpose, and for no other use or purpose whatever.'" (Id 170, District Court citing POLLAND V. HAGEN. 

In 1787, Congress also specified that new states shall be admitted into the Union "...on an equal footing with the original states in all respects whatever." (Id 170, District Court citing POLLAND V. HAGEN). 

"Whenever the United States shall have fully executed these trusts, the municipal sovereignty of the new states will be complete throughout their respective borders, and they, and the original states, will be upon an equal foot, in all respects whatever." (Id 170, District Court citing POLLAND V. HAGEN). 

The Nevada court addressing the property clause declares that "the limitations on what the federal government can do with its property, by reason of the origin of the property clause, apply only to lands within the original thirteen states..." (Id 171, citing UNITED STATES V. GRATIOT 39 U.S. (14 Pet) 526 10 L. Ed. 573) (1840). 

Said court discussed the reasons for insertion of the property clause in the Constitution. "The federal government was to be one of carefully limited powers, and it had no grant of authority to receive and administer the unappropriated lands and other properties, such as military equipment and supplies, which the thirteen original sovereign states wished to cede to it for the common good. " (Id 170, District Court citing POLLAND V. HAGEN). The raising of money to pay the public debt by selling the lands was the main object of the cessions. The property clause provided the United States government with the power to take possession of the properties and protect them, so that they could be disposed of in an orderly fashion. It applies only to the property which the states held in common at that time, and has no reference whatever to any territory or other property which the new sovereignty might afterwards itself acquire." DRED SCOTT V. STANFORD, 60 U.S. (19 How) 393, 15, L. Ed. 691 (1856). "It does not speak of any territory, nor of territories, but uses language which, according to its legitimate meaning points to a particular thing. The power is given in relation only to the territory of the United States. That is, a territory then in existence, and known or claimed as the territory of the United States. It begins its enumeration of powers by that of deposing, in other words, meaning sale of the lands, or raising money from them, which as we already said, was the main object of the cessions, and which accordingly the first thing provided for in the article." DRED SCOTT V. STANFORD, 60 U.S. (19 How) 393, 436 (1856). 

In KANSAS V. COLORADO, 206 U.S. 46, "The first article, treating legislative powers, does not make a general grant of legislative power. It reads Article 1, Section 1, all legislative powers herein granted shall be vested in a Congress, etc." Then, in Section 8 it mentions and defines the legislative powers that are granted. By reason of the fact that there is not a general grant of legislative power, it has become an accepted constitutional rule that this is a government of enumerated powers. Further, Kansas citing FAIRBANK V. UNITED STATES, 191 U.S. 283, 288: "We are not confronted here with a question of the extent of the powers of Congress, but one of the limitations imposed by the Constitution on its action, and it seems to us clear that the same rule and spirit of construction must also be recognized. If powers granted are to be taken as broadly granted and as carrying with them authority to pass those acts which may be reasonably necessary to carry them to full execution; in other words, if the Constitution in its grant of powers is to be construed that Congress shall be able to carry into full effect the powers granted, it is equally imperative that, where prohibition or limitation is placed upon the powers of Congress, prohibition or limitation should be enforced in its spirit and to its entirety. It would be a strange fault of construction that language granting powers is to be liberally construed, and that language of restriction is to be narrowly and technically construed." (Id 91). 

"But it is useless to pursue the inquiry further in this direction. It is enough for the purpose of this case that each state has full jurisdiction over the lands within its borders, including the beds of streams and other waters." (Id 93). 

ST. LOUIS-SAN FRANCISCO RY. V. SATTERFIELD 27F 2d 586 (1928), "The legislature of a state has unlimited power to transfer jurisdiction to the United States except as it may be restricted by state or federal Constitutions.'~ 

KLEPPE V. NEW MEXICO 426 U.S. 529, 49 L. Ed. 2d 34 (1976), is another constitutional issue like the Nevada case. The question asked was if the Wild and Free-Roaming Horse and Burros Act was constitutional. Here again this case did not involve a claim of title to the land. The Supreme Circuit Court found the Wild Horse Act constitutional. 

This case was a reversal of the District Court ruling. Supreme Court Justice Marshall, "...appellees mistakenly read this language to limit Congress' power to regulate activity on the public lands...and while the furthest reaches of the power; granted by the Property Clause have not yet been definitively resolved, we have repeatedly observed that the power over the public lands thus entrusted to Congress is without limitation... we find that, as applied to this case, the act is a constitutional exercise of congressional power under the Property Clause...we need not, and do not decide whether the Property Clause would sustain the act in all of its conceivable applications." (Id 538, 539, 546). 

A most recent case NEW YORK V. UNITED STATES 120 L. Ed 2d 120 (1992), "...the Constitution question is as old as the Constitution: it consists of discerning the proper division of authority between the federal government and the states. We conclude that while Congress has substantial power under the Constitution to encourage the states to provide for the disposal of the radioactive waste generated within their borders, the Constitution does not confer upon Congress the ability simply to compel the states to do so..." (Id 133). 

"...If a power is delegated to Congress in the Constitution, the Tenth Amendment expressly disclaims any reservation of the power to the states; if a power is an attribute of state sovereignty reserved by the Tenth Amendment, it is necessarily a power the Constitution has not conferred on Congress." See UNITED STATES V. OREGON 366 U.S. 643, 649, 6 L E. 552, 66 S ct 438 (1946); OKLAHOMA EX REL. PHILLPS V. GUY F. ATKINSON CO., 313 U.S. 508, 534, 85 L. Ed. 1487, 61 S ct 1050 (1941) (Id 137). 

"It is in this sense that the Tenth Amendment 'states but a truism that all is retained which has not-been surrendered.' UNITED STATES V. DARBY, 312 U.S. 100, 124, 85 1 Ed. 609, 61 S ct 451, 132 ARL 1430 (1941). As Justice Story put it, 'This amendment is a mere affirmation of what, upon any just reasoning, is a necessary rule of interpreting the Constitution. Being an instrument of limited and enumerated powers, it follows irresistible, that what is not conferred, is withheld, and belongs to the state authorities..."' (Id 137). 

"Congress exercises its conferred power subject to the limitations contained in the Constitution." (Id 137). (my emphasis added). 

The United States Constitution did not allow for the Congress to regulate private property in the states; the regulation of private property in any state falls under the sovereignty and jurisdiction of the state's policy power. In NEW YORK V. UNITED STATES, the court further states, "As an initial matter, Congress may not simply commandeer the legislative process of the states by directly compelling them to enact and enforce a federal regulatory program." HODEL V. VIRGINIA SURFACING MINING AND RECLAMATION ASSOCIATION INC., 452 U.S. 254, 288, 69 L Ed 2d 1, 101 S ct 2352 (1981). In HODEL, the court upheld the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 precisely because it did not 'commandeer' the states into regulation mining." The court found that "the states are not compelled to enforce the steep-slope standard, to expend any state funds, or to participate in the federal regulatory program in any manner whatsoever." (Id 141). 

IF THE STATE RATIFIED OR GIVES CONSENT TO ANY AUTHORITY WHICH IS NOT SPECIFICALLY GRANTED BY THE UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION, IT IS NULL AND VOID. 
The NEW YORK court further states: "Where Congress exceeds its authority relative to the states; therefore, the departure from the Constitutional plan cannot be ratified by the "consent" of state officials." An analogy to the separation of powers among the branches of the federal government clarifies this point. The Constitution's division of power among the three branches is violated where one branch invades the territory of another, whether or not the encroached-upon branch approves the encroachment. In BUCKLEY V. VALEO, 424 U.S. 1, 118-137, 35 L. Ed. 2d 659, 96 S ct 612 (1976), for instance, the court held that the Congress had infringed the President's appointment power, despite the fact that the President himself had manifested his consent to the statute that caused the infringement by signing it into law. See NATIONAL LEAGUE OF CITIES V. USERY, 426 U.S., AT 842, N 12, 49 L. Ed. 2d 245, 96 S ct 2465...Congress cannot be expanded by the 'consent' of the governmental unit whose domain is thereby narrowed, whether that unit is the executive branch or the state's." (Id 154). 

"State officials cannot consent to the enlargement of the powers of Congress beyond those enumerated in the Constitution." (Id 154). (my emphasis added). 

SUMMARY 
When the United States Constitution was adopted, it was a new basic law of the land. Some people today consider it as the "Supreme Land Management Plan" (Cliff Gardner, Elko County Rancher/Historian, October 1, 1993). 

The evidence is clear that the United States Constitution does not delegate any powers to Congress that allows Congress to grant to any federal agency legal claim to all public lands within Nevada's borders, except those pursuant to 1.8.17. Nor does Congress have any delegated power to grant power to the federal agencies to regulate private property on the public lands within Nevada's borders. 

The Supreme Court of the United States holds that the federal government has no right or power under the constitution to own, hold control of, or exercise any complete municipal sovereignty over any land of any kind except - the District of Columbia; land it had purchased within a state, with the consent of the state legislature, for its own governmental uses, (forts, arsenals, dockyards and other needful buildings) and over acquired territory before it is divided into states. That is exactly what the Constitution says and that is what the Supreme Court said it means. 

Some consider the case of NEW YORK V. UNITED STATES (1992) as the strongest states rights case ever by the United States Supreme Court (Don Bowman, Churchill County Businessman, October 27, 1993). The Supreme Court of the United States held that Congress exercises its conferred powers subject to the limitations contained in the Constitution, if the state ratifies or gives consent to any authority which is not specifically granted by the United States Constitution, it is null and void, state officials can not consent to the enlargement of the powers of Congress beyond those enumerated in the Constitution. 

The United States Constitution is clear, NEVADA LAW IS CLEAR. Nevada owns all the public lands in Nevada and all the minerals subject to existing rights, and has complete jurisdiction and control of these lands. NRS 321.5973(1) 

The Tonopah Resource Management Plan and Environmental Impact Statement and Rangeland Reform '94 apply only to federal property in Nye County pursuant to 1.8.17 of the United States Constitution. 

Again, if anyone can produce any evidence to the contrary, please bring your evidence forward. 

As I was born and raised in Smoky Valley, Nevada and as a Nye County Commissioner, I strongly believe in the principals o,f multiple use which will provide the greatest benefit to the people of Nye County, the State of Nevada, and the United States. As a county commissioner, I believe in management of our natural resources that is closest to the people and to the resources themselves. This being with county government, as our founders of this great country believed in when they settled America. 

With the strong leadership in Nye County, we can address through our Nye County Land Use Plan, all issues presently being managed by the federal agencies. With the appointment of a Nye County Public Lands Commission, we can involve the actual public land users as advisors to the Nye County Board of Commissioners. 

Article 15, Section 2 of the Constitution of the State of Nevada required that I take the oath to support, protect and defend the Constitution and Government of the United States and the Constitution and Government of the State of Nevada. The United States Constitution limits the land that the federal government can own and manage. The Nevada state law clearly establishes ownership of the public lands. The supremacy clause of the United States Constitution makes Nevada law supreme in the absence of power granted to Congress by the United States Constitution. My constituents are demanding that I fulfill my oath of office by making sure it is recognized that within the borders of the state 

NEVADA OWNS ALL PUBLIC LANDS. 
Richard L. Carver, Vice Chairman 
Nye County Board of Commissioners 
HCR 60, Box 5400 
Round Mountain, NV 89045-9801 
(702)377-2175 

cc: 
The Honorable Harry Reid, U.S. Senator 
The Honorable Richard Bryan, U.S. Senator 
The Honorable Barbara Vucanovich, U.S. Representative 
The Honorable James Bilbray, U.S. Representative 
The Honorable Frankie Sue Del Papa, Nevada Attorney General 
All Nevada Legislators 
Mr. Dean Rhoads, Chrmn, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. John Marvel, Vice-Chrmn, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. Roy Neighbors, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. Mike McGinnis, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. Mark James, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. Jack Regan, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Ms. Karen Hayes, NV Committee on Public Lands 
Mr. John Crossley, Director, Legislative Council Bureau 
Mr. Pete Morrow, NV Department of Natural Resources 
Mr. Tom Ballow, Nevada Department of Agriculture 
Mr. Russ Fields, Nevada Department of Minerals 
Mr. Willie Molini, Nevada Department of Wildlife 
Ms. Pamela Wilcox, Nevada Division of State Lands 
Mr. James Currivan, BLM, Battle Mountain District Manager 
Mr. Billy R. Templeton, BLI1, Nevada State Director 
Mr. James Elliott, BLM, Carson City District Manager 
Mr. Kenneth Walker, BLM, Ely District Manager 
Mr. Rodney Harris, BLM, Elko District Manager 
Mr. Ben Collins, BLM, Las Vegas District Manager 
Mr. Theodore Angle, BLM, Tonopah Resource Area Manager 
Mr. Wayne King, BLM, Shoshone Resource Area Manager 
Mr. James Phillips, BLM, Lahontan Resource Area Manager 
Mr. John Mattheissen, BLM, Walker Resource Area Manager 
Mr. Runore Wycoff, BLM, Stateline Resource Area Manager 
Mr. Gerald Smith, BLM, Schell Resource Area Manager 
Mr. Gene Drais, BLM, Egan Resource Area Manager 
Mr. R.M. "Jim" Nelson, Supervisor, Toiyabe National Forest 
Mr. John Inman, Supervisor, Humboldt National Forest 
Mr. David Grider, USFS, Tonopah District Ranger 
Mr. Dayle Flanigan, USFS, Austin District Ranger 
Mr. Guy Pence, USFS, Carson District Manager 
Mr. Jim Tallerico, USFS, Las Vegas District Ranger 
Mr. Jerry L. Green, USFS, Ely District Ranger 
Mr. John S. Turner, Director, U.S. Fish &amp; Wildlife Service 
Mr. David Harlow, Nevada, US Fish &amp; Wildlife Service 
All Nevada County Commissioners 
All Nevada County District Attorneys 
Nevada Farm Bureau 
Nevada Cattlemans Association 
Nevada Sheep Growers Association 
Nevada Mining Association 
Nevada Miners &amp; Prospectors Association 
Nevada Association of Cities 
Nevada League of Cities 
C.A.R.E.E.﻿

Meer lezen (1100 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-VIksTgJL2aU/U0_tq465TXI/AAAAAAAArfc/hZOxFt-30gw/w426-h319/1045088_4099048410529_2088166338032998639_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/109667384864782087641/albums/5665998155954793825/5665998156638478546</link><title>Congress v the President 
♻: https://plus.google.com/109667384864782087641/posts/BhqoYhc49qh 

Even if you get your President in, you lose. Congress trumps the President, always. Congressional authority to impeach corrupt officials is owned by corporations and banks. 

Take Ralph Nader for an example. He will go down in history as costing the Democrats the President to George Bush. I personally believe in Nader's right to have run. I also think it's important to factor in that he met with Kerry and others and he would say if those running were running on issue he agreed with, then he wouldn't have run. 

What Nader might say is that there was a difference between him and the others which required him to run instead of lending his support. I might agree with him on that. There is an argument that Clinton failed to veto some of the deregulations that preceded the market collapse. So the assumption is that had George Bush not been in power, he wouldn't have veto'd or that a Democratic President would have veto'd more bills. 

The argument over the President in a &gt; two party election is a least best case senario. You assume neither will win and the distinction between the two is the reason for the win. This is a function of the two party system where one of the two parties sacrifices personal issues for power and the other does not. 

But his whole argument is mute because the President does not have real power. 

The President does not have the power to change the things that someone like Nadar or Ron Paul would want to change. That lies with Congress. So even if Nadar got in (or Ron Paul), they would not change the things they want to change. Those changes depend on Congress. The only thing a President can do is veto. 

Given a Presidential veto, Congress can override it. This is rarely done and that tells you something. Congress has all the power. Also, the Presidential veto is influenced by his own re-election or other contributions and business dealings. Even Obama has taken a lot of money from Wall Street, contrary to some of his previous campaign promises about transparency and accountability. 

The focus on the President is done purposely by the media as funded by corporations through advertising. The office is also romanticized since the days of JFK. It's why the First Lady is also a huge deal. In the UK, the Prime Minister's wife is not such a big deal because they already have the Queen. 

Party polarization is purposely designed into the system by corporations to save money. Glenn Beck, FOX News, Bill O'Reilly, The Daily Kos, etc. All the issues that are important to people are forced to fall into two buckets leaving much of the decision making up to moderates and corporations. A recent GOP measure passed by the house need 209 votes and it got 237 with 34 Democrats voting for it. This is lobbyist influence. The more polarized the two parties are the cheaper it costs to lobby those Representatives. 

Most of the real concern lies in Congress and the House representatives via districting/gerrymandering, etc. A lot of money is also spent needlessly on campaigns for 435 Representatives in the house. 

As of 1911, Congress has the authority to change that number. The Reapportionment Act of 1929 capped the size of the House at 435. The original founders intended that the House of Representatives keep the elder statesmen in the Senate in check using the bicameral Congress structure, with the house being a 1:30000 representation. This was latter capped. 

When the Constitution was created, and when the House was capped at 435 in 1929, THERE WAS NO INTERNET. The house was originally intended to be the House of the People, The People's House. to keep Congress, the Senate, Judges, and the President in check. 

We have lost that check and balance. 

Some argue that public financing or campaign finance reform would solve this issue but it would only kick the ball down the field. First it would take funds from the Federal government to fund 435 + 100 elections. You could save the cost of 435 elections and pay for a direct vote. Keep the publicly financed 100 Senatorial elections and use the direct vote in the House to keep them in check. 

The Constitution specifically granted the House of Representatives the authority to impeach corrupt officials. If those same corrupt officials are the ones that have this power, they will never use it. And that is what you have seen. Congress only uses impeachment in extreme circumstances. This means it's okay to be corrupt, just as long as you are not extremely corrupt. The House of Representatives has actually initiated impeachment proceedings only 62 times since 1789. Two cases did not come to trial because the individuals had left office. 

Actual impeachments of 19 federal officers have taken place. Of these, 15 were federal judges: Thirteen district court, one court of appeals (who also sat on the Commerce Court), and one Supreme Court Associate Justice. Of the other four, two were Presidents, one was a Cabinet secretary, and one was a U.S. Senator. 

Only one Senator has ever been corrupt in the history of Congress? Really? That is quite impressive. And that one single Senator to ever been impeached was William Blount http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Blount who was expelled from the Senate on July 7, 1797 and was to be impeached in 1978 but the impeachment was dropped on the grounds that no further action could be taken beyond his expulsion. He was expelled because he wanted to incite some Florida Indians to aid the British in conquering territory so that his land holdings would have more value._ 

So Congress simply impeaches Judges because the judicial branch is a check on Congress and Congress is a check on the judical and executive. They do not impeach their own, except for one Senator. 

And when the corporations have the control of the House, they can use the impeachment for political reasons as in the case of Clinton, not to mention to waste money. 

While the Republicans still maintained majority control of the United States House of Representatives after the 1998 midterm elections, they would also lose a large number of seats to the Democrats in an election. 

Shortly after the mid-term elections, Speaker of the United States House of Representatives Newt Gingrich, who was one of the people leading the impeachment proceedings against Clinton, announced he would resign from Congress as soon as he was able to find somebody to fill his vacant seat; Gingrich fulfilled this pledge and officially resigned from Congress on January 25, 1999. 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Impeachment_of_Bill_Clinton 

It was this wide lack of support for Clinton's impeachment that lead to Newt's downfall. Ironically, he is now running for President. 

This is what is wrong with the government. Everything else is bullshit. Tax reform... bullshit. Spending... bullshit (except for military spending). Deregulation... bullshit. Even if you have regulation, they will just get out of it or they will suck horribly at it like the SEC. Nobody has been held to account or impeached because they own Congress. 

A direct vote in the House of Representatives is an order of magnitude more important than who becomes President. 
http://wh.gov/285﻿

Meer lezen (143 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-j3O1-ZBhfW4/TqGrTcB0YNI/AAAAAAAAJlY/UXnrOfu_W9U/w426-h246/0411_congress-stock-photo.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/111607197519973101083/albums/5927266407074899201/5927266407565871186</link><title>Congress passed the Judiciary Act on this day in 1789, which established the U.S. federal judiciary. The Act set the number of Supreme Court justices at six: one Chief Justice and five Associate Justices, and created 13 judicial districts within the 11 states that had then ratified the Constitution. It established a circuit court and district court in each judicial district, and created the Office of Attorney General, whose primary responsibility was to represent the United States before the Supreme court. The Act also created a United States Attorney and a United States Marshal for each judicial district. Learn more by visiting Federal Hall National Monument, or click here: http://www.cr.nps.gov/nr/travel/presidents/federal_hall.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-VW07ctUgx28/UkHhZMgRyFI/AAAAAAAADo4/XYmJFAkOLnA/w426-h322/3eA8r.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/102961581170694777301/albums/5808586860682834145/5808586865862444962</link><title>Does this mean the impact of slavery is still felt today?  Well here in Maryland we've come pretty far. We are rarely even considered part of the south anymore 
\---- 
My comments are getting lost so I'll pull them up here. 

(Also did anyone else love the movie Cloud Atlas?) 

Here's an interesting idea however. It may not that people voting are "racist" as many went to feel is implied here. Or that any particular party is swayed by race at all. It could be that the electoral college itself is a remnant of the time of slavery: 

"There is no reason to feel sentimental about the Electoral College. One of the main reasons the founders created it was slavery. The southern states liked the fact that their slaves, who would be excluded from a direct vote, would be counted — as three-fifths of a white person — when Electoral College votes were apportioned." http://www.nytimes.com/2008/11/20/opinion/20thu1.html 

"The real serious continuing legacy of slavery in this country is the electoral college in the U.S. Senate.  Because what the electoral college in the U.S. Senate are about is a set of compromises that were made in 1789 around slave holding states versus free states.  And it was about this question of how are we gonna be represented in the federal government.  How are we, as Americans, going to be represented.  Large states that had . . . that were slave holding states in the South clearly wanted representation in the House, and they wanted it to be based on how many people there were in each state; and they wanted to count slaves as being among those people in order to get more representation. " http://bigthink.com/ideas/2661﻿ 

"The delegates to the 1787 Constitutional Convention had a variety of reasons for settling on the electoral college format, but protecting smaller states was not among them. Some delegates feared direct democracy, but that was only one factor in the debate. Remember what the country looked like in 1787: The important division was between states that relied on slavery and those that didn’t, not between large and small states. A direct election for president did not sit well with most delegates from the slave states, which had large populations but far fewer eligible voters. They gravitated toward the electoral college as a compromise because it was based on population. The convention had agreed to count each slave as three-fifths of a person for the purpose of calculating each state’s allotment of seats in Congress. For Virginia, which had the largest population among the original 13 states, that meant more clout in choosing the president." http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/five-myths-about-the-electoral-college/2012/11/02/2d45c526-1f85-11e2-afca-58c2f5789c5d_story.html﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_nM63wYvuvE/UJw--rK7B6I/AAAAAAAAYgo/3dCbQO7QRBg/s426/1082_10101431274461982_2037135002_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/105474544524715065767/albums/5786259191513037665/5786259189698104402</link><title>Romney Says Obama Wants to Replace U.S. Currency With "Monopoly Money" 
source: THE NEWSOSPHERE 
http://thenewsosphere.wordpress.com/ 

Recently, GOP nominee and Hair Club for Men spokesman Mitt Romney accused President Obama of wanting to remove the phrase "In God We Trust" from all U.S. currency.  "But the most damning idea is to remove our dollars entirely, and replace them instead with Monopoly Money," said Romney. 

Both Parker Brothers and the White House deny both accusations, calling them "ridiculous" and "expected".  "But I will say this," said Jay Carney, White House Press Secretary, "you gotta admit there is no end to the laughs generated by the Republican Party." 

One campaign advisor wished to clarify that the derogatory tone Romney took with the board game was absolutely unintentional, as "Mitt's favorite part of the classic game is the Get Out of Jail Free card". 

"I do not condone the act of replacing currency," said VP pick Paul Ryan, "but I am pressing my party to pass legislation enabling our members to make that particular card a reality." 

In related news, God released a press statement addressing the accusation, simply saying quote, "Mitt, put a cork in it", end quote. ﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4f05KH6XzY8/UEzsE3xLjFI/AAAAAAAAPtU/cJQndX9Ldx8/w426-h320/romney-is-a-god.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/106292767786679411800/albums/5975826690831536513/5975826695854356034</link><title>On this day in 1790, the United States Supreme Court meets for the first time. Three of the Justices had assembled a day earlier, but had been forced to delay their meeting due to a lack of a quorum. 

There is quite a bit that could be said about the Supreme Court, isn’t there?! So, for now, let me focus on a few trivia items that you may not know. 

George Washington appointed John Jay as the first Chief Justice of the United States on September 24, 1789. (Yes, this is the same John Jay who wrote a handful of the Federalist Papers.) His appointment was confirmed with a speed that can only be envied by modern-day Justices. A mere two days later, on September 26,the Senate confirmed Jay’s appointment. 

The first Supreme Court consisted of 5 associate justices, plus the Chief Justice. Jay called for this Court to meet in New York on February 1, 1790. As with so many other events, 18th-century transportation problems caused that meeting to be delayed for a day, as mentioned above. Indeed, transportation issues would dominate the life of our first Supreme Court justices in a way that we cannot imagine today. The Judiciary Act of 1789 required Justices to travel the circuit and hold circuit court twice a year. The idea was to enable Justices to be familiar with local concerns and local laws. 

Once again, the founding generation showed its concern regarding faraway governmental officials and looked for ways to keep them accountable to the citizens. It’s a concern that modern Americans seem to have forgotten, to our own detriment. 

The Justices apparently hated the traveling requirement. Jay, for instance, traveled 7 months out of the year, which was hard with young children at home. By 1793, the law had changed and Justices were required to travel the circuit only once in a year. The traveling requirement was not completely eliminated until 1891. Today, of course, the Justices simply hear cases in D.C. and are not required to travel at all. 

Jay served as Chief Justice until 1795. In 1800, President John Adams asked him to resume the role, but Jay declined. 

Hard to imagine too many jurists turning down such an appointment today, isn’t it?! Oh, to be back in the days when a job as a Supreme Court Justice was viewed as a bit of a chore—a sacrifice to be made for your country for a few years before resuming normal life! 

&lt;del&gt;\-------------&lt;/del&gt; 
If you enjoyed this post, please don't forget to +1 and SHARE. Our schools and media don’t always teach the stories of our founding! Let’s do it ourselves. 

#TDIH #AmericanHistory #USHistory﻿

Meer lezen (48 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-DgJ5htv26Ao/Uu5mt_Wx9kI/AAAAAAAAAbQ/46RwxsP56SY/w426-h431/Judiciary%2BAct%2Bof%2B1789_Google.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/113811492775425960680/albums/5869963654282306961/5869963658748175506?authkey=CKizqpCxr8ei-gE</link><title>Kiobel v. Shell &amp; the Future of Alien Tort Litigation 

After more than a decade of awaiting and predicting the final outcome in the case of Kiobel v. Royal Dutch Petroleum Co., the United States Supreme Court reached a decision on April 17, 2013. 

The case is a class action suit brought by Esther Kiobel on behalf of Nigerian residents against Royal Dutch Petroleum and its affiliates “Shell Transport and Trading Company” and “Shell Petroleum Development Company of Nigeria” (hereinafter referred to as “Shell”). The defendant companies are incorporated in the Netherlands, the United Kingdom, and Nigeria, respectively. They have been engaged in oil exploration and production in the Ogoni region of Nigeria. A group of Nigerian citizens protested against the environmental destruction caused by Shell’s oil exploration in the region. The plaintiffs claim that Shell has been complicit in the torturing and killing of the protestors by the Nigerian military. In other words, Shell allegedly aided and abetted the Nigerian government in committing violations of the law of nations in Nigeria. 

None of the relevant facts of the case seem to point towards the United States. The unlawful conduct took place in Nigeria, the victims are Nigerian citizens (who are now legal residents of the United States) and the companies who allegedly took part in the crimes are incorporated in European and African countries. Nonetheless, in 2002 the plaintiffs filed their claim with a United States District Court. The suit was brought under the Alien Tort Statute (ATS), 28 U.S.C. §1350, enacted in 1789, which states: “The district courts shall have original jurisdiction of any civil action by an alien for a tort only, committed in violation of the law of nations or a treaty of the United States.” 

At issue in the Kiobel case was the proper interpretation of the Alien Tort Statute. Originally, the Supreme Court was only asked to rule on the matter whether corporations can be held liable for international human rights violations under the ATS.  But the Court broadened the scope of its judgment and also answered the question whether and under what circumstances US courts may hear a case brought under the ATS, for violations of the law of nations occurring within the territory of a sovereign other than the United States. 

Last Wednesday (April 17, 2013), the Supreme Court rendered its judgment and ruled unanimously. Four justices concurred with the Chief Justice’s opinion. The other four justices concurred in the outcome of the decision, but followed a different reasoning. Succinctly put, the Court decided that the plaintiffs were not entitled to damages under the ATS. More broadly, the Court ruled that the ATS is not applicable to actions committed on foreign soil. The justices stated that “the presumption against extraterritoriality applies to claims under the Alien Tort Statute, and nothing in the statute rebuts that presumption”. This judgment seems to put an end to the extraterritorial jurisdiction of the United States for claims brought under the ATS for human rights violations that were committed on foreign territory and that have no sufficient link to the United States. From now on, one cannot file a claim for human rights violations against a corporation in the USA, simply because they have a presence in the USA. Chief Justice Roberts justly wrote that “corporations are often present in many countries, and it would reach too far to say that mere corporate presence suffices.” An additional connection to the United States is required. Justice Kennedy wrote in his concurrence that the Court’s opinion leaves open a lot of significant questions regarding the reach and interpretation of the ATS. One of these remaining questions would indeed be what would constitute an additional sufficient connection. Professor Childress’ recent blog post provides several hypotheses and possible answers to that question (http://conflictoflaws.net/2013/what-will-kiobels-impact-be-on-alien-tort-statute-claims/). 

Even though the Kiobel case turned out to be a substantial victory for the defendant corporations, they did not get their most favorable outcome. When it comes to the first question regarding the interpretation of the ATS, the Supreme Court has not closed the door to all cases of human rights violations committed by corporations. The Court did not decide that corporations are immune from the ATS. 

The reactions to the judgment are – as expected – divided. Multinational companies read the judgment with a sigh of relief. Human rights lawyers on the other hand state that this judgment is not only a disaster for the Nigerian citizens, but the narrow interpretation of the ATS also drastically cuts down on the means and odds to seek redress for other future victims of international human rights violations in foreign and especially in developing countries. The USA are said to be turning their back on a global trend towards human rights enforcement. Some argue that the Supreme Court has interpreted the ATS in a way that is inconsistent with decades of use of the ATS. For over thirty years, the ATS has been used to bring human rights cases before federal courts. 

Nonetheless, the judgment has its merits. From a human point of view, it is an understatement to say that it is tragic that the plaintiffs in this case will not be compensated. However, one cannot bend the law as far as one would like it to reach. The text of the ATS does indeed grant the United States jurisdiction for certain international law violations, but it does not explicitly state that this is the case for conduct on foreign soil. By clearly bringing the presumption against extraterritoriality to the fore, the Supreme Court restores the guiding principle that a nation does not have jurisdiction for causes of action that occur outside their borders. And even for foreign victims of human rights violations committed on foreign territory, the Supreme Court left the door to the US courtrooms ajar. The Chief Justice’s words “and even where claims touch and concern the territory of the United States, they must do so with sufficient force to displace the presumption against extraterritorial application” indicate that in limited cases there is still the possibility to set aside the presumption against extraterritoriality. In other words, a case that concerns human rights violations committed on foreign territory but which nonetheless shows a greater nexus to the United States, may still fall under United States jurisdiction. Whereas professor Childress argues that in the end the possibilities for foreign victims to file ATS claims in federal court will be very limited, in my view the Supreme Court has left the US courts just the right amount of space to rule in cases of international human rights violations concerning foreign victims. A too far reaching extraterritorial jurisdiction for the United States in international human rights cases would establish a type of legal colonialism. It is not up to the United States – or any other country for that matter – to become the world police when it comes to human rights violations and to rule on these violations, regardless of where they occur. Or as Justice Story puts it: “No nation has ever yet pretended to be the custos morum of the whole world…” (United States v. The La Jeune Eugénie). In the Kiobel case, it would be up to Nigeria to choose their own means to deal with the conflict in their own way. 

In conclusion, it may be said that the Supreme Court has found the right balance in the Kiobel judgment: the Court does not claim the United States to be “a uniquely hospitable forum for the enforcement of international norms” irrespective of where the violation takes place, but leaves room to rule on such cases and to give redress to the victims, as long as these cases show a sufficient connection with United States territory. 

And 

The wave of tort suits under the Alien Tort Statute (ATS) may not be brought to an end as a result of a decision issued yesterday by the U.S. Supreme Court, Kiobel v. Royal Dutch Petroleum, but it is likely to subside considerably.  For the past several decades, the ATS has served as the favorite vehicle of human rights activists seeking to challenge the overseas business practices of U.S. corporations, but the Supreme Court has now ruled that the ATS applies only to conduct within the United States or on the high seas. 

The ATS is a 1789 law that grants jurisdiction to federal courts to hear tort claims by aliens alleging violations of “the law of nations.”  The law lay dormant for two centuries, primarily because litigants assumed that the number of torts to which the law applied was extremely narrow – perhaps limited only to claims by foreign ambassadors that they had been assaulted in this country.  But in 1980, the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit held in Filartiga v. Pena-Irala that the ATS applied to a wide array of alleged human rights violations.  In the decades that followed, activists sued U.S. corporations under the ATS for an increasing variety of overseas activities, from operating facilities that allegedly polluted the environment to administering medications without allegedly first providing informed consent to giving financial support to oppressive foreign governments.  WLF has been actively involved in many of those suits, opposing expansive interpretations of the ATS, including through an amicus brief in Kiobel. 

But then in 2010, the Second Circuit (which along with the Ninth Circuit has handled the great majority of ATS cases) ruled 2-1 in Kiobel that the ATS is inapplicable to corporations.  The court explained that because corporate liability is not a discernible norm of customary international law, the ATS should not be interpreted as having authorized suits against corporations.  The Supreme Court agreed to review Kiobel during its 2011-12 Term, but was unable to come up with a decision and instead asked the parties to submit new briefs on whether the ATS applies extraterritorially.  ATS litigation across the country has been on hold for the past year as lower courts awaited the Supreme Court’s decision. 

Yesterday’s decision (unanimous in the holding but split 5-4 on rationale) will lead to the dismissal of virtually all pending ATS cases.  The majority decision, written by Chief Justice Roberts, said that its decision was controlled by “the presumption against extraterritoriality”:  Congress is presumed not to intend its statutes to apply outside the United States unless it provides a “clear indication” otherwise.  The Court discerned no such intent on the part of the 1789 Congress.  Indeed, the Court noted, the first Congress appears to have adopted the ATS in order to provide foreign ambassadors the ability to seek redress in the federal courts if they were attacked while in the United States – as very famously happened twice in the 1780s.  Noting that assertions of jurisdiction by American courts over events that occur in a another country could have negative foreign policy ramifications for the United States, the Court said that any decision to permit such suits should be made by Congress explicitly, not by the courts. 

The Court’s rejection of extraterritorial suits was not as broadly worded as it might have been, with the result that human rights activists are highly likely to resist efforts to dismiss their suits.  The Chief Justice may have been required to use less categorical language in order to garner the vote of Justice Anthony Kennedy, widely regarded as the swing vote on ATS issues.  In particular, the majority opinion recognized that ATS cases in which a portion of the conduct occurred overseas may still be sustainable, so long as at least some portion of “the relevant conduct” occurred within the United States.  While stating that “mere corporate presence” in the United States is insufficient to qualify as the requisite “relevant conduct,” the Court never spelled out just what conduct would qualify. 

While it is unlikely that the majority had in mind a mere meeting in a New York office at which corporate executives discussed the corporation’s operations in the country where alleged human rights abuses occurred, plaintiffs’ lawyers will undoubtedly raise such claims in an effort to distinguish Kiobel.  They are also likely to cite the following passage from Justice Kennedy’s concurring opinion that provides a small ray of hope to overseas plaintiffs: 

Other cases may arise with allegations of serious violations of international law principles protecting persons, cases covered neither by the [Torture Victim Protection Act] nor by the reasoning and holding of today’s case; and in those disputes the proper implementation of the presumption against extraterritorial application may require some further elaboration and explanation. 

Plaintiffs’ lawyers are likely also to assert that their allegations of overseas human rights abuses can go forward as common law tort actions alleging violations of state law.  States are largely free to craft their tort law without interference from the federal government, so plaintiffs’ lawyers barred from raising overseas human rights claims in federal court under the ATS may well decide to file their lawsuits in state courts instead.  Of course, most states are likely to decide, for many of the same reasons that motivated the Supreme Court in Kiobel, that it would be inappropriate for them to stand in judgment of events that took place in foreign countries.  But if even one state makes known its willingness to hear suits alleging overseas human rights abuses, one can reasonably expect plaintiffs’ lawyers to flock there. 

In sum, yesterday’s Kiobel decision is likely to make it far more difficult for human rights activists to sue U.S. corporations based on the corporation’s overseas activities.  But the decision left activists with sufficient wiggle room that we can expect to see multinational corporations regularly being sued for their overseas activities for the foreseeable future. 
Source: http://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2013/04/18/supreme-court-observations-kiobel-v-royal-dutch-petroleum-the-future-of-alien-tort-litigation/ 

And 

Thursday’s Kiobel v Royal Dutch Shell ruling by the US Supreme Court provides much-needed clarification about the scope of an obscure US law utilised by a growing number of claimants from emerging economies. 

The Kiobel case alleged that Shell was complicit in human rights abuses committed in Nigeria in the late 1990s, when activists protesting against the oil industry were hanged by the government. The case was unusual in seeking redress in US courts for a case involving a non-US company and non-US claimants for a crime committed in a non-US jurisdiction. How is this possible? 

The Nigerian claimants referenced the Alien Tort Claims Act of 1789, which determined that if any human rights infringement occurs anywhere in the world, US courts can deal with it. Jonathan Verschuuren, environmental law expert at the Netherlands’ Tilburg University, said that the act “dates back to the start of the US, when they thought that US courts should do justice to the world. It was a very aspirational idea.” 

Use of the ATC Act has been growing since the 1970s, especially from claimants in emerging countries. From apartheid-related cases against Daimler, Ford and General Motors to human rights cases against Exxon and Rio Tinto, claimants have invoked the law more than 150 times in the past 20 years. Judges are now scrutinising the Act, perhaps a fearing a wave of claims that might turn the US into a public court for the world’s grievances. 

The Kiobel case seems to have put paid to that, limiting the scope of ATC. Judges agreed that Shell could not be tried. Chief Justice Roberts wrote that “all relevant conduct took place outside the United States”. Other judges have also said that ATC applies to conduct only within the US. 

While corporate lawyers see the ruling as setting a vital precedent, it may not deal a terminal blow to claimants seeking use of ATC. Du v. Cisco, filed in 2011, is pending in the US district of Maryland. It was brought by Chinese citizens claiming Cisco technologies – including those enabling access to private internet communications and identification of anonymous bloggers – helped the Chinese Communist Party to commit torture and unlawful detention through its technologies. Unlike the Kiobel case, Cisco is a US corporation which may allow the ATC Act to enable a case to be heard. 

Another case, against Cincinnati-based Chiquita – who are accused of financing paramilitary death squads in Colombia, – might also go forward. 

And non-US companies can be forced to answer a case if they have a considerable presence in the US, as is shown by Sarei v Rio Tinto. Claimants said the Papua New Guinean government used Rio Tinto helicopters and vehicles to kill protestors in a 1988 revolt. The California district court noted that while the case concerned allegations in a non-US jurisdiction, Rio Tinto had a considerable US presence – with 47 per cent of operating assets in North America – giving the court jurisdiction. 

However, only certain types of crimes categorised as ‘violations of the laws of nations’ fell within federal jurisdiction for that case: specifically, genocide and war crimes . 

Other crimes, such as sexual violence of the kind alleged in one Exxon case in Indonesia were rejected by one court as being outside the remit of the ATC Act. 
Source: http://blogs.ft.com/beyond-brics/2013/04/18/kiobel-v-shell-the-limits-of-atc-act/﻿

Meer lezen (308 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-hdungS8mopE/UXZM2OQjJJI/AAAAAAAABow/RdJ0YbBPtOU/w426-h369/Shell.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7189-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/judiciary%20act%201789/photos/106499455728631210762/albums/5937692030080600929/5937692085077271826</link><title>1988 Council of Europe Adopted an Law to punish Corporations: 
1. Enterprises should be able to be made liable for offences committed in the exercise of their activities, even where the offence is alien to the purposes of the enterprise. #Trafficking #Paedophilia   #ManufacturedConflict #NarcoticsTerrorism #ElectionRigging   
2. The enterprise should be so liable, whether a natural person who committed the acts or omissions constituting the offence can be identified or not. 
3. To render enterprises liable, consideration should be given in particular to: 
a. applying criminal liability and sanctions to enterprises, where the nature of the offence, the degree of fault on the part of the enterprise, the consequences for society and the need to prevent further offences so require; 
b. applying other systems of liability and sanctions, for instance those imposed by administrative authorities and subject to judicial control, in particular for illicit behaviour which does not require treating the offender as a criminal. 
4. The enterprise should be exonerated from liability where its management is not implicated in the offence and has taken all the necessary steps to prevent its commission. 
5. The imposition of liability upon the enterprise should not exonerate from liability a natural person implicated in the offence. In particular, persons performing managerial functions should be made liable for breaches of duties which conduce to the commission of an offence. 

http://conventions.coe.int/Treaty/Commun/QueVoulezVous.asp?NT=197&amp;CM=1&amp;CL=ENG 

SOSA V. ALVAREZ-MACHAIN (03-339) 542 U.S. 692 (2004) 331 F.3d 604, reversed. 
Alien Tort statute (ATS), a 1789 law giving district courts “original jurisdiction of any civil action by an alien for a tort only, committed in violation of the law of nations … ,” §1350. 
 28 U.S.C. § 1346(b)(1) 
http://www.law.cornell.edu/supct/search/display.html?terms=sosa&amp;url=/supct/html/03-339.ZS.html 
Council of Europe Convention on Action against Trafficking in Human Beings CETS No.: 197 
http://conventions.coe.int/Treaty/Commun/QueVoulezVous.asp?NT=197&amp;CM=1&amp;CL=ENG﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7189_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-s9n6NTAUmaA/Umbrffyt5RI/AAAAAAAAGlU/YndDJ2RR2t4/w426-h237/COE_CSR.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>