<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:06:25" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/110107953824427730254/albums/5931496305307197073/5931496309998658274</link><title>The contraceptive sponge. 

The contraceptive sponge combines barrier and chemical method of contraception. Natural sea sponges and modern manufactured sponges were used with various spermicides (vinegar or boric acid were common choices) to prevent conception. 

Reverend Alfred Henry Tyrer writes in his 1943 book Sex Marriage and Birth Control: 

A recent development is the medicated sponge. It can be made inexpensively and does not require a medical examination. The reliability of a foam sponge is somewhere between 55-95% effective, and physicians agree that the diaphragm-jelly is more reliable but that the simplicity and availability of the sponge adds to its usefulness. 

Norman E. Himes, Ph. D. also described how to use a contraceptive sponge in his 1938 book Practical Birth-Control Methods: 

The sponge should be cut 2-3 inches in diameter, but it is better to err on the side of too big than too small. It is advised to use a spermicidal agent with the sponge. Soap can be used, jellies or a new foam powder are recommended. Strong soaps, like laundry detergent are not to be used. The sponge should be disinfected, either by soap and water or a disinfecting solution. Rubber sponges can be boiled, but the sea sponge tends to shrink and harden when boiled. 

#birthcontrol   #contraceptivesponge   #contraception 

http://tinyurl.com/oo392m4﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-aMZLTrfSHSw/UlDod7ACouI/AAAAAAAArGM/twVP2bEdeTg/w426-h264/Screenshot_10.bmp</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/108250403292856337796/albums/5726326855392495809/5738902754370245218</link><title>Al-Baqarah: 233 
Nursing the infant 
بسم الله الرحمن الرحيم 

The mothers shall give suck to their children for two whole years, for those who wish the suckling to be completed..." [Al-Baqarah 2:233] 

We have instructed man concerning his parents. Bearing him caused his mother great debility, and the period of his weaning was two years: "Give thanks to Me and to your parents. I am your final destination." (Surat Luqman: 14) 

And We have enjoined upon man goodness towards his parents: His mother bore him by bearing strain upon strain, and his weaning was in two years: “[Hence, O man,] be grateful to Me and to your parents; to Me is the eventual coming.” (Qur'an 31:14) 

BENEFITS OF BREASTFEEDING 
Breast milk is widely acknowledged as the most complete form of nutrition for infants, with a range of benefits for infants' health, growth, immunity and development. 
\-- Healthy People 2010, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Atlanta, Georgia 

Breast milk is a unique nutritional source that cannot adequately be replaced by any other food, including infant formula.Infants are fragile and susceptible to disease, partly because their bodies are not fully developed. They must be treated with special care and given adequate nourishment. Infant formulas are able to mimic a few of the nutritional components of breast milk, but formula cannot hope to duplicate the vast and constantly changing array of essential nutrients in human milk. 

Studies have demonstrated a number of important health benefits to breastfeeding. Among them: 
• Breast-fed children are more resistant to disease and infection early in life than formula-fed children 
• Breast-fed children are less likely to contract a number of diseases later in life, including juvenile diabetes, multiple sclerosis, heart disease, and cancer before the age of 15 
• Mothers who breastfeed are less likely to develop osteoporosis later in life, are able to lose weight gained during pregnancy more easily and have a lower risk of breast, uterine and ovarian cancer 

BENEFITS TO THE CHILD IN THE FIRST YEARS OF LIFE 
A variety of studies have demonstrated that breastfeeding increases a child's immunity to disease and infection: 
• Many studies show that breastfeeding strengthens the immune system. During nursing, the mother passes antibodies to the child, which help the child resist diseases and help improve the normal immune response to certain vaccines. 
• Respiratory illness is far more common among formula-fed children. In fact, an analysis of many different research studies concluded that infants fed formula face a threefold greater risk of being hospitalized with a severe respiratory infection than do infants breast-fed for a minimum of four months. 
• Diarrheal disease is three to four times more likely to occur in infants fed formula than those fed breast milk. 
• Breastfeeding has been shown to reduce the likelihood of ear infections, and to prevent recurrent ear infections. Ear infections are a major reason that infants take multiple courses of antibiotics. 
• Researchers have observed a decrease in the probability of Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (SIDS) in breast-fed infants. 
• Another apparent benefit from breastfeeding may be protection from allergies. Eczema, an allergic reaction, is significantly rarer in breast-fed babies. A review of 132 studies on allergy and breastfeeding concluded that breastfeeding appears to help protect children from developing allergies, and that the effect seems to be particularly strong among children whose parents have allergies. 

BENEFITS TO THE CHILD LATER IN LIFE 
Some benefits of breastfeeding become apparent as the child grows older. Among the benefits demonstrated by research: 
• Infants who are breast-fed longer have fewer dental cavities throughout their lives. 
• Several recent studies have shown that children who were breast-fed are significantly less likely to become obese later in childhood. Formula feeding is linked to about a 20 to 30 percent greater likelihood that the child will become obese. 
• Children who are exclusively breast-fed during the first three months of their lives are 34 percent less likely to develop juvenile, insulin-dependent diabetes than children who are fed formula. 
• Breastfeeding may also decrease the risk of childhood cancer in children under 15 years of age. Formula-fed children are eight times more likely to develop cancer than children who are nursed for more than six months. (It is important to note that children who are breast-fed for less than six months do not appear to have any decreased cancer risk compared to bottle-fed children.) 
• As children grow into adults, several studies have shown that people who were breast-fed as infants have lower blood pressure on average than those who were formula-fed. Thus, it is not surprising that other studies have shown that heart disease is less likely to develop in adults who were breast-fed in infancy. 
• Significant evidence suggests that breast-fed children develop fewer psychological, behavioral and learning problems as they grow older. Studies also indicate that cognitive development is increased among children whose mothers choose to breastfeed. 
• In researching the psychological benefits of breast milk, one researcher found that breast-fed children were, on average, more mature, assertive and secure with themselves as they developed. 

BENEFITS TO THE MOTHER 
Studies indicate that breastfeeding helps improve mothers' health, as well as their children's. A woman grows both physically and emotionally from the relationship she forms with her baby. Just as a woman's breast milk is designed specifically to nourish the body of an infant, the production and delivery of this milk aids her own health. For example: 
• Breastfeeding helps a woman to lose weight after birth. Mothers burn many calories during lactation as their bodies produce milk. In fact, some of the weight gained during pregnancy serves as an energy source for lactation. 
• Breastfeeding releases a hormone in the mother (oxytocin) that causes the uterus to return to its normal size more quickly. 
• When a woman gives birth and proceeds to nurse her baby, she protects herself from becoming pregnant again too soon, a form of birth control found to be 98 percent effective -- more effective than a diaphragm or condom. Scientists believe this process prevents more births worldwide than all forms of contraception combined. In Africa, breastfeeding prevents an estimated average of four births per woman, and in Bangladesh it prevents an estimated average of 6.5 births per woman. 
• Breastfeeding appears to reduce the mother's risk of developing osteoporosis in later years. Although mothers experience bone-mineral loss during breastfeeding, their mineral density is replenished and even increased after lactation. 
• Diabetic women improve their health by breastfeeding. Not only do nursing infants have increased protection from juvenile diabetes, the amount of insulin that the mother requires postpartum goes down. 
• Women who lactate for a total of two or more years reduce their chances of developing breast cancer by 24 percent. 
• Women who breastfeed their children have been shown to be less likely to develop uterine, endometrial or ovarian cancer. 
• The emotional health of the mother may be enhanced by the relationship she develops with her infant during breastfeeding, resulting in fewer feelings of anxiety and a stronger sense of connection with her baby. 
• A woman's ability to produce all of the nutrients that her child needs can provide her with a sense of confidence. Researchers have pointed out that the bond of a nursing mother and child is stronger than any other human contact. Holding the child to her breast provides most mothers with a more powerful psychological experience than carrying the fetus inside her uterus. The relationship between mother and child is rooted in the interactions of breastfeeding. This feeling sets the health and psychological foundation for years to come. 

http://www.nrdc.org/breastmilk/benefits.asp﻿

Meer lezen (145 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_02_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-tzEEXRGJhG4/T6Stpiq_0mI/AAAAAAAABNQ/U8v0hpqRkZs/w426-h320/Al-Baqarah+233+benefits+of+breastfeeding.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/109393959420844829852/albums/5771704726517579457/5771704725372704290</link><title>*I am both pro-choice and pro-life and here is why* 

A person can choose their actions, but more often then not can't choose the consequences of those actions. Science and religion agree that the main purpose, or consequence, of having intercourse is procreation. While there are many other great side benefits and reasons that is unquestionably the main reason and consequence. 

Humans have devised many ways to make the choice to have sex and prevent the consequence of pregnancy. 

1\. A woman has the right to CHOOSE to abstain from sex. 

2\. A woman has the right to CHOOSE to use a condom 

3\. A woman has the right to CHOOSE to take a birth control pill 

4\. A woman has the right to CHOOSE to only have sex at certain times of the month when the risk of pregnancy is very low. 

5\. The woman has the right to CHOOSE to use a Diaphragm. 
6. The woman has the right to CHOOSE to use an IUD. 
7\. And finally The woman has the right to CHOOSE to take the morning after pill. 
Now, if a woman has CHOSEN to use her body to have sex and CHOSEN not to use all of these methods to prevent the main consequence of having sex then why should she have the right to kill a beautiful, innocent, sweet little baby? 
That baby deserves the right to CHOICE too. That baby deserves the right to CHOOSE life. He/she deserves the right to CHOOSE to go to college. He/she deserves the right to CHOOSE to be a Dr, lawyer, teacher, veterinarian, farmer, firefighter, mother, father, artist, musician, gymnast, athlete or even an astronaut. 
A woman's poor choices should not take away that little persons right to CHOOSE. 
-I don't usually promote myself, but I would ask you to please share this if you agree. If you disagree or want to have a civil discussion of this issue then comment on it. I welcome all points of view, but will kick anyone off the thread who uses personal attacks, threats, or foul language in their comments.﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-w-TUTQdWd1U/UBk23jBIliI/AAAAAAAACqo/exOXVcCZizI/w426-h576/newborn-baby-image.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/108126252237712807089/albums/5998884928321040609/5998884938114771378</link><title>From my short experience arguing with feminists online. 

Feminist logic: You disagree with me, therefore... Misogyny! 

#feminism   #victimideology   #misogyny   #mensrights﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-G-xBU2fVN3I/U0BSEVjFqbI/AAAAAAAAXXY/m5Flt-voR2Q/s426/Feminist%2Blogic.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/115226685658132369903/albums/5943942693735487985/5943942697715842802</link><title>Are you headed to the International Conference on Family Planning in Addis Ababa, Ethiopia? We'll be there featuring three contraceptive technologies advanced by PATH and our partners: Sayana® Press, a new form of injectable contraceptive in the PATH-developed Uniject™ autodisable injection system; the Woman’s Condom, a PATH-designed female condom; and the SILCS diaphragm, a single-sized, easy-to-use barrier contraceptive. Here's how to connect with PATH at the conference: http://bit.ly/193InAi. #ICFP2013﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-LH76zhfz608/Un0gZCahPvI/AAAAAAAABTY/AQpqZAKZlgQ/s426/ICFP-2013-Unmet-Need-Graphic-FINAL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/111784248812389846488/albums/5682372713694239313/5699793145301533266</link><title>Green Valley 4-H Scott Teixeira, Nathan Teixeira﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-GzOIFWqTEuA/Txm7qrbnglI/AAAAAAAAAsc/Me3wCWfAWrc/w426-h320/Left%2Bto%2Bright%2B%2B%2BGreen%2BValley%2B4-H%2B%2BScott%2BTeixeira%252C%2BNathan%2BTeixeira.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/103133177397090504113/albums/5717934138657685473/5717934137622745154</link><title>Vicious. 

"Never has there been a more vicious anti-Catholic advertisement in a prominent American newspaper than the one in today’s New York Times by Freedom From Religion Foundation. The demonization of Catholicism is palpable. [snip] Not a single Catholic who reads this ad will be impelled to leave the Church. That is not the issue (Catholicism, unlike many other religions, is actually growing in the U.S., and worldwide). The issue is the increase in hate speech directed at Catholics. Nothing will stop Catholics from demanding that the Obama administration respect their First Amendment rights, this vile assault by FFRF notwithstanding. Why the Times allowed this ad is another issue altogether." - Catholic League blowhard Bill Donohue. 

Full text below: 

http://www.catholicleague.org/frontal-assault-on-catholicism/ 

Images from http://joemygod.blogspot.com/2012/03/full-page-ad-in-todays-nytimes-urges.html 

What got him all steamed up? The following open letter, which was introduced by the cartoon image below: 

Dear ‘Liberal’ Catholic: 

It’s time to quit the Roman Catholic Church. 

It’s your moment of truth. Will it be reproductive freedom, or back to the Dark Ages? Do you choose women and their rights, or Bishops and their wrongs? Whose side are you on, anyway? 

It is time to make known your dissent from the Catholic Church, in light of the U.S. Catholic Conference of Bishops’ ruthless campaign endangering the right to contraception. If you’re part of the Catholic Church, you’re part of the problem. 

Why are you propping up the pillars of a tyrannical and autocratic, woman-hating, sex-perverting, antediluvian Old Boys Club? Why are you aiding and abetting a church that has repeatedly and publicly announced a crusade to ban contraception, abortion and sterilization, and to deny the right of all women everywhere, Catholic or not, to decide whether and when to become mothers? When it comes to reproductive freedom, the Roman Catholic Church is Public Enemy Number One. Think of the acute misery, poverty, needless suffering, unwanted pregnancies, social evils and deaths that can be laid directly at the door of the Church’s antiquated doctrine that birth control is a sin and must be outlawed. 

A backer of the Roman Catholic presidential candidate says that if women want to avoid pregnancy we should put an aspirin between our knees? Catholic politicians are urging that the right to contraception should be left up to states? Nearly 50 years after the Supreme Court upheld contraception as a privacy right, we’re going to have to defend this basic freedom all over again? 

You’re better than your church. So why? Why continue to attend Mass? Tithe? Why dutifully sacrifice to send your children to parochial schools so they can be brainwashed into the next generation of myrmidons (and, potentially, become the next Church victims)? For that matter, why have you put up with an institution that won’t put up with women priests, that excludes half of humanity? 

No self-respecting feminist, civil libertarian or progressive should cling to the Catholic faith. As a Cafeteria Catholic, you chuck out the stale doctrine and moldy decrees of your religion, but keep patronizing the establishment that menaces public health by serving rotten offerings. Your continuing Catholic membership, as a “liberal,” casts a veneer of respectability upon an irrational sect determined to blow out the Enlightenment and threaten liberty for women worldwide. You are an enabler. And it’s got to stop. 

If you imagine you can change the church from within — get it to lighten up on birth control, gay rights, marriage equality, embryonic stem-cell research — you are deluding yourself. If you remain a “good Catholic,” you are doing “bad” to women’s rights. You’re kidding yourself if you think the Church is ever going to add a Doctrine of Immaculate ContraCeption. 

It is disgraceful that U.S. health care reform is being held hostage to the Catholic Church’s bizarre opposition to medically prescribed contraception. No politician should jeopardize electability for failure to genuflect before the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops. (Question to ask your Bishop: Does he hold up an umbrella against the rain? Isn’t that just as “unnatural” as using a condom or diaphragm?) 

Your Church hysterically claims that secular medical policy is “an assault against religious liberty.” You are savvy enough to realize that the real assault is by the Church against women’s rights and health care. As Nation columnist Katha Pollitt asks: Is it an offense against Jehovah Witnesses that health care coverage will include blood transfusions? The Amish, as Pollitt points out, don’t label cars “an assault on religious liberty” and try to force everyone to drive buggies. The louder the Church cries “offense against religious liberty” the harder it works to take away women’s liberty. 

Obama has compromised, but the Church never budges, instead launching a vengeful modern-day Inquisition. Look at its continuing directives to parish priests to use their pulpits every Sunday to lobby you against Obama’s policy, the Church’s announcement of a major anti-contraception media campaign — using your tithes, contributions and donations — to defeat Obama’s laudable health care policy. The Church has introduced into Congress the “Respect for Rights of Conscience Act, ” a bill to place the conscienceless Catholic Church’s “rights of conscience” above the rights of conscience of 53 percent of Americans. That the Church has “conscience rights” to deny women their rights is a kissing cousin to the claim that “corporations are people.” The Church that hasn’t persuaded you to oppose contraception now wants to use the force of secular law to deny contraceptive rights to non-Catholics. 

But is there any point in going on? After all, your misplaced loyalty has lasted through two decades of public sex scandals involving preying priests, children you may have known as victims, and church complicity, collusion and coverup going all the way to the top. Are you like the battered woman who, after being beaten down every Sunday, feels she has no place else to go? 

But we have a more welcoming home to offer, free of incense-fogged ritual, free of what freethinker Bertrand Russell called “ideas uttered long ago by ignorant men,” free of blind obedience to an illusory religious authority. Join those of us who put humanity above dogma. 

As a member of the “flock” of an avowedly antidemocratic club, isn’t it time you vote with your feet? Please, exit en Mass. 

Very truly, 

Annie Laurie Gaylor 
Co-President 
Freedom From Religion Foundation﻿

Meer lezen (130 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-uzbtHM5XiNE/T1ouzaIVUEI/AAAAAAAADOo/Tz-0WQ2a8jM/w426-h253/FFRF1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/100787235288393230084/albums/5814718721159252369/5814718727998323778</link><title>มารู้จัก ฟองน้ำคุมกำเนิด (Contraceptive Sponge) กัน : อาหารสมอง - http://variety.teenee.com/foodforbrain/12719.html 

ฟองน้ำคุมกำเนิด - 
http://www.siamhealth.net/public_html/mother_child/birth_control/sponge.html 

การคุมกำเนิดโดยใช้ Diaphragm - http://www.siamhealth.net/public_html/mother_child/birth_control/diaphram.html 

บทความสุขภาพ : การคุมกำเนิด วิธีต่างๆ (นอกจากการใช้ถุงยางอนามัย) - 
http://bbs.siamtalk.org/showthread.php/showthread.php/1088-บทความสุขภาพ-การคุมกำเนิด-วิธีต่างๆ-(นอกจากการใช้ถุงยางอนามัย)﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TrKAVQjApd4/ULIH4BsmvEI/AAAAAAAAAT8/BTozQ8JpAs8/w426-h320/52364.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/104811830066099855786/albums/5883800347781931777/5980162136574362098</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_10_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1UiYeBGuX4c/Uv3Nx2nBgfI/AAAAAAAAItw/UkgrLkc29kc/w426-h320/IMAGE_2129.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7197-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/contraceptive%20diaphragm/photos/113664776160150493710/albums/5807130259886710881/5807130266330717586</link><title>My plan will create 12 million new jobs http://mi.tt/VMpzQe﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7197_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-lPTIJ48LIC8/UJcSNbEP3ZI/AAAAAAAAqaU/fUfn1OBIFeI/s426/jobs.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>