<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 17:10:26" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/104477202728652698005/albums/6013629758558879953/6013629761244922930</link><title>Not A Photoshopped 
Railroad track damage from the Canterbury Earthquake in 2010 
The 2010 Canterbury earthquake was a 7.1 magnitude earthquake,which struck the South Island of New Zealand. 
YouTube : Top 10 Unbelievable Photos that arere not Photoshopped﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1jETxHum6gY/U3S0aAG4hDI/AAAAAAACTzc/bCAgs8733-s/w426-h320/6.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/102877039067512129128/albums/6015431748809314289/6015431745862017314</link><title>3\. When a survivor of an earthquake found a treasured photo album intact in Sichuan, China﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/--EIEGgaQWg8/U3sbTT62oSI/AAAAAAAAtg0/ZY_q0pAC_ms/w426-h284/image003+%281%29.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/114290269850278997601/albums/6015325749882940145/6015325752173679330</link><title>THE BIG ONES? Earthquake researchers now say it's more likely that the Bay Area will experience a flurry of mid-sized quakes, rather than one giant earthquake. http://abc7ne.ws/1o08s05 

SHARE this with others who live in the Bay Area. 

Prepare NorCal --&gt; http://abc7ne.ws/1hImMmn﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-WLtj6T5DDwI/U3q65qqSUuI/AAAAAAAAuNw/qa8PI4nxlcU/s426/051914-ap-89quake-social-img.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/117980522234225090192/albums/6015466591943920001/6015466601006829698</link><title>Seismic Summary 
6:15 am, Tuesday, 20 May 2014 

The United States Geological Survey (USGS) lists a total of 136 earthquakes seen worldwide in the last 24 hours.  The largest of these was a magnitude 5.4 quake that occurred yesterday at 22:47:21 UTC (5:47:21 pm CDT) near Visokoi Island in the far southern Atlantic Ocean.  The USGS report on this quake is at http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/usb000qvt4#summary. 

In the United States, 115 earthquakes were recorded by the USGS in the last 24 hours.  The largest of these was a magnitude 3.8 quake that occurred yesterday at 20:08:51 UTC (3:08:51 pm CDT) in southern California.  The USGS report on this quake is at http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci15503377#summary. 

No earthquakes were recorded in the southeastern United States region by the USGS in the last 24 hours. 

EARTHQUAKE HISTORY TODAY     On this date in 1992, a magnitude 6.3 earthquake struck in northern Pakistan.  At least 36 people were killed and 100 were injured in the Peshawar and Kohat Districts, including 20 people killed at Shakkar Khel.  At least 400 houses were destroyed in the Kohat District.  The quake was felt at Islamabad and 
Lahore, and also in the Srinagar area, Kashmir and in parts of northern India. (source: USGS) 

NORTHERN ALABAMA SEISMICITY    The most recent AlabamaQuake real-time seismic heliplot display is below, showing the last 18 hours of northern Alabama seismicity.  No significant (&gt;M6.0) seismic events were observed during the period.  See http://alabamaquake.com/seismicity.html for more details.﻿

Meer lezen (30 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_04_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-WS7NOGiR6sQ/U3s7AJc9EII/AAAAAAAAFYA/1ikbAAeCIpw/w426-h284/hv3_20May14.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/105952312491491054032/albums/6015137974053670001/6015137976391241490?sqi=109415819365164322479&amp;sqsi=d52d72d4-7f9a-46bf-a5c0-529aba9bde80</link><title>Social Media Helping Communities Heal 

Christchurch, NZ, was hit by a earthquake. Social media helped them build community, awareness and interesting in their city, helping it land on the New York Times list of best places to visit in 2014. 

http://enveritasgroup.com/2014/05/16/social-media-helps-communities-heal/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TdRXAUNmD-4/U3oQHrXDDxI/AAAAAAAAAq8/7_jDfX3Jy5w/w426-h237/Rebuild-Disaster.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/108600825644961084085/albums/6015022250884219393/6015022251973498514</link><title>I arrived at my office this morning after the #earthquake on Saturday and found a victim :(﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3qQEGEgX4QY/U3mm3oTzVpI/AAAAAAAAJ-g/Ry9UOZ8g9JQ/w426-h320/19.05.14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/103983140042012599416/albums/6009671321701365009/6009671327041557442</link><title>Good morning from Tokyo! 
We just had an earthquake and it's a little bit big one. 
And this cloudy sky...it is far from fun. 

But everything is okay.  We have prepared for earthquake... 

#tokyo   #morningsky   #goodmorning   #goodmorningworld  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Fjsgd-YCHiA/U2akOzkpk8I/AAAAAAAAaH4/KSNMv4dG1aA/w426-h757/2014-05-05%2B05.04.35.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/111028887594339088815/albums/6014868753859858193/6014868760100690018?sqi=111431221870263866201&amp;sqsi=a1ccf0e1-1b50-4eac-a31d-423ea40465d8</link><title>#earthquake  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-3wbv6ppOCuE/U3kbROhlWGI/AAAAAAAADYc/5YM2ls8Hf04/w426-h282/bp36.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/6012590114455329361/6012590119310357154</link><title>Mysterious Booming Sounds In Missouri Ozarks Warning Of Coming Earthquake On New Madrid Fault? http://b4in.org/p1LT 

The authorities in the Ozarks have no clue what the huge booms residents heard. When the New Madrid had the huge earthquake of 1811-1812, it was reported that residents then heard strange, big booms, prior to the major quakes. This was such a major event, the Mississippi River ran backwards and it made some parts of land in the area into swamp lands. 

There have been some earthquakes in the New Madrid Seismic Zone this week. 

This sequence of three very large earthquakes is usually referred to as the New Madrid earthquakes, after the Missouri town that was the largest settlement on the Mississippi River between St. Louis, Missouri and Natchez, Mississippi. 

On the basis of the large area of damage (600,000 square kilometers), the widespread area of perceptibility (5,000,000 square kilometers), and the complex physiographic changes that occurred, the New Madrid earthquakes of 1811-1812 rank as some of the largest in the United States since its settlement by Europeans. They were by far the largest east of the Rocky Mountains in the U.S. and Canada. 

The area of strong shaking associated with these shocks is two to three times as large as that of the 1964 Alaska earthquake and 10 times as large as that of the 1906 San Francisco earthquake. Because there were no seismographs in North America at that time, and very few people in the New Madrid region, the estimated magnitudes of this series of earthquakes vary considerably and depend on modern researchers’ interpretations of journals, newspaper reports, and other accounts of the ground shaking and damage. 

The magnitudes of the three principal earthquakes of 1811-1812 described below are the preferred values taken from research involved with producing the 2008 USGS National Seismic Hazard Map . 

More http://b4in.org/p1LT﻿

Meer lezen (36 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ILU1jGF6lbM/U3EC24GEcqI/AAAAAAAA-Zg/jK6eiyNZAhM/w426-h470/CentralUS_seismicity2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7207-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/earthquake/photos/117879909215135297796/albums/6010457370759955169/6010457378040171106</link><title>Earthquake in Thailand killed an 83-year-old woman 
Thai officials say one person was killed and 23 others injured in the 6.0-magnitude earthquake that hit the northern part of the country Monday. 
Officials said Tuesday an 83-year-old woman died when a wall in her home collapsed in Chiang Rai province, near the epicenter of the quake. 
http://kimedia.blogspot.com/2014/05/thai-earth-quake.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7207_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-QTzMQBl5s-c/U2lvI_u1ymI/AAAAAAAFhlQ/ffBUXfv8QW8/w426-h240/10178105_722318331153325_6282396550995680271_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>