<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:49:24" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/104476427991703947407/albums/5974434562186331697/5974434564795654818</link><title>John Gruber's style guide succinctly explaining why the use of punctuation in the name of Walt Mosberg's new tech website, Re/code, can be confusing.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ETdzf823FgM/Uul0lTB14qI/AAAAAAAAWFc/Hkc7UbP4uck/w426-h237/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-01-29%2Bat%2B21.36.58.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/111474406259561102151/albums/5789993184849011041/5789993184512919266</link><title>An an Oatmeal-loving, semicolon-wielding Godzilla myself, I thought I should  share The Oatmeal Semicolon Poster, A guide to the most feared punctuation on earth ... http://theoatmeal.com/comics/semicolon 
:-)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_02_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-IRPqHFz1E48/UFowH-bTRuI/AAAAAAAAbAM/0rpnM-rcy64/w426-h237/Screen%2Bshot%2B2012-09-19%2Bat%2B4.49.41%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/113332630920899214863/albums/5968892805959327505/5968892809839461410?sqi=102094410756336687390&amp;sqsi=99e5a756-6455-4641-b767-ac441d24b715</link><title>New Year’s Eve Celebration Captured in Breathtaking Timelapse 
http://goo.gl/YRYqik 

A New Years Eve celebration perhaps culturally is more widely observed during the holiday season, the occasion being more of a calendar event and nothing else. For others, New Years Eve brings a fitting punctuation to ending the holiday season, capping off weeks of parties and get-togethers. It is after all, the beginning of all beginnings, another new year. Very few places in the world perhaps, can lay claim to being a New Years Eve attraction as Times Square in New York. 

#timelapsevideo   #timelapsephotography   #timessquare  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9rcjypKBMSg/UtXEYtDdRCI/AAAAAAAAOsY/uHjsfxo0SvA/w426-h239/times-square-new-years-eve.tiff</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/116721517328428480443/albums/5685995838717490161/5685995836692741778</link><title>Do you have architect friends, family, or clients? Or perhaps trying to get noticed by one? This might come in handy. 

"As a bonus service to our friends and clients, we thought it appropriate to provide this guide chart on: How To Talk With An Architect 

Those of you who are not school-trained in architecture will find this invaluable in conversing with designers and governmental authorities. Just think of any 4-digit number (say 2447), consult this handy chart, and read off the similarly numbered phrases from Columns A, B, C, and D. For example, 2447 = "Aesthetically speaking the initial stage of conceptual development necessitates that urgent considerations be made of the philosophy of commonality and standardization." 

Never mind what it means, just use it and watch the way you stop conversation. You can compose entire speeches or profound reports just by using varied number combinations. (Now you know 1 of my secrets to delivering my lectures). 

As you become more proficient in its use, you may wish to experiment with varying column sequences, i.e., BADC, CBAD, etc. However, these advanced configurations are not recommended for beginners as they require sophisticated dexterity with punctuation."﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_04_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-LNP1ZebN1QI/Tui3FnhrvpI/AAAAAAAAC2I/clKUSkJuOAQ/w426-h329/How%2BTo%2BTalk%2BWith%2BAn%2BArchitect%2BChart.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/107402358665832470529/albums/5978699144586387377/5978699149927720946</link><title>Common writing mistakes to avoid 

You may be armed with the world's most interesting story, but if you aren't careful with the more technical side of writing, the power of your story will fall short. 

Styles vary from person to person which is why reading and writing is interesting. Every language, however, has its own rules for grammar and punctuation. These rules are, for the most part, standardized. While you rebels out there might cringe at any notion of standard, meeting certain expectations in your writing is a good thing. 

Writing that is free of basic grammatical and punctuation errors can communicate a degree of intelligence or authority. More importantly though, when aspects are standard, they become expectations. Defying those expectations unnecessarily or thoughtlessly (i.e. technical errors in writing) is distracting from your message. Unless your purpose is to highlight that specific error, you just succeeded in calling attention away from your intended message. 

We make mistakes, and that's why we look over writing again. We live in a mobile world and in the world of iPhone autocorrect, and that's why we glance over our message before hitting Send. Sometimes we're in a rush on Google+ and share a post rifled with mistakes, and that's why we love the Edit option. 

Even in grammar, rules have exceptions, but Gini Dietrich of the OPEN forum mentions eight mistakes that you should never make again. She hits the following: 

affect/effect 
impact 
there/their/they're 
care less 
irregardless 
your/you're 
fewer/less 
punctuation inside/outside quotation marks 

Gini Dietrich also notes that if you don't have a copy of The Elements of Style, you should find one. There's an older version by William Strunk available for free in the Kindle store. The later and more popular editions that EB White revised (commonly known as 'Strunk and White's') will set you back $3.00 for an electronic copy and less than $5.00 (plus shipping) for a hard copy. It's very much worth it. 

'8 Common Grammar Mistakes You Should Never Make Again': http://j.mp/1iPsMvj 

BONUS: While we're at it, be sure to avoid these other common mistakes as well: 

than vs then 
lose vs loose 
supposably 
aggravate vs irritate 

HT +Guy Kawasaki 
#communication   #grammar   #ns   #writing  ﻿

Meer lezen (57 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-UqHLEeqNero/UvibM0pfJ_I/AAAAAAAADvk/E-QevM0vEaM/w426-h331/quotation-marks%255B1%255D.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/105677707057444177691/albums/5818635338594754049/5818635339913242386</link><title>Do You Want to Learn About the Spiritual World(你想了解靈界嗎) 

                                           2010-05-24 師父開示 
                                     MESSAGES FROM OSIFU 
                                              the Spiritual World 

2010-05-24 下午師父開示：靈界、通靈、不動心、正法大道、回歸之路〇sifu 15:15:49 

Teachings given by Osifu in the afternoon of May 24th 2012: Keywords: The spirit world, Psychic, keep the mind motionless, the Great Way of Proper Dharma, the Path for Returning 

靈界的問題很複雜，正能量、負能量都有。 

The spirit world is very complex, where there is both positive energy and negative energy. 

靈界的問題很複雜，正信息、負信息都有。 

The spirit world is very complex, where there is both positive information and negative information. 

靈界的問題很複雜，正力量、邪力量都有。 

The spirit world is very complex, where there are both positive forces and evil forces. 

靈界的複雜遠遠超過人間。 

The complexity of the spirit world is far more than that of the human world. 

靈界的複雜遠遠超過肉眼可見的世界。 

The complexity of the spirit world is far more than that of the visible world. 

靈界的複雜遠遠超過人類所能思維。 

The complexity of the spirit world is far more beyond the human's thinking. 

靈界的複雜往往吞沒很多修行人，包括一些所謂的高人。 

The complexity of the spirit world tends to engulf many cultivators including some so called superiors. 

師父再點一點，靈界的問題。你們看清路、目標明、方向準、心法正，腳下實，一定要走穩！ 

Osifu would like to reveal some issues about the spirit world again. You should look into your path, make clear goal, steer accurate direction, stay in righteous mind-method, step on solid ground and walk steadily! 

你們根基好，修到一定層次，靈界的大門就會打開。 

All of you have good groundwork and when a certain level is achieved, the door of spirit world will be opened for you. 

靈界的大門打開是好事，也是壞事。 

The opening of the spirit world is a good thing but a bad thing as well. 

就像窗子打開，新鮮空氣陽光可以進來，蒼蠅蚊子灰塵也可以進來。在你沒有足夠定力、開啟智慧之前，打開靈界大門是很危險的。 

It is like once the window is opened, the fresh air and sunlight can come in, while the flies, mosquitoes and the dust will also come in. It is very dangerous to open the door to the spirit world before you have enough Samadhi power and wisdom. 

真修行人，不可不慎！ 

A real cultivator cannot be careless about it! 

今天師父進一步點破靈界。 

Today Osifu further reveals the mystery of the spirit world bluntly. 

靈界並不神秘，因為你也有靈。因為你從來沒有停止過和靈界能量信息的交換。你或者說，沒有呀？ 

The spirit world is not mysterious at all because you also have spirit; because you've never stopped the energy-information exchange with the spirit world. Perhaps you may say, is that so? 

呵呵，你的夢、你的感應、你的直覺、你的靈感、你的預知等等，無一不是你和靈界的傳感、共振。 

Well, your dreams, your response, your intuition, your inspiration, your foresight and so on, none of these are not your information channeling and vibration with the spirit world. 

現在，師父給你點破何謂靈界。 

Now, Osifu rev​​eals to you bluntly what the spirit world is. 

靈界是肉眼不可見的生靈形成的能量場。 

The spirit world is an energy field formed by creatures that is invisible to the physical eyes. 

師父稱之為陰態生靈，或者稱為無形、隱態、多維次生靈，說法不同而已。 

Osifu calls it beings of Yin state, or calls it the invisible, beings of hidden state, multi-dimensional beings. These are just different versions. 

陰態生靈，之所以神秘就是因為：肉眼不可見；天眼難全見；見了不可捉摸；變幻莫測；無量無邊。 

The mystery of beings of Yin state is because that they are invisible to the physical eyes; it is hard to see them all with the third eye; they are unpredictable even if you can see them; they are capricious and limitless. 

人類現有智識、智能、科技無法研究印證陰態世界的千萬億分之一。 

The humankind cannot use the existing intellectual knowledge, intellectual ability, science and technology to capture one quadrillionth of the world of Yin state. 

說白了，人類現有智識、智能、科技還無法捕捉到陰態世界中的低層次生靈--鬼的影像。更難做到與之交流、對話。高層次生靈，人類更是望塵莫及 。 

Frankly speaking, the humankind cannot use the existing intellectual knowledge, intellectual ability, science and technology even to capture the ghost images —low level beings of Yin state, it is more difficult to start a conversation or dialogue with them. Let alone a conversation with the high level beings. 

有的人就問了，現在高科技做不到和陰態生靈的溝通交流，為何很多人能做到？ 

Some people may ask that the humankind cannot manage to use the existing high-tech to communicate with beings of Yin state, why can so many people do that? 
這就是所謂的“通靈人”。 

These are so called "psychic." 

所謂的“通靈人”非常複雜，層次不一。 

The so-called "psychics" are very complex with various levels. 

現在，人間的通靈人多數為附體通、鬼通、魔通，有的是精神病、精神分裂症、臆想。 

Currently, the majority of the human psychics are possessed by ghosts, demons, and some of them are patients suffering from mental illness, schizophrenia and hypochondria. 

真正通過今生今世艱苦修煉而來的修得通，非常少。猶如珍寶。 

There are very few psychics who gain their psychic abilities through hard cultivati​​on in this lifetime, which is as few as the priceless treasure. 

師父希望自己的弟子無所求而自得神通，通過自己艱苦修煉自然而然出現神通，並且有了神通只把神通作為救人度人的善巧方便，而不能用來撈取名聞利養、五欲六塵。 

Osifu hopes that his followers pursue nothing but naturally gain the supernatural powers through their own hard cultivati​​on, and use their supernatural powers only as skillful means to rescue and help people, and don't use them as tools to fish for fame and profits, the Five Desires and Six External Objects. 

呵呵人類、人一直以來都想和靈界溝通，目的是什麼呢？ 

Well, the humankind, humans always wanted to communicate with the spirit world, what is the purpose of it? 

靈界一直以來也想和人類、人溝通，為什麼呢？ 

The spirit world always wanted to communicate with the humankind and humans, why? 

呵呵 佛有佛的目的。 

Well, the Buddhas have Buddhas' purpose. 

菩薩有菩薩的目的。 

The Bodhisattvas have Bodhisattvas' purpose. 

神有神的目的。 

The Deities have Deities' purpose. 

仙有仙的目的。 

The Immortals have Immortals' purpose. 

鬼有鬼的目的。 

The ghosts have ghost's purpose. 

魔有魔的目的。 

The devils have devils' purpose. 

怪有怪的目的。 

The monsters have monsters' purpose. 

精有精的目的。 

The sprites have sprites' purpose. 

外星生靈有外星生靈的目的。 

The aliens have aliens' purpose. 

多維次生靈和人類和人溝通也是各有目的。 

The multidimensional beings also have their purposes to communicate with the humankind and humans. 

呵呵 各有各的盤算。各有各得算盤。 

Well, each has his own calculations. Each has his own thinking. 

呵呵若是如此單純，大救度就不會等到今天。 

Well, If it were so simple, the Great Salvation would not have to wait until today. 

若是如此同心，大回歸就不會等到今天。 

If it were so one-heart concerted, the Great Returning would not have to wait until today. 

若是如此和諧，大同修就不會等到今天。 

If it were so harmonious, the Great Cultivati​​on would not have to wait until today. 

呵呵對待大救度的意見，神佛仙真聖已經空前統一。 

Well, As for the Great Salvation, views of the Divinities, Buddhas, Immortals, Allahs and Sages have been unprecedented unified. 

所以，接到神佛仙真聖關於支持大救度的信息，非常一致。都表態全力支持。 

Therefore, messages received from them about supporting the Great Salvation are very consistent. All of them declare full support. 

神佛仙真聖是支持大救度的正面力量、陽性能量、正信息。 

The Divinities, Buddhas, Immortals, Allahs and Sages are the positive forces, positive energy and positive information that support the Great Salvation. 

神佛仙真聖也在無形中幫助有緣人修煉上層次。 

The Divinities, Buddhas, Immortals, Allahs and Sages are also invisibly helping all predestined friends to cultivate for higher levels. 

與此同時，與之對應的邪勢力、負信息、負能量。也在時時干擾修行人、阻礙大救度。 

Meanwhile, the corresponding evil forces, negative information, negative energy are also discomposing cultivators and hindering the Great Salvation. 

你們、我們都處在這麼一個超級複雜的能量場中。 

You, we are all in such a super-complex energy field. 

我們與佛相應，就接收到了佛的能量信息。 

Responding to Buddhas, we receive the Buddhas' energy and information. 

倘若與魔相應，就接收到了魔的能量信息。 

If responding to demons, we receive the demons' energy and information. 

倘若與鬼相應，就接收到了鬼的能量信息。 

If responding to ghosts, we receive the ghosts' energy and information. 

倘若與神相應，就接收到了神的能量信息。 

If responding to deities, we receive the deities' energy and information. 

倘若與精怪相應，就接收到了精怪的能量信息。 

If responding to deities, we receive the deities' energy and information. 

好一個龐雜的能量信息場！ 

What a complicated energy-information field! 

師父打一個比喻，就像手機一樣。 

Osifu would like to make an analogy, which is somewhat like a cell phone. 

你可以給地痞流氓通電話。 

You may call bandits and gangsters. 

你可以登錄佛教網站。 

You may log on the Buddhism websites. 

你可以登錄黃色網站。 

You may log in to pornographic websites. 

你的手機處在一個龐雜的能量信息場中，被電磁波重重交織覆蓋。 

Your mobile phone is in a complex energy-information field and is covered by heavy and intertwined electromagnetic waves. 

你的手機時刻都有“當下”，當下你的手機處於什麼狀態，好比你的心態。 

Your mobile phone has "the present moment" all the time. What state your phone is at the present moment is like your mentality 

選擇、決策的權利在你自己，而不在外在。 

The choice or decision-making rights depend on your own mind rather than the external world. 

師父常說“時時與佛相應、時時得佛加持”。 

Osifu often says: "always responding to Buddhas, always have the Buddhas' blessing." 

每一個眾生，都具有佛性，同樣也具有魔性。 

Every living being has both Buddha-nature and Demon-nature. 

在我們手機的周圍充滿了黃色網站的電磁波，我們不去登錄，這些電磁波對我們來說還會有乾擾嗎？ 

Our mobile phones are surrounded by electromagnetic waves of pornographic websites, if we do not log in to them, will the electromagnetic waves still bring interference for us? 

本來，一切的一切都是虛幻。 

In fact, everything of all is illusory. 

你執著了動心了，它就有。 

It exists once you cling to it and then have your mind tempted. 

你不執著不動心，當下即空。 

If you don't abide in it and keep your mind unmoved, it is empty instantly. 

所以，解決問題的辦法、方法、法寶，都在你的心裡。 

So the solution, method, magic weapons to problems is in your heart. 

密碼和鑰匙就是你的心。 

The password and key is your mind. 

說到這裡，這個問題也算講透徹了。 

Here, this issue can be discoursed thoroughly. 

但師父，再強調一點。 

But Osifu would like to stress one point again. 

即使你看到、聽到、感應到是佛菩薩給你傳感、靈感、信息、能量、法寶也不可執著動心。 

Even If you see, hear and feel that the Buddhas and Bodhisattvas who channel you, or transmit inspiration, messages, energy or magic weapons, you should not cling to that and have your mind tempted. 

你一動心，又上當了。 

You will fall into traps once you have your mind tempted. 

禪宗一句話說得很好“佛來佛斬魔來魔斬”。 

There is a good saying in Zen school "chop Buddhas when the Buddhas come, chop demons when the demons come." 

心經金剛經說得更好，一定要堅持每日必誦。 

Heart Sutra and Diamond Sutra make better points, so you must persevere with daily compulsory recitation. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執自己或宣揚自己是某佛某菩薩某神某仙某聖某真再來者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or publicize that he or she is a reinc​​arnation of some Buddha, Bodhisattva, Deity, Immortal, Sage or Allah are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執〇sifu或宣揚〇sifu是某佛某菩薩某神某仙某聖某真再來者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or publicize that Osifu is a reinc​​arnation of some Buddha, Bodhisattva, Deity, Immortal, Sage or Allah are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執自己或宣揚自己具有神通者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or publicize that he or she has supernatural powers are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執〇sifu或宣揚〇sifu具有神通者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or publicize that Osifu has supernatural powers are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執或追求邪法小術者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or pursue evil teachings and small magic are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執或追求靈通感應者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or pursue spiritual penetrations or telepathy are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執或追求名聞利養者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or pursue fame and profits are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執或追求五欲六塵者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or pursue the Five Desires and Six External Objects are not Osifu's disciples. 

師父今天再咐囑一遍，妄執或追求酒色財氣者，非吾弟子。 

Today Osifu would like to exhort you once again. Those who falsely cling to or pursue wine， women， avarice and pride are not Osifu's disciples. 

依教奉行 才有資格做弟子。 

Only those who perform in accordance with teachings are eligible to be Osifu's disciples. 

師父要一再咐囑、告誡眾弟子的太多太多。 

Osifu has too much to repeatedly exhort and warn all disciples. 

奈何，說多了也不濟事。點到為止吧！ 

Nonetheless, too much exhortation would not make much sense, so it would be better to just mention it. 

呵呵“迷時師度悟時自度”，各自珍重吧！ 

Well "When one is in delusion, a master is needed to guide him; while one realizes the delusion, he needs to guide himself," each of you treasures it yourself! 

不要毀了自己的好根基，那可是多生歷劫積累來的。 

Don't ruin your good groundwork that has been cultivated and accumulated since many lifetimes and kalpas. 

不要毀了自己的好機緣，那可是多生歷劫修積來的。 

Don't ruin your good opportunity that has been cultivated and accumulated since many lifetimes and kalpas. 

呵呵有的弟子問，“正法大道是什麼？怎麼從來沒聽師父講？” 

Well, Some follower asked, "What is the Great Way of Proper Dharma? Why have I never heard Osifu talking about it?" 

師父笑了 

Osifu laughed. 

好可愛的弟子。 

Such a cute follower! 

希望，眾弟子有緣人每天必看圓滿閣群聊天記錄，持之以恆。 

Hope all followers and predestined friends read the group chatting records of the Perfection Loft every day and keep perseverance at it. 

正法大道的經典一直在書寫。 

The classics of the Great Way of Proper Dharma have been being written. 

正法大道這是一本寫在師父心里和你們心裡的天書。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a heavenly book written in Osifu's heart and yours. 

正法大道這是一本寫在師父心里和你們心裡的佛書。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a Buddhism book written in Osifu's heart and yours. 

正法大道這是一條在師父心裡也在你們心裡的天路。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a way leading to heaven written in Osifu's heart and yours. 

正法大道這是一條在師父心裡也在你們心裡的佛路。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a way leading to achieve the Buddhahood written in Osifu's heart and yours. 

正法大道是通往西方極樂世界的回歸之路。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a returning path leading to the Western Land of Ultimate Bliss. 

正法大道是通往佛心性海的回歸之路。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a returning path leading to the Buddha-source and Nature Ocean. 

正法大道 是通往宙心的回歸之路。 

The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a returning path leading to the Cosmic Source. 

呵呵正法大道究其本質就是一條路、一條大道。 

Well, The Great Way of Proper Dharma is a Path, an Avenue by nature. 

一弟子:師父自己修煉得來的通與妖通附體通有何區別呀？ 

Some follower: Osifu, what are the differences between supernatural powers that obtained through one's own diligent cultivati​​on and that possessed by demons or foreign souls? 

〇sifu 17:13:14 
弟子 繼續精進，無所求而自得。 

Osifu: dear follower, keep on cultivati​​ng diligently! Pursue nothing and gain naturally! 

無我 No ego 
無欲 No desire 
無為 No intention 
無求 No seeking 
無爭 No fighting 
清淨 Purity 
平等 Equality 
正覺 Awareness 
即正 It is the proper enlightenment. 
即覺 It is the proper awareness 
即佛 It is the Buddha 

反之有我、有欲、有為、有求、有爭、不淨、分別，即邪、即迷、即魔。 

On the contrary, ego, desire, intention, seeking, fighting, non-purity, discrimination, is the evil, is the delusion, is the demon. 

我們發言也要嚴謹負責，不要使用錯別字，最好用對標點符號。對大家、對眾生負責。 

We should be rigorous and responsible for our speeches, don't type the words wrong and had better use the punctuation mark right; be responsible to everybody and all living beings. 

我們就是在寫經典，而且是一次性寫成。 

We are writing scriptures, and in a way of complete-in-one-time. 

盡心盡力做到完美、圓滿。 

Try our utmost effort to make it the most perfect and successful. 

時空不會倒流，我們每說一句話、每寫一個字、每做一件事、每走一步路，都在成為歷史。 

The time-space will never flow back, and every word of our speeches, every word we write, everything we do and every step of our progress are becoming the history. 

好的，利益人天、普濟萬靈的，會萬古流芳。 

The good will benefit both the humans and celestial beings, and will bring bliss to all living beings, which will last forever. 

惡的，傷天害理、禍害萬靈的，會遺臭萬年。 

The evil will offend both the heaven and the law, and will bring scourge to all living beings, which will go down in history as a symbol of infamy. 

時時觀照自己 

Always observe ourselves. 

勿以善小而不為，勿以惡小而為之。 

Do not think any virtue trivial, and so neglect it; do not think any vice trivial, and so practice it. 

歷史不僅僅會記住大人物，歷史也同樣會記住小人物。因為，歷史面前人人平等。 

History will not only remember the big shots, but also the small potatoes as everyone is equal before the history. 
============================================================================================== 

〇 sifu found Segment in the world to help the Earth rose 108 the cosmic center angel . If you look 〇 sifu message and feel Soul has touched . Maybe you can found us ！ 

——The cosmic center angel 〇bobe 

〇sifu在尋找分部在全球的108位幫助地球揚升的宙心使者，如果當你看到〇sifu的信息心靈有所觸動，請主動聯繫我們！ 

——宙心使者〇bobe 

============================================================================================== 
Contact 〇sifu： 
〇sifu's student： ocindy1977@msn.cn, chicheng1980@hotmail.com, oobobe@live.com 

1.来自〇sifu的信息(1.Messages from 〇sifu ): 
http://www.osifu.net 

2.谷歌专页: (2.G+ Page): 
https://plus.google.com/105677707057444177691 

3.宇宙高维次生灵对地球人类2012年的帮助(3.The universe of high-dimensional creatures of our help in 2012 ): 
http://ocindy-lydia.blogspot.com/ 

4.宇宙高维次提升能量的方法。--视频(4.The universe of high-dimensional approach to enhance energy --you tube): 
http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCALSyZTSs0Oea8YR2zkz1Fw?feature=watch 

5.Obobe FB(5.Obobe FB): 
http://www.facebook.com/oobobe 

6.我们的face book群组(6.Welcome to our facebook group): 
http://www.facebook.com/groups/211563415625916/ 

7.Obobe G+(7.Obobe G+): 
https://plus.google.com/100486970326885897582/posts 

8.Obobe WP(8.Obobe WP): 
http://obobe.wordpress.com/﻿

Meer lezen (672 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vn8DzfxnTTE/UL_yA2EQJxI/AAAAAAAACRw/ct8Vy5yCPVg/w426-h320/Parama_padam.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/118222582858805158414/albums/5888205738325187265/5888205739733979730?authkey=CLmU6saEuLT5ugE</link><title>a pretty nice summary about current console wars. 
http://www.escapistmagazine.com/videos/view/zero-punctuation/7417-Next-Gen-Buyers-Guide﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_07_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-djLOhB8eBjc/Ubcb7FlCklI/AAAAAAAADXo/HeLIuWnGkrg/w426-h237/yahtzee-consoles.PNG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/101900719299149038656/albums/5949561480311309585/5949561481155683122</link><title>A #Blogger's Ultimate Guide to Avoid Looking Stupid: Punctuation [infographic] 

Found at http://buff.ly/18Qwm22﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Go-gI8fjLjs/UpEWpR2hozI/AAAAAAAAAqI/9MZ65dzShcI/w426-h930/1e04e265-938c-46fa-9748-e2c71d7c615c</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/115692328428363633787/albums/5919631524899030753/5919631525482860770?authkey=CKHnqY3CxOmUvAE</link><title>It’s all in the Punctuation 

An English professor wrote the words, ‘Woman without her man is nothing’ on the board and told his students to punctuate it correctly. 

The men wrote: ‘Woman, without her man, is nothing.’ 

The women wrote: ‘Woman: Without her, man is nothing.’ 

Quraan 9:70: And the believers, men and women, are protecting friends one of another… 

This Reminds Me Of So MAny Tafsir Over Which This Ummah Is Divided Today Because Of This Same " *PUNCTUATION " . 

We Must Know That Punctuations In Al Qur'aan Did *NOT COME from ALLAH, Djebreel (allahi wa salaam) And Nabi (salla allahu allahi wa salaam). 

Those Who Are Wrong Sill Earn  A Point As For Those Who Are Right ; Earns Two Points. 

ALLAH Does Not Neglect Our Efforts So Why Should We Be FIGHTING Each Other Calling Each Other " *Kafir* " ? 

May ALLAH Guide Us All Aright Aameen.﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-0SCviYwSJo8/UibBgkWcEOI/AAAAAAAC528/-QyE9K91Jz4/w426-h413/1005821_629976960376523_1792008648_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7211-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/punctuation%20guide/photos/109966083662126719849/albums/5773376287736864769/5927375415305349682</link><title>Well, we don't have to guess how excited you were when you woke up this morning. Yes, it's Christmas for word nerds! Happy NATIONAL PUNCTUATION DAY! (Actually, it was yesterday, but it's a US event so we're celebrating with our American friends today.) Copy/paste the hashtag #NationalPunctuationDay into the search bar to lose yourself in a plethora of punctuation memes and strident defences of the Oxford comma. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7211_10_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-9hUp20MnlTs/UkJEiR-oqjI/AAAAAAAAALs/aBxw7N01koQ/w426-h343/Thats_ec5db2_1018630.gif</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>