<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:04:43" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/112907692856486407871/albums/5821329071631663089/5821329071540731362?authkey=CMaOsJXWrNvPHg</link><title>Like basal cell carcinoma, sun exposure is a common cause of squamous cell carcinoma, and thus, this type of skin cancer often appears on parts of the body exposed to the sun. 

Squamous cell carcinomas often grow more quickly than basal cell carcinomas, and as such are a more aggressive type of cancer.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Wgh1QiqJpcU/UMmD8qXW_eI/AAAAAAAAAho/7EYm0C7dfyE/w426-h320/9947.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/112907692856486407871/albums/5821693751333538145/5821693758112707842?authkey=COzLs8akhMjMLA</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma sometimes spreads to the fatty tissue underneath the epidermis, and from there can spread to other sites in the body. 

You cannot control if you get skin cancer, or what type, but you can reduce your risk by wearing sunblock, sunglasses, sun protecting clothing and hats in the sun.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Kl1K7B-CZ8s/UMrPoNtqtQI/AAAAAAAAAiI/dJyqG8g6nY0/w426-h635/2345185-218417-young-smiling-woman-wearing-sunglasses-and-relaxing-at-the-beach.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/117908596108692972115/albums/5927435374412153777/5927435380696771154?sqi=103495304304122247711&amp;sqsi=e3a92c73-2a8d-4332-8335-bcef7b12322b</link><title>Basal cell carcinoma vs Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin.  Which of the two is more associated with organ tx patients?  Check it out in this table.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_03_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-4E3e-ZgAIe8/UkJ7EueDalI/AAAAAAAABmo/q1Q3NiG7W0o/w426-h237/BCC%2Bvs%2BSCC%2Bof%2BSkin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/117432197458595992096/albums/5989964623564511489/5989964621263526834</link><title>Detection of #HPV in head and neck #squamous-cell carcinoma. #NewVideo 

http://www.jove.com/video/51426/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Om0dD1oLirs/UyChFjuR27I/AAAAAAAAAcg/_KvbtQ-XVkQ/w426-h239/4QQI5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/117019963265323023762/albums/5925051507213110001/5925051515254850786?authkey=CMyw5d2pmJyIogE</link><title>Clinical Applications of The Cancer Genome Atlas Project (TCGA) for Squamous Cell Lung Carcinoma #carcinoma 

Very little progress has been made in the treatment of patients with metastatic squamous cell lung cancer over the past 2 decades. Identification of novel molecular alterations for targeted therapies is necessary to improve outcomes. Advances in genomic technology have now made it possible to analyze the genomic landscape of tumor tissues comprehensively. 

http://www.cancernetwork.com/display/article/10165/2157878?cid=G+﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_05_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-9yUF1L-Zs9o/UjoC9fqnxOI/AAAAAAAABRs/hEVrbhX8l_A/w426-h385/image_gallery.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/104240157078340595548/albums/5815191450892650833/5815191449831834226</link><title>Benign Lichenoid Keratoses Mimicking Squamous and Basal Cell Carcinoma 

During a periodic recall examination, a 63-year-old man was found to have an asymptomatic, erythematous, scaling plaque on the postero-lateral aspect of the left arm. Aside from a few routine actinic keratoses on the face, the rest of the cutaneous inspection was unremarkable. 

http://www.consultantlive.com/dermclinic/content/article/10162/2111613?cid=G+﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-u0HRBM0lLHE/ULO10DwdgnI/AAAAAAAAANY/3jvuZVjSBgk/w426-h268/Oct_12Case6b.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/108193598632605977933/albums/5792143230115815809/5792143232821813362</link><title>Types of Bladder Cancer 
The main types of bladder cancer are named for the type of cells that become cancerous. The most common is transitional cell carcinoma, which begins in the cells that line the inside of the bladder. Squamous cell carcinoma and adenocarcinoma are much less common.  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-F4YBk5pOCAs/UGHTlQiG4HI/AAAAAAAAA-g/ZmweTjY1Rh8/w426-h289/25.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/104984516469461796485/albums/5841221712233080097/5841221715370579842?authkey=CL3ulYW3q8vLnAE</link><title>A new study finds that some cancer mutations slow tumor growth, possibly offering a new way to treat the disease. http://mitne.ws/TAMzFK 

(Image: A scanning electron micrograph of a squamous cell carcinoma, a type of skin cancer. The cell has been frozen and split open to reveal its nucleus. Credit: Anne Weston, LRI, CRUK. Wellcome Images)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-vtfQDbYRg9M/URAwM7b2F4I/AAAAAAAABdw/7NSuhkEAeuw/w426-h237/gplus-cn.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/117715241857029325637/albums/5911314517870905281/5911314520905236946</link><title>#saffron 

Initial research suggests that carotenoids present in saffron are anticarcinogenic (cancer-suppressing),anti-mutagenic (mutation-preventing), and immunomodulatory. Dimethylcrocetin, the compound thought responsible for these effects, counters a wide range of murine (rodent) tumours and human leukaemia cell lines. Saffron extract also delays ascites tumour growth, delays papilloma carcinogenesis, inhibits squamous cell carcinoma, and decreases soft tissue sarcoma incidence in treated mice. Researchers theorise that, based on the results of thymidine-uptake studies, such anticancer activity is best attributed to dimethylcrocetin's disruption of the DNA-binding ability of a class of enzymes known as type II topoisomerases. As topoisomerases play a key role in managing DNA topology, the malignant cells are less successful in synthesizing or replicating their own DNA. 
Saffron's pharmacological effects on malignant tumours have been documented in several studies: it extends the lives of mice that are intraperitoneally impregnated with transplanted sarcomas, namely, samples of S-180, Dalton's lymphoma ascites (DLA), and Ehrlich ascites carcinoma (EAC) tumours. Researchers followed this by orally administering 200 mg (0.0071 oz) of saffron extract for each kg of mouse body weight. As a result the life spans of the tumour-bearing mice were respectively altered to 111.0%, 83.5%, and 112.5% of the baseline or reference span. Researchers also discovered that saffron extract exhibits cytotoxicity in relation to DLA, EAC, P38B, and S-180 tumour cell lines cultured in vitro. 
Besides wound-healing and anticancer properties, saffron is also an antioxidant. This means that, as an "anti-aging" agent, it neutralises free radicals. Methanol extractions of saffron neutralise at high rates the DPPH (IUPAC nomenclature: 1,1-diphenyl-2-picrylhydrazyl) radicals. This occurred via vigorous proton donation to DPPH by two of saffron's active agents, safranal and crocin. At concentrations of 500 and 1000 ppm, crocin studies showed neutralisation of 50% and 65% of radicals, respectively. Safranal displayed a lesser rate of radical neutralisation than crocin. Such findings give saffron extracts promise as an ingredient for use as an antioxidant in pharmaceuticals, cosmetics, and as a food supplement.Antidepressant effects have been demonstrated.﻿

Meer lezen (35 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-XE0jtgJi-Xg/Ugk1PL4qQdI/AAAAAAAAKyo/9NTW25Wt2Y8/w426-h570/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7215-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/squamous%20cell%20carcinoma/photos/114258404620606187735/albums/5935418524498503777/5935418526645410082</link><title>The answer to yesterday's "What's Your Diagnosis?" is Squamous Cell Carcinoma of the third eyelid. 

Squamous Cell Carcinoma (SCC) is the most common cancer found in or around the eye in horses. SCC often presents looking "wart-like". Horses with non-pigmented third eyelids are especially at risk for this locally based neoplasm. Treatment is typically surgical excision and followed up with cryotherapy. Referral to a veterinary ophthalmology specialist may be necessary in some cases.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7215_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-gm62zIeumIU/Ul7Xs-n42SI/AAAAAAAAAng/66JmhywE9Rc/w426-h319/3rvTV.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>