<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 17:26:26" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/117275841617008405590/albums/6012938755345037857/6015201532691530562</link><title>Study Reveals Salmonella’s Hideout Strategy The body’s innate immune system is a first line of defense, intent on sensing invading pathogens and wiping them out before they can cause harm. It should not be surprising then that bacteria hav 

\- See more at: http://globalbiodefense.com/2014/05/19/study-reveals-salmonellas-hideout-strategy/ 

#salmonella   #foodsafety  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_01_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-SQ3oB6jf14g/U3pJ7JB2w0I/AAAAAAAAAtI/VHoqMMMvJb4/w426-h412/salmonella_typhi_cdc.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/113910389916975197051/albums/5828738635059288417/5830892746329812338?authkey=CKHqqbqyvavL8QE</link><title>Study Discovers New Salmonella ‘Superbug’ -According to a study from French researchers, salmonella reports from England, Wales, France, Denmark and the US have demonstrated a new strain of salmonella with a high resistance to antimicrobial treatment. 

The salmonella strain is named S. Kentucky and has infected 489 patients between... - http://www.yourwellness.com/2013/01/study-discovers-new-salmonella-superbug/-Yourwellness﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-jtQRduZXw4U/UOt-DzRj7XI/AAAAAAAACjs/yKcwXjIO6Bk/w426-h241/Study-Discovers-New-Salmonella-%25E2%2580%2598Superbug%25E2%2580%2599-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/107660875906928406568/albums/5820277638424108625/5820645076532517266?authkey=CLif_ar7m6aptgE</link><title>Salmonella - Just what every kid wants for Christmas! 

Another awesome +Secret Santa gift that arrived - a gigantic plushie microbe. Kidlet is totally in love, it's her new favourite snuggle toy to sleep with - Salmonella has even ousted Mia the stuffed cat that's been her sleep-comfort-toy for several years! Because honestly, who wouldn't want to snuggle up with salmonella at bedtime? 

#secretsanta #santagift  http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/3U3T0YWL3ZXJQ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-0SqSef0tF8g/UMcV26ZY2ZI/AAAAAAAAcOs/VHCUJA7RTrI/w426-h568/09%2Bsalmonella.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/106772544387169323774/albums/5735453035928446929/5735453042248396018</link><title>UC Santa Barbara researchers have discovered Salmonella bacteria that are up to 100 times more capable of causing disease. Their findings may help prevent food poisoning outbreaks that continue to plague public health and the food industry. 
These "hypervirulent" bugs can override vaccines and pose a risk to food safety –– and mitigation efforts are currently under way. 

Previous strategies to find the more dangerous bugs were unsuccessful since they behave like a "Trojan Horse"— exposing their weapons only when causing disease — but looking much like their less-virulent cousins in the environment. 

Now that scientists know what to look for, they are developing methods to discriminate them from their less-virulent cousins. The researchers have been successful in forcing the bacteria to reveal their weapons in the laboratory –– the first step in combating them. 

Salmonella, found virtually everywhere, is the most common cause of foodborne illness in the United States. According to the researchers, the emergence of more powerful strains could eventually overtax the current public health system, which regularly deals with outbreaks from tainted food. Currently, the system is coping with an outbreak that has sickened more than 100 people in 20 states. 

Image: Salmonella typhimurium (red) invades cultured human cells in this color-enhanced scanning electron micrograph. 
Credit: Rocky Mountain Laboratories, NIAID, NIH 

Source: http://www.ia.ucsb.edu/pa/display.aspx?pkey=2692﻿

Meer lezen (28 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-yJrbKf13JMg/T5hsJ3kmLPI/AAAAAAAAMIs/aRcELWGoUMk/w426-h358/image.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/109102265263486263584/albums/5730853541955858353/5730853541737337090</link><title>Method Developed to Detect Stealthy, Hypervirulent Salmonella Strains http://goo.gl/R8KAo 

A recent discovery of "hypervirulent" Salmonella bacteria has given UC Santa Barbara researchers Michael Mahan and Douglas Heithoff a means to potentially prevent food poisoning outbreaks from these particularly powerful strains. 

Salmonella is the most common cause of infection, hospitalization, and death due to foodborne illness in the U.S. This burden may continue to worsen due to the emergence of new strains that would tax current health-control efforts. To address this problem, researchers sought out –– and found –– hypervirulent strains that present a potential risk to food safety and the livestock industry. 
You can read and cite the original research paper here http://goo.gl/WhTLB 

www.facebook.com/microbiologynews 
~﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-kGSCwh0yQNA/T4gU7s8LEQI/AAAAAAAAA1s/U-1OmWjLv0o/w426-h358/salmonella.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/111371195521214299537/albums/5829329335267934913/5829329342126736034?authkey=CPig2-eW-NPgKw</link><title>Salmonella is one of the most common foodborne pathogens &amp; causes of foodborne illness. The Solution - the 3M™ Molecular Detection Assay Salmonella, an effective way to test with real-time results. Learn more at http://bit.ly/3M_MDS #3M #salmonella #pathogen﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-2iaOLeFREO4/UOXwJsw5wqI/AAAAAAAAALE/srtGeGeJ91g/w426-h312/Assay%2BSalmonella.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/113910389916975197051/albums/5828738635059288417/5830529302208527474?authkey=CKHqqbqyvavL8QE</link><title>Salmonella Outbreak Could Be Caused by Watermelons -You may indulge in exciting fruits like watermelons for a bit of variety during your weight loss or wellness regime, but an outbreak of a strain of Salmonella has hinted that eating watermelons had led to diarrhoea, vomiting, abdominal pain, fever and, in one case, death. 

The Health... - http://www.yourwellness.com/2013/01/salmonella-outbreak-could-be-caused-by-watermelons/-Yourwellness﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-NKq1pGaNCMw/UOozgkalPHI/AAAAAAAACC4/zViLFpxar9c/w426-h241/Salmonella-Outbreak-Could-Be-Caused-by-Watermelons.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/105464086446332347945/albums/5778053760824288241/5778053765708844354</link><title>A Word on Salmonella - 
Recent headlines : "Another Outbreak of Salmonella From Cantaloupes in Indiana". 

The article said to make sure you wash your fruits and vegetables thoroughly to avoid being infected.  What are they talking about?!!! 

My research has shown that the salmonella is INSIDE the fruit and no amount of washing will remove it. 

My research has also shown that contamination, mostly likely, happens on the farm during the growing process.  That's how it gets INSIDE.  The source of contamination can be run off from dairy or meat packing plants, the use of recycled sludge as fertilizer, unsanitary conditions for the farm workers and/or irrigation with reclaimed water. 

Another good reason to know your farm.  Is it clean? 

At J R Organics there are no meat or dairy plants, we use only the finest fertilizers, we irrigate with uncontaminated water and we provide adequate sanitation for our workers.﻿

Meer lezen (18 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-KOf_YyUgbyM/UC_FSVYvDUI/AAAAAAAAAZQ/kjIlcFVs5YA/w426-h268/Cantaloupe.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/103652816560501784624/albums/5984111934947582993/5984111941040937666?sqi=110555615319066448343&amp;sqsi=5fe0189c-1314-495b-bfee-b0d83dbd08bc</link><title>Fine-tuning Salmonella-based Vaccines 

A new vaccine technology uses re-engineered salmonella to provide protective immunity. These vaccines, called recombinant attenuated salmonella vaccines or RASVs have the potential to become a safe, low-cost, orally-administered defense against bacterial, viral, fungal and parasitic infections. 

Read more here: http://goo.gl/69E8P4 

Image: Color-enhanced scanning electron micrograph showing Salmonella Typhimurium (red) invading cultured human cells 

Credit: Rocky Mountain Laboratories, NIAID, NIH﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-T_Zgx0XotKA/UwvWGu3rGsI/AAAAAAAAD5w/xkHQS3qSF84/w426-h357/916px-SalmonellaNIAID.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7216-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/salmonella/photos/109102265263486263584/albums/5704856299335326369/5704856305680134898</link><title>Watermelon found to be source of salmonella outbreak 

A salmonella outbreak linked to watermelons has affected 35 people in the UK, health experts have revealed. 

One person has died, although they had serious underlying health issues. 

The Health Protection Agency (HPA) said three times the usual number of cases of Salmonella Newport infection for this time of year had been seen. 

Cases of illness caused by the same strain have been seen in Ireland and Germany. 

Over 200 cases of Salmonella Newport are reported in the UK each year. 

Infection causes a similar illness to other forms of salmonella infection and symptoms include diarrhoea, vomiting, abdominal pain and fever. 

The people affected in this outbreak, which began in early December, ranged in age from six months to 85 years. 

Around 70% of cases were in women, and the East of England has had more cases than other regions. 

Experts say there are two possible ways watermelons could have caused infection. 

One is that the surface of the melons could have been contaminated with Salmonella bacteria which may have transferred on to the flesh of the melon during the cutting process. 

The second is if the melons were stored or washed in contaminated water, the salmonella bacteria could have got into the flesh of the melon through the cut stem. 
www.facebook.com/microbiologynews﻿

Meer lezen (36 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7216_10_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-pJdVohd9oZs/Tyu4lZq2MvI/AAAAAAAAAUQ/Ft4HdMd9WjE/w426-h320/evil-watermelon.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>