<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7217">who was lincolns vice president</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:13:04" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/104872267704857110019/albums/6002543367789128625/6002543364436677202</link><title>On the evening of the assassination of President Lincoln, Vice President Andrew Johnson woke to a loud pounding on his door at the Kirkwood hotel in Washington, D.C. Former Wisconsin Governor Leonard Farwell, who had just come from Ford's Theater, told Johnson the news. 

Johnson wanted to rush to Lincoln's side but was told to stay put until order was restored. He arrived at Lincoln's bedside at dawn. After paying his respects, he returned to the Kirkwood. 

On today's date in 1865, he took the oath of office in the hotel lobby. He had served as vice president for six weeks after a career in Tennessee politics. 

This 1864 campaign flag supported the Republican ticket including Lincoln and Johnson. More about the flag: http://bit.ly/1eEkZmE 

More on Johnson's stormy presidency: http://1.usa.gov/1l2bRGB 

#todayinhistory   #presidentialhistory  ﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9GLMfeNr6nI/U01RYxogUlI/AAAAAAAAB2Q/DxRKjTpB0n8/w426-h294/NMAH-AHB2008q15016.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/114529371273443966439/albums/6001034481438347761/6005597700589188338</link><title>Nothing new because  The Rothschilds’ had prepared long for this,agenda remains the same all the time - total World control.."1860 
Israel belongs to the Rothschilds 
We are the forces in the United States and in the world who are above the law and able to influence the highest US Government officials, including the President of the United States himself or any President in World 
Israeli spokeswoman, Tzipora Menache﻿ 
“You know very well, and theAmericans know equally well, that we control their government, irrespective of who sits in the White House. 
http://ministerpresidentrutte.wordpress.com/2011/10/22/rothschild-crash-rothschilds-exposed/ 
JFK: The Last President to Tell the truth about Illuminati(The Freemasonry and Zionism) 
Freemasonry and Zionism) 

The Truth Behind The Rothschild Family: World's Only Trillionaires 

http://www.pearltrees.com/#/N-play=0&amp;N-s=1_4347739&amp;N-u=1_498972&amp;N-p=35223228&amp;N-f=1_4347739&amp;N-fa=4131833 
Rothschild Cartel behind the rise of Hitler also funding communism socialism and world war 
Rothschild Cartel behind the rise of Hitler also funding communism socialism and world war 
The Rothschilds &amp; the Vatican 
The Rothschilds &amp; the Vatican 

Rothschild’$ Exposed: $500 Trillion Worth Includes: Bank of England, Reuters News, Associated Press, ABC,CBS, NBC, CNBC, CNN, Royal Dutch SHELL, Israel, Federal Reserve, US/UK Governments, CIA, NATO, Half Of World 
http://ministerpresidentrutte.wordpress.com/2011/10/22/rothschild-crash-rothschilds-exposed/ 

httpsThe Man in Charge of the World; The Great Rothschild Exposing YouTube 
://The Man in Charge of the World; The Great Rothschild Exposing YouTube 

Nothing new because khazarian's agenda remains the same all the time - total control... 
"1860 
In the American South, since American independence, a close business relationship had developed between the cotton growing aristocracy and the cotton manufacturers in England. The cotton was even delivered from America to France and Britain on Rothschild owned ships. The Rothschilds’ decided that this was America’s achilles heel that they could exploit to re-establish themselves in America, following the destruction of their central bank by 
President Andrew Jackson in 1836. 
The Rothschilds’ had prepared long for this, and this year the Southern States of America contained a vast number of Rothschild agents. They carefully manipulated the population by conspiring with local politicians they had in their pocket, and spreading propaganda amongst the people. This resulted in the secession of South Carolina on December 29th, 1860. Only a few weeks later, another six states would join the conspiracy against the Union, and form a 
breakaway union called the, “Confederate States of America,” with Jefferson Davis as its’ President. 
In order to provoke the North, these Rothschild agents and their brainwashed followers, raid armies, seize forts, arsenals, mints and other Union property. Even members of President Buchanan’s cabinet conspire to destroy the Union by damaging the public credit and working to bankrupt the nation. Buchanan claims to deplore secession but takes no steps to check it, even when a United States ship is fired upon by South Carolina shore batteries."﻿ 

Nathan Mayer, Freiherr von Rothschild (16 September 1777 – 28 July 1836), known as Nathan Mayer Rothschild, was a London-based Ashkenazi Jewish banker and financier and one of five sons of the second-generation of the Rothschild banking dynasty. He was born in Frankfurt am Main, the fourth child of Mayer Amschel Rothschild (1744–1812) and Gutle Schnapper (1753–1849). 

Nathan Meyer Rothschild was known for his role in the abolition of the slave trade through his part-financing of the 20 million pound British government buyout of the plantation industry's slaves. 

However in 2009 it was claimed that as part of banking dealings with a slave owner, Rothschild used slaves as collateral. The Rothschild bank denied the claims and said that Nathan Mayer Rothschild had been a prominent civil liberties campaigner with many like-minded associates and “against this background, these allegations appear inconsistent and misrepresent the ethos of the man and his business”. 

He set up his London business, N. M. Rothschild and Sons at New Court in St Swithin's Lane, City of London, where it trades today. He also purchased a country house at Gunnersbury Park near Acton in western London.﻿ 
“Let me issue and control a nation’s money and I care not who writes the laws.Rothschild 
globalist-jewish 

[1) Lord Jacob de Rothschild. 2) Nathaniel Rothschild. 3) Baron John de Rothschild 4) Sir Evelyn de Rothschild 5) David Rockefeller 6) Nathan Warburg 7) Henry Kissinger 8) George Soros 9) Paul Volcker 10) Larry Summers 11) Lloyd Blankfein 12) Ben Bernanke] 

http://piotrbein.wordpress.com/2012/03/23/lista-zydow-w-zniewalanej-polsce/﻿ 

The Rothschild-Owned Central Banks of the World 
controlling the world's money.... 

Afghanistan: Bank of Afghanistan 
Albania: Bank of Albania 
Algeria: Bank of Algeria 
Argentina: Central Bank of Argentina 
Armenia: Central Bank of Armenia 
Aruba: Central Bank of Aruba 
Australia: Reserve Bank of Australia 
Austria: Austrian National Bank 
Azerbaijan: Central Bank of Azerbaijan Republic 
Bahamas: Central Bank of The Bahamas 
Bahrain: Central Bank of Bahrain 
Bangladesh: Bangladesh Bank 
Barbados: Central Bank of Barbados 
Belarus: National Bank of the Republic of Belarus 
Belgium: National Bank of Belgium 
Belize: Central Bank of Belize 
Benin: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Bermuda: Bermuda Monetary Authority 
Bhutan: Royal Monetary Authority of Bhutan 
Bolivia: Central Bank of Bolivia 
Bosnia: Central Bank of Bosnia and Herzegovina 
Botswana: Bank of Botswana 
Brazil: Central Bank of Brazil 
Bulgaria: Bulgarian National Bank 
Burkina Faso: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Burundi: Bank of the Republic of Burundi 
Cambodia: National Bank of Cambodia 
Cameroon: Bank of Central African States 
Canada: Bank of Canada - Banque du Canada 
Cayman Islands: Cayman Islands Monetary Authority 
Central African Republic: Bank of Central African States 
Chad: Bank of Central African States 
Chile: Central Bank of Chile 
China: The People’s Bank of China 
Colombia: Bank of the Republic 
Comoros: Central Bank of Comoros 
Congo: Bank of Central African States 
Costa Rica: Central Bank of Costa Rica 
Côte d’Ivoire: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Croatia: Croatian National Bank 
Cuba: Central Bank of Cuba 
Cyprus: Central Bank of Cyprus 
Czech Republic: Czech National Bank 
Denmark: National Bank of Denmark 
Dominican Republic: Central Bank of the Dominican Republic 
East Caribbean area: Eastern Caribbean Central Bank 
Ecuador: Central Bank of Ecuador 
Egypt: Central Bank of Egypt 
El Salvador: Central Reserve Bank of El Salvador 
Equatorial Guinea: Bank of Central African States 
Estonia: Bank of Estonia 
Ethiopia: National Bank of Ethiopia 
European Union: European Central Bank 
Fiji: Reserve Bank of Fiji 
Finland: Bank of Finland 
France: Bank of France 
Gabon: Bank of Central African States 
The Gambia: Central Bank of The Gambia 
Georgia: National Bank of Georgia 
Germany: Deutsche Bundesbank 
Ghana: Bank of Ghana 
Greece: Bank of Greece 
Guatemala: Bank of Guatemala 
Guinea Bissau: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Guyana: Bank of Guyana 
Haiti: Central Bank of Haiti 
Honduras: Central Bank of Honduras 
Hong Kong: Hong Kong Monetary Authority 
Hungary: Magyar Nemzeti Bank 
Iceland: Central Bank of Iceland 
India: Reserve Bank of India 
Indonesia: Bank Indonesia 
Iraq: Central Bank of Iraq 
Ireland: Central Bank and Financial Services Authority of Ireland 
Israel: Bank of Israel 
Italy: Bank of Italy 
Jamaica: Bank of Jamaica 
Japan: Bank of Japan 
Jordan: Central Bank of Jordan 
Kazakhstan: National Bank of Kazakhstan 
Kenya: Central Bank of Kenya 
Korea: Bank of Korea 
Kuwait: Central Bank of Kuwait 
Kyrgyzstan: National Bank of the Kyrgyz Republic 
Latvia: Bank of Latvia 
Lebanon: Central Bank of Lebanon 
Lesotho: Central Bank of Lesotho 
Libya: Central Bank of Libya 
Lithuania: Bank of Lithuania 
Luxembourg: Central Bank of Luxembourg 
Macao: Monetary Authority of Macao 
Macedonia: National Bank of the Republic of Macedonia 
Madagascar: Central Bank of Madagascar 
Malawi: Reserve Bank of Malawi 
Malaysia: Central Bank of Malaysia 
Mali: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Malta: Central Bank of Malta 
Mauritius: Bank of Mauritius 
Mexico: Bank of Mexico 
Moldova: National Bank of Moldova 
Mongolia: Bank of Mongolia 
Montenegro: Central Bank of Montenegro 
Morocco: Bank of Morocco 
Mozambique: Bank of Mozambique 
Namibia: Bank of Namibia 
Nepal: Central Bank of Nepal 
Netherlands: Netherlands Bank 
Netherlands Antilles: Bank of the Netherlands Antilles 
New Zealand: Reserve Bank of New Zealand 
Nicaragua: Central Bank of Nicaragua 
Niger: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Nigeria: Central Bank of Nigeria 
Norway: Central Bank of Norway 
Oman: Central Bank of Oman 
Pakistan: State Bank of Pakistan 
Papua New Guinea: Bank of Papua New Guinea 
Paraguay: Central Bank of Paraguay 
Peru: Central Reserve Bank of Peru 
Philippines: Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas 
Poland: National Bank of Poland 
Portugal: Bank of Portugal 
Qatar: Qatar Central Bank 
Romania: National Bank of Romania 
Russia: Central Bank of Russia 
Rwanda: National Bank of Rwanda 
San Marino: Central Bank of the Republic of San Marino 
Samoa: Central Bank of Samoa 
Saudi Arabia: Saudi Arabian Monetary Agency 
Senegal: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Serbia: National Bank of Serbia 
Seychelles: Central Bank of Seychelles 
Sierra Leone: Bank of Sierra Leone 
Singapore: Monetary Authority of Singapore 
Slovakia: National Bank of Slovakia 
Slovenia: Bank of Slovenia 
Solomon Islands: Central Bank of Solomon Islands 
South Africa: South African Reserve Bank 
Spain: Bank of Spain 
Sri Lanka: Central Bank of Sri Lanka 
Sudan: Bank of Sudan 
Surinam: Central Bank of Suriname 
Swaziland: The Central Bank of Swaziland 
Sweden: Sveriges Riksbank 
Switzerland: Swiss National Bank 
Tajikistan: National Bank of Tajikistan 
Tanzania: Bank of Tanzania 
Thailand: Bank of Thailand 
Togo: Central Bank of West African States (BCEAO) 
Tonga: National Reserve Bank of Tonga 
Trinidad and Tobago: Central Bank of Trinidad and Tobago 
Tunisia: Central Bank of Tunisia 
Turkey: Central Bank of the Republic of Turkey 
Uganda: Bank of Uganda 
Ukraine: National Bank of Ukraine 
United Arab Emirates: Central Bank of United Arab Emirates 
United Kingdom: Bank of England 
United States: The Dirty Nasty Stinky Fed, Federal Reserve Bank of New York 
Uruguay: Central Bank of Uruguay 
Vanuatu: Reserve Bank of Vanuatu 
Venezuela: Central Bank of Venezuela 
Vietnam: The State Bank of Vietnam 
Yemen: Central Bank of Yemen 
Zambia: Bank of Zambia 
Zimbabwe: Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe 
Hist"ory records that the money changers have used every form of abuse, intrigue, deceit, and violent means possible to maintain their control over governments by  controlling money and its issuance." 

“Let me issue and control a nation’s money and I care not who writes the laws.” Baron M.A Rothschild 
I care not what poppet is placed upon the throne of England to rule Empire on witch the sun never sets The man who controls Britain's money supply controls the British Empire and I control the British money supply 
-Nathan  Rothschild 
Give me control of a nation's money and I care not who makes the laws."    my Central Bank control Global money only tree countries left than I control the world Evelyn Rothschild﻿ 

“Money plays the largest part in determining the course of history.” 
-Karl Marx 

"The real truth of the matter is,as you and I know, that a financial element in the large centers has owned the government ever since the days of Andrew Jackson..." 
-Franklin D. Roosevelt 

“It is well enough that people of the nation do not understand our banking and money system, for if they did, I believe there would be a revolution before tomorrow morning.” 
-Henry Ford 

"The Government should create, issue, and circulate all the currency and  credits needed to satisfy the spending power of the Government and the buying power of  consumers. By the adoption of these principles, the taxpayers will be saved immense sums of interest. Money will cease to be master and become the servant of humanity." 
-Abraham  Lincoln 

"If congress has the right under the Constitution to issue paper money, it was  given them to use themselves, not to be delegated to individuals or corporations." 
-Andrew Jackson 

"When a government is dependent upon bankers for money, they and not the leaders of the government control the situation, since the hand that gives is above the hand that takes… Money has no motherland; financiers are without patriotism and without decency; their sole object is gain.” 
– Napoleon Bonaparte, Emperor of France, 1815 
Research who was the financiers 

“I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies.” 
– Thomas Jefferson 

"The modern theory of the perpetuation of debt has drenched the earth with blood, and crushed its inhabitants under burdens ever accumulating." 
-Thomas Jefferson 

“The few who understand the system will either be so interested in its profits or be so dependent upon its favours that there will be no opposition from that class, while on the other hand, the great body of people, mentally incapable of comprehending the tremendous advantage that capital derives from the system, will bear its burdens without complaint, and perhaps without even suspecting that the system is inimical to their interests.” 
-The Rothschild brothers of London writing to associates in New York, 1863.﻿ 

Rothschild’$ Exposed: $500 Trillion Worth Includes: Bank of England, Reuters News, Associated Press, ABC,CBS, NBC, CNBC, CNN, Royal Dutch SHELL, Israel, Federal Reserve, US/UK Governments, CIA, NATO, Half Of World 
http://ministerpresidentrutte.wordpress.com/2011/10/22/rothschild-crash-rothschilds-exposed/﻿ 
They funded both sides in almost all modern wars since the Napoleonic wars '' 

The History of the House of Rothschild 
The Rothschilds have been in control of the world for a very long time, and I produce my evidence for this below in a timeline. The Rothschilds have, with their founding of Zionism, betrayed the principles of the Torah, and have caused great suffering around the world. I name individual Rothschilds where I can, but due to the secrecy which they shroud themselves in, naming the exact Rothschild is not always possible. I also wish to point out that this article is not criticising everyone with the name Rothschilds, simply the criminal element of that group that have carried out the treachery I detail below. Furthermore a great deal of this criminal element no longer carry the name Rothschild and there is a great deal of evidence pointing to the fact that those people currently in control of the United States, British and Israeli government are in fact Rothschilds. 

Rothschild Timeline 

1743: Mayer Amschel Bauer, born Frankfurt, Germany, the son of Moses Amschel Bauer, a money lender and the proprietor of a counting house. Over the entrance door he places a red sign. 
This sign is a six pointed star (which geometrically and numerically translates into the number 666) which under Rothschild instruction will end up on the Israeli flag some two centuries later. 
1753: Gutele Schnaper (future wife of Mayer Amschel bauer) born. 
1760: During this decade Mayer Amschel Bauer works for a bank owned by the Oppenheimers’ in Hanover, Germany, he is highly successful and becomes a junior partner. Whilst working at the bank he becomes acquainted with General von Estorff. 
Following his father’s death, Bauer returns to Frankfurt to take over his father’s business. Bauer recognises the significance of the red sign and changes his name from Bauer to Rothschild, after the red sign signifying 666 hanging over the entrance door (“Rot,” is German for, “Red,” “Schild,” is German for, “Sign”). 
Now Mayer Amschel Rothschild, he discovers that General von Estorff is now attached to the court of Prince William of Hanau. He therefore makes the General’s re-acquaintance on the pretext of selling him valuable coins and trinkets at discounted prices. 
As he plans, Rothschild is subsequently introduced to Prince William himself who is more than pleased with discounted prices he charges for his rare coins and trinkets, and Rothschild offers him a bonus for any other business the Prince can direct his way. Rothschild subsequently becomes close associates with Prince William, and ends up doing business with him and members of the court. 
1769: Mayer Amschel Rothschild is given permission by Prince William to hang a sign on the front of his business premises declaring that he is, “M. A. Rothschild, by appointment court factor to his serene highness, Prince William of Hanau.” 
1770: Mayer Amschel Rothschild marries Gutele Schnaper. 
Mayer Amschel Rothschild draws up plans for the creation of the Illuminati and entrusts Adam Weishaupt with its organization and development. 
1773: Amschel Mayer Rothschild born. 
1774: Salomon Mayer Rothschild born. 
1777: Nathan Mayer Rothschild born. 
1788: Kalmann (Carl) Mayer Rothschild Born. 
1791: The Rothschilds through Alexander Hamilton (their agent in George washington’s cabinet) set up a central bank in the USA called the Bank of the United States. This is established with a 20 year charter. 
1792: Jacob (James) Mayer Rothschild born. 
1796: Amschel Mayer Rothschild marries Eva Hanau. 
1798: Nathan Mayer Rothschild leaves Frankfurt for Manchester, England, where will the help of his father and brothers he exports English textiles to Europe. 
1800: Salomon Mayer Rothschild marries Caroline Stern. 
1806: Napolean states that it is his, “object to remove the house of Hess-Cassel from rulership and to strike it out of the list of powers.” On hearing this, Prince William of Hanau, flees Germany, goes to Denmark and entrusts his fortune valued at $3,000,000 at that time to Mayer Amschel Rothschild for safekeeping. 
Nathan Mayer Rothschild marries Hannah Barent Cohen the daughter of a wealthy London merchant and begins to move his business to London. 
1808: Nathan Mayer Rothschild has his first son born Lionel Nathan de Rothschild. 
1809: As the Channel blockade was making the export business difficult, Nathan Mayer Rothschild, went to New Street, London and set himself up as a banker. 
1810: Sir Francis Baring and Abraham Goldsmid die. This leaves Nathan Mayer Rothschild as the remaining major banker in England. 
Salomon Mayer Rothschild goes to Vienna, Austria and sets up the bank, M. von Rothschild und Söhne. 
1811: The charter for the Rothschilds Bank of the United States runs out and Congress votes against its renewal. At the time Andrew Jackson (who would become the 7th President of the United States from 1829 to 1837) says, “If Congress has a right under the Constitution to issue paper money, it was given them to use by themselves, not to be delegated to individuals or corporations.” 
Nathan Mayer Rothschild is not amused and he stated, “Either the application for renewal of the charter is granted, or the United States will find itself involved in a most disastrous war.” 
Andrew Jackson’s response to this is to say, “You are a den of thieves vipers, and I intend to rout you out, and by the Eternal God, I will rout you out.” 
Nathan Mayer Rothschild’s reply to that being, “Teach those impudent Americans a lesson. Bring them back to colonial status.” 
1812: Backed by Rothschild money, the British declare war on the United States. The Rothschilds plan was to cause the United States to build up such a debt in fighting this war that they would have to surrender to the Rothschilds and allow the charter for the Rothschild owned Bank of the United States to be renewed. 
Mayer Amschel Rothschild dies. In his will he lays out specific laws that the House of Rothschild were to follow: all key positions in the family business were only to be held by family members; only male members of the family were allowed to participate in the family business (It is important to note that Mayer Amschel Rothschild also has five daughters, so today the spread of the Rothschild Zionist dynasty without the Rothschild name is far and wide); the family was to intermarry with it’s first and second cousins to preserve the family fortune; no public inventory of his estate was to be published; no legal action was to be taken with regard to the value of the inheritance; the eldest son of the eldest son was to become the head of the family (this condition could only be overturned when the majority of the family agreed otherwise). 
This was straightaway the case and Nathan Mayer Rothschild was elected head of the family following his father, Mayer Amschel Rothschild’s death. 
Jacob (James) Mayer Rothschild goes to Paris, France to set up the bank, de Rothschild Frères. 
Nathaniel de Rothschild, the son in law of Jacob (James) Mayer Rothschild, born. 1814: With regard to the $3,000,000 Prince William of Hanau had entrusted to Mayer Amschel Rothschild for safekeeping, for an account of what happened next we turn to the Jewish Encyclopaedia, 1905 edition, Volume 10, page 494, which states, 

“According to legend this money was hidden away in wine casks, and, escaping the search of Napoleon's soldiers when they entered Frankfurt, was restored intact in the same casks in 1814, when the elector (Prince William of Hanau) returned to the electorate (Germany). The facts are somewhat less romantic, and more businesslike.” 
This last line indicates the money was never returned by Rothschild to Prince William of Hanau. The encyclopaedia goes on to state, Nathan Mayer Rothschild invested this $3,000,000 in, “gold from the East India company knowing that it would be needed for Wellington's peninsula campaign.” 
On the stolen money Nathan made, “no less than four profits: i) On the sale of Wellington's paper which he bought at 50 cents on the dollar and collected at par; ii) on the sale of gold to Wellington; iii) on its repurchase; and iv) on forwarding it to Portugal.” 
1815: The five Rothschild brothers work to supply gold to both Wellington’s army (through Nathan in England) and Napoleon’s army (through Jacob in France), and begin their policy of funding both sides in wars. 
Due to the fact that these brothers had banks spread out across Europe this gave them the facility to set up an unrivalled network of secret routes and fast couriers. These Rothschild couriers were the only merchants allowed to pass through the English and French blockades. 
It was these couriers who also kept Nathan Mayer Rothschild up to date with how the war was going so he could use that intelligence to buy and sell from his position on the stock exchange in accordance with that intelligence. 
At that time British bonds were called consuls and they were traded on the floor of the stock exchange. Nathan Mayer Rothschild instructed all his workers on the floor to start selling consuls. They made all the other traders believe that the British had lost the war so they started selling frantically. 
Therefore the consuls plummeted in value which was when Nathan Mayer Rothschild discreetly instructed his workers to purchase all the consuls they could lay their hands on. When news came through that the British had actually won the war, the consuls went up to a level even higher than before the war ended leaving Nathan Mayer Rothschild with a return of approximately 20 to 1 on his investment. 
This gave the Rothschild family complete control of the British economy, now the financial centre of the world following Napolean’s defeat, and forced England to set up a new Bank of England, which Nathan Mayer Rothschild controlled. Nathan Mayer Rothschild would later state, 
“I care not what puppet is placed upon the throne of England to rule the Empire on which the sun never sets. The man who controls Britain's money  controls.British Empire and I control the Britain's money ﻿ 

US Presidents Murdered By The Rothschild Banking Cartel 

Lincoln's Private War: The Trail of Blood 

Lincoln's Birthday gives us an appropriate opportunity to examine some deep American traditions which may also give us some unusual insights into the "principalities and powers" of Ephesians Chapter 6. 

Abraham Lincoln worked valiantly to prevent the Rothschild's attempts to involve themselves in financing the Civil War. 

Interestingly, it was the Czar of Russia who provided the needed assistance against the British and French, who were among the driving forces behind the secession of the South and her subsequent financing. Russia intervened by providing naval forces for the Union blockade of the South in European waters, and by letting both countries know that if they attempted to join the Confederacy with military forces, they would also have to go to war with Russia. 

The Rothschild interests did succeed, through their agent Treasury Secretary Salmon P. Chase, to force a bill (the National Banking Act) through Congress creating a federally chartered central bank that had the power to issue U.S. Bank Notes. Afterward, Lincoln warned the American people: 
"The money power preys upon the nation in time of peace and conspires against it in times of adversity. It is more despotic than monarchy, more insolent than autocracy, more selfish than bureaucracy. I see in the near future a crisis approaching that unnerves me, and causes me to tremble for the safety of our country. Corporations have been enthroned, an era of corruption will follow, and the money power of the country will endeavor to prolong its reign by working upon the prejudices of the people, until the wealth is aggregated in a few hands, and the republic is destroyed. " 
Lincoln continued to fight against the central bank, and some now believe that it was his anticipated success in influencing Congress to limit the life of the Bank of the United States to just the war years that was the motivating factor behind his assassination. 

The Lone Assassin Myth is Born 

Modern researchers have uncovered evidence of a massive conspiracy that links the following parties to the Bank of Rothschild. Lincoln's Secretary of War Edwin Stanton, John Wilkes Booth, his eight co-conspirators, and over seventy government officials and businessmen involved in the conspiracy. 

When Booth's diary was recovered by Stanton's troops, it was delivered to Stanton. When it was later produced during the investigation, eighteen pages had been ripped out. These pages, containing the aforementioned names,were later found in the attic of one of Stanton's descendants. 
&gt;From Booth's trunk, a coded message was found that linked him directly to Judah P. Benjamin, the Civil War campaign manager in the South for the House of Rothschild. When the war ended, the key to the code was found in Benjamin's possession. 

The assassin, portrayed as a crazed lone gunman with a few radical friends, escaped by way of the only bridge in Washington not guarded by Stanton's troops. 

"Booth" was located hiding in a barn near Port Royal, Virginia, three days after escaping from Washington. He was shot by a soldier named Boston Corbett, who fired without orders. Whether or not the man killed was Booth is still a matter of contention, but the fact remains that whoever it was, he had no chance to identify himself. It was Secretary of War Edwin Stanton who made the final identification. Some now believe that a dupe was used and that the real John Wilkes Booth escaped with Stanton's assistance. 

Mary Todd Lincoln, upon hearing of her husband's death, began screaming, "Oh, that dreadful house!" Earlier historians felt that this spontaneous utterance referred to the White House. Some now believe it may have been directed to Thomas W. House, a gun runner, financier, and agent of the Rothschild's during the Civil War, who was linked to the anti-Lincoln, pro-banker interests.&lt;http://www.servelec.net/lincoln.htm#6&gt;6 

The Federal Reserve 

Another myth that all Americans live with is the charade known as the "Federal Reserve." It comes as a shock to many to discover that it is not an agency of the United States Government. 

The name "Federal Reserve Bank" was designed to deceive, and it still does. It is not federal, nor is it owned by the government. It is privately owned.7 It pays its own postage like any other corporation. Its employees are not in civil service. Its physical property is held under private deeds, and is subject to local taxation. Government property, as you know, is not. 

It is an engine that has created private wealth that is unimaginable, even to the most financially sophisticated. It has enabled an imperial elite to manipulate our economy for its own agenda and enlisted the government itself as its enforcer. It controls the times, dictates business, affects our homes and practically everything in which we are interested. 

It takes powerful force to maintain an empire, and this one is no different. The concerns of the leadership of the "Federal Reserve" and its secretive international benefactors appear to go well beyond currency and interest rates. 

Andrew Jackson 

Andrew Jackson was the first President from west of the Appalachians. He was unique for the times in being elected by the voters, without the direct support of a recognized political organization. He vetoed the renewal of the charter for the Bank of the United States on July 10, 1832. 

In 1835, President Andrew Jackson declared his disdain for the international bankers: 
"You are a den of vipers. I intend to rout you out, and by the Eternal God I will rout you out. If the people only understood the rank injustice of our money and banking system, there would be a revolution before morning." 
There followed an (unsuccessful) assassination attempt on President Jackson's life. Jackson had told his vice president, Martin Van Buren, "The bank, Mr. Van Buren, is trying to kill me...." 

Was this the beginning of a pattern of intrigue that would plague the White House itself over the coming decades? Was his (and Lincoln's) death related by an invisible thread to the international bankers? 

James Garfield 

President James Abram Garfield, our 20th President, had previously been Chairman of the House Committee on Appropriations and was an expert on fiscal matters. (Upon his election, among other things, he appointed an unpopular collector of customs at New York, whereupon the two Senators from New York-Roscoe Conkling and Thomas Platt--resigned their seats.) 
President Garfield openly declared that whoever controls the supply of currency would control the business and activities of all the people. After only four months in office, President Garfield was shot at a railroad station on July 2, 1881. Another coincidence. 

John F. Kennedy 

President John F. Kennedy planned to exterminate the Federal Reserve System. In 1963 he signed Executive Orders EO-11 and EO-110, returning to the government the responsibility to print money, taking that privilege away from the Federal Reserve System. 

Shortly thereafter, President John F. Kennedy was assassinated.11 The professional, triangulated fire that executed the President of the United States is not the most shocking issue. The high level coordination that organized the widespread coverup is manifest evidence of the incredible power of a "hidden government" behind the scenes. (Sound preposterous? Read Kill Zone, by Craig Roberts for an update on the events in Dealey Plaza.) 

The Trail of Blood Continues 

In the 70's and 80's, Congressman Larry P. McDonald spearheaded efforts to expose the hidden holdings and intentions of the international money interests. His efforts ended on August 31, 1983, when he was killed when Korean Airlines 007 was "accidentally" shot down in Soviet airspace. A strange coincidence, it would seem. 

Senator John Heinz and former Senator John Tower had served on powerful Senate banking and finance committees and were outspoken critics of the Federal Reserve and the Eastern Establishment. On April 4, 1991, Senator John Heinz was killed in a plane crash near Philadelphia. 

On the next day, April 5, 1991, former Senator John Tower was also killed in a plane crash. The coincidences seem to mount. 

Attempts to just audit the Federal Reserve continue to meet with failure. It is virtually impossible to muster support for any issue that has the benefit of a media blackout. (The bizarre but tragic reality that the American people suffer from a managed and controlled media is a subject for another discussion.) 

Beginning of a Series 

For many years, numerous authors have attempted to sound the alarm that there exists a hidden "shadow government" that actually rules America. Most of us have dismissed these "conspiracy theory" views as extremist and unrealistic. However, when I had the opportunity to have lunch with Otto von Habsburg,&lt;http://www.servelec.net/lincoln.htm#15&gt;15 Member of the European Parliament, he made two remarks that caught my attention. The first was: "The ignorance in America is overwhelming." Indeed, the contrast in general awareness of world affairs between the average American and the average European is striking. 

It was his second observation that really provoked me: "The concentration of power in America is frightening." As a reasonably circumspect senior executive, having spent three decades in international finance and viewing America as a broadly based representative democracy, his remark shocked me. It prompted me to do some more homework. The results of my inquiries are most disturbing. 

http://rense.com/general86/pres.htm 

Source http://asso.in/url/bl5﻿ 

globalist-jewish 

[1) Lord Jacob de Rothschild. 2) Nathaniel Rothschild. 3) Baron John de Rothschild 4) Sir Evelyn de Rothschild 5) David Rockefeller 6) Nathan Warburg 7) Henry Kissinger 8) George Soros 9) Paul Volcker 10) Larry Summers 11) Lloyd Blankfein 12) Ben Bernanke] 

http://piotrbein.wordpress.com/2012/03/23/lista-zydow-w-zniewalanej-polsce/﻿ 

US Presidents Murdered By The Rothschild Banking Cartel 

Lincoln's Private War: The Trail of Blood 

Lincoln's Birthday gives us an appropriate opportunity to examine some deep American traditions which may also give us some unusual insights into the "principalities and powers" of Ephesians Chapter 6. 

Abraham Lincoln worked valiantly to prevent the Rothschild's attempts to involve themselves in financing the Civil War. 

Interestingly, it was the Czar of Russia who provided the needed assistance against the British and French, who were among the driving forces behind the secession of the South and her subsequent financing. Russia intervened by providing naval forces for the Union blockade of the South in European waters, and by letting both countries know that if they attempted to join the Confederacy with military forces, they would also have to go to war with Russia. 

The Rothschild interests did succeed, through their agent Treasury Secretary Salmon P. Chase, to force a bill (the National Banking Act) through Congress creating a federally chartered central bank that had the power to issue U.S. Bank Notes. Afterward, Lincoln warned the American people: 
"The money power preys upon the nation in time of peace and conspires against it in times of adversity. It is more despotic than monarchy, more insolent than autocracy, more selfish than bureaucracy. I see in the near future a crisis approaching that unnerves me, and causes me to tremble for the safety of our country. Corporations have been enthroned, an era of corruption will follow, and the money power of the country will endeavor to prolong its reign by working upon the prejudices of the people, until the wealth is aggregated in a few hands, and the republic is destroyed. " 
Lincoln continued to fight against the central bank, and some now believe that it was his anticipated success in influencing Congress to limit the life of the Bank of the United States to just the war years that was the motivating factor behind his assassination. 

The Lone Assassin Myth is Born 

Modern researchers have uncovered evidence of a massive conspiracy that links the following parties to the Bank of Rothschild. Lincoln's Secretary of War Edwin Stanton, John Wilkes Booth, his eight co-conspirators, and over seventy government officials and businessmen involved in the conspiracy. 

When Booth's diary was recovered by Stanton's troops, it was delivered to Stanton. When it was later produced during the investigation, eighteen pages had been ripped out. These pages, containing the aforementioned names,were later found in the attic of one of Stanton's descendants. 
&gt;From Booth's trunk, a coded message was found that linked him directly to Judah P. Benjamin, the Civil War campaign manager in the South for the House of Rothschild. When the war ended, the key to the code was found in Benjamin's possession. 

The assassin, portrayed as a crazed lone gunman with a few radical friends, escaped by way of the only bridge in Washington not guarded by Stanton's troops. 

"Booth" was located hiding in a barn near Port Royal, Virginia, three days after escaping from Washington. He was shot by a soldier named Boston Corbett, who fired without orders. Whether or not the man killed was Booth is still a matter of contention, but the fact remains that whoever it was, he had no chance to identify himself. It was Secretary of War Edwin Stanton who made the final identification. Some now believe that a dupe was used and that the real John Wilkes Booth escaped with Stanton's assistance. 

Mary Todd Lincoln, upon hearing of her husband's death, began screaming, "Oh, that dreadful house!" Earlier historians felt that this spontaneous utterance referred to the White House. Some now believe it may have been directed to Thomas W. House, a gun runner, financier, and agent of the Rothschild's during the Civil War, who was linked to the anti-Lincoln, pro-banker interests.&lt;http://www.servelec.net/lincoln.htm#6&gt;6 

The Federal Reserve 

Another myth that all Americans live with is the charade known as the "Federal Reserve." It comes as a shock to many to discover that it is not an agency of the United States Government. 

The name "Federal Reserve Bank" was designed to deceive, and it still does. It is not federal, nor is it owned by the government. It is privately owned.7 It pays its own postage like any other corporation. Its employees are not in civil service. Its physical property is held under private deeds, and is subject to local taxation. Government property, as you know, is not. 

It is an engine that has created private wealth that is unimaginable, even to the most financially sophisticated. It has enabled an imperial elite to manipulate our economy for its own agenda and enlisted the government itself as its enforcer. It controls the times, dictates business, affects our homes and practically everything in which we are interested. 

It takes powerful force to maintain an empire, and this one is no different. The concerns of the leadership of the "Federal Reserve" and its secretive international benefactors appear to go well beyond currency and interest rates. 

Andrew Jackson 

Andrew Jackson was the first President from west of the Appalachians. He was unique for the times in being elected by the voters, without the direct support of a recognized political organization. He vetoed the renewal of the charter for the Bank of the United States on July 10, 1832. 

In 1835, President Andrew Jackson declared his disdain for the international bankers: 
"You are a den of vipers. I intend to rout you out, and by the Eternal God I will rout you out. If the people only understood the rank injustice of our money and banking system, there would be a revolution before morning." 
There followed an (unsuccessful) assassination attempt on President Jackson's life. Jackson had told his vice president, Martin Van Buren, "The bank, Mr. Van Buren, is trying to kill me...." 

Was this the beginning of a pattern of intrigue that would plague the White House itself over the coming decades? Was his (and Lincoln's) death related by an invisible thread to the international bankers? 

James Garfield 

President James Abram Garfield, our 20th President, had previously been Chairman of the House Committee on Appropriations and was an expert on fiscal matters. (Upon his election, among other things, he appointed an unpopular collector of customs at New York, whereupon the two Senators from New York-Roscoe Conkling and Thomas Platt--resigned their seats.) 
President Garfield openly declared that whoever controls the supply of currency would control the business and activities of all the people. After only four months in office, President Garfield was shot at a railroad station on July 2, 1881. Another coincidence. 

John F. Kennedy 

President John F. Kennedy planned to exterminate the Federal Reserve System. In 1963 he signed Executive Orders EO-11 and EO-110, returning to the government the responsibility to print money, taking that privilege away from the Federal Reserve System. 

Shortly thereafter, President John F. Kennedy was assassinated.11 The professional, triangulated fire that executed the President of the United States is not the most shocking issue. The high level coordination that organized the widespread coverup is manifest evidence of the incredible power of a "hidden government" behind the scenes. (Sound preposterous? Read Kill Zone, by Craig Roberts for an update on the events in Dealey Plaza.) 

The Trail of Blood Continues 

In the 70's and 80's, Congressman Larry P. McDonald spearheaded efforts to expose the hidden holdings and intentions of the international money interests. His efforts ended on August 31, 1983, when he was killed when Korean Airlines 007 was "accidentally" shot down in Soviet airspace. A strange coincidence, it would seem. 

Senator John Heinz and former Senator John Tower had served on powerful Senate banking and finance committees and were outspoken critics of the Federal Reserve and the Eastern Establishment. On April 4, 1991, Senator John Heinz was killed in a plane crash near Philadelphia. 

On the next day, April 5, 1991, former Senator John Tower was also killed in a plane crash. The coincidences seem to mount. 

Attempts to just audit the Federal Reserve continue to meet with failure. It is virtually impossible to muster support for any issue that has the benefit of a media blackout. (The bizarre but tragic reality that the American people suffer from a managed and controlled media is a subject for another discussion.) 

Beginning of a Series 

For many years, numerous authors have attempted to sound the alarm that there exists a hidden "shadow government" that actually rules America. Most of us have dismissed these "conspiracy theory" views as extremist and unrealistic. However, when I had the opportunity to have lunch with Otto von Habsburg,&lt;http://www.servelec.net/lincoln.htm#15&gt;15 Member of the European Parliament, he made two remarks that caught my attention. The first was: "The ignorance in America is overwhelming." Indeed, the contrast in general awareness of world affairs between the average American and the average European is striking. 

It was his second observation that really provoked me: "The concentration of power in America is frightening." As a reasonably circumspect senior executive, having spent three decades in international finance and viewing America as a broadly based representative democracy, his remark shocked me. It prompted me to do some more homework. The results of my inquiries are most disturbing. 

http://rense.com/general86/pres.htm 

Source http://asso.in/url/bl5﻿ 

Youtube: Rothschild Cartel behind the rise of Hitler also funding communism socialism and world war 
TABLE 7-1: FINANCIAL LINKS BETWEEN U.S. INDUSTRIALISTS AND ADOLF HITLER Link: http://reformed-theology.org/html/books/wall_street/table_7-1.htm 

Who Financed Adolf Hitler? Via Expose Australia 
(The Mind of Adolf Hitler: The Secret Wartime Report) contains facts which contradict most biographies of Hitler, including Hitler's own "Mein Kampf." The tragedies and hardships sustained during his rough childhood combined with his harsh endeavors in Austria and Germany provide the base for his adult life where he lives anything but a relative normal one. 

Though Hitler's madness may appear to be based primarily on his anti-Semitic beliefs, the book rarely focuses on this subject and shows that there was more to his hate than just hate for the Jews. Ironically, as the book explains, he befriended and was aided by a number of Jews throughout his life. 

Clearly ambition and Providence play a key role in Hitler's life, and one can only wonder what Hitler would have done with his life had he not endured such malaise before his rise to power. Ironically, Langer's perspective on Hitler makes it possible for the reader to feel an iota of sympathy for a man who is responsible for killing millions of people. 

There are many facts found in the book that I would never have imagined could have been true. I recommend this book to anyone who wishes to find out almost everything there is to know about Adolf Hitler. 

The Mind of Adolf Hitler: The Secret Wartime Report ... 

The Mind of Adolf Hitler: The Secret Wartime Report'According to a book by a psychoanalyst, Walter Langer(a JEW), called The Mind of Hitler, not only was Hitler supported by the Rothschilds, he WAS a Rothschild. This revelation fits like a glove with the actions of the Rothschilds and other Illuminati bloodlines in Germany who brought Hitler to the fore as dictator of that nation. He was also supported by the British Royal Family, the House of Windsor (in truth the German House of Saxe-Coburg-Gotha), and these included the British royal "war hero", Lord Mountbatten, a Rothschild and a Satanist. Their royal relatives in Germany, who you would never have thought would normally support an apparent guy from the street like Hitler, were among his most enthusiastic supporters. But, of course, they knew who he really was. There is no way in the world when you do any study of the Illuminati obsession with bloodline that Hitler would not have been one of them. Langer writes: 

"Adolf's father, Alois Hitler, was the illegitimate son of Maria Anna Schicklgruber. It was generally supposed that the father of Alois Hitler (Schicklgruber) was Johann Georg Hiedler.There are some people who seriously doubt that Johann Georg Hiedler was the father of Alois (an Austrian document was) prepared that proved Maria Anna Schicklgruber was living in Vienna at the time she conceived. At that time she was employed as a servant in the home of Baron Rothschild. As soon as the family discovered her pregnancy she was sent back home..where Alois was born." 

Langer's information came from the high level Gestapo officer, Hansjurgen Koehler, published in 1940, under the title "Inside the Gestapo". He writes about the investigations into Hitler's background carried out by the Austrian Chancellor, Dolfuss, in the family files of Hitler. 

Koehler actually viewed a copy of the Dolfuss documents which were given to him by Heydrich, the overlord of the Nazi Secret Service. The file, he wrote, "caused such havoc as no file in the world ever caused before" (Inside the Gestapo, p 143). He also revealed that: 

"..The second bundle in the blue file contained the documents collected by Dolfuss. The small statured, but big-hearted Austrian Chancellor must have known by such a personal file he might be able to check HitlerHis task was not difficult; as ruler of Austria he could easily find out about the personal data and family of Adolf Hitler, who had been born on Austrian soil...Through the original birth certificates, police registration cards, protocols, etc., all contained in the original file, the Austrian Chancellor succeeded in piecing together the disjointed parts of the puzzle, creating a more or less logical entity.. 

A little servant girl (Hitler's grandmother) came to Vienna and became a domestic servant, mostly working for rather rich families. But she was unlucky; having been seduced, she was about to bear a child. She went home to her village for her confinementWhere was the little maid serving in Vienna? This was not a very difficult problem. Very early Vienna had instituted the system of compulsory police registration. Both servants and the employers were exposed to heavy fines if they neglected this duty. Chancellor Dolfuss managed to discover the registration card. The little, innocent maid had been a servant at the Rothschild mansion. ..and Hitler's unknown grandfather must be probably looked for in this magnificent house. The Dolfuss file stopped at this statement." 

Was Hitler's determination to take over Austria anything to do with his desire to destroy records of his lineage? 

A correspondent who has extensively researched this subject writes: 

"It appears to me that Hitler knew about his connection long before his Chancellorship. Like his father before him, when the going got rough, the Hitlers went to Vienna. Hitler's father left his home village at an early age to seek his fortune in Vienna. When Hitler was orphaned, after his mother died in December of 1907, he left for Vienna not long after the funeral. There he seemed to drop out of sight for ten months! What happened during this ten-month stay in Vienna is a complete mystery on which history sheds no light. It makes sense, now that it has become established that Hitler was a Rothschild, that he and his cousins were getting aquainted, and his potentiall for future family endeavors was being sized up". 

The Rothschilds and the Illuminati produce many offspring out of wedlock in their secret breeding programmes and these children are brought up under other names with other parents. Like Bill Clinton, who is almost certainly a Rockefeller produced in the same way, these "ordinary kids from ordinary backgrounds" go on to be extraordinarily successful in their chosen field. Hitler, too, would have produced unofficial children to maintain his strand of the bloodline and there will obviously be people of his bloodline alive today. 

So which Rothschild was the grandfather of Hitler? My thanks to a website correspondent for the additional, updated, information to this article, a man has researched this story in some detail. Alois, Hitler's father, was born in 1837 in the period when Salomon Mayer was the only Rothschild who lived at the Vienna mansion. Even his wife did not live there because their marriage was so bad that she stayed in Frankfurt. Their son, Anselm Salomon spent most of his working life in Paris and Frankfurt away from Vienna and his father. 

Father Salomon Mayer, living alone at the Vienna mansion where Hitler's grandmother worked, is the prime, most obvious candidate. And Hermann von Goldschmidt, the son of Salomon Mayer's senior clerk, wrote a book, published in 1917, which said of Salomon: 

"by the 1840s he had developed a somewhat reckless enthusiasm for young girls.." 

and 

"He had a lecherous passion for very young girls, his adventures with whom had to be hushed up by the police." 

And Hitler's grandmother, a young girl working under the same roof would not have been the subject of Salomon's desire? And this same girl became pregnant while working there? And her grandson becomes the Chancellor of Germany, funded by the Rothschilds, and he started the Second World War which was so vital to the Rothschild-Illuminati agenda? And the Illuminati are obsessed with putting their bloodlines into power on all "sides" in a conflict? And the Rothschilds are one of their most key bloodlines? And it is all a co-incidence? 
Rothschild Cartel behind the rise of Hitler also funding communism socialism and world war 
_________________________________________ 

Sometimes the symbolic details speak volumes. 

Emil Georg von Stauss, the president of Germany's largest bank, the Deutsche Bank, lent Hitler a portable Remington so he could write his infamous anti-Jewish banker manifesto "Mein Kampf." 

Von Stauss, a principal Nazi Party fundraiser, also was a longtime business associate of the Rothschilds. 

Hitler dictated "Mein Kampf" to typists Rudolf Hess and Emil Maurice during his cushy eight-months stay at Landsberg Prison in April-December 1924. (His five-year sentence was commuted. He had a two-room suite with a view and was allowed to receive gifts and visitors.) 

Von Stauss was part of a "Hitler support group" consisting of wealthy Illuminati. Helene Bechstein, the wife of the piano manufacturer pretended to be Hitler's adopted mother and smuggled out sections of the manuscript. She took care of all Hitler's expenses and hoped he would marry her daughter Lotte. Franz Thyssen, the chairman of United Steelworks sent Hitler a birthday gift of 100,000 gold marks. 

This account is taken from Rudolf Hess' letters by Belgian author Stan Lauryssens, ("The Man Who Invented the Third Reich" 1999, pp.130-135.) 

It contradicts the image we have of Hitler in 1924 leading a grass roots fringe party. In fact, he was a front man for the international bankers he pretended to oppose. But if we read the "The Protocols of Zion" carefully, we shouldn't be surprised. 

The Secret Masonry is setting up "our own, to all appearance, off position, which in at least one of its organs will present what looks like the very antipodes to us. Our real opponents at heart will accept this simulated opposition as their own and will show us their cards." (Protocol 12.11) 

Both Nazism and Communism were fake opposition concocted by Illuminati bankers. As we are dragged kicking and screaming into the next world war, let's recall that the people who issue our currency are behind every war and control both sides. 

DEUTSCH BANK, VON STAUSS AND ROTHSCHILDS 

The Deutsch Bank helped to create Hitler because he represented war profit. (Branch managers and executives belonged to the Nazi Party.) During the Second World War, the Deutsche Bank profited when it took over banks and industries in occupied countries, "Aryanized" Jewish-owned businesses, and confiscated Jewish accounts. (See Harold James, "The Deutsche Bank and the Nazi Economic War Against the Jews" 2001.) 

Before becoming president of the bank, Von Stauss was General Director of Steaua Romana, a Romanian oil company owned by the bank. He was Managing Director of the European Petroleum Union, (EPU), an oil cartel. The E.P.U. was "an international association of industrialists whose object was to make the greatest possible profit on their products." 

The EPU represented the Rothschild interests, the Nobel interests and the Deutsche Bank interests. The latter two probably included Rothschild interests. 

After the Nazi seizure of power, Von Stauss coordinated the war buildup at major German corporations such as Daimler Benz and BMW, who were connected to Deutsch Bank. 

One book describes him as "an enigmatic character of the Wiemar and National Socialist periods, albeit one who has rarely been given his due in historical studies." While a major supporter, he never became a member of the Nazi Party and "always maintained good relations with prominent economic figures who were Jews such as his colleague Oscar Wassermann at the Deutsch Bank." (David Bankier ed. "Probing the Depth of German Anti Semitism," 2000, pp 256-257.) 

Nevertheless he was instrumental in Aryanizing Jewish assets, even those of Jews who had long ago converted and intermarried. Clearly there were in-Jews and out-Jews, i.e. Illuminati or not. 

WHY BANKERS CREATE WAR 

War is the centerpiece of the bankers' longterm plan to decimate, degrade and enslave humanity, which is necessary to protect their fraudulent world monopoly over our credit. This logic explains the real meaning of "revolution," and why they consider war "revolutionary." 

Mankind is stymied because a tiny clique usurped control of money making. This began when gold dealers realized they could issue receipts for gold they didn't have. They became bankers who figured they could also issue more loans than they have money, by a simple bookkeeping entry. 

They used this Golden Goose to take control of the world's wealth and put accomplices in charge of government, media and education. They arranged for our national governments to guarantee the paper they print. 

War distracts us from this state of affairs, degrades, brutalizes, and increases debt and profits. (The bankers naturally put most faith in government debt.) Central bankers also love socialism. They buy people with their own debt. 

Woodrow Wilson was a pawn of this "money power." But to save his soul, he said American industrialists are afraid of "a power somewhere, so organized, so subtle, so watchful, so interlocked, so complete, so pervasive" that they dared not speak above their breath. 

Wilson actually identified this power: 

"The great monopoly in this country is the monopoly of big credits. A great industrial nation is controlled by its system of credits. The growth of the nation, therefore, and all of our activities, are in the hands of a few men who chill and check and destroy genuine economic freedom." (Robertson, Human Ecology, p. 166.) 

CONCLUSION 

War, including the "war on terror", is designed to create a world police state to protect the central banker monopoly on power and wealth. With the exception of Ron Paul and Dennis Kucinich, it doesn’t really matter who gets elected. They all work for the central bankers. 

The Illuminati bankers sacrificed Jews when they created Nazism, Communism and Zionism. If necessary, they will do so again to create their New World Order. 
Masons, Bilderbergs, Jesuits and Zionists are all empowered by the bankers. Mankind will never get on the right foot until bankers turn over their power to create money using our credit. In the meantime, our lives are shaped by a series of fantastic hoaxes, not the least of which is war. 

Hitler Was A Rothschild controlled JEW - 3 of 12 - Alex Jones - 2010-08-25 
Hitler Was A Rothschild controlled JEW - 3 of 12 - Alex Jones - 2010-08-25 

The Rothschilds &amp; The Two World Wars 
The Rothschilds &amp; The Two World Wars 

Hitler Was a British Agent - Greg Hallett . Rothschild Zionists Funded Both Hitler &amp; Churchill 
Hitler Was a British Agent - Greg Hallett . Rothschild Zionists Funded Both Hitler &amp; Churchill 

Who Financed Adolf Hitler? 
We do know that prominent European and American industrialists were sponsoring all manner of totalitarian political groups at that time, including Communists and various Nazi groups. The U.S. Kilgore Committee records that: 

By 1919 Krupp was already giving financial aid to one of the reactionary political groups which sowed the seed of the present Nazi ideology. Hugo Stinnes was an early contributor to the Nazi Party (National Socialistische Deutsche Arbeiter Partei). By 1924 other prominent industrialists and financiers, among them Fritz Thyssen, Albert Voegler, Adolph [sic] Kirdorf, and Kurt von Schroder, were secretly giving substantial sums to the Nazis. In 1931 members of the coalowners' association which Kirdorf headed pledged themselves to pay 50 pfennigs for each ton of' coal sold, the money to go to the organization which Hitler was building.3 

Hitler's 1924 Munich trial yielded evidence that the Nazi Party received $20,000 from Nuremburg industrialists. The most interesting name from this period is that of Emil Kirdorf, who had earlier acted as conduit for financing German involvement in the Bolshevik Revolution.4 Kirdorfs role in financing Hitler was, in his own words: 

In 1923 I came into contact for the first time with the National-Socialist movement .... I first heard the Fuehrer in the Essen Exhibition Hall. His clear exposition completely convinced and overwhelmed me. In 1927 I first met the Fuehrer personally. I travelled to Munich and there had a conversation with the Fuehrer in the Bruckmann home. During four and a half hours Adolf Hitler explained to me his programme in de tail. I then begged the Fuehrer to put together the lecture he had given me in the form of a pamphlet. I then distributed this pamphlet in my name in business and manufacturing circles. 

Since then I have placed myself completely at the disposition of his movement, Shortly after our Munich conversation, and as a result of the pamphlet which the Fuehrer composed and I distributed, a number of meetings took place between the Fuehrer and leading personalities in the field of indus. try. For the last time before the taking over of power, the leaders of industry met in my house together with Adolf Hitler, Rudolf Hess, Hermann Goering and other leading personalities of the party.5 
http://reformed-theology.org/html/books/wall_street/chapter_07.htm﻿ 

Rothschild Family Time Line 
His five sons were spread throughout Europe in the late 1700s and early 1800s – in Frankfurt, Vienna, London, Naples, and Paris – forming a financial dynasty. In June of 1815, Nathan Rothschild’s secret courier network was the first to make it back to London with news that Napoleon’s French troops had been defeated by the British at Waterloo. Rothschild, who, as usual, had funded both sides in the war, cunningly pretended that the French had won and started dumping British “consuls” on the stock exchange. The market plummeted and then Nathan quietly started buying up everything in sight, and by the time the real news of Britain’s success in the battle reached the public in London, the House of Rothschild had bought control of the British economy. By the mid 1800s they dominated the banking industry, funding people such as the Morgans, Vanderbilts, Carnegies, and Cecil Rhodes.﻿ 
Show less﻿ 
Show less﻿

Meer lezen (1330 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QGWk3q2KPbM/U1grSieFdPI/AAAAAAACtDE/ky_3CMnjBAE/w426-h582/BlXW4FyCUAAZnUJ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/109751346983763043211/albums/5691565591578758545/5691565599017912354</link><title>It is the birthday of Andrew Johnson (1808), the 17th President of the United States, who succeeded Abraham Lincoln after the assassination. Originally a Tennessee Democrat, he was elected Vice President on Lincoln's second-term ticket as a candidate of the splinter Free Soil Party. Under Lincoln he advocated emancipation and rights of freedmen but when he became President his white supremacist views became apparent. He vetoed the Civil Rights Act, which gave black people the right to vote, and was overridden by Congress. He also gave pardons to Southern Confederacy leaders, engendering ire in the North. He was the first President ever impeached by the House, though the measure failed in the Senate. He is generally regarded among the worst Presidents in history.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-7D0HnlaoFwk/TvyAwdFLyCI/AAAAAAAAAVk/E6XwQGKCfsM/w426-h628/AndrewJohnson.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/104082778585748794509/albums/5695995064561555409/5695995065533623122</link><title>Lincoln MKZ Concept: Future Vision Today 
http://www.conceptcarz.com/z21033/Lincoln-MKZ-Concept.aspx 
The new Lincoln MKZ Concept, revealed today at the North American International Auto Show, signals a significant step in Lincoln's reinvention, providing a clear vision of its next-generation vehicles. 

'With the Lincoln MKZ Concept, we are not introducing a new car. We are essentially introducing a new brand,' said Derrick Kuzak, Ford Motor Company group vice president for Global Product Development. 'The MKZ Concept is the next step in the reinvention of Lincoln, something we've been quietly but aggressively pursuing.'﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zuBd168_TB8/Tww9VVuCa1I/AAAAAAAAA4c/2mV-C2KWWYc/w426-h237/Lincoln-MKZ_Concept-Sedan-2012-Image-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/107134874156233891178/albums/5745590250074986257/5745590251142286626</link><title>Abraham Lincoln never quits. 

Born into poverty, Lincoln was faced with defeat throughout his life. He lost eight elections, twice failed in business and suffered a nervous breakdown. 

He could have quit many times – but he didn’t and because he didn’t quit, he became one of the greatest presidents in the United States history. 

Here is a sketch of Lincoln’s road to the White House: 

1816 His family was forced out of their home. He had to work to support them. 
1818 His mother died. 
1831 Failed in business. 
1832 Ran for state legislature – lost. 
1832 Also lost his job – wanted to go to law school but couldn’t get in. 
1833 Borrowed some money from a friend to begin a business and by the end of the year he was bankrupt. He spent the next 17 years of his life paying off this debt. 
1834 Ran for state legislature again – won. 
1835 Was engaged to be married, sweetheart died and his heart was broken. 
1836 Had a total nervous breakdown and was in bed for six months. 
1838 Sought to become speaker of the state legislature – defeated. 
1840 Sought to become elector – defeated. 
1843 Ran for Congress – lost. 
1846 Ran for Congress again – this time he won – went to Washington and did a good job. 
1848 Ran for re-election to Congress – lost. 
1849 Sought the job of land officer in his home state – rejected. 
1854 Ran for Senate of the United States – lost. 
1856 Sought the Vice-Presidential nomination at his party’s national convention – get less than 100 votes. 
1858 Ran for U.S. Senate again – again he lost. 
1860 Elected president of the United States.﻿

Meer lezen (34 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-zj_FqjEAPes/T7xv5FhIjSI/AAAAAAAAABE/5ZlF8Gi5yck/w426-h328/574952_415402225157191_127603680603715_1328307_6330944_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/106292767786679411800/albums/6002488331410939393/6002488332019651154</link><title>On this day in 1865, Abraham Lincoln passes away. He had been shot by an assassin the day before. 

On Good Friday, the President decided to attend a comedy at Ford’s Theater in Washington, D.C. It had been only 5 days since General Robert E. Lee surrendered to General Ulysses S. Grant, bringing the Civil War to a close. As the President watched from his box, an assassin burst through the door and shot Lincoln in the back of the head. The assassin, John Wilkes Booth, then dropped his pistol and began waving a dagger in the air. 

Another occupant of the box, Major Henry R. Rathbone, lunged for Booth and forced him toward the railing. Booth leapt from the box shouting “Sic semper Tyrannis! The South is avenged!” His boot caught on a flag as he jumped, and his leg was broken when he landed. Despite his injury, Booth managed to flee the scene. 

In the meantime, a doctor in the audience had made it upstairs to Lincoln’s box. The bullet had lodged behind the President’s right eye. Lincoln was carried, barely breathing, across the street to a boardinghouse. He died a little after 7:00 a.m. on April 15. 

You may or may not know that Booth had co-conspirators who were trying to assassinate other members of Lincoln’s cabinet. One accomplice, Lewis Powell (a.k.a. Lewis Payne), attacked the Secretary of State, William Henry Seward, on the same night that Lincoln was shot. Seward was at home recovering from a carriage accident. Powell talked his way into the house and slashed Seward’s throat. He left, believing that he’d killed Seward. However, Seward was wearing a metal surgical collar—the collar saved his life. 

Booth and his co-conspirators also intended to kill Vice President Andrew Johnson and General Ulysses S. Grant. Instead, Booth’s four co-conspirators were convicted and hung for their crimes. 

As for Booth, he was discovered hiding in a barn in Virginia several days after he assassinated Lincoln. He was killed during the attempt to capture him. 

&lt;del&gt;\------------&lt;/del&gt; 
If you enjoyed this post, please don't forget to +1 and SHARE. Our schools and media don’t always teach the stories of our founding! Let’s do it ourselves. 

Gentle reminder: Morning history posts are copyright © 2013, 2014 by Tara Ross. I appreciate it when you use the Google+ “share” feature instead of cutting/pasting. 

#TDIH #AmericanHistory #USHistory﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Gp5Mu98tISA/U00fVd51UlI/AAAAAAAABe0/g6Hbg__67gI/w426-h769/1505db8d-358b-4c56-975b-dc6cf380ee73</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/117925078332680845741/albums/5834437567793675185/5834437570055122738?authkey=CLjCu4C_46zWBw</link><title>This is interesting! 
(Along with everything else at +Smithsonian Magazine!) 

Smithsonian 
President Lincoln’s Inaugural Ball Invitation, 1865 

On Nov. 8, 1864, with the Civil War in its final stages and only six weeks before his assassination at nearby Ford’s Theater, President Lincoln was elected for a second presidential term. 

On the evening of March 6, 1865, a $10 ticket admitted “one gentleman and two ladies” to President Lincoln’s second inaugural ball, held in the elegant building that now contains the Smithsonian American Art Museum. 

The honor of company was requested by President Lincoln and Vice President Andrew Johnson through this paper invitation to the National Inauguration Ball. Engraved by Demsey &amp; O’Toole, the invitation includes the inaugural ball committee managers listed in three columns. 

What would it have been like to attend the ball? A National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Institution curator imagines what it would be like to experience it: http://s.si.edu/gTAXk 

Check it out:﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-xJUOSfZmLfg/UPgWDstULzI/AAAAAAAACbw/MgBWyMrK17M/w426-h592/Lincoln%2BInauguration.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/113206013512040331335/albums/5840602388975589201/5840602518276997922</link><title>An 1863 Daguerreotype of Lincoln, at the age of 54. 
16th President of the United States 
In office March 4, 1861–April 15, 1865 
Vice President Hannibal Hamlin 1861–1865 
Andrew Johnson 1865 
Preceded by James Buchanan 
Succeeded by Andrew Johnson 
Member of the U.S. House of Representatives 
from Illinois's 7th district 
In office March 4, 1847–March 4, 1849 
Preceded by John Henry 
Succeeded by Thomas Harris 
Personal details 
Born February 12, 1809 
Hodgenville, Kentucky, U.S. 
Died April 15, 1865 aged 56 
Petersen House 
Washington, D.C., U.S. 
Resting place Lincoln's Tomb, Oak Ridge Cemetery 
Springfield, Illinois, U.S. 
Nationality American 
Political party Republican 1854–1865 
National Union 1864–1865 
Other political 
affiliations Whig Before 1854 
Spouse(s) Mary Todd 
Children Robert Todd Lincoln 
Edward Baker Eddie Lincoln 
William Wallace Willie Lincoln 
Thomas Tad Lincoln 
Profession Lawyer 
Politician 
Military service 
Service/branch Illinois Militia 
Years of service 1832 
Rank Captain 
Battles/wars Black Hawk War﻿

Meer lezen (33 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-UQGCzof_gPA/UQ39C6gnAyI/AAAAAAAA_GU/kmiW_2ZJreI/w426-h544/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/104082778585748794509/albums/5726979071775044177/5726979074553194962</link><title>http://www.conceptcarz.com/z21362/Lincoln-MKZ.aspx 

The all-new Lincoln MKZ makes its debut at the New York International Auto Show, marking a key milestone in Lincoln's reinvention. 

'The new Lincoln MKZ represents the future of Lincoln in both style and substance,' said Jim Farley, Group Vice President, Global Marketing, Sales and Service. 'It is proof of our commitment to deliver a new breed of Lincolns for a new generation of Lincoln clients – motor cars that are distinctive, elegant, full of technology and a delight to own.'﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-kGIT4Bk4ti8/T3pRIB7WqdI/AAAAAAAADOM/CY_weFkE9ys/w426-h277/2013-Lincoln-MKZ_Sedan-Image-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7217-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/who%20was%20lincolns%20vice%20president/photos/108447489553774449640/albums/5938289981330211937/5938289987512041570</link><title>Persistence is stronger than failure. Abraham Lincoln's record. 

1831: Failed in business 
1832: Defeated for legislature 
1833: Failed in business again 
1834: Elected to legislature 
1835: Sweetheart died 
1836: Had a nervous breakdown 
1838: Defeated for speaker 
1840: Defeated for elector 
1843: Defeated for congressional nomination 
1846: Elected to Congress 
1848: Defeated for Congress 
1855: Defeated for Senate 
1856: Defeated for Vice President 
1859: Defeated for Senate 
1860: Elected President of the United States 

More  - http://blog.lifemanifestos.com/abraham-lincoln-persistence-stronger-failure/﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7217_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ttoooj2sgO4/UmkLR_7qAGI/AAAAAAAAC9Q/34ngyyGeqLQ/w426-h320/IMG_20131018_190302.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>