<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 17:47:09" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/115291256283155802113/albums/5688310317571065009/5688310317415954498</link><title>(Virtual) Flight of the (Nauseated) Navigator 

"After sessions in flight simulators, highly trained pilots...get 'simulator sickness': they tend to crash their cars, become nauseated, and so on...[Why] is it that after flying real planes, and seeing roughly the same sorts of images as as in the simulator, pilots do not tend to crash their cars, become sick, and so on?" (David Morris, The Sense of Space, 2004) 

While it may be tempting to assume the pilot's disorientation and nausea to be the result of prolonged immersion in a primitively-rendered environment or the effects of navigating an uncanny topology, this answer is too narrow. What it fails to take into account is the interdependent cooperation of the various perceptual systems in the subject's experience and exploration of the environment (See James J. Gibson's excellent The Senses Considered as Perceptual Systems, 1966). Although it's imprudent and perhaps misleading to speak of the subject or her perceptual systems in such monolithic terms, I think in this instance it helps to decompose the traditional presumptions of atomic sensations and clearly defined "senses" or perceptual organs. 

Regardless of the level of graphical sophistication in the simulation, the pilot of the virtual aircraft does not have access to the same rich reservoir of perceptual information as can be found in the natural environment. This discontinuity with and alienation from the environment is then experienced as nausea. The pilot may in a limited sense see her virtual environment, but she cannot feel it's full presence from this partial and incomplete data set. As Morris (and Gibson before him) would say, you don't see with your eyes, but with your entire body. 

(Image: screenshot from the computer game Microsoft Flight Simulator X) 

P.S., if you need to cleanse your palette after this post (or maybe just I do?), then please enjoy this trailer for the fantastic and classic Pee-Wee Herman as an alien spaceship from the future film, Flight of the Navigator: http://youtu.be/XnB7rIL2fy8﻿

Meer lezen (35 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-O489S6-jU3E/TvDwGIHEeEI/AAAAAAAAC8A/rpaY-Y2TMU0/w426-h324/flightsimulator-x.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/100845053883350365874/albums/5975293325456873249/5975293326211476482</link><title>Captain's Trivia: Flight Simulator 
Flight simulators are mainly used for pilot training/exams but also provides pilots with a highly realistic training experience. One is known as the "Smoke Generator" for a cockpit smoke emergency. Vegetable oil is used to create actual (but harmless) smoke. Flight simulators are essential to flight safety! 
#flightsafety #safety #flightsimulator #pilottraining  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-KGMYQim7yVI/UuyBnymY7AI/AAAAAAAAAtw/eil6tlOBmhc/w426-h320/1618621_10152150097875536_1140062736_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/106946780945801510575/albums/5882278833784309361/5882278904712518306</link><title>Flight simulators﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uqO0aRpSB4E/UaINf4kp2qI/AAAAAAAAAXM/XxA5jZq7sAw/w426-h284/foto07.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/112943946047332492941/albums/5915005064737106497/5915005064272707298</link><title>Sensors and flight simulators are helping scientists understand how fatigued pilots function at 30,000 feet. Their goal is to make sure you land safely at your destination. 

http://bit.ly/12t6JEN﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-JQ31LUfYUM0/UhZRxFScfuI/AAAAAAAAN_Y/qwbURcF9V2k/w426-h304/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/104050123095171815400/albums/5835454782302754193/5835454782385701698?authkey=CJDT-OKOufuJmgE</link><title>I mentioned this in our hangout (re: flight simulators).﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-SjLJXDFORKU/UPuzNP70Q0I/AAAAAAAABpQ/XGERy1Uu8Cs/w426-h577/A22106DE-3F6C-433E-A3C7-669C08890AEE.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/117817366279516597276/albums/5862771869767818737/5862771875157524594?authkey=CMT_tIXk59aWjAE</link><title>Do you think clinical simulators are equally important as flight simulators? We do. Did you know we have close to 3 dozen human patient simulators for our crews and plans for another two dozen?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-uPAt1b5LuNY/UVy_9UnqQHI/AAAAAAAAAKw/IqsZdrQQ-kc/w426-h285/482192_586671504691126_456672459_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/109968107710438362917/albums/5988177828076033585/5988177834401536962</link><title>Within recent times I have taken up the hobby of flight simulators, I am not sure that I get the glider plane, although I imagine that quite a few people do. I guess my thing is that you need a tow to get you up there. 

SOARING WITH GLIDER BOB 

http://itsogs.com/2014/03/soaring-with-glider-bob/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-c5hiwOY4TOg/UxpIA39fG8I/AAAAAAAAgcQ/zohN6Xx_zsY/w426-h238/x240-kOm.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/114426643380533041038/albums/5945589008415618913/5945589007736066690</link><title>Christchurch-based flight simulator manufacturer, Pacific Simulators, has completed deals that will lead to its Flight Experience stores opening in the United States and China: http://buff.ly/1aDA4f7﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-cMm6swqAto8/UoL5s5KTUoI/AAAAAAAACQo/bTmKlfLpONg/w426-h237/ea0dcb9b-0a10-4b11-a73f-65f74b46e7eb</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/114871758977113366934/albums/5997589511530224961/5997589512482205042</link><title>Fan of Flight Simulators? Come to Hobbitech this weekend at the John Barrable Hall in Benoni to try out this one -﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-f7FsO3Z8uoA/Uzu34pAcLXI/AAAAAAAABU4/jJ6eXTt5g7A/w426-h319/56ngU.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7241-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/flight%20simulators/photos/116558795524534766084/albums/5839281629118224177/5839281634129694738?authkey=CMrn9Ojam56ZsgE</link><title>"Oak and ply computer desk. I fly flight simulators and wanted a realistic cockpit to fly my computer from. LOL It has teak and oak inlay to form a waving checkered flag on the sides and armrests." - By Richard R. Welch 

Show Us Your Custom Computer Table.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7241_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-HD8NQzNLWQ4/UQlLtVnDUBI/AAAAAAAAAvo/VtRgZ7Um6-I/w426-h320/100_0116.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>