<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 05:48:54" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/113811492775425960680/albums/5854036979578392945/5854036978498452050?authkey=CN6Yz57b1czjCg</link><title>The Hague Conference on Private International Law has issued its Second Guide on Accreditation and Adoption Accredited Bodies under the 1993 Hague Convention 

Accreditation practice differs widely. The understanding and implementation of the Convention’s obligations and terminology vary greatly. It is recognised that there is an urgent need to bring some common or shared understanding to this important aspect of intercountry adoption to achieve greater consistency in the operation of accredited bodies. 

The purpose of this Guide is therefore to have an accessible resource, expressed in plain language, which is available to Contracting States, accredited bodies, parents and all those other actors involved in intercountry adoption. The Guide aims to: 

• that the principles and obligations of the Convention apply to all actors in Hague Convention intercountry adoptions; 

• clarify the Convention obligations and standards for the establishment and operation of accredited bodies; 

• encourage acceptance of higher standards than the minimum standards of the Convention; 

• identify good practices to implement those obligations and standards; and 

• propose a set of model accreditation criteria which will assist Contracting States to achieve greater consistency in the professional standards and practices of their accredited bodies. 

It is hoped that this Guide will assist the accrediting and supervising authorities in the Contracting States to perform their obligations more comprehensively at the national level, and thereby achieve more consistency at the international level. 

 It can be freely downloaded here: http://www.hcch.net/upload/adoguide2en.pdf 

http://www.hcch.net/index_en.php?act=publications.details&amp;pid=5504&amp;dtid=3﻿

Meer lezen (39 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-WgLmYwcJ1pQ/UT23na1mulI/AAAAAAAABf0/oqpt2xDIw-k/w426-h237/Hcch.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/109995777873026216796/albums/5736083936838988993/5736083940862102850</link><title>Third World Country -- Constitutional Rights 
Geneva Convention -- Protection of Third World 
Hague Law -- Human Rights (Basic Privacy)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-n-6UOzSqEB4/T5qp9ADojUI/AAAAAAAAAAs/058fIcHnDCs/w426-h320/U+S+Marshalls+couldn%27t+see+this.MPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/117661322411522129396/albums/5776986521573011201/5776986526094629986</link><title>FSA using illegal led tip expanding ammunition in Syria 

I found an image on telegraph.co.uk where FSA terrorist loading their magazines during clashes with Syrian Army in the Salaheddine neighbourhood. 

As far as i can see on this picture it looks like they are using led tip ammunition which are illegal and a war crime. 

"The Hague Convention of 1899, Declaration III, prohibits the use in international warfare of bullets which easily expand or flatten in the body, giving as example a bullet with a jacket with incisions or one that does not fully cover the core.[14] This is often incorrectly believed to be prohibited in the Geneva Conventions, but it significantly predates those conventions, and is in fact a continuance of the Declaration of St Petersburg in 1868, which banned exploding projectiles of less than 400 grams." 

You find more information about this type of ammunition on wikipedia here: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Expanding_bullet 

Picture: REUTERS/Goran Tomasevic 
Source: http://goo.gl/rvzQn﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-LrjcSaekv2U/UCv6o0AWnGI/AAAAAAAADhA/jHK4dKAHClE/w426-h318/20120807-magazine_2303958k.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/115079117807033796132/albums/5933560041087537585/5933560042888705266</link><title>Global chemical weapons watchdog wins 2013 Nobel Peace Prize 

The Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons won the Nobel Peace Prize on Friday for working to eliminate the scourge that has haunted generations from World War I to the battlefields of Syria. 
The OPCW was formed in 1997 to enforce the Chemical Weapons Convention, the first international treaty to outlaw an entire class of weapons. Based in The Hague, Netherlands, it has largely worked out of the limelight until this year, when the United Nations called on its expertise to help investigate alleged chemical weapons attacks in Syria. 

More Info - http://y.ahoo.it/ZNWDY 

#nobelpeaceprize #nobelprize #foxnews #breaking #OPCW  ﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-75K9Xixmr9M/Ulg9a_HVNPI/AAAAAAAABJ4/wTQEHzVs-ZI/w426-h284/opcw.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/104710531226567482127/albums/5994710547055988465/5994710551133238738</link><title>Pakistan for global efforts against nuclear terrorism 

THE HAGUE: Pakistan assured world community that it is considering ratification of the 2005 Amendment to the Convention on Physical Protection of Nuclear Material (CPPNM) and are actively conducting a review to meet its various requirements. 
Pakistan has also called for its inclusion in all international export control regimes, especially the nuclear suppliers group and international treaties and forums should supplement national actions to fortify nuclear security. 

http://goo.gl/thMrpO﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-26A0BoFGBpE/UzF9fCOVNdI/AAAAAAAABkE/0tG_Yo70EBs/w426-h237/53305bc7daadf-660x330.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/111305510462394592332/albums/5894253583662432593/5894253586176309138?authkey=CImU8smYtvq3FQ&amp;sqi=116868486074545793953&amp;sqsi=c52c670c-e5c6-43b9-a4c2-1c7dc2d1dd7f</link><title>Experts recommend the Government recognize the United Nations Convention on the law of the sea of 1982, to be able to defend their rights against the petitions of the Nicaraguan people. 
"The continental shelf of Nicaragua is spread over an immense space of almost 500 miles of extension. Unlike the natural platform of Colombia, which is very short, like that of Panama and most of countries of the Caribbean in South America", explained Carlos Argüello, Ambassador of Nicaragua to the Hague, in a recent interview published in the press in his country. It added the brains of the Nicaraguan defense than the privileged continental shelf which has your country and the maritime spaces which are "not can be depleted, regardless of who has mastery of four stones that are irrigated out there".﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-5Rp-ywyqVLQ/UcyYaFQcd5I/AAAAAAAANb0/TirXdDaZ3n0/w426-h288/nicaragua-200%255B1%255D.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/107091251485500137914/albums/5810701633488842769/5810701639396370642</link><title>استخدام صور عدوك حيا أو ميتا انتهاك 

انظروا مع من يتصورون ؟؟ 

 And if you are not satisfied, now, with the truth the following pictures are war crimes as defined by the UN, The Hague and the Geneva Convention. 

 Using images of your enemy dead or alive (violation) ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-itEW0PPet8g/UKPCWsgAKNI/AAAAAAAAACA/dL1P0Epeu5g/w426-h917/%25D9%258A%25D9%2587%25D9%2588%25D8%25AF.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/101011928831325188678/albums/5845408632340888497/5845408638878887970</link><title>( Faces of Abducted Canadian Children ) ABDUCTED from CANADA to POLAND - Alexander &amp; Christopher Watkins - (Press “See More” below) - Stephen Watkins is a member of the iCHAPEAU Association. Stephen Watkins is a Canadian citizen and father of ALEXANDER WATKINS (aka: Aleksander Ustaszewski) and CHRISTOPHER WATKINS (aka: Krzysztof Ustaszewski) also known world-wide in the news and through social media as the "Watkins Missing Children" from Canada. Both Alexander and Christopher were born in Canada and their father, Stephen Watkins, was granted sole custody by the Ontario Courts in January 26, 2009 after a 7-day trial with liberal access visits every second weekend to their mother. 

PHOTO: http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=412068622193132 

The boys were living with their mother, Edyta ( Ustaszewski / Ustaszewska ) Watkins, initially upon separation in 2004 with a Joint Custody Agreement finalized through the Ontario Courts in 2006 but the children were later apprehended by the Children’s Aid Society and the Ontario Courts in 2007 after reports were made by the teachers of the children’s school and daycare of serious child protection concerns. The boys lived with their father full time since 2007 until they were internationally abducted out of Canada 6-weeks after the courts January 26, 2009 ruling. Stephen Watkins was married to Edyta Watkins ( Ustaszewski / Ustaszewska ) and has been fighting to bring his sons back to Canada after they were abducted by their non-custodial mother, missing for 2.5 years and then found living under different names in the country of Poland. Alexander &amp; Christopher Watkins have been held in Poland against the father’s will more than 3 years. 

Alexander &amp; Christopher Watkins were abducted internationally from Canada into the United States then to Europe on March 6, 2009 with the use of a "Canceled" Canadian Passport by the non-custodial Mother, Edyta Watkins and two Canadian Passports for the children where she refused to turn over to the Ontario Courts who ordered their return on multiple court appearances. The Ontario Courts failed to enforce their own orders and did not take any action even though the issue of an International Child Abduction was very likely which was brought up by the father’s legal council to the Judge during the custody trial in December 2008. The Abducting mother's Drivers License and Canadian Passport had been confirmed Canceled by the Ontario Government and confirmed by the Ombudsman of Passport Canada 42-Days prior to the abduction of the Watkins Children due to Provincial Enforcement measures from non-payment of Child Support. The children's Canadian Passports were ordered by the Courts to be handed over repeatedly, with the non-custodial Mother refusing to comply. U.S. Homeland Security confirmed with Canadian Authorities that all three flew Delta Airlines Flight 51 to Frankfort Germany using 3-Canadian Passports. 

Poland, who has been a non-complaint member of the Hague Convention for years has ordered the two Canadian children NOT to return home to Canada even though they were in hiding for more than 1.5 years either in Germany or in Poland. In addition, in contravention to the Hague Convention procedures, it took the Polish Courts 11-months to contact the searching father and Canadian authorities on the whereabouts of the missing Canadian boys even though another Polish Court already had a Hague Convention Application field by Canadian authorities and Ordered Polish Police to search Poland-wide on January 8, 2010. Polish Court papers documents that as early as September 14, 2010 show that the missing / abducted Canadian boys were living in the owned residence of the Edyta’s father, Tadeusz (TED) Ustaszewski, in Warsaw Poland. Polish Police later confirmed this information with York Regional Police in Canada. Tadeusz Ustaszewski, who lives in Canada, had refused to help York Regional Police help locate the missing children. 

To make matters worse, while the boys were in hiding without the knowledge of their father or the Canadian Authorities, they were secretly enrolled into a Polish School in 2010 with different names without the knowledge by Polish Police authorities. In 2010 the Polish School witnessed child protection concerns and brought a court action themselves against the mother in the Polish Courts where her parental rights were ordered “Limited” by the Courts. Neither the Polish School nor the Polish Courts contacted the Polish Police to check to see if there were any Police reports issued for the children. The Polish courts assigned a Court Appointed Guardian to oversee the children’s welfare in Poland, but due to polish language issues, they left the boys in the direct care of the accused mother. 

Their grandfather, Tadeusz (TED) Ustaszewski, in Canada was charged by York Regional Police (YRP) in Ontario with assisting in this International Child Abduction and the children's disappearance. He solely picked up the boys at their schools in Newmarket for a supervised weekend visit with their non-custodial mother but instead drove all of them across into the United States and left them at a U.S. Tim Horton's coffee shop before returning alone to Canada. The boys were to be brought back to their school in Newmarket the next day as he had previously done many times before. 

In a criminal court case ruling against the grandfather in the "Watkins Missing Children" International Child Abduction held on August 23, 2012 the Canadian Courts found the maternal father, Tadeusz Ted Ustaszewski, GUILTY of assisting his daughter and the non-custodial mother, Edyta Ustaszewska, in the International Parental Child Abduction Case of Alexander Watkins &amp; Christopher Watkins. Sentencing and victim impact statements are scheduled for October 24, 2012 in the Newmarket Courts, Ontario, Canada. 

It was also communicated by his Honor in the Criminal Courts that with the guilty finding of Tadeusz Ustaszewski in this case that it had also been determined that the abducting non-custodial mother, Edyta Ustaszewska, was also clearly in breach of Canadian Laws in this international kidnapping but the Country of Poland has yet to take any actions against the non-custodial mother who's name appears on the RCMP's "Canada most Wanted" list and on and INTERPOL "Red Notice" issued by Canada since 2010. Both Canada and Poland are both signatories of the INTERPOL treaty. 

Even though the Polish lower Courts have refused to Order the Canadian boys back to Canada, Stephen Watkins is now fighting and brining this case before the Superior Courts of Poland for the return of his sons back to Canada. Like so many other left behind parents in the same situation around the world, he feels like he is doing it alone with not only dealing with his metal anguish of not being able to see his own child but also being burden with huge costs of paying for courts, lawyers and translations. 

Poland has a long history of non-compliance when returning abducted children through the “Hague Convention On The Civil Aspects Of International Child Abduction” and Poland is also signatory of the “U.N. Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties (VCLT)” and the “U.N. Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC)” where International Child Abduction is addressed which is why Stephen Watkins believes that the only way Polish Government will comply to the Hague Convention is if the Canadian government helps to enforce treaties that Poland or other nations are signatories to bring back home Canadian citizens. 

PHOTO: http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=412068622193132 

Follow “Watkins Missing Children” case here: 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/Watkins.Missing.Children 
YOUTUBE: http://www.youtube.com/stephenawatkins 
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/Child_Abduction (@Child_Abduction) 
WEBSITE: http://www.Watkins-Missing-Children.com/ ﻿

Meer lezen (138 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_08_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-8giWQrlWMeQ/UR8QL89gMCI/AAAAAAAAAaY/q2g6_fyZt-g/w426-h292/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/101011928831325188678/albums/5845408386815784225/5845408389883442610</link><title>( Faces of Abducted Canadian Children ) ABDUCTED from CANADA to BRAZIL - Alice Pires Caetano - (Press “See More” below) - Cesar Pimenta Caetano is a member of the iCHAPEAU Association. Cesar Pimenta is a Canadian citizen with Brazilian heritage and father of Alice Pires Caetano, who was born in Toronto Canada, nine years ago. He was married to Luciana Pires Caetano and has been fighting to bring his daughter back to Canada after she was wrongfully retained in Brazil. Alice has been held in Brazil against the father’s will more than 3 years. It's important to highlight this abduction is recurrent, as Alice was held in Brazil by her mother some years before. 

PHOTO: http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=409882319078429 

In October 2003, his former wife was still without legal status in Canada and went to Brazil on a condition of waiting for immigration documents. After 15 days, she said that she would not return to Canada any more. 

Urgently, the father filed complaint of international kidnapping to the Ontario Central Authority of Canada who immediately sent the complaint to the Hague Central Authority of Brazil. 

The process was left in hold, forgotten in Brazil; however, the taking parent had regretted the illegal act and returned to Canada to live with her husband in December 2005. They lived together until 2007 when the couple separated. 

In July 2008, custody was given to the mother, with visitation rights for the father, but the Order was made with these important points: 

~Court Order July 15, 2008 - Paragraph~ 

# 3 - The Applicant (mother) shall not remove the child from Canada without the written consent of respondent. 

# 5 - The Respondent waives the requirement of parental consent for the applicant to travel with the child outside Ontario, Canada if the travel is 45 days or less. If more than 45 days, consent will not be unreasonably withheld by Respondent. The Applicant will provide a contact number and address of travel destination to Respondent for emergency purposes and telephone access. 

In October 2009, the father was going back to court to increase his visitation order with his daughter but the mother had delayed the court matter 3 times. The 3rd court date was scheduled for October 29, 2009 but records show that the mother had fled Canada on October 28, the day before the court date. 

As soon she arrived in Brazil, she went into hiding. 

The left behind father again reported the Central Authority of Canada this situation in February 2010 and only in August 2010 the Brazilian attorneys had request judicial enforcement of the Hague Convention. 

The Brazilian government attorneys were careless and inept leaving this case in limbo for a substantially time, damaging the child which should be in Canada, growing and developing in the country that she was born. Alice has been missing the chance to be with her loving and heartbroken father regardless if the mother decided to move back to Brazil. 

The abducting mother used a Women’s shelter named Interim Place in Mississauga, Ontario as a shield to keep her daughter in Brazil by reporting violence without any supporting evidence or investigations by Canadian Police, Children’s Aid Agencies or by Doctors / Hospital records. 

The Interim Place shelter forwarded a letter and their own internal notes directly to Brazilian Court in support of the mother without verifying any of the facts or without providing a clear indication of the source of the allegations. 

Considering Interim Place is not an authority agency in Canada, the Brazilian Courts utilized these case notes and treated them as “fact” rather then allegations. In any reasonable court situation, this amounts to heresy testimony from the Abducting parent to justify their abduction and the preponderance of evidence, as required by the Hague Convention was not met, but still utilized by the Brazilian courts to harbour and retain Alice Caetano from being ordered returned to Canada. 

In attempts to have Interim Place communicate to the Brazilian Courts a statement of clear facts of the supporting evidence and to clarify the notes which they provided directly to the Brazilian Courts, letters were forwarded in and around September 29, 2011 to Interim Place by Canada’s Foreign Affairs and by the Ministry of the Attorney General who operates the Ontario Central Hague Authority. 

In the letter issued by the Ministry of the Attorney General on September 29, 2011 to Interim Place, it stated that; 

“The respondent, mother as named above has absconded with the child, and has made claims abroad that she was abused to due to the fact that she was in your facility.” 

The letter goes on to state that; 

“Traditionally, women who are factually being abused by their partners seek refuge in facilities such as yours, attend court to obtain the appropriate court orders and file a report with the local police.” 

The Ministry of the Attorney General letter then states these facts; 

“Records have been checked and there is NO RELEVANT report with respect to abuse against the mother. She also did not obtain a court order or consent to take the child out of the country; however you housed her and the child and have not provided any causes for your involvement.” 

In addition to these important facts the Ministry of the Attorney General also goes on to state; 

“Although the safety of the mother is surly paramount, the interest of the child was not at all considered when assisting this mother. The respondent mother is a repeat abductor and should your facility conduct sufficient checks on the clientèle, that information would have been realized.” 

After no response was given immediately by Interim Place and in order to put pressure on Interim Place to have meetings or to respond to the previous letters issued by the Canadian and Ontario governments. Cesar Caetano shot a video at one of Interim Place’s public events on July 29, 2012 to show how this organization was handling and avoiding the issues. 

SEE THE VIDEO HERE: Bring Alice Home: 

After waiting over 1 year, a letter was issued on October 4, 2012 by Galldin &amp; Robertson Feminist Lawyers Association Law Firm retained by Interim Place to the Ministry off the Attorney General. In this letter, they completely ignored the Ministry off the Attorney General September 29, 2011 request of information when asking these questions; 

“The mother has made many claims against the father to the Ontario Court and has not been able to prove the violence against her. What recourse is taken to prove a woman claiming to be abused by her partner prior your assistance? What advocacy was applied with the mother; did you help her in court or attend the police station to support her while making a police statement?” 

Instead, Interim Place, through their lawyers issued the following statement in their letter; 

“Without a signed release, Interim Place cannot discuss information shared by any current, or past, client or resident. Interim Place staff and volunteers are not able to confirm whether someone has accessed services or whether someone was a resident of the shelter. Therefore, Interim Place is not able to discuss any details of the confidential services staff may have provided Mr. Caetano’s former partner.” 

Considering that the Abducting mother has allegedly committed a criminal offence of Canada of child abduction and is purposely hiding in another country, it seems controversial that Interim Place would require her signature for the release of information when being requested directly by Ministry of the Attorney General in a Hague Convention on the Civil Aspects of International Child Abduction case? 

Cesar Caetano is still fighting in the Brazilian courts for the return of his Canadian daughter back to Canada. In international cases, it is more complicated when such organizations as Interim Place support international child abductions by NOT conducting sufficient background checks or screening of their clientèle in addition to providing unsupported evidence by the abducting patent to foreign nations court system without any authoritative supporting evidence or investigations by the Canadian Courts, Police, Children’s Aid Agencies, by Doctors or Hospitals. 

Like so many other left behind parents in the same situation around the world, he feels like he is doing it alone with not only dealing with his metal anguish of not being able to see his own child but also being burden with huge costs of paying for courts, lawyers and translations. 

Brazil has a long history of non-compliance when returning abducted children through the “Hague Convention On The Civil Aspects Of International Child Abduction” which is why Cesar believes that the only way Brazilian Government will comply to the Hague Convention is if the Canadian government helps to enforce treaties that Brazil or other nations are signatories to bring back home Canadian citizens. 

PHOTO: http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=409882319078429 

Follow the “Bring Alice Home” case here: 
WEBSITE: http://www.BringAliceHome.com/ 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/BringAliceHome1 
YOUTUBE: http://www.youtube.com/user/BringAliceHome 
TWITTER: http://www.twitter.com/bringalicehome 
QR CODE: http://www.uqr.me/Bring-Alice-Home 

If your Child has been abducted within CANADA &lt;del&gt;or&lt;/del&gt; from CANADA to another country, contact us now. 

Canada’s iCHAPEAU Association 
Please JOIN, LIKE and SUBSCRIBE to all our social links and help to share our cause: 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/iCHAPEAU 
YOUTUBE: http://www.youtube.com/iCHAPEAU 
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/iCHAPEAU_Law(@iCHAPEAU_Law) 
WEBSITE: http://www.iCHAPEAU.ca/ (Under Construction) 
EMAIL: Info@iCHAPEAU.ca— with Dallas Soonias.﻿

Meer lezen (205 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_09_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-xtAWxtL5XXU/UR8P9dYXNbI/AAAAAAAAAao/2j2LaXmY-s0/w426-h292/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7242-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/hague%20convention/photos/117084128288640556986/albums/5975531412090949729/5975531407553552370</link><title>On Friday 24 January 2014, Japan became the 91st Contracting State to the Hague Convention of 25 October 1980 on the Civil Aspects of International Child Abduction. 

Japan's instrument of ratification was deposited by HE Mr Masaru Tsuji, Japan's Ambassador to the Netherlands, who was accompanied by several other officials. The broad delegation underlines the importance that the Japanese Government attaches to this event. Japan's ratification of the Convention is indeed a milestone in the history of the Convention, which will provide a key tool to return children victims of cross-border abduction involving a Japanese parent. 

The Convention will enter into force for Japan on 1 April 2014. ﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7242_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-6K4zrWpe6kw/Uu1aJ8trX_I/AAAAAAAAAOs/BH8fB2SD9po/s426/2014%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>