<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:16:16" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/114419644117023258040/albums/5914727977102057681/5919911138479045170</link><title>727-Pound Alligator Smashes State Records / vidio included 
http://abcnews.go.com/blogs/headlines/2013/09/727-pound-alligator-smashes-state-records/ 
  Email 134 Smaller Font Text Larger Text | Print 
Samantha Riley 
http://abcnews.go.com/blogs/headlines/2013/09/727-pound-alligator-smashes-state-records/ 
By Samantha Riley /@SamanthaRiley9 
Sep 2, 2013 4:35pm 

Alligators heavier than 700 pounds sound straight out of a nightmare for most, but they became record-breaking reality for hunters in Mississippi over the weekend. Two groups of hunters smashed the record for largest gator in the state, not once but twice during opening weekend of alligator season. 

Beth Trammell of Madison, and her team of five broke the previous record of 697.5 pounds early Saturday morning by reeling in a 723.5 pound mammoth. “When we first saw him,” she recalls, “I yelled ‘oh my gosh we caught the Loch Ness Monster!’” It took five hours and the help of two additional hunters, but eventually they hoisted the animal into their boat. “It was totally unbelievable,” Trammell remembers. 

Her record, however, was defeated two hours later by Dustin Bockman, another amateur who managed to wrangle in a 727-pound male, his very first catch. He and two partners struggled with the record-breaker for over four hours in the early morning before pulling him to a sandbar to wait for help. “My goal was to get a 10-footer,” he explained. “I couldn’t believe it when it was that big.” 

These massive creatures come as no surprise to Ricky Flint, Mississippi Alligator Program coordinator. This is the first year there has been a state-wide alligator season, opening up massive new hunting territory to those picked via lottery. “We expect the records to get broken and these will be broken, as well. Maybe before the end of this season,” he said. 

For this challenge, Bockman is ready. “If someone beats my record, I’ll go out and try to top it.” While regulations will force him to wait until next season to reel in anything that large, he remains optimistic. “There’s always a bigger one out there.” Until then, both Trammell and Bockman will mount their harvests to remember their struggles. Trammell is planning a party next weekend to enjoy the meat with friends. 
HT largest alligator 02 jef 130902 16x9 608 727 Pound Alligator Smashes State Records 

Dustin Bockman wrangled a 727 pound alligator, smashing the Mississippi state record. (Image credit: Dustin Bockman)﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-oZzQIpbydMo/Uie_0L7r-jI/AAAAAAAAmcA/BIeQuZRCOpc/w426-h240/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/111614210492112835492/albums/5795260013311675313/5795260021211717714</link><title>This giant alligator was caught in Mississippi. it weighs over 697 pounds. The record was 690.5 pounds, but was broke by this big guy.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-B2d-fDXWCKg/UGzmSOFY4FI/AAAAAAAAABA/DBzWjDR3OnM/w426-h282/awesomeness.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/101241183982769454084/albums/5919270818597514257/5919270822879830962?authkey=CN7b8aKw64jF7wE</link><title>That's a big old Alligator...nothing on the Australian Crock's though 

http://www.clarionledger.com/article/20130901/NEWS01/130901011/Record-largest-Miss-gator-falls-twice 

#alligator   #ride   #australia   #usa   #dunkpunked   #largest  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_03_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Iep_nXhtWfw/UiV5c6cWI7I/AAAAAAABRdQ/xu9LyB1_J_E/w426-h255/Ride-Croc.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/106176762220398854458/albums/5763937298774833665/5763937299347913234</link><title>This my friends is Lolong, the largest crocodile in captivity in the Philippines! Measuring at 20.24 feet long, the 2,368-pound saltwater crocodile was the target of a 3-week long hunt and is suspected of attacking several people and killing two. The only way to verify if it truly is the perpetrator of the attacks however is to actually cut open the entrails and look inside. Officials were able to induce Lolong to vomit, however that did not produce any human remains. The record setting croc appears to be having a positive impact on conservation, with new resolutions being introduced in the Philippine Senate designed to strengthen laws protecting the saltwater and Philippine crocodile, a species considered critically endangered. 

http://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2012/07/120702-biggest-crocodile-lolong-guinness-world-records-animals-science/﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BeqG3uvfJyU/T_2eb2NBuhI/AAAAAAABPYU/wSlBOZ_EQnU/w426-h269/giant-saltwater-crocodile-found-philippines-night_39955_600x450.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/114810779645279671611/albums/5919133086784445953/5919133090191565026?authkey=COfevZ6E6ov7_AE</link><title>Record-setting alligator catches in Mississippi tip the scales, boggle minds. http://ow.ly/ouzSl﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-M3fFe8Wg0_E/UiT8L0Mg4OI/AAAAAAADkQY/S_O98KTTOwo/w426-h283/1075835_634188513267849_341655050_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/114626044795714305855/albums/5773860443433724977/5773860450187633586</link><title>22 foot - 2500 pound Crocodile 

The people in a village on the Niger River in Africa were losing fellow villagers at such a rapid rate, that they had to call in the Army to hunt down the culprit. A 22 foot, 2500 pound Crocodile﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-kjnqAyx4R1M/UCDffPwcY7I/AAAAAAAAKlU/7wpactSIjEw/w426-h329/a.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/108496131965965723428/albums/5788451235338482673/5788451239242142674</link><title>Monster from Congo 
Maximum Length: Up to 5 feet 
Maximum Weight: Up to 154 pounds A True Goliath: When your name is "Goliath," you'd better be one humongous, ferocious creature, and the goliath tigerfish definitely lives up to its moniker. A native of the Congo River basin, the Lualaba River, Lake Upemba and Lake Tanganyika in Africa, it's the largest member of the tigerfish clan, a genus of fierce predators with protruding, daggerlike teeth. The biggest one on record was nearly 5 feet long and weighed 154 pounds, the equivalent of a super-welterweight prizefighter. And it outclasses other African game fish in speed and power. No Fear: Locals say it's the only fish that doesn't fear the crocodile and that it actually eats smaller ones. It's also been known to attack humans in rare instances. It's so lightning quick and forceful that not only will it snap an angler's line, but it will sometimes make off with his or her tackle. No wonder one fishing safari promoter requires clients read a cautionary treatise on the goliath before agreeing to a fishing trip. Slice and Dice: The goliath tigerfish likes turbulent waters, where fish who are less powerful swimmers struggle against the current, rendering them vulnerable to attack. It has excellent eyesight and the ability to sense low-frequency vibrations emitted by prey. It generally circles the unlucky fish before striking with the brutality of a piranha. The goliath has been known to pounce on a 60-pound catfish and literally slice it in half. Scary, huh? The goliath's lifespan in the wild is uncertain, but they've lasted 10 to 15 years in captivity.﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SJAgNkNih7o/UFS1u8qyk9I/AAAAAAAAC4Y/wzb-wVw9B1k/w426-h270/goliath-tigerfish-324x205.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/113006303368931624177/albums/5992947831879123633/5992947832992293058</link><title>Humans are usually predators, but we can be prey too. The people in a village on the Niger River in Africa were losing fellow villagers at a rapid rate and called in the army, which shot a 7 m, 1200 Kg crocodile. 

Please Follow +Interesting Amazing World :)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zZPnuwKmxeg/Uys6TVbz4MI/AAAAAAAA0lA/PLE_Bj0opb0/w426-h320/Humans%2Bare%2Busually%2Bpredators%252C%2Bbut%2Bwe%2Bcan%2Bbe%2Bprey%2Btoo.%2BThe%2Bpeople%2Bin%2Ba%2Bvillage%2Bon%2Bthe%2BNiger%2BRiver%2Bin%2BAfrica%2Bwere%2Blosing%2Bfellow%2Bvillagers%2Bat%2Ba%2Brapid%2Brate%2Band%2Bcalled%2Bin%2Bthe%2Barmy%252C%2Bwhich%2Bshot%2Ba%2B7%2Bm%252C%2B1200%2BKg%2Bcrocodile..jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/100188557028585168265/albums/5890093067727288001/5890093072569100290?authkey=CIiygeaRqfO0zgE</link><title>The Alligator Gar ("Gator Gar"), Atractosteus spatula, is a primitive ray-finned fish. Unlike other Gars, the mature Alligator Gar possesses a dual row of large teeth in the upper jaw. Its name derives from the alligator-like appearance of these teeth along with the fish's elongated snout. The dorsal surface of the Alligator Gar is a brown or olive color, while the ventral surface tends to be lighter. Their scales are diamond-shaped and interlocking (ganoid) and are sometimes used by Native Americans for jewelry and arrow heads. 
Along with its status as the largest species of Gar, the Alligator Gar is the largest exclusively freshwater fish found in North America, measuring 8 to 10 feet (2.4 to 3.0 m) and weighing at least 200 lb (91 kg) at maturity. The largest Alligator Gar caught by net was caught by Kenny Williams, from Vicksburg, Mississippi, in February 2011, [1] and measured 8 ft 5 in (2.57 m) long, 327 lb (148 kg) in weight, and nearly 48 in ( 120 cm) around. The fish is believed to have been between 50 and 70 years old, wildlife officials said. Williams has donated the fish to the Mississippi Museum of Natural Science in Jackson where it will be on permanent display in the future. The current world record for the largest Alligator Gar caught on rod and reel is 279 lb (127 kg). [Note 1] [2] The largest taken by bowfishing is 365 lb (166 kg). [Note 2] [3] The fish is also known for its ability to survive outside the water, being able to last for up to two hours above the surface.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alligator_gar 

Thanks +Bob Nagy for telling me about your experience the other day with one of these while swimming! ﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-xVAfqnr-AAQ/Ub3QcUR4aAI/AAAAAAAA28w/RDn90Hp5lcM/w426-h422/Alligator_Gar.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7249-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/largest%20alligator%20on%20record/photos/103226166584311556924/albums/5878431051259666449/5878431059379984530?authkey=CKWX_v3T2MS0hwE</link><title>#Texas   #Alligators   #StateRecords 

Teen Bags Biggest Gator Ever Caught In Texas 

A Texas teen bagged a record 800-pound alligator during his first public gator hunt with his dad. It’s the biggest gator ever certified in Texas, according to the Texas Parks and Wildlife Department. 

KHOU - http://goo.gl/yF96D ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7249_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Fl6pbBuwkPc/UZRh5zr3mJI/AAAAAAAA83U/ioQRVqVopM8/w426-h237/texas-gator2.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>