<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:23:55" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/110025041402259716178/albums/5969765234198043457/5969765234708160738</link><title>Autoimmune diseases also referred to as collagen vascular diseases or autoimmunity are disorders where the body's immune system reacts against some of its own cells and produces antibodies to attack it. These disorders are classified into two types, organ-specific (directed mainly at one organ) and non-organ-specific (widely spread throughout the body). Autoimmune diseases keep the healthy body from releasing an immunological army that destroys all healthy cells it encounters. 
http://health-forever.com/articles/Autoimmune-disease﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-4vJ-PUHNwHs/Utjd2g9BoOI/AAAAAAAAAS0/u9KdRK2lLIA/w426-h332/womeninpain_shoulder_optimized.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/115935493787673296321/albums/5986702698697382049/5986702697716732626</link><title>Is Rosacea treatable? 

What is rosacea:  it is a chronic vascular disorder which is exasperated with the presence of certain environmental conditions and the particular genetic make up of the patient. 

A case study done by Dr. David M. Verebelyi shows that patient with rosacea when treated with Intense Pulse Light and a Non-Ablative 1064Nd:Yag in conjunction with the use of antibiotics,   screen and Skin   has shown significant improvement in the overall appearance of the skin and has had lasting results.  This treatment can be performed at Lotus Skin Care Center and Medi-Spa in Massapequa, Massapequa, Long Island New York, 516.798.0200, http://www.lotuslasertreatments.com 

The symptoms are characterized by the vascular telangiectasia and general erythema that are visible on the face, sometimes accompanied with pustules and papules.  There is no unified consensus as what causes this disease.  What is known is that there is a significant increase in Demodex Folliculorum, a hair mite in patients with rosacea.  The hair mites clog glands which lead to the inflammation seen in rosacea patient.  What researchers are also focusing on is the genetics of rosacea patients.  How certain cell receptors affect specific cell’s function in the presence of dust mites antigens and bacterial proteases leading to increase inflammation in the skin. 

What does the Intense Pulse Light and a Non-Ablative 1064Nd:Yag; laser Genesis treatment performed at Lotus Skin Care Center and Medi-Spa in Massapequa, Massapequa, Long Island New York, 516.798.0200, http://www.lotuslasertreatments.com do? 
The Laser Genesis heats up the papillary dermis reaching vessels beyond the reach of the IPL.  As a result the heat stimulates cytokine release and brings fibroblast all over the treated site over the next seven day to ten days, which translates to increase collagen production. This new collagen helps support existing vessels.  As we age, collagen decrease and we begin to sag because of continuous UV exposure and the supporting structure of the coetaneous vessels break down.  This is possibly the reason we see the symptoms of rosacea patient worsen at the age of thirty and over.  Following the use of the Laser Genesis the IPL will be used, which will address the diffuse redness, telangiactatic matting. 
Patients receiving this treatment at Lotus Skin Care Center and Medi-Spa in Massapequa, Massapequa, Long Island New York, 516.798.0200, http://www.lotuslasertreatments.com also urged use Skniceutical Physical Sunscreen and Redness neutralizer.  When these products are used in conjunction with the treatments the redness is controlled and the UV exposure is minimized. 

Photo courtesy Dr David Goldberg, MD from Cutera's web site.﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Cjq7iDHYy_4/UxUKYnlHUtI/AAAAAAAAAUw/OBDepMJ0Cw8/w426-h320/Rosacea%2Bpic.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/107671971548457502702/albums/5871843852631699281/5871851738029625666?authkey=CPGw24ebg7GvgAE</link><title>Price per Unit (piece): Php 1,150.00 

Grape Seed Extract and oligomeric proanthocyanidins (OPCs) clearly possess remarkable antioxidant properties. Their effects on reducing free radical damage and oxidative stress suggest that they may be particularly effective in reducing the risk of cancer, cardiovascular disease and a number of the chronic diseases associated with ageing. It is 20 times more potent than Vitamin C and 50 times stronger than Vitamin E. 

It is an antiallergenic or antihistamine, anti-inflammatory, and an antioxidant. It strengthens blood vessels, improves skin and aids in circulation. Researchers have discovered that Grape Seed Extract can help defeat the hormone dihydrotestosterone (DHT) which stops the hair follicle growth cycle. Grape Seed Extract can help stimulate healthy hair growth. 

Health Benefits: 
·         Antioxidant 
·         Cardio protection (reduces risk of atherosclerosis) 
·         Reduces cancer risk like prostate cancer, colon cancer etc. 
·         Improves vascular strength (inflammation/swelling) 
·         Restores collagen (stronger blood vessels) 
·         Reduces edema (inflammation/swelling) 
·         Promotes eye health (reduces risk of macular degeneration and cataracts) 
·         Helps skin to remain young looking 
·         Improves circulation 
·         Promotes healing﻿

Meer lezen (25 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-QwtwQKNfiQU/UX0CC5sEEUI/AAAAAAAAAHk/nB7rRwvnoLA/s426/grapeseed.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/110265788529286523789/albums/5889704934692922753/5889704932555961570?authkey=CMG4x63mw4Gvdg</link><title>Most people get too much sodium in their diet. 

Heart disease is the leading cause of death worldwide.  The World Health Organization (WHO) estimates that hypertension-related diseases result in 26.9% of developed countries' deaths, and 21.6% of underdeveloped countries' deaths.  High blood pressure (hypertension) is experienced by 90% of people at some point in their life and is a major contributor to heart attacks and strokes.  The WHO website says that daily intake of more than 2000 mg of sodium or less than 3500 mg potassium can cause hypertension  ► http://www.who.int/mediacentre/news/notes/2013/salt_potassium_20130131/en/. 

Here is an informative video about salt from CDC ► Salt Matters: Preserving Choice, Protecting Health.  About 75% of salt intake is from processed and restaurant foods.  Buying the foods with no sodium helps:).  Most people get enough sodium from natural foods, no salt is needed. It is best to cook at home with no salt added in a pressure cooker (it is the fastest cooking method - up to 5 times faster - and it retains up to 9 times more anti-oxidants, vitamins), while avoiding eating restaurant and canned salty foods (metals can leak into the foods).  Also, draining the liquid in canned salty foods can often remove almost half the sodium.  Harvard School of Public Health has more salt studies ► http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/salt-and-heart-disease/. 

We only need 200-1200 mg of sodium, depending on weight and activity levels (sweating eliminates sodium).  Potassium relaxes the blood vessels and lowers blood pressure, while sodium tenses blood vessels and increases BP.  Also, too much sodium can damage the bones ► http://healthyliving.msn.com/diseases/osteoporosis/potassium-and-sodium-the-dynamic-duo-1. 

When using a lot of salt, it is even more important to blood pressure control to limit the intake of sugar (sucrose) and fructose. Studies show those consuming too many simple sugars [sweet fruits (rich in fructose) or processed foods with added high fructose corn syrup or sugar] have higher blood pressure ►http://www.medpagetoday.com/Cardiology/Hypertension/21000. 
Some recommend eating less than 15 g of fructose a day, less than half a banana.  No sodas or drinks with added sugar ► http://articles.mercola.com/sites/articles/archive/2010/05/25/startling-research-findings-a-newly-discovered-cause-of-high-blood-pressure-and-obesity.aspx. " In 1892, there were just two cases of diabetes per 100,000 people, according to a famous medical textbook by Sir William Osler, The Principles and Practice of Medicine. Today, the rate is 9 percent across all age groups, and sadly one of every three children is either diabetic or pre-diabetic." 

High sodium and low potassium intake led to higher mortality in this study ►http://archinte.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=1106080.  When combined with high sugars this high ratio of sodium to potassium leads to serious heart problems. People have noticed a big drop in blood pressure within weeks of changing sugar, sodium and potassium intake.  Many supermarkets sell KCl, potassium chloride salt, so using this kind of salt at home is another way to get more potassium.  Normal salt is sodium chloride, NaCl. 

http://www.nutritiondata.com allows searching foods to see their sugars, potassium and omega 3 fatty acids (unsaturated fat) levels.  Besides decreasing sodium, saturated fat and omega 6 acids intake, increasing omega 3 fatty acids intake lowers blood pressure ► http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2013/02/27/1221997110. Many people eat omega 6: omega 3 in ratios of 30:1 to 10:1.  The healthier (for blood pressure and also for increased telomere length) ratios are in the range 4:1 to 1:1. Some beans (black, pinto, white, etc) have high potassium and also roughly equal amounts of omega 3 to omega 6. Beans are better than many fried foods with trans fats or oxysterols that clog the arteries.  However, beans have fats too and cooking those fats can cause some harmful fats to emerge, so for diabetics especially it's much better to eat raw unroasted walnuts with omega 3: omega 6 ratio of 1:4 and 400 mg potassium per 100g.  All nuts should be eaten unroasted, since oxidized fats clog the arteries and raise blood pressure. Interestingly, coconut saturated fat eaters have less heart disease than us ► http://coconutoil.com/litalee/.  Sri Lankans used to have the lowest heart disease rate in the world in 1953 when they are 136 coconuts a year on average ► http://www.pca.da.gov.ph/heartdisease.php. 

Too much of whole grains or beans, i.e. too many carbohydrates, can cause an increase in blood pressure long term due to spike in insulin levels, so much so that diets with more monounsaturated fats lead to lower blood pressure ► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16249527. Insulin levels being high is also how Alzheimer can develop faster. However, among high carbohydrate eaters, eating complex (beans and grains) carbohydrates instead of simple ones (sugar, fructose in fruits) leads to comparatively lower blood pressure ► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/18845707. 

Studies show those eating least meat and dairy have the lowest (healthiest) blood pressure ► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/12372158. It became evident that those eating no red meat are less likely to die of heart disease and they live longer ► http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324423904578523190441042514.html.  The scientifically proven (and covered by Medicare and many private insurance companies) Dr. Ornish’s Program for Reversing Heart Disease helped thousands to lower blood pressure through a healthier low fat diet ► http://www.ornishspectrum.com/ornish-certified-site-directory/reversing-programs/. 

Scientists found that good sleep prevents hypertension ► http://healthland.time.com/2011/08/30/could-lack-of-deep-sleep-fuel-high-blood-pressure/, diabetes ► http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2012/09/120929140234.htm, weak immune system ► http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2012/07/120701191638.htm and other health problems. During sleep the body does a lot of self-repair.  Meditation, eating as little fat as possible (except for the minimum omega 3 needed), peaceful music (example ► MOUNTAIN STREAM Nature Sounds (10 Hours) Relax, Meditate, Sleep) and emotions, natural diuretics (cucumber, tomatoes, fresh ginger tea, etc), lower stress, avoiding gaining weight, not smoking, not drinking alcohol can also help lower blood pressure. 

Few people know that ginger tea can lower blood pressure by 10 points (► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/15613983 for the mechanics of ginger).  http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16157513 presents ginger tea effect on blood pressure, while http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16117603 shows anti-inflammatory effects of ginger (boosts immune system).  100g of raw ginger contains 410mg of potassium, about 10% of daily needs.  Ginger is easier to eat as tea, but in many nations it's added to already cooked foods in raw form after cooking.  Raw is more potent.  Ginger has been used for thousands of years as medicine. The studies show the more concentrated the tea or the more ginger we eat, the lower the blood pressure. So, with ginger one can lower the blood pressure by 20 points also: be it as tea made from raw ginger, raw in salads, or added raw before or after cooking foods. 

Hibiscus tea lowers blood pressure too (► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20018807).  Here is an interesting comparison between teas showing how black tea increases blood pressure while hibiscus tea dramatically decreases blood pressure by 15-20 points ► http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/18685605. Many stores sell hibiscus flowers in the bulk section. 

The normal pulse rate is 60-100 bpm (beats per minute) and ideal blood pressure is less than 115/75 mm Hg (less than 115 systolic AND less than 75 diastolic) for those older than 18.  Normally they say less than 120/80, but it's always better to aim for lower since it prevents issues decades later.  The best athletes or meditators (who can attain deep peace) can have pulse of 40 and still be in perfect health.  The known world record is 27 bpm.  One can take blood pressure and pulse at home, with one of those $10-40 monitors available at Walmart, etc. In general, the lower the values, the longer the person will live heart disease free.  Studies show that the lower the heart rate the longer we live ► http://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/news/20130416/higher-heart-rate-tied-to-earlier-death-even-in-fit-people, independent of whether we exercise or not. Harvard Medical School agrees with this finding ► http://www.health.harvard.edu/press_releases/slower-heart-rate-may-translate-into-longer-life.  Being free from anger lowers heart rate and blood pressure, so staying happy helps:). 

#health   #longevity   #science    ﻿

Meer lezen (155 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-qSvmDNAN5J0/UbxvbmDdNOI/AAAAAAAADO8/RaOJj-1Ycr4/w426-h596/sodium-less.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/112986940331096635201/albums/5969167087254651425/5969167093891150786</link><title>Rosacea Home Care Remedy 

#Rosacea is a skin disorder marked by redness. Bumps, pimples and papules sometimes develop on the affected area. It principally occurs on the face (forehead, nose and cheeks). In extreme case, the chin, scalp, upper back, chest and ears may be affected. 

When rosacea first develops, it may appear then disappear. It may return after a few days or weeks. When it disappears on its own i.e. without medication, the skin does not return to its original colour. 

The surface of skin of the affected area may remain rosy and sometimes a spidery network of reddish lines may be visible. The reddish lines are the remnants of enlarged blood vessels. This medical condition of enlarged blood vessels is called telangiectasias. 

The ocular rosaceatic subtype causes inflammation and irritation of the eyelids. It can lead to blurry vision, and in extreme cases; it can lead to temporary blindness. 

Treatment of Rosacea 
The appropriate treatment technique for a rosaceatic inflammation depends on the subtype and severity. Even though, it is not recommended, some people leave mild cases untreated. Sometimes, they disguise the symptoms by applying makeup on the affected area. 

Moderate and severe cases can be treated with medication, laser surgery or topical agents. 

Trigger avoidance is the first step in any treatment. Trigger avoidance consists of modifying your behavior in such a way as to minimize your exposure to factors that provoke rosaceatic eruptions. 

Here is a non-exhaustive list of the triggers which, you must avoid: excessive exposure to sunlight, emotional stress, anxiety, depression, sunburns, hot weather, cold weather, windy conditions, strenuous exercise, alcohol consumption, red wine, spicy foods, humidity, indoor heat, certain skin care products, heated beverages, certain cosmetics, marinated meat, steroids and histamine-rich foods. 

Medication consist of topical and oral antibiotics. 

The most frequently prescribed oral antibiotics include tetracycline, doxycycline and minocycline. Metronidazole is the most frequently prescribed topical antibiotic. 

Antibiotics are effective in treating the inflammatory rosaceatic subtypes. Subtypes such as papulopustular and phymatous rosacea respond well to antibiotics. These subtypes are characterized by red bumps (papules) and pus-filled pustules. 

A shortcoming of antibiotics is their inability to kill skin bacteria. Both oral and topical antibiotics have this disadvantage. Furthermore, antibiotics need to be used for months before you can expect to start seeing the effects. 

As with all chemicals, you should avoid long-term use. People with a history of kidney diseases may not use tetracycline antibiotics because the antibiotics tend to re-ignite the kidney problems. 

Furthermore, these antibiotics are not for pregnant women or women that are breastfeeding as they can be the source of birth defects for unborn babies. 

Be honest with your dermatologist and reveal any allergies or medical problems that you may have. Using these antibiotics while you have medical problems can lead to the aggravation of your situation. 

Laser surgery is increasingly popular in treatment of rosacea. 

Laser surgery is effective for vascular rosaceatic subtypes like fulminans and erythematotelangiectatic. During a treatment session, intense pulsed light lasers are beamed through the epidermis to the oxy-hemoglobin of the cells of the dermis. 

The structure of the infected oxy-hemoglobin is destroyed, when heated over 75 °C (158 °F). The destruction of the oxy-hemoglobin causes the walls of the capillaries to break down. You will need several laser treatment sessions to achieve full remission. 

Rosacea Home Care Remedy 
Revitol rosacea cream is a top of the line over-the-counter homeopathic treatment. The effectiveness and high safety standards of the revitol formula is widely extolled in the dermatological community. 

The revitol formula contains anti-inflammatory ingredients that treat telangiectasias. Telangiectasias is the condition that is responsible for the red, spidery lines that run across your face. The anti-inflammatory ingredients of revitol treats this problem by constricting the blood vessels near the surface of the skin. 

Rosaceatic outbreaks weaken the ability of your skin to produce its natural protective film of oil. Revitol contains ingredients that stimulate your skin to naturally produce oil. 

Your skin may become dry and flaky due to the nature of rosaceatic disorder. The collagen boosting ingredients in revitol hydrate and moisturize your skin. This helps prevent any bacteria from aggravating your condition. 

The potent and all-natural revitol formula guarantees proven health results. Order the clinically approved revitol formula now and eradicate your rosacea. 

Full article @ http://stilettoqueens.wordpress.com/2014/01/15/rosacea-home-care-remedy/﻿

Meer lezen (110 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-GSO9ykoKZWk/Uta92IxVM8I/AAAAAAAAFjs/4CIi_gEcpGc/w426-h512/pic3%2BRosacea%2BTreatment.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/103672676700935888675/albums/5997320236689368657/5997320234044743314</link><title>Hey, my dear friend. That is why we always stick to ride a bicycle. 

See the following article 

30 reasons to take up cycling 

1\. You’ll get there faster 

Commute by bike in the UK’s major cities and you’ll get there in half the time of cars, research by Citroen shows. In fact, if you drive for an hour in Cardiff’s rush hour, you’ll spend over 30 minutes going absolutely nowhere and average just 7mph, compared to averaging around 12-15mph while cycling. 

2\. Sleep more deeply 

An early morning ride might knacker you out in the short term, but it’ll help you catch some quality shut-eye when you get back to your pillow. Stanford University School of Medicine researchers asked sedentary insomnia sufferers to cycle for 20-30 minutes every other day. The result? The time required for the insomniacs to fall asleep was reduced by half, and sleep time increased by almost an hour. 

“Exercising outside exposes you to daylight,” explains Professor Jim Horne from Loughborough University’s Sleep Research Centre. “This helps get your circadian rhythm back in sync, and also rids your body of cortisol, the stress hormone that can prevent deep, regenerative sleep.” 

3\. Look younger 

Scientists at Stanford University have found that cycling regularly can protect your skin against the harmful effects of UV radiation and reduce the signs of ageing. Harley Street dermatologist Dr Christopher Rowland Payne explains: “Increased circulation through exercise delivers oxygen and nutrients to skin cells more effectively, while ﬂushing harmful toxins out. Exercise also creates an ideal environment within the body to optimise collagen production, helping reduce the appearance of wrinkles and speed up the healing process.” Don’t forget to slap on the factor 30 before you head out, though. 

4\. Boost your bowels 

According to experts from Bristol University, the beneﬁts of cycling extend deep into your core. “Physical activity helps decrease the time it takes food to move through the large intestine, limiting the amount of water absorbed back into your body and leaving you with softer stools, which are easier to pass,” explains Harley Street gastroenterologist Dr Ana Raimundo. 

In addition, aerobic exercise accelerates your breathing and heart rate, which helps to stimulate the contraction of intestinal muscles. “As well as preventing you from feeling bloated, this helps protect you against bowel cancer,” Dr Raimundo says. 

5\. Increase your brain power 

Need your grey matter to sparkle? Then get pedalling. Researchers from Illinois University found that a ﬁve percent improvement in cardio-respiratory ﬁtness from cycling led to an improvement of up to 15 percent in mental tests. That’s because cycling helps build new brain cells in the hippocampus – the region responsible for memory, which deteriorates from the age of 30. 

“It boosts blood ﬂow and oxygen to the brain, which ﬁres and regenerates receptors, explaining how exercise helps ward off Alzheimer’s,” says the study’s author, Professor Arthur Kramer. 

6\. Beat illness 

Forget apples, riding’s the way to keep the doctor at bay. “Moderate exercise makes immune cells more active, so they’re ready to ﬁght off infection,” says Cath Collins, chief dietician at St George’s Hospital in London. 

In fact, according to research from the University of North Carolina, people who cycle for 30 minutes, ﬁve days a week take about half as many sick days as couch potatoes. 

7\. Live longer 

King’s College London compared over 2,400 identical twins and found those who did the equivalent of just three 45-minute rides a week were nine years ‘biologically younger’ even after discounting other inﬂuences, such as body mass index (BMI) and smoking. 

“Those who exercise regularly are at signiﬁcantly lower risk of cardiovascular disease, type two diabetes, all types of cancer, high blood pressure and obesity,” says Dr Lynn Cherkas, who conducted the research. “The body becomes much more efﬁcient at defending itself and regenerating new cells.” 

8\. Save the planet 

Twenty bicycles can be parked in the same space as one car. It takes around ﬁve percent of the materials and energy used to make a car to build a bike, and a bike produces zero pollution. 

Bikes are efﬁcient, too – you travel around three times as fast as walking for the same amount of energy and, taking into account the ‘fuel’ you put in your ‘engine’, you do the equivalent of 2,924 miles to the gallon. You have your weight ratio to thank: you’re about six times heavier than your bike, but a car is 20 times heavier than you. 

9\. Improve your sex life 

Being more physically active improves your vascular health, which has the knock-on effect of boosting your sex drive, according to health experts in the US. One study from Cornell University also concluded that male athletes have the sexual prowess of men two to ﬁve years younger, with physically ﬁt females delaying the menopause by a similar amount of time. 

Meanwhile, research carried out at Harvard University found that men aged over 50 who cycle for at least three hours a week have a 30 percent lower risk of impotence than those who do little exercise. 

10\. It’s good breeding 

A ‘bun in the oven’ could beneﬁt from your riding as much as you. According to research from Michigan University in the US, mums-to-be who regularly exercise during pregnancy have an easier, less complicated labour, recover faster and enjoy better overall mood throughout the nine months. Your pride and joy also has a 50 percent lower chance of becoming obese and enjoys better in-utero neurodevelopment. 

“There’s no doubt that moderate exercise such as cycling during pregnancy helps condition the mother and protect the foetus,” says Patrick O’Brien, a spokesman for the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists. 

11\. Heal your heart 

Studies from Purdue University in the US have shown that regular cycling can cut your risk of heart disease by 50 percent. And according to the British Heart Foundation, around 10,000 fatal heart attacks could be avoided each year if people kept themselves ﬁtter. Cycling just 20 miles a week reduces your risk of heart disease to less than half that of those who take no exercise, it says. 

12\. Your boss will love you 

No, we don’t mean your Lycra-clad buttocks will entice your superiors into a passionate ofﬁce romance, but they’ll appreciate what cycling does for your usefulness to the company. A study of 200 people carried out by the University of Bristol found that employees who exercised before work or at lunchtime improved their time and workload management, and it boosted their motivation and their ability to deal with stress. 

The study also reported that workers who exercised felt their interpersonal performance was better, they took fewer breaks and found it easier to ﬁnish work on time. Sadly, the study didn’t ﬁnd a direct link between cycling and getting a promotion. 

13\. Cycle away from the big C 

There’s plenty of evidence that any exercise is useful in warding off cancer, but some studies have shown that cycling is speciﬁcally good for keeping your cells in working order. One long-term study carried out by Finnish researchers found that men who exercised at a moderate level for at least 30 minutes a day were half as likely to develop cancer as those who didn’t. And one of the moderate forms of exercise they cited? Cycling to work. Other studies have found that women who cycle frequently reduce their risk of breast cancer by 34 percent. 

14\. Lose weight in the saddle 

Loads of people who want to shift some heft think that heading out for a jog is the best way to start slimming down. But while running does burn a ton of fat, it’s not kind to you if you’re a little larger than you’d like to be. Think about it – two to three times your body weight goes crashing through your body when your foot strikes the ground. If you weigh 16 stone, that’s a lot of force! Instead, start out on a bike – most of your weight is taken by the saddle, so your skeleton doesn’t take a battering. Running can wait… 

15\. You’ll make more money 

If you’re cycling to lose weight then you could be in line for a cash windfall… Well, sort of. Researcher Jay Zagorsky, from Ohio State University, analysed data from the National Longitudinal Survey of Youth – which saw 7,300 people regularly interviewed between 1985 and 2000 – to see how their obesity and wealth changed over that period. Zagorsky concluded that a one unit increase in body mass index (BMI) score corresponded to an £800 or eight percent reduction in wealth. So, shed a few BMI points on the bike and start earning. 

16\. Avoid pollution 

You’d think a city cyclist would suck up much more pollution than the drivers and passengers in the vehicles chucking out the noxious gases. Not so, according to a study carried out by Imperial College London. Researchers found that passengers in buses, taxis and cars inhaled substantially more pollution than cyclists and pedestrians. 

On average, taxi passengers were exposed to more than 100,000 ultraﬁne particles – which can settle in the lungs and damage cells – per cubic centimetre. Bus passengers sucked up just under 100,000 and people in cars inhaled about 40,000. Cyclists, meanwhile, were exposed to just 8,000 ultraﬁne particles per cubic centimetre. It’s thought that cyclists breathe in fewer fumes because we ride at the edge of the road and, unlike drivers, aren’t directly in the line of exhaust smoke. 

17\. Enjoy healthy family time 

Cycling is an activity the whole family can do together. The smallest tyke can clamber into a bike seat or tow-along buggy, and because it’s kind on your joints, there’s nothing to stop grandparents joining in too. 

Moreover, your riding habit could be sowing the seeds for the next Bradley Wiggins. Studies have found that, unsurprisingly, kids are inﬂuenced by their parents’ exercise choices. Put simply, if your kids see you riding regularly, they think it’s normal and will want to follow your example. Don’t be surprised, though, if they become embarrassed by your tendency to mismatch ﬂuorescent Lycra when they become teenagers. 

18\. It means guilt-free snacks 

Upping your salt intake is seldom your doctor’s advice, but in the few days leading up to a big ride or sportive, that’s exactly what you should do. This gives you the perfect excuse to munch on crisps and other salty foods you might normally avoid. The sodium in them helps protect your body against hyponatraemia, a condition caused by drinking too much water without enough sodium that can lead to disorientation, illness and worse. 

19\. Get better at any sport 

Whether you want to keep in prime shape or just improve your weekly tennis game, a stint in the saddle is the way to begin. A recent medical study from Norway carried the title Aerobic Endurance Training Improves Soccer Performance, which makes it pretty clear that the knock-on beneﬁts to other sports and activities are immense. 

20\. Make creative breakthroughs 

Writers, musicians, artists, top executives and all kinds of other professionals use exercise to solve mental blocks and make decisions – including Jeremy Paxman, Sir Alan Sugar and Spandau Ballet. A study found that just 25 minutes of aerobic exercise boosts at least one measure of creative thinking. Credit goes to the ﬂow of oxygen to your grey matter when it matters most, sparking your neurons and giving you breathing space away from the muddle and pressures of ‘real life’. 

21\. You’re helping others 

Many cyclists turn their health, ﬁtness and determination into fundraising efforts for the less fortunate. The London to Brighton bike ride has raised over £40 million for the British Heart Foundation since the two became involved in 1980, with countless other rides contributing to the coffers of worthy causes. 

22\. You can get fit without trying too hard 

Regular, everyday cycling has huge beneﬁts that can justify you binning your wallet-crippling gym membership. According to the National Forum for Coronary Heart Disease Foundation in the US, regular cyclists enjoy a ﬁtness level equal to that of a person who’s 10 years younger. 

23\. Boost your bellows 

No prizes for guessing that the lungs work considerably harder than usual when you ride. An adult cycling generally uses 10 times the oxygen they’d need to sit in front of the TV for the same period. Even better, regular cycling will help strengthen your cardiovascular system over time, enabling your heart and lungs to work more efﬁciently and getting more oxygen where it’s needed, quicker. This means you can do more exercise for less effort. How good does that sound? 

24\. Burn more fat 

Sports physiologists have found that the body’s metabolic rate – the efﬁciency with which it burns calories and fat – is not only raised during a ride, but for several hours afterwards. “Even after cycling for 30 minutes, you could be burning a higher amount of total calories for a few hours after you stop,” says sports physiologist Mark Simpson of Loughborough University. 

And as you get ﬁtter, the beneﬁts are more profound. One recent study showed that cyclists who incorporated fast intervals into their ride burned three-and-a-half times more body fat than those who cycled constantly but at a slower pace. 

25\. You’re developing a positive addiction 

Replace a harmful dependency – such as cigarettes, alcohol or eating too much chocolate – with a positive one, says William Glasser, author of Positive Addiction. The result? You’re a happier, healthier person getting the kind of ﬁx that boosts the good things in life. 

26\. Get (a legal) high 

Once a thing of myth, the infamous ‘runner’s high’ has been proven beyond doubt by German scientists. Yet despite the name, this high is applicable to all endurance athletes. University of Bonn neurologists visualised endorphins in the brains of 10 volunteers before and after a two-hour cardio session using a technique called positive emission tomography (PET). Comparing the pre- and post-run scans, they found evidence of more opiate binding of the happy hormone in the frontal and limbic regions of the brain – areas known to be involved in emotional processing and dealing with stress. 

“There’s a direct link between feelings of wellbeing and exercise, and for the ﬁrst time this study proves the physiological mechanism behind that,” explains study co-ordinator Professor Henning Boecker. 

27\. Make friends and stay healthy 

The social side of riding could be doing you as much good as the actual exercise. University of California researchers found socialising releases the hormone oxytocin, which buffers the ‘ﬁght or ﬂight’ response. 

Another nine-year study from Harvard Medical School found those with the most friends cut the risk of an early death by more than 60 percent, reducing blood pressure and strengthening their immune system. The results were so signiﬁcant that the researchers concluded not having close friends or conﬁdants is as detrimental to your health as smoking or carrying extra weight. Add in the ﬁtness element of cycling too and you’re onto a winner. 

28\. Be happy 

Even if you’re miserable when you saddle up, cranking through the miles will lift your spirits. “Any mild-to-moderate exercise releases natural feel-good endorphins that help counter stress and make you happy,” explains Andrew McCulloch, chief executive of the Mental Health Foundation. That’s probably why four times more GPs prescribe exercise therapy as their most common treatment for depression compared to three years ago. “Just three 30-minute sessions a week can be enough to give people the lift they need,” says McCulloch. 

Sounds counter-intuitive but if you feel too tired for a ride, the best thing you can do is go for ride. Physical activity for even a few minutes is a surprisingly effective wake-up call. A review of 12 studies on the link between exercise and fatigue carried out between 1945 and 2005 found that exercise directly lowers fatigue levels. 

30\. Spend quality time with your partner 

It doesn’t matter if your paces aren’t perfectly matched – just slow down and enjoy each other’s company. Many couples make one or two riding ‘dates’ every week. And it makes sense: exercise helps release feel-good hormones, so after a ride you’ll have a warm feeling towards each other even if he leaves the toilet seat up and her hair is blocking the plughole again.﻿

Meer lezen (370 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-K8tohDU7rS0/UzrC-kp_3pI/AAAAAAAAA10/Kf39ugzdCTA/w426-h271/5007bc6049c5d.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/114659984763264201106/albums/5874528638897321329/5874528646238959810?authkey=CKn8q4Cx8reNqwE</link><title>What Causes Dry Eyes? 
In addition to an imbalance in the tear-flow system of the eye, dry eyes can be caused by situations that dry out the tear film. This can be due to dry air from air conditioning, heat, or other environmental conditions. Other conditions that may cause dry eyes are: 
-The natural aging process, especially menopause. 
-Side effects of certain drugs such as antihistamines and birth control pills. 
-Diseases that affect the ability to make tears, such as Sjogren's syndrome, rheumatoid arthritis, and collagen vascular diseases. 
-Structural problems with the eye lids that don't allow them to close properly. 

http://www.webmd.com/eye-health/eye-health-dry-eyes﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9cts7T9DRao/UYaErd3t-MI/AAAAAAAAATI/Ittrus90inM/w426-h285/BVC4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/106749088806096753384/albums/5988472222398876241/5988472223514819058</link><title>UCTD (UNDIFFERENTIATED CONNECTIVE TISSUE DISEASE) VS LUPUS: A WASTE BASKET TERM OR A REAL DISEASE? 

Read on... 

Annmarie H. asks, "Dr T.. Your posts have been incredibly informative and I am grateful for you sharing your knowledge . I was hoping you could post some information on uctd. ... Thank you" 

ANSWER: First things first... anyone who carries a diagnosis of UCTD... you DO have an illness and your doctor is not putting you in to a "waste basket" term. Try not to not feel like you are in limbo at all. Instead... educate yourself and consider taking Plaquenil when you get the diagnosis (and use sunscreen religiously every day, get my vitamin D level above 40 ng/mL, exercise regularly, not smoke, and eat omega-3 fatty acids daily [walnuts, flax seed, tofu, cold water fish] all of which would potentially help.) 

"Connective tissue disease" is the same as "collagen vascular disease" and "systemic autoimmune disease". "Undifferentiated" means that this person has evidence of an inflammatory disorder that appers to be involving the entire body, possibly an autoimmune disorder, but has not "differentiated" itself, or made itself 100% clear yet. 

Of special note... UCTD and MCTD are often mixed up... not only by patients, but also by doctors to include rheumatologists. Countless times I have diagnosed someone with UCTD only to see the diagnosis changed to MCTD by another physician. Here is information on MCTD in a previous article of mine: https://plus.google.com/106749088806096753384/posts/HiAREYW9sMe 

Some Facts to ponder regarding this diagnosis: 

\- The systemic autoimmune diseases such as systemic lupus, rheumatoid arthritis, Sjogren's syndrome, polymyositis, scleroderma, and vasculitis sometimes come on very slowly, only showing one problem or blood test at a time. 

\- We rely upon classification criteria to make a diagnosis of these disorders. 

\- These disorders can cause very similar problems. All of the following can occur in every single one of them: fatigue, pain, arthritis, rash, interstitial lung disease, pleurisy, Raynaud's. 

\- These disorders can all cause the following blood test results: ANA, RF, SSA, RNP, anemia, high ESR, high CRP, low white blood cell count 

\- So... if someone develops the above problems and blood tests but the disease has not fully declared itself yet and does not satisfy criteria, it is called a "UCTD". It is still a disease. 

\- Just to throw in a wrench... we as humans like to pigeon hole everything with a word... and why shouldn't we? The systemic autoimmune diseases may be too complex for this. Why is every lupus patient different? Why do we say that one person with recurrent blood clots and Raynauds has systemic lupus and we give the same disease name to a person who has kidney inflammation, arthritis and a butterfly rash? Many feel that systemic lupus actually is many different diseases... and that the systemic autoimmune diseases are caused by the same genes, same environmental triggers, but that each person may just end up getting different autoimmune problems and manifestations... we just want to try to call each one a certain name. Well, UCTD is one of those names. 

\- Even though we may not know exactly which one it is, we can still treat it. For example, we would treat Raynaud's and arthritis similarly whether we end up calling this disorder "lupus" or "Sjogren's syndrome" or "UCTD" in the long run. 

\- Over time, about 1/3 cases of UCTD just goes away. We believe that these cases were due to a viral infection causing systemic inflammation and masquerading as a UCTD (e.g parvovirus). I always wish my patients ended up in this category. 

\- 1/3 of cases evolve over time into one of the well described systemic autoimmune diseases such as systemic lupus. 

\- 1/3 of the time the UCTD stays the same and doesn't get any worse. 

\- Taking Plaquenil (hydroxychloroquine) daily can decrease the chances of UCTD evolving into a more severe case of systemic lupus over time ... If I had UCTD, I would want to take Plaquenil immediately (it is so safe compared to possibly evolving to a severe case of SLE). I would also use sunscreen religiously every day, get my vitamin D level above 40 ng/mL, exercise regularly, not smoke, and eat omega-3 fatty acids daily (walnuts, flax seed, tofu, cold water fish) all of which would help. 

Please SHARE this with every UCTD person you know. There is not very much out on the internet about it, and the ACR does not have a good pamphlet about it to educate patients. 

By Donald Thomas, MD 
lupusencyclopedia@gmail.com 
Follow me on Twitter @ https://twitter.com/lupuscyclopedia 
Follow me at http://www.facebook.com/LupusEncyclopedia . Answers to "What is lupus?" as well as goes into detail about the symptoms (such as rash and arthritis) of lupus and related conditions such as fibromyalgia and Sjögren’s syndrome. Go to www.facebook.com/LupusEncyclopedia , click "LIKE" to get daily tips and facts about learning to live with and fight lupus 

photo credit: kimberlymcbee.com﻿

Meer lezen (105 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-OyhxSmvyXQg/UxtTwk3k-fI/AAAAAAAAAo4/bpXBMUd2tHw/w426-h682/UCTD+kimberlymcbee+com.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/111322608101362774746/albums/5782368149367011985/5782368151263160738</link><title>146 Reasons Sugar Sucks! 

Chemically speaking, high fructose corn syrup reallyisn’t that different from table sugar (sucrose).  High fructose corn syrup—at least the most common kind found in soft drinks—is 55 percent fructose and 45 percent glucose.  It’s not a huge difference from the 50/50 mix in plain old sugar. 

1\.  Sugar can suppress the immune system. 
2\.  Sugar upsets the mineral relationships in the body. 
3\.  Sugar can cause hyperactivity, anxiety, difficulty concentrating, and crankiness in children. 
4\.  Sugar can produce a significant rise in triglycerides. 
5\.  Sugar contributes to the reduction in defense against bacterial infection (infectious diseases). 
6\.  Sugar causes a loss of tissue elasticity and function, the more sugar you eat the more elasticity and function you loose. 
7\.  Sugar reduces high density lipoproteins. 
8\.  Sugar leads to chromium deficiency. 
9   Sugar leads to cancer of the ovaries. 
10\. Sugar can increase fasting levels of glucose. 
11\. Sugar causes copper deficiency. 
12\. Sugar interferes with absorption of calcium and magnesium. 
13\. Sugar can weaken eyesight. 
14\. Sugar raises the level of a neurotransmitters: dopamine, serotonin, and norepinephrine. 
15\. Sugar can cause hypoglycemia. 
16\. Sugar can produce an acidic digestive tract. 
17\. Sugar can cause a rapid rise of adrenaline levels in children. 
18\. Sugar malabsorption is frequent in patients with functional bowel disease. 
19\. Sugar can cause premature aging. 
20\. Sugar can lead to alcoholism. 
21\. Sugar can cause tooth decay. 
22\. Sugar contributes to obesity 
23\. High intake of sugar increases the risk of Crohn's disease, and ulcerative colitis. 
24\. Sugar can cause changes frequently found in person with gastric or duodenal ulcers. 
25\. Sugar can cause arthritis. 
26\. Sugar can cause asthma. 
27\. Sugar greatly assists the uncontrolled growth of Candida Albicans (yeast infections). 
28\. Sugar can cause gallstones. 
29\. Sugar can cause heart disease. 
30\. Sugar can cause appendicitis. 
31\. Sugar can cause multiple sclerosis. 
32\. Sugar can cause hemorrhoids. 
33\. Sugar can cause varicose veins. 
34\. Sugar can elevate glucose and insulin responses in oral contraceptive users. 
35\. Sugar can lead to periodontal disease. 
36\. Sugar can contribute to osteoporosis. 
37\. Sugar contributes to saliva acidity. 
38\. Sugar can cause a decrease in insulin sensitivity. 
39\. Sugar can lower the amount of Vitamin E (alpha-Tocopherol  in the blood. 
40\. Sugar can decrease growth hormone. 
41\. Sugar can increase cholesterol. 
42\. Sugar can increase the systolic blood pressure. 
43\. Sugar can cause drowsiness and decreased activity in children. 
44\. High sugar intake increases advanced glycation end products (AGEs)(Sugar bound non-enzymatically to protein) 
45\. Sugar can interfere with the absorption of protein. 
46\. Sugar causes food allergies. 
47\. Sugar can contribute to diabetes. 
48\. Sugar can cause toxemia during pregnancy. 
49\. Sugar can contribute to eczema in children. 
50\. Sugar can cause cardiovascular disease. 
51\. Sugar can impair the structure of DNA 
52\. Sugar can change the structure of protein. 
53\. Sugar can make our skin age by changing the structure of collagen. 
54\. Sugar can cause cataracts. 
55\. Sugar can cause emphysema. 
56\. Sugar can cause atherosclerosis. 
57\. Sugar can promote an elevation of low density lipoproteins (LDL). 
58\. High sugar intake can impair the physiological homeostasis of many systems in the body. 
59\. Sugar lowers the enzymes ability to function. 
60\. Sugar intake is higher in people with Parkinson’s disease. 
61\. Sugar can cause a permanent altering the way the proteins act in the body. 
62\. Sugar can increase the size of the liver by making the liver cells divide. 
63\. Sugar can increase the amount of liver fat. 
64\. Sugar can increase kidney size and produce pathological changes in the kidney. 
65\. Sugar can damage the pancreas. 
66\. Sugar can increase the body's fluid retention. 
67\. Sugar is enemy #1 of the bowel movement. 
68\. Sugar can cause myopia (nearsightedness). 
69\. Sugar can compromise the lining of the capillaries. 
70\. Sugar can make the tendons more brittle. 
71\. Sugar can cause headaches, including migraine. 
72\. Sugar plays a role in pancreatic cancer in women. 
73\. Sugar can adversely affect school children's grades and cause learning disorders.. 
74\. Sugar can cause an increase in delta, alpha, and theta brain waves. 
75\. Sugar can cause depression. 
76\. Sugar increases the risk of gastric cancer. 
77\. Sugar and cause dyspepsia (indigestion). 
78\. Sugar can increase your risk of getting gout. 
79\. Sugar can increase the levels of glucose in an oral glucose tolerance test over the ingestion of complex carbohydrates. 
80\. Sugar can increase the insulin responses in humans consuming high-sugar diets compared to    low sugar diets. 
81  High refined sugar diet reduces learning capacity. 
82\. Sugar can cause less effective functioning of two blood  proteins, albumin, and lipoproteins, which may reduce the body’s ability to handle fat and cholesterol. 
83\.  Sugar can contribute to Alzheimer’s disease. 
84\. Sugar can cause platelet adhesiveness. 
85\. Sugar can cause hormonal imbalance; some hormones become underactive and others become overactive. 
86\. Sugar can lead to the formation of kidney stones. 
87\. Sugar can lead to the hypothalamus to become highly sensitive to a large variety of stimuli. 
88\. Sugar can lead to dizziness. 
89\. Diets high in sugar can cause free radicals and oxidative stress. 
90\. High sucrose diets of subjects with peripheral vascular disease significantly increases platelet adhesion. 
91\. High sugar diet can lead to biliary tract cancer. 
92\. Sugar feeds cancer. 
93\. High sugar consumption of pregnant adolescents is associated with a twofold increased risk for delivering a small-for-gestational-age (SGA) infant. 
94\. High sugar consumption can lead to substantial decrease in gestation duration among adolescents. 
95\. Sugar slows food's travel time through the gastrointestinal tract. 
96\. Sugar increases the concentration of bile acids in stools and bacterial enzymes in the colon. This can modify bile to produce cancer-causing compounds and colon cancer. 
97\.  Sugar increases estradiol (the most potent form of naturally occurring estrogen) in men. 
98\.  Sugar combines and destroys phosphatase, an enzyme, which makes the process of digestion more difficult. 
99\.  Sugar can be a risk factor of gallbladder cancer. 
100\. Sugar is an addictive substance. 
101\. Sugar can be intoxicating, similar to alcohol. 
102\. Sugar can exacerbate PMS. 
103\. Sugar given to premature babies can affect the amount of carbon dioxide they produce. 
104\. Decrease in sugar intake can increase emotional stability. 
105\. The body changes sugar into 2 to 5 times more fat in the bloodstream than it does starch. 
106\. The rapid absorption of sugar promotes excessive food intake in obese subjects. 
107\. Sugar can worsen the symptoms of children with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). 
108\. Sugar adversely affects urinary electrolyte composition. 
109\. Sugar can slow down the ability of the adrenal glands to function. 
110\. Sugar has the potential of inducing abnormal metabolic processes in a normal healthy individual and to promote chronic degenerative diseases. 
111.. I.Vs (intravenous feedings) of sugar water can cut off oxygen to the brain. 
112\. High sucrose intake could be an important risk factor in lung cancer. 
113\. Sugar increases the risk of polio. 
114\. High sugar intake can cause epileptic seizures. 
115\. Sugar causes high blood pressure in obese people. 
116\. In Intensive Care Units, limiting sugar saves lives. 
117\. Sugar may induce cell death. 
118\. Sugar can increase the amount of food that you eat. 
119\. In juvenile rehabilitation camps, when children were put on a low sugar diet, there was a 44% drop in antisocial behavior. 
120\.  Sugar can lead to prostrate cancer. 
121\. Sugar dehydrates newborns. 
122\. Sugar increases the estradiol in young men. 
123\.  Sugar can cause low birth weight babies. 
124\. Greater consumption of refined sugar is associated with a worse outcome of schizophrenia 
125\. Sugar can raise homocysteine levels in the blood stream. 
126\. Sweet food items increase the risk of breast cancer. 
127\. Sugar is a risk factor in cancer of the small intestine. 
128\. Sugar may cause laryngeal cancer. 
129\. Sugar induces salt and water retention. 
130\. Sugar may contribute to mild memory loss. 
131\. As sugar increases in the diet of 10 years olds, there is a linear decrease in the intake of many essential nutrients. 
132\. Sugar can increase the total amount of food consumed. 
133\. Exposing a newborn to sugar results in a heightened preference for sucrose relative to water at 6 months and 2 years of age. 
134\. Sugar causes constipation. 
135\. Sugar causes varicous veins. 
136\. Sugar can cause brain decay in prediabetic and diabetic women. 
137\. Sugar can increase the risk of stomach cancer. 
138\. Sugar can cause metabolic syndrome. 
139\. Sugar ingestion by pregnant women increases neural tube defects in embryos. 
140\. Sugar can be a factor in asthma. 
141\. The higher the sugar consumption the more chances of getting irritable bowel syndrome. 
142\. Sugar could affect central reward systems. 
143\. Sugar can cause cancer of the rectum. 
144\. Sugar can cause endometrial  cancer. 
145\. Sugar can cause renal (kidney) cell carcinoma. 
146\. Sugar can cause liver tumors.﻿

Meer lezen (203 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-so48lbYqw8I/UD8ZMoCSqaI/AAAAAAAAHzI/JTovE48wY7k/w426-h502/sugarb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7250-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/collagen%20vascular%20disease/photos/107671971548457502702/albums/5871843852631699281/5871849161117773010?authkey=CPGw24ebg7GvgAE</link><title>Price per Unit (piece): Php 385.00 

Why Royalè-C? 

•  Easily Absorbed by the System 
•  Alkaline –Non-Acidic 
•  Tummy-Friendly 
•  Mother of all Vitamins 

Benefits of Royalè-C: 
•  Boosts immune system 
•  Strengthens bones and joints 
•  Increases iron absorption 
•  Anti-Oxidant 
•  Promotes collagen renewal 
•  Adjunct in the prevention of cardio vascular problems 
•  Detoxifies 
•  Strengthens the capillaries &amp; other blood vessels 
•  Stops constipation &amp; shrink hemorrhoids 
•  Reduces insulin requirement of  diabetics 
•  Prevents infertility as it maintains the ovaries 
•   Prevents weakening of the sperm 
•   Enhances sexual performance by aiding endocrine glands 

Addresses the harmful effects of the following: 
•  Fatigue and stress 
•  Loose teeth 
•  Nose bleed 
•  Poor digestion 
•  Rough skin 
•  Scurvy 
•  Cough 
•  Adrenal insufficiency 
•  Effects of air pollution 
•  Allergies 
•  Cancer 
•  Cataracts 
•  Discomfort from arthritis 
•  Effects of radiation 
•  Free radicals 
•  Glaucoma 
•  Alcoholism 
•  Mental illness 
•  Periodontal disease 
•  Depression 
•  Bleeding gums 
•  Bone abnormalities 
•  Confusion 
•  Dental cavities 
•  Easy bruising 
•  Colds 

Why do we need Sodium Ascorbate? 

The GLO Gene is absent in many people. Scientists believe that this happened around 60 million years ago. The absence of this gene makes us unable to biosynthesize the specific enzyme L- gulonolactone oxidase. This is an end-stage liver enzyme that bio-converts blood glucose to Ascorbate; without it, our bodies cannot produce any Ascorbate.  In the long term, the lack of Ascorbate causes our bones to dissolve and teeth to fall out; in other words, sub-clinical scurvy and a tendency to develop cancer. 

Ascorbic Acid is produced in large quantities in almost all animals, e.g. 6 grams a day in goat, or up to 100grams daily if the goat is stressed. But it is not the Ascorbic Acid our body requires, rather a SALT of Ascorbic Acid. A daily supplementation of Ascorbate several times a day is a simple way to make up for this genetic defect.﻿

Meer lezen (66 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7250_11_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-I8eC-Ftl-B0/UXz_s58ZrNI/AAAAAAAAAF4/ek2E4QKGblc/s426/royalec.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>