<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:49:09" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/106136450056876804759/albums/5802749873010557441/5802749881590684882</link><title>Come &amp; Enjoy International, Italian &amp; Swahili Dishes at The Majlis Restaurant. Open for Both In-house &amp; External Guests!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-qyCA8hdERMQ/UIeCReSnHNI/AAAAAAAABiE/MZQMp1so4wo/w426-h284/wp-content_gallery_the-restaurant_majlis-restaurant-and-terrace-bar-at-night.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/103145429239923145864/albums/5742929643810108801/5742929646213639970</link><title>PLAN YOUR KENYA SAFARI-EATING OUT 

A GASTRONOMIC PRIVILEGE 
Chandigarh, 15th May 2012 : Kenya’s abundance of natural produce, combined with the rich variety of cultures and traditions, have created a great culinary nation attracting the food connoisseurs from across the world. The fertile volcanic soil of the Rift Valley produces a bounty of fresh vegetables, while the coast is a great source of tropical fruit and fresh seafood. The coast is also the home of the World’s renowned Swahili cuisine, a blend of Middle Eastern and African cooking with a particular coastal twist. 

Dining out in Kenya is a gastronomic delight, because many restaurants offer the opportunity to dine alfresco and take in some dramatic scenery. All over Kenya, the climate is ideal for alfresco dining. In many camps, lodges and restaurants, meals are served outside, letting you enjoy a feast with a view. You can start the day with a bush breakfasts after an early morning game drive, and finish it with sundowner drinks and snacks taking in the view of one of Kenya's spectacular sunsets. 

Along coastal regions you will find the focus is on locally caught seafood, although there is also no shortage of restaurants offering Asian and European cuisine. Swahili dishes are also very popular on the coast, combining middle eastern and African flavours, whilst further inland, Kenyans are formidable meat eaters. One of the best known Kenyan specialties is Nyama Choma- meaning literally ‘roasted meat’. There are many popular 'Choma Joints' in most Kenyan towns. Probably the best known is Nairobi's Carnivore, Kenya’s most famous restaurant. This is usually slow roasted over an open fire or charcoals, and served with a mixture of basic greens (known as Sukuma Wiki) and Ugali. Ugali is the much loved staple food of Kenya. Essentially a stiff porridge of maize flour, Ugali is served in large, freshly cooked bricks. Pieces of Ugali are broken off and used to eat meat, stews or vegetables. 

Vegetarians need not feel threatened- Kenya's large Asian population has led to a great many Indian, Pakistani and sub-continental restaurants throughout the country. Excellent vegetarian meals can always be found alongside the best of regional Indian cuisine. For the Indian food lover, Shehnai is definitely the place to get the best of the Indian cuisine that Mombasa has to offer. Other popular Indian restaurants in Nairobi are Haandi and Haveli’s where all types of traditional Indian dishes are available; from curries to tandoor and mughlai dishes. 

There is an incredible range of restaurants in Nairobi covering a world of cuisines. From Korean BBQ to French Novelle Cuisine, Ethiopian Injera to a Traditional Roast Sunday lunch, Hamburgers to Tandoori specialties, you'll find exactly what you're looking for, or a new and unexpected treat. There is also no shortage of nightlife in Kenyan resorts, ranging from bars and nightclubs to more family oriented entertainment in hotels and clubs. 

You may not have associated Kenya with world class cuisine, but after a safari here, you most certainly will. 

For more information please contact: : 
Kenya Tourist Board,www.magicalkenya.com 
C/o TRAC Representations India Pvt. Ltd. 
Chiranjib Biswas |011-23311289, 09999403005 | email kenya@tracrep.com 
Pourushasp Mehta |022-24981777, 09820664262 | email tracrepinfo@gmail.com﻿

Meer lezen (60 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QuJwybSoJKY/T7L8FfyfryI/AAAAAAAAD3w/lIKH3zDxndU/w426-h281/KTB_PR_14.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/103297116363377492173/albums/5826208452941381457/5826208452997167970</link><title>Swahili Dishes﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-leEFSzAnhfk/UNrZuCxGO2I/AAAAAAAAABk/8A29vD1IwRc/w426-h320/Photo0173.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/104699451308359350533/albums/5971090990711325073/5971090993992710594?sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba&amp;sqi=102098984492936602519&amp;sqsi=c54cbebd-c21f-4fed-b8f5-ae115df70dba</link><title>Islam Connection to Bible and Prophets Totally Debunked: 
100 Reasons Why Islam has no connection with the bible or prophets. 
. 
Islam has no connection with the bible nor the prophets, none at all! 
. 
This one post which will have Added content weekly until it reaches 100 reason why Islam has no connection with bible or the prophets! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
1) First Reason 
. 
The historical and chronological information about Islam! 
. 
When Jesus was born there was: 
No Arabic Language 
No Islam 
No Quran 
No Hadith 
No Mosque 
No Muhammad, peace be upon him 
No Allah because you get Allah in Arabic!I 
. 
This is the facts! 
. 
Here is a copy of the dates of religious writtens, note Islam? 
1473 B.C.E.) Pentateuch (Bible) 
(900 B.C.E.)Veda (Hinduism) 
(510 B.C.E.)Tao Te Ching (Taoism) 
(480 B.C.E.)The Analects (Confucianism) 
(443 B.C.E.) Hebrew Scriptures completed (Bible) 
(1 B.C.E.) Three Baskets (Buddhism) 
(98 C.E.) Whole Bible completed 
(650 C.E.) KORAN ISLAM (650 C.E.) 
(720 C.E.) Kojiki and Nihon shoki (Shinto)  . 
. 
Islamic Leadership has taught Muslim a historical lie by saying 
Adam religion was Islam, this is a Lie? Because there was No Islam or Arabic when Adam was on earth and from the chart above Islam came next to last alone with the Arabic language! 
. 

2) Second Reason 
. 
The Teaching of Hell Purgatory, Immortality and many others! 
. 
The teaching of hell is totally different from the bible, because the bible doesn't teach a person will burning in hell, and in understanding hell these words are very important.Hell, Purgatory, Hades, Sheol, Gehenna and Death. 
. 
Hell: Islam teaches a BURNING HELL, and although the bible says HELL it doesn't mean a BURNING PLACE, so what Islam and false christianity teaches is lies about Hell and by doing so they slander Yahweh-Jehovah's God precious name by telling the Muslim community that they will burn in blistering Hell, scare tactic! 
While the bible has never taught that a person will burn in hell even for a short period of time. 
. 
To prove how false it is just by reasoning, please read below see can you reason with this related. 
. 
Does the Devil Carry Out God’s Will? 
. 
There’s something else you might consider about the teaching of hellfire. 
. 
Who do people usually say is “in charge” of hellfire, and Who supposedly punishes people that are in hell? The Devil most will say. 
. 
Yet, the Devil is God’s worst enemy. 
. 
If God sends people to a fiery hell to be tormented by the Devil, wouldn't that imply a level of cooperation between God and the Devil? 
. 
To illustrate the point—you're a mother or father! Imagine that your son becomes very rebellious. He does a lot of bad things that sadden you. 
. 
What would you do? 
. 
As a loving parent you will try to correct him, doing so repeatedly to help him get back on the right track or the right path. 
. 
Let’s say that despite all your efforts, he rejects what you're telling him. Eventually, you may feel that you have no choice but to punish him in some way, and this will make any parent sad. 
. 
But what if you found out that an evil man had been influencing your son, teaching him to do all those bad things? 
. 
For sure we as parents will be angry with that man. 
. 
Now how reasonable is it knowing that a wicked, immoral man had influenced your son against you, would you turn to that man and ask him to punish your son for you? 
. 
Of course not. That wouldn't make any sense! 
. 
Really, then, does it make sense that God would ask Satan the Devil the very one who influences wicked people—to punish those same people? 
. 
No, Absolutely not. 
. 
For that matter, if God wanted the wicked to be punished, why would the Devil—God’s archenemy—comply with God’s wishes and torment them? 
. 
Perhaps you never thought of it that way before! 
. 
But God doesn't use the devil to carry out his will, and nor is hell a burning place as the bible will soon show! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
3) Third Reason 
. 
The Name of God in the Quran and other languages! 
. 
Islam doesn't even bear the REAL name of God in the quran which show that there is no relation in the bible and Islam, none at all! 
. 
God Name: Accordingly to Islam Satan has a name, but God doesn't! 
Allah isn't a name but a title, and since they believe in the prophets Moses, Abraham and Jesus, then why they don't name the prophets God as their God! They have lied to the muslim community for years! 
. 
The God of the bible Yahweh-Jehovah has given mankind his own name, and God name is mentioned no where in the Quran, but they believe that Muhammad is on a mission from this nameless God! 
. 
If you look at the image at the foot of this post, the highlights are God name from a manuscript that Pre-Islam. Islamic Leadership has lied to the honest muslim community. 
. 
The Divine Name in the Hebrew Scriptures 
. 
The divine name in the Hebrew letters used after the Babylonian exile 
The divine name, represented by the four Hebrew consonants יהוה, appears nearly 7,000 times in the Hebrew Scriptures. This translation renders those four letters, known as the Tetragrammaton, “Jehovah.” That name is by far the most frequently occurring name in the Bible. While the inspired writers refer to God by many titles and descriptive terms, such as “Almighty,” “Most High,” and “Lord,” the Tetragrammaton is the only personal name they use to identify God. 
. 
Why is the name missing from many Bible translations? 
. 
The reasons vary. 
. 
Some feel that Almighty God does not need a unique name to identify him. Others appear to have been influenced by the Jewish tradition of avoiding the use of the name, perhaps out of fear of desecrating it. Still others believe that since no one can be sure of the exact pronunciation of God’s name, it is better just to use a title, such as “Lord” or “God.” 
. 
Such objections, however, lack merit for the following reasons: 
. 
Those who argue that Almighty God does not need a unique name ignore evidence that early copies of his Word, including those preserved from before the time of Christ, contain God’s personal name. As noted above, God directed that his name be included in his Word some 7,000 times. Obviously, he wants us to know and use his name. 
. 
Translators who remove the name out of deference to Jewish tradition fail to recognize a key fact. While some Jewish scribes refused to pronounce the name, they did not remove it from their copies of the Bible. Ancient scrolls found in Qumran, near the Dead Sea, contain the name in many places. Some Bible translators hint that the divine name appeared in the original text by substituting the title “LORD” in capital letters. But the question remains, Why have these translators felt free to substitute or remove God’s name from the Bible when they acknowledge that it is found in the Bible text thousands of times? Who do they believe gave them authority to make such a change? Only they can say.﻿ 
. 
Here is a list og the name of God in other languages! 
. 
God - Afrikaans 
Zot – Albanian 
الله - Arabic 
Jainkoaren – Basque 
bog – Bosnian 
De'u – Catalan 
sa Dios – Cebuano 
bog – Croatian 
Buh – Czech 
Gud – Danish 
God – English 
Dio – Esperanto 
Jumal – Estonian 
Diyos – Fillipino 
Jumala – Finnish 
Dieu – French 
Deus – Galician 
Gott – German 
Bondye – Haitian Creole 
Vajtswv – Hmong 
Isten – Hungarian 
Guo – Icelandic 
Chineke – Igbo 
Dio – Italian 
Tuhan – Indonesian 
Dia – Irish 
Deus – Latin 
dievs – Latvian 
Dievas – Lithuanian 
te Atua – Maori 
Gud – Norwegian 
Bog - Polish 
deus – Portuguese 
dumnezeu – Romanian 
boh – Slovak 
Bog – Slovenian 
Dios – Spanish 
Mungu – Swahili 
Gid – Swedish 
Tanri – Turkish 
Thien Chua – Vietnamese 
duw – Welsh 
Olorun – Yoruba 
Unkulunkulu - Zulu. 
. 
. 
4) Fourth Reason 
. 
The bible paradise is totally different from Islam paradise. 
It is an insult to the Holy and the Most High Yahweh-Jehovah 
to promise these things that the muslim offer as paradise! 
. 
It wasn't like that with Adam and Eve, and it won't be with 
this surreal vision by the Hadith, which Muhammad said 
himself wasn't given by God, but by men! 
. 
This paradise violate all that is holy and promises a physical and material vision that will never materialize! 
. 
In addition to Quranic translations of 78:33 specifying the virgins will be voluptuous, Sahih International translates it as "full-breasted [companions] of equal age". Tafsir al-Jalalayn says "and buxom maidens (kawā‘ib is the plural of kā‘ib) of equal age (atrāb is the plural of tirb)". Several Islamic scholars explain that they will have "large, round breasts which are not inclined to hang". 
. 
Sahih International 
And full-breasted [companions] of equal age Muhsin Khan And young full-breasted (mature) maidens of equal age;Pickthall And voluptuous women of equal age; 
. 
Yusuf Ali 
And voluptuous women of equal age; 
. 
Shakir 
And voluptuous women of equal age; 
. 
Dr. Ghali 
And youthful virgins, like of age, 
. 
Abu Sa`id al-Khudri said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “The humblest of the People of Paradise shall have eighty thousand servants and seventy-two wives. A palace of pearl and peridot(a: A pale green variety of chrysolite; used as a gemstone) and sapphire shall be erected for him as wide as the distance between al-Jabiya [a valley about 70 kms. East of Makka] and San`a’ [in Yemen].” 
. 
Abu Umama said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “None is made to enter Paradise by Allah Most High except Allah Most High shall marry him to seventy-two wives, two of them from the wide-eyed maidens of Paradise and seventy of them his inheritance from the People of Hellfire, not one of them but her attraction never lags nor his arousal ever wanes.” 
. 
Anas said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “The servant in Paradise shall be married with seventy wives.” Someone said, “Messenger of Allah, can he bear it?” He said: “He will be given strength for a hundred.” 
Sifat al-Janna, al-`Uqayli in the Du`afa’, and Musnad of Abu Bakr al-Bazzar 
. 
Anas said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “The servant in Paradise shall be married with seventy wives.” Someone said, “Messenger of Allah, can he bear it?” He said: “He will be given strength for a hundred.” 
From Zayd ibn Arqam, Allah be well-pleased with him, when an incredulous Jew or Christian asked the Prophet, upon him blessings and peace, “Are you claiming that a man will eat and drink in Paradise??” He replied: “Yes, by the One in Whose hand is my soul, and each of them will be given the strength of a hundred men in his eating, drinking, coitus, and pleasure.” 
Sifat al-Janna, al-`Uqayli in the Du`afa’, and Musnad of Abu Bakr al-Bazzar 
. 
Abu Hurayra said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “The humblest of the People of Paradise in rank shall have seven levels and as he will be on the sixth, below the seventh, he will have three hundred servants, every morning and evening three hundred dishes of gold shall be brought before him, every dish carrying something the other does not. He will taste pleasure as sharply with the first dish as he will with the last. He shall say, ‘My Lord! If you gave me permission, I would feed all the people of Paradise and water them from what I have and nothing should go missing from it.’ He will most certainly have seventy-two wives from the wide-eyed maidens of Paradise, the couch of only one of whom is as wide as a square mile on earth.” 
Musnad Ahmad ibn Hanbal 
. 
Ibn Abi Awfa said, Allah be well-pleased with him: The Messenger of Allah said, upon him blessings and peace: “Every man from the People of Paradise shall be married off to four thousand virgins, eight thousand slave-girls, and one hundred wide-eyed maidens of Paradise. They shall all meet him within every seven days. They shall say with their exquisite voices no creature has ever heard the like before: ‘We are the everlasting women, we never grow old, we are the refined women, we never grow sour, we are the ever-pleased women, we never anger, we are the sedentary ones, we never travel away, blessings to him who is for us and we are for him!’” 
Abu al-Shaykh in al-`Azama and al-Bayhaqi in al-Ba`th wal-Nushur 
. 
Hatib ibn Abi Balta`a said, Allah be well-pleased with him: I heard the Messenger of Allah say, upon him blessings and peace: “The believer in Paradise shall be married off to seventy-two women,seventy women of the hereafter and two women of the women of this world.” 
Abu al-Shaykh in al-`Azama and al-Bayhaqi in al-Ba`th wal-Nushur 
. 
Abu Hurayra said, Allah be well-pleased with him: It was asked, “Messenger of Allah, do we reach our women in Paradise?” He replied, “A man will reach in a single day one hundred virgins.” 
Al-Tabarani in al-Saghir and al-Awsat, Abu Nu`aym in Sifat al-Janna, and al-Khatib in Tarikh Baghdad 
. 
The stronger hadiths indicate that the Believers shall have two wives, in Bukhari and Muslim from Abu Hurayra, from the Prophet, upon him blessings and peace: Each man among them shall have two wives, the marrow of each of the two wives' shanks will be seen glimmering under the flesh, and there is not in all Paradise a single unmarried man. They will have up to a hundred concubines in Paradise while the Shuhada shall have seventy-two wives, numbers indicating abundance rather than an exact quantity, and Allah knows best. 
How Many Wives Will The Believers Have In Paradise? 
Shaykh Gibril Haddad, SunniPath.com, Question ID:4828 

. 
. 
. 
5) Fifth Reason 
. 
The creation of Adam and Eve in the bible versus the Quran shows that there is no connection whatsoever! 
. 
The quran copied and changed it to suit them. 
. 
In the Bible, the woman is created from the rib of the man. 
. 
In the Qur'an, Eve is not mentioned by name, but it states that all mankind were created from one soul (Adam). 
. 
However, the  Hadith confirms that Eve was created and whatever the Quran miss the Hadith finds it and corrects it, this being the case the hadith has been the instrument that govern the muslim which they have received so many lies from! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
6) Sixth Reason 
. 
No Prophecies in the Quran versus almost 2000 in the bible again shows that the bible and Quran has NO connection. 
. 
Lack of Prophecies! At best I have heard that Muhammad had one or two prophecies, and I would like to examine them. But what these so called prophecies was saying was already sealed in the bible, hardly a prophecy if it was already said, but this is what you believe! 
. 
The Bible has upwards of 2000 prophecies and NOT ONE OF THEM are connected to Islam in a way that validates what the islamic community 
are saying. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
7) Seventh Reason 
. 
Genealogy in the Quran versus Genealogy in the bible is different! 
. 
Genealogy is very complex in the bible and totally different the way that islam express it! This genealogy will prove that Ishmael seed promises from God has already been fulfilled! 
. 
So Muhammad has been published to be Jesus successor by the Islamic leadership and Muslim really believe this! Wow! 
. 
But it is a lie! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
8) Eight Reason 
. 
Prophesy about Ishmael doesn't apply to Muhammad? This proves that Yahweh-Jehovah doesn't approve of Muhammad as the successor! 
. 
The prophecy about Ishmael doesn't apply to Muhammad at all, peace be upon him! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
9) Ninth Reason 
. 
The Bible View On Circumcision versus The Quran View, proves that Islam didn't get none of the major information from the bible! 
. 
What did the bible say and what we now know? 
. 
The Qur'an itself does not mention circumcision in any verse, not one! But some Hadith mention it, Imagine that! 
. 
Some accounts report that Heraclius, Emperor of Byzantium, had referred to Muhammad as the "leader of the circumcised people". 
Some hadith mentions circumcision in a list of practices known as fitra (acts considered to be of a refined person). 
. 
According to some hadith (Abdullah Ibn Jabir and Aisha),Muhammad supposedly circumcised his grandsons on the seventh day after their birth. 
. 
Under Sunni Islam, and Amongst Ulema (Muslim legal scholars), there are differing opinions about the compulsion of circumcision in Sharia (Islamic law). Imams Abū Ḥanīfa, founder of the Hanafi school of Fiqh(Islamic jurisprudence), and Malik ibn Anas, maintain that circumcision is a Sunnah Mu'akkadah—not obligatory but highly recommended. 
. 
Under Shia Islam, Most Shia traditions regard the practice as obligatory. They rely on sayings that come from classical Shia authors.In one narration Muhammad was asked if an uncircumcised man could go to pilgrimage. He answered "not as long as he is not circumcised". They quote Ali as saying: "If a man becomes Muslim, he must submit to circumcision even if he is 80 years old". Another narration from Al-Sadiq says: "Circumcise your sons when they are seven days old as it is cleaner (athar) and the flesh grows faster and because the earth hates the urine of the uncircumcised". 
. 
The Quranist, There is a Quran alone movement within Islam that rejects making male circumcision a religious requirement due to the fact it is not mentioned in any verse in the Qur'an. At the same time the Qur'an is supposed to explain all things (Qur'an 12:111). 
. 
Islamic sources do not fix a particular time for circumcision. It depends on family, region and country. A majority of Ulema however take the view that parents should get their child circumcised before the age of ten.The preferred age is usually seven although some Muslims are circumcised as early as on the seventh day after birth and as late as at the commencement of puberty. 
. 
Thousands of years  before the Quran, the Egyptians practice circumcision but the Moabites, the Ammonites, and the Edomites also did. (Jer 9:25, 26) Later, the Samaritans that adhered to the requirements set out in the Pentateuch were also circumcised. On the other hand, the Assyrians, the Babylonians, the Greeks, and notably the Philistines did not practice circumcision. The latter in particular, rather than the Canaanites in general, are derogatorily spoken of as “the uncircumcised,” and it was from fighting with them that trophies of foreskins were brought.—Judges 14:3; 15:18; 1Sameul 14:6; 17:26; 18:25-27; 2Sameul1:20; 1Chronicles 10:4. 
. 
Abraham’s descendants through Isaac and Jacob faithfully kept the covenant of circumcision. “Abraham proceeded to circumcise Isaac his son when eight days old, just as God had commanded him.” (Ge 21:4; Ac 7:8; Ro 4:9-12). 
. 
Circumcision Under the Law was made a mandatory requirement of the Mosaic Law. “On the eighth day [after the birth of a male] the flesh of his foreskin will be circumcised.” (Leviticus 12:2, 3) So important was it that, if the eighth day fell on the highly regarded Sabbath, circumcision was to be performed anyway. (John 7:22, 23) Examples of parents under this Law who faithfully had their children circumcised on the eighth day include the parents of John the Baptizer, Jesus, and Paul. (Luke 1:59; 2:21; Philipians 3:4, 5) The Law also required aliens to be circumcised before they were allowed to eat the passover.—Exodus 12:43-48. 
. 
Thus, in God’s eyes, circumcision had nothing to do with manhood. It was performed to indicate that a person belonged to the Israelite descendants of Abraham, who were privileged to be “entrusted with the sacred pronouncements of God.”—Romans 3:1, 2. 
. 
Why did the Law specify that circumcision be done on the eighth day? 
God did not explain, nor was it necessary that he do so. His ways are always right; his reasons, the best. (2Sa 22:31) 
. 
 However, in recent years man has learned some of the physical reasons why the eighth day was a good time to circumcise. Normal amounts of the blood-clotting element called vitamin K are not found in the blood until the fifth to the seventh day after birth. Another clotting factor known as prothrombin is present in amounts only about 30 percent of normal on the third day but on the eighth day is higher than at any other time in the child’s life—as much as 110 percent of normal. So, following God's instructions would help to avoid the danger of hemorrhage. As Dr. S. I. McMillen observes:“From a consideration of vitamin K and prothrombin determinations the perfect day to perform a circumcision is the eighth day . . . [the] day picked by the Creator of vitamin K.”—None of These Diseases, 1986, p. 21. 
…................................................................................. 

This FGM is an ungodly practice! 
. 
Yet another custom commonly practiced in some countries is what some term “female circumcision,” now generally called female genital mutilation (FGM). The operation removes part or most of a girl’s genitalia. 
. 
The custom was publicized by Waris Dirie, a well-known fashion model and special ambassador for the United Nations Population Fund. In accord with local Somalian custom, as a child she was subjected to FGM by her mother. According to one report, between eight and ten million women and girls in the Middle East and Africa are at risk of undergoing FGM. Even in the United States, an estimated 10,000 girls are at risk. 
. 
What beliefs underlie this practice? Some think that the female genitals are evil and that they make a girl unclean and therefore unmarriageable. In addition, cutting off, or removing, the genitals is looked upon as insurance of the child’s virginity and faithfulness. Failure by the mother to perpetuate this custom may incur the wrath of her husband and the local community. 
Many mothers, however, have come to realize that there is no legitimate reason—religious, medical, or hygienic—to support this painful practice. The Nigerian documentary Repudiating Repugnant Customs reveals that many mothers have courageously refused to subject their daughters to it. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
10) Tenth Reason 
. 
Love in the bible is totally different in the Quran! Again proves that the Quran has no connection with the bible! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
11) Eleventh Reason 
. 
Discrimination Against Women in Quran and Ancient Writings 
. 
From the first century C.E. onward, writers such as Philo of Alexandria began to use Greek philosophy to reinterpret the Genesis account. 
For Philo, Eve was guilty of sexual sin and was therefore condemned to a life that “utterly deprives her of her freedom and subjects her to the dominion of the man who is her companion.” Such contempt for women infiltrated Judaism, as well as the writings of the Church Fathers. 
. 
In the Midrash Rabba, a second-century Jewish text, a rabbi explained why he felt women should wear a veil, saying: “She is like one who has done wrong and is ashamed of people.” Theologian Tertullian, whose writings were influential as early as the second century C.E., taught that women should walk about “as Eve mourning and repentant.” Such teachings, often wrongly regarded as coming from the Bible, have contributed to much discrimination against women.﻿ 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
12) Twelfth Reason 
. 
Freewill understanding is different as it relates to Yahweh-Jehovah Creation! 
. 
In creating humans God had two choices: 
. 
Robots (Automatons) – Automatons is a Robot which is program to do as you say, and has no mind nor feeling of his own. 
. 
Freewill – Freewill is when we make our own independent choice to do something in the absence of fear. 
. 
. 
Plants grow with no free will choice! The stars move in orbit with no free will choice! 
God’s laws of nature control them and they cannot resist! 
. 
As a result, the universe of such bodies is orderly and harmonious throughout. 
. 
The animals have “Instinct Wisdom Programed Before Birth”... 
Scientist took a shark who had never travel and place it on the other side of the world, and it made it back to it birthplace without ever making the trip......This knowledge is programmed in the sharks data banks at birth. 
How its hunt/food choices, mating season information and seasonal information are all embedded inside at birth! 
. 
But man is a free will/free moral agent and can if he so desires exercise his choice of action in an discriminate or indiscriminate way. If he does it by bible principle (Understanding by God spirit) he is considered to be in the light, and if he against bible principle he is considered in darkness, against the creator! 
. 
Also, human ruler which original wasn't a God given right, but are allowed to exist with no interruptions from God (Will explain later)...... 
. 
Human rulers who use fear of (retaliation or death) to mentally control a person “freewill” by man made laws are doing so not because God are telling them but because of their own agenda! This is normally manifested by related penalty law....This is outside the order of what God even does!........Free Will is your “God Given Right” 
and in God word the bible, God doesn't make you do nothing! He ask you! It is imperfect human rulers who goes beyond that! 
. 
The bible say that God is love and it is this love that God convinces us to have and use...... 
God ask us to love one another, not hate! 
God ask us to respect one another not to disrespect one another! 
God say if you find a woman or man that you love, than only love that person, not having many! 
God said take care of the ones who came before you and love them even if they have grown old! 
God said to love each other equally, but do we do this, do the world at large does this, no! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
13) Thirteenth Reason 
. 
The biblical information that the earth is round versus the Quran shows that the bible had it before the Quran! 
. 
The Earth - Aristotle's model vs. Isaiah bible imagery? (Isaiah 40:22) 

1300 years before the Arabic Language, The Quran, Islam, mosque, the Hadith and any of Muslims holy books was written, Jehovah God had Isaiah write under the inspiration and direction of his “Holy Spirit” a phenomenon about the earth which Aristotle and Christopher Columbus and the Quran missed..... 
. 
 Note what Isaiah writes under Holy Spirit! 
. 
Isaiah 40:22 - King James Version (KJV) 
It is he that sitteth upon the circle of the earth, and the inhabitants thereof are as grasshoppers; that stretcheth out the heavens as a curtain, and spreadeth them out as a tent to dwell in: 
. 
"The Circle of the earth" Wow 
. 
Aristotle reasoned that the celestial spheres were rigid. The one holding the stars in place like the others, could neither shrink nor expand..........While Christopher Columbus believe the earth was flat! 
. 
It stand to reason that the bible information was ready available because the book of Isaiah was completed around 732 B.C.E. (Before Common Era) which means over 1000 years had elapsed since God summoned Isaiah to write down those heavenly facts! Please don't get confused B.C.E. vs. C.E. different years altogether! 
. 
The Islamic Prophet (Not Bible Prophet, But Islam) Muhammad died the same year which the Quran followed centuries later, so this proves that the Quran didn't have it first, and the same year Aristotle died in 632 C.E. (Common Era) 1000 after Isaiah complete his God given this commission....This allowed biblical knowdledge for Muhammad foundation only to be applied later! 
. 
What this proves is that if they had read the bible they would have known that it was round, because God told Isaiah to write it down! 
. 
Only in the 20th century has it been possible for humans to travel by airplane, and later into outer space and even to the moon, thus giving them a clear view of “the circle” of earth’s horizon. 
. 
In effect, science has rendered Aristotle’s model obsolete, while the bible with modern technology has proven what Isaiah wrote almost 2750 year ago still stand..... 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
If a person decided that they didn't want to serve God today, God will not haunt them down to kill them this is mankind leadership, not God's......Because God is love! 
God would be so hurt that you decided that you will abandon him, and in the bible say when a person who has left returns than all the angels rejoice in heaven....God truly love you!. 
. 
Because we are allowed such wide latitude of free will choice God has given us some guidance. 
Some of it is built in and the rest is in the bible.......This month we will explore both! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
14) Fourteenth Reason 
. 
Prayer that muslim pray and how and what the bible speaks on prayers are totally different. 
. 
If there are similarity of prayers than Muslim stolen them from the bible. 
. 
Also, note that the bible distinguish two different prayers, those of the pharisees that God didn;t approve of and those that Jesus spoke about and which meet with God's approval. 
. 
1 Kings 8:54 
54 And as soon as Sol′o·mon finished offering to Jehovah this entire prayer and request for favor, he rose up from before the altar of Jehovah, where he had been kneeling with his hands spread out to the heavens. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
15) Fifthteenth Reason 
. 
The first Mosque ever built was built in 622 C.E. over 600 years after Jesus...SO before than how can they say that Jesus assumed their position... All lies! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
16) Sixteenth Reason 
. 
Scriptural integrity between the quran and the bible proves that the bible and islam are not connected! 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
17) Seventhenth Reason 
. 
Islam Copied New and OLD Testament from Catholics. 

Muslims Here Is 1000% Proof that Islamic Leadership Copied from the Catholics False Doctrines and lied To All Sincere Muslims Worldwide. 
. 
Muslims Will Be In A State Of Shocked When They Read This Post! 
. 
Debunked: Islamic Leaders and Muslims Final Testament Propaganda 
The Quran Isn't The Final Testament! 
. 
Debunked: Islamic Scholars Copied Final Testament from False Information and this Post will provide biblical proof that it did! 
. 
Muslims How Can You believe That The Quran Is The Last Testament of God When There Has Never Been A Old or New Testament or a First or Second Testament, much less a last and Final Testament! 
. 
Muslims has been deceived and now it is time for you to WAKE UP!! 
. 
Many Sincere Muslims Worldwide May Not Be Aware That Islamic Leadership Has Copied Almost All Of Their Belief off of the Catholics From Prayer Beads, Purgatory, Hell and Soul! 
. 
The only difference is that they tweaked it so it won't resemble it! 
. 
Purgatory, Hell and Soul are lies as well! 
. 
So now the true God Yahweh-Jehovah Holy Scriptures are exposing them to show sincere Muslims that the information is false, and they should learn the real truth from the bible and discontinue with these false doctrines such as Testament, Hell, Purgatory and Islam Promise Paradise which will never materialized.. 
. 
Jesus Spoke About The Apostasy, and Muslim Copied That Apostate Information, Which Proves Islam And The Bible Has No Connection 
and it further proves that Islam Leadership has copied from the Catholics and turned around and lied to all sincere Muslim people! 
. 
Islamic Leadership has deceived Muslims in believing in a final testament, when the hijackers and impostors of the bible has 
changed and misinterpreted the scriptures themselves saying the New and Old testament which the bible has NEVER said in History. 
. 
Take a look at the bible image below it says the "Holy Scriptures" and you will never see an New or Old Testament in it, and here is why? 
. 
Why do Satan want you to believe that the bible is Old and out dated is because the bible major prophesies from Isaiah, Daniel and Ezekiel are undergoing fulfillment right under your eyes today, and if Satan can use others to keep you away from this information than you could miss out on the promise paradise that was made for you. 
. 
Let US now examine the truth about TESTAMENT! 
. 
The “Old Testament” and “New Testament.” Not from the bible, but from Catholics, So Muslim HAS COPIED THIS TERM FROM THEM! 
. 
Today it is a common practice to refer to the Scriptures written in Hebrew and Aramaic as the “Old Testament.” 
. 
This is based on the reading in 2 Corinthians 3:14 in the Latin Vulgate, the King James Version and the Catholic Douay-Rheims 1899. 
. 
Muslims, Notice how the (Catholic Douay Bible and King James) use the phrase Old Testament and this is what (Islam copied), but the bible never said Old Testament, Only the Catholics, and this is proof that Islam copied from the Catholics And Not The bible. 
. 
Also look below and see what the others translation are saying and than you will see the PLOT with your own eyes, and see that I am not lying to you, but I desire us to be brother and sister, truthfully! 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 - 21st Century King James Version (KJ21) 
14 But their minds were blinded; for until this day the same veil remaineth untaken away in the reading of the (Old testament), which veil is done away with in Christ. 
. 
3:14 ﻛﻮﺭﻧﺜﻮﺱ ﺍﻟﺜﺎﻧﻴﺔ 
Arabic Life Application Bible (ALAB) 
 وَلَكِنَّ أَذْهَانَهُمْ قَدْ أُعْمِيَتْ، لأَنَّ ذَلِكَ الْحِجَابَ مَازَالَ مُسْدَلاً حَتَّى الْيَوْمِ عِنْدَمَا يُقْرَأُ الْعَهْدُ الْقَدِيمُ، وَهُوَ لاَيُزَالُ إِلاَّ فِي الْمَسِيحِ 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 Douay-Rheims 1899 American Edition (DRA) 
14 But their senses were made dull. For, until this present day, the selfsame veil, in the reading of the (Old Testament), remaineth not taken away (because in Christ it is made void). 
. 
II Corinthios 3:14 Biblia Sacra Vulgata (VULGATE) 
14 sed obtusi sunt sensus eorum usque in hodiernum enim diem id ipsum velamen in lectione (Veteris Testamenti) manet non revelatum quoniam in Christo evacuatur 
. 
This is how it suppose to read! 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 (New World Translation Of The Holy Scriptures) 
But their minds were dulled. For to this present day, the same veil remains uplifted when the (old covenant) is read, because it is taken away only by means of Christ. 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 American Standard Version (ASV) 
14 but their minds were hardened: for until this very day at the reading of the (old covenant) the same veil remaineth, it not being revealed to them that it is done away in Christ. 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 English Standard Version (ESV) 
14 But their minds were hardened. For to this day, when they read the (old covenant), that same veil remains unlifted, because only through Christ is it taken away. 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 New International Version (NIV) 
14 But their minds were made dull, for to this day the same veil remains when the (old covenant) is read. It has not been removed, because only in Christ is it taken away. 
. 
2 Corinthians 3:14 New Revised Standard Version (NRSV) 
14 But their minds were hardened. Indeed, to this very day, when they hear the reading of the (old covenant), that same veil is still there, since only in Christ is it set aside. 
. 
However, the rendering “Old Testament” in this text is incorrect. 
. 
The Greek word di·a·the′kes here means “covenant,” as it does in the other 32 places where it occurs in the Greek text. Many modern translations correctly read “old covenant.” (NE, RS, JB) The apostle Paul is not referring to the Hebrew and Aramaic Scriptures in their entirety. Neither does he mean that the inspired Christian writings constitute a “new testament (or, covenant).” The apostle is speaking of the old Law covenant, which was recorded by Moses in the Pentateuch and which makes up only a part of the pre-Christian Scriptures. 
. 
For this reason he says in the next verse, “whenever Moses is read.” 
. 
Hence, there is no valid basis for the Hebrew and Aramaic Scriptures to be called the “Old Testament” and for the Christian Greek Scriptures to be called the “New Testament.” 
. 
Jesus Christ himself referred to the collection of sacred writings as “the Scriptures.” 
. 
Matthew 21:42  (New World Translation Of The Holy Scriptures) 
Jesus said to them: “Did you never read in the (Scriptures), ‘The stone that the builders rejected, this has become the chief cornerstone. This has come from Jehovah, and it is marvelous in our eyes’? 
. 
Matthew 21:42 American Standard Version (ASV) 
42 Jesus saith unto them, Did ye never read in the (Scriptures), The stone which the builders rejected, The same was made the head of the corner; This was from the Lord, And it is marvelous in our eyes? 
. 
Mark 14:49 (New World Translation Of The Holy Scriptures) 
Day after day I was with you in the temple teaching, and yet you did not take me into custody. 
Nevertheless, this is to fulfill the Scriptures.” 
. 
Mark 14:49 Douay-Rheims 1899 American Edition (DRA) 
49 I was daily with you in the temple teaching, and you did not lay hands on me. But that the (Scriptures) may be fulfilled. 
. 
John 5:39 NWT (New World Translation Of The Holy Scriptures) 
“You are searching the (Scriptures) because you think that you will have everlasting life by means of them; and these are the very ones that bear witness about me. 
. 
John 5:39 Douay-Rheims 1899 American Edition (DRA) 
39 Search the (scriptures), for you think in them to have life everlasting; and the same are they that give testimony of me. (Mt 21:42; Mr 14:49; Joh 5:39) 
. 

. 
The apostle Paul referred to them as “the holy Scriptures,” “the Scriptures,” and “the holy writings.”—Ro 1:2; 15:4; 2Ti 3:15. 
. 
Romans 1:2 King James Version (KJV) 
2 (Which he had promised afore by his prophets in the holy scriptures,) 
. 
Romans 1:2 New Revised Standard Version (NRSV) 
2 which he promised beforehand through his prophets in the holy scriptures, 
. 
Romans 15:4 New Revised Standard Version (NRSV) 
4 For whatever was written in former days was written for our instruction, so that by steadfastness and by the encouragement of the (Scriptures) we might have hope. 
. 
Romans 15:4 King James Version (KJV) 
4 For whatsoever things were written aforetime were written for our learning, that we through patience and comfort of the scriptures might have hope. 
. 
2 Timothy 3:15 King James Version (KJV) 
15 And that from a child thou hast known the holy scriptures, which are able to make thee wise unto salvation through faith which is in Christ Jesus. 
. 
2 Timothy 3:15 New Revised Standard Version (NRSV) 
15 and how from childhood you have known the sacred writings that are able to instruct you for salvation through faith in Christ Jesus. 
. 
Attention All Muslim, New Testament and Old Testament is APOSTATE Teaching along with Purgatory and Hell. 
So now Muslims see that Islam copied the prayer beads from 
the catholic and tweaked it alone with Hell and Purgatory. 
. 
Please Dr. Naik, you are the scholar just tell the sincere Muslims the truth that Islam copied the Purgatory and hell from the Catholics, just tell them the truth and let them decide. 
. 
But Don't scholastically deceive them intentionally!﻿ 
. 
. 
. 
. 
.Abraham and Ismeal 

The Qur'an says Abraham built it Qur'an 2:125 - Muhammed says it was built 40 years prior to the Temple at Jerusalem Sahih Bukhari4:55:636 
The Temple at Jerusalem was built by Solomon around 958-951 BC. This implies that if Muhammad were to be believed, the Ka’aba must have been built approximately 998-991 BC. But Abraham lived around 2000 BC and both Abraham and Ishmael would have been dead by then. 
If Muhammad is correct, then the Qur’an [and therefore Allah] is wrong. But if the Qur’an is correct in stating that Abraham and Ishmael built the Ka’aba, then Muhammad and the hadith is wrong. 
The Ka’aba has nothing to do with Abraham or Ishmael. It has a wholly pagan heritage. Egyptian Professor and foremost authority on Arabic literature, Dr. Taha Husayn, said the following: 
The case for this episode is very obvious because it is of recent date and came into vogue just before the rise of Islam. Islam exploited it for religious reasons 
﻿ 

Muhamid is a liar 
Sahih Al-Bukhari HadithHadith 6.378        Narrated byMasruq 
I said to 'Aisha, "O Mother! Did Prophet Muhammad see his Lord?" 'Aisha said, "What you have said makes my hair stand on end ! Know that if somebody tells you one of the following three things, he is a liar: Whoever tells you that Muhammad saw his Lord, is a liar." Then Aisha recited the Verse: 
"No vision can grasp Him, but His grasp is over all vision. He is the Most Courteous Well-Acquainted with all things."   (6.103) "It is not fitting for a human being that Allah should speak to him except by inspiration or from behind a veil."  (42.51)  'Aisha further said, "And whoever tells you that the Prophet knows what is going to happen tomorrow, is a liar." She then recited: 

"No soul can know what it will earn tomorrow." (31.34) She added: "And whoever tells you that he concealed (some of Allah's orders), is a liar." Then she recited: "O Apostle! Proclaim (the Message) which has been sent down to you from your Lord..." (5.67) 'Aisha added, "But the Prophet saw Gabriel in his true form twice." 

Sahih Al-Bukhari HadithHadith 9.477        Narrated byMasruq 
'Aisha said, "If anyone tells you that Muhammad has seen his Lord, he is a liar, for Allah says: 'No vision can grasp Him.' (6.103) And if anyone tells you that Muhammad has seen the Unseen, he is a liar, for Allah says: "None has the knowledge of the Unseen but Allah." 

﻿ 

according to the quran the earth is flat. 
Qur'an 20:53  Qur'an 43:10 Qur'an 50:7 Qur'an 51:48 Qur'an 71:19 Qur'an 78:6 Qur'an 79:30 Qur'an 15:19 
In Arabic, each word must be derived from its root. The root usually consists of three letters that can be manipulated, by adding vowels, prefixes and suffixes in order to produce different words with different meanings. For example, "ka-ta-ba" (to write) is the root for many words such as kitab (book), maktaba (library), katib (author), maktoob (written), kitabat (writings) et cetera. 
 "Duhiya". This word is not a root. It is a noun and is derived from "da-ha-wa", the same root that the verb "dahaha" comes from. Furthermore, Duhiya does not even mean the egg of an ostrich. 
Al-udhy, Al-idhy, Al-udhiyya, Al-idhiyya, Al-udhuwwa:The place in sand where an ostrich lays its egg. That's because the ostrich spreads out the earth with its feet then lays its eggs there, an ostrich doesn't have a nest. 
LOL WHAT A BUNCH OF KAFIRS﻿

Meer lezen (1056 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-byaUAQGh3hs/Ut2Tn3J4OcI/AAAAAAAACnY/aLTO64zoBbc/w426-h414/The%2BTetragrammaton%2Band%2Bthe%2BDivine%2BName%2Bin%2Bthe%2BHebrew%2BScriptures%2B1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/114208209189461132868/albums/5697564349197767585/5697564353067988338</link><title>It's a soup kind of day for me. For lunch, I'm having egg noodles in a beef and mushroom broth with three types of shrooms (beech, shiitake and button) topped with hot sauce hot, jalapeno and scallions. 

What's on your menu? 

#foodie 
#teamtorta 
#foodporn﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-CWPaE__L--o/TxHQl5WLtXI/AAAAAAAAG0k/A0a33DX6iKg/w426-h284/eggnoodles_mushroom.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/116492394921952587453/albums/5917561464429561297/5917561468817561986?authkey=COW3n5mYpevvKA</link><title>If I was to create my own personal list of the wonders of the world, Angkor would definitely be on the list. I visited here in 2008. 

Many people confuse Angkor Wat, which is one temple, with the entire Angkor complex. Angkor is an entire city of temples. If you look at a satellite images, you can clearly see a giant green rectangle in Cambodia. THAT is Angkor. 

It will easily take you several days to see Angkor and if you were taking your time it could take as much as a week. Then there are still smaller temple ruins surrounding Angkor all around Siem Reap. 

#cambodia   #angkorwat   #angkortemples   #travelphotography 
http://everything-everywhere.com/2010/02/24/daily-travel-photo-angkor-cambodia-4/﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-lTpgi9hjbxk/Uh9mzaVo2YI/AAAAAAAAFQU/Y_vp-grNZR0/w426-h285/3018982984_2ece36a4b5_o-X3.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/106136450056876804759/albums/5886692219619459057/5886692220924959250?authkey=CNLs2biYy43QtQE</link><title>The Majlis Resort Restaurant serves the mixture of international dishes including Italian and Swahili dishes.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4F1hF6vatnc/UbG7YspJmhI/AAAAAAAADKA/PSOZuzDCPrs/w426-h284/02-food-shot-majlis-restaurant.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/106136450056876804759/albums/5772048036331359713/5772048038300072866</link><title>The Majlis Restaurant is a focal point of the hotel due to its unique architecture as well as its excellent cuisine, which includes International, Italian (seafood, pasta, wooden pizza oven and home-made ice cream) and Swahili dishes. The restaurant is open both for in-house guests and external guests. In-house guests of the hotel typically book an all-inclusive stay because of the lack of good and easy to access restaurants in the Lamu archipelago.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1mMFJgaYrig/UBpvG_Vdu6I/AAAAAAAABHQ/reDlDcYDsXM/w426-h285/A%2BTaste%2Bof%2B%2BParadise%2B%2526%2BRomantic%2BRestaurant%2Bwith%2Ba%2BView%2Bin%2BThe%2BMajlis%2BHotel.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/106136450056876804759/albums/5805364862150570801/5805364865597210834</link><title>The restaurant of The Majlis Resort provides mouth-watering delicacies which are a combination of local Swahili cuisine blended with international and Italian dishes.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-oqTwKuDj0JQ/UJDMlk10gNI/AAAAAAAABls/Rm7ue7mvJ_U/w426-h320/167859_175664249140612_325937_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7258-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/swahili%20dishes/photos/115980725439982061421/albums/5854999399496010721/5854999399828275570</link><title>this is my new years resolution. i save recipes to make later, except some of these are older than my kids. this year they get made. 

note: these do not include desserts, those will take a few more years ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7258_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Q-jr_DOvh-8/UUEi7trjwXI/AAAAAAAAGkA/Wx5MXVz308I/w426-h316/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>