<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:57:24" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/103264645106286817206/albums/5866679617951474961/5866679620050813218?authkey=CLz8oIjM9tmZYA</link><title>Understanding the health benefits of radishes 

Radish roots and leaves of vegetables that it has numerous properties. 
Radish plant height, stem up to a meter a year, that is. Its leaves are broad, rough, fluff and irregular cuts. 

The flowers are white, light yellow, light blue and purple that appears at the end of branches. 

Some properties of this plant are: 

• radish leaves and roots have plenty of vitamin C. 

• The amount of vitamin C found in the leaves of this vegetable, it is five times more than its roots. 

• The red spherical root vegetables also contain plenty of potassium, folic acid and copper. 

• Radishes and anti-cancer properties of these herbs have long been used to treat liver disorders. 

• From radishes to stave off kidney stones is used to treat gout and rheumatism and helpful. 

• If the leaf is eaten with food aid is good for digestion. Radish leaves juice is good for strengthening the eyes. [Understanding the properties of certain foods are beneficial for strengthening the eyes] 

• Eating eggs, radishes, increases the secretion of breast feeding. 

• Radish seeds are tonic.﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Z8jGDLolwiE/UWqiCAwnASI/AAAAAAAAAVU/xlTO3Rf-HsE/w426-h320/%25D8%25B3%25D8%25A8%25D8%25B2%25DB%258C-%25D8%25AE%25D9%2588%25D8%25B1%25D8%25AF%25D9%2586.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/101860536014427450904/albums/5776132263193083505/5776132261279288882</link><title>Health benefits of radish 

In China, radish along with cabbage and soybean curd (tofu) is believed as healthy food. A Chinese proverb says, "Eating pungent radish and drinking hot tea, let the starved doctors beg on their knees". 

Radishes are very low calorie root vegetables; contains only 16 calories per 100 g. However they are very good source of anti-oxidants, minerals, vitamins and dietary fiber. 

Fresh Radishes are rich in vitamin C; provide about 15 mg or 25% of DRI of vitamin C per 100 g.  Vitamin C is a powerful water soluble anti-oxidant required by the body for synthesis of collagen. Vitamin C helps body scavenge harmful free radicals, prevention from cancers, inflammation and helps boost immunity. 

In addition, they contain adequate levels of folates, vitamin B-6, riboflavin, thiamin and minerals such as iron, magnesium, copper and calcium. 

They contain many phytochemicals like indoles which are detoxifying agents and zeaxanthin, lutein and beta carotene which are flavonoid antioxidants. 

Selection and storage 

In general, radishes are available year-around with peak season during winter and spring. Daikons are most flavorful and juicy during winter. 

Look for roots that feature fresh, stout and firm in texture. Their top greens also should be fresh and feature crispy greens. Avoid roots that have cracks or cuts on their surface. Look carefully for the change in their texture and color. Yellowness indicated the stock is old. If the root yields to pressure and soft, the interior likely be pithy instead of crispy. 

Once at home, remove the top greens as they rob nutrients of the roots. Then wash thoroughly in clean water to rid off surface dust and soil. Store them in a zip pouch or plastic bag in the refrigerator where they remain fresh for up to a week.﻿

Meer lezen (39 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Wen9tjo8b5c/UCjxsDk5zjI/AAAAAAAAAM8/jDloUdhWG2g/w426-h601/radish.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/103710647743740067347/albums/5965979605619550865/5965979611241572610?sqi=106213124031919971055&amp;sqsi=bd218993-ad6f-4bb4-8352-5e195a8d705b</link><title>Radishes 
Radishes are root vegetables related to the turnip and horseradish family, with crisp texture and peppery hot flavor.  Radishes have often been dismissed as decoration and garnish. 

Sliced radish can be drying by the microwave 

read more :http://www.microwavedrying.net/products/Dry_Equipment/index.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-yKaijhQbQAM/Ustq2OlG6QI/AAAAAAAAF0g/SKwuevP7mtU/w426-h595/Easter%2BEgg%2BRadishes.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/106943921756625363910/albums/5781724024398721841/5781724031928601266</link><title>Don't judge a green by it's root! Have you ever passed up adding radish greens to your smoothie because you don't like the root? Well, I have some good news for you... the greens taste nothing like the root! Give them a try next time. This smoothie is 8 ounces of coconut water, 1 small banana, 1 cup pitted cherries, 1 cup frozen blueberries, 1 teaspoon cinnamon, 2 cups radish greens and 1/2 head of butterhead lettuce. It's one serving with about 340 calories, 7 grams of protein, 11.6 grams of fiber, 16% DV of calcium and 3.9 mg of iron. What's in your blender?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-7wq3_KASiZg/UDzPX8hxirI/AAAAAAAAAc4/Ergf2o50e4I/w426-h423/IMGP1869.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/107452501990644031425/albums/5729223209040823681/5729223214575543250</link><title>Japanese Radish 

Japanese Radish is called daikon in Japan. The Japanese word “dai” means “large” and “kon” means “root” in English. There are many kinds of radishes in various sizes and forms. 

Learn more at http://j-simplerecipes.com/foodstuffs_vegetables&amp;mushrooms.html#vegetables&amp;mushrooms﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-mbkN1As7FC4/T4JKKK-yY9I/AAAAAAAAAsc/Iu6RUKdx5zw/w426-h375/%25E5%25A4%25A7%25E6%25A0%25B9with%25E5%2585%2584%25E3%2580%2580google%252B.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/100228818068902560308/albums/5741714820703377361/5741714820429133170</link><title>Pacific Breeze Juice 
1 small papaya, 1 orange, 1 red radish, 1 small beetroot, 1carrot, 1 cup spinach, ½ inch ginger root.The taste of papaya merges with the taste of orange and beetroot to pack an incredible amount of enzymes, vitamins, and antioxidants into this powerful juice. 
With the compliments of Beautiful on Raw﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MLe30udpr2c/T66rNVFGNXI/AAAAAAAAAew/EGuSwqThk_0/w426-h400/Pacific%2BBreeze%2BJuice%2B1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/102345534186126041144/albums/5861576175384519137/5861576176301098786?authkey=CPrrtLy3oIjSNQ&amp;sqi=111997324016341780156&amp;sqsi=e9190295-cf39-442b-9711-d82a6066f349</link><title>"Bathtub Cured Radish" #川味 #洗澡萝卜 

This is one of those slow curing but low effort  #Szechuan  dishes, a quick cousin of famed Szechuan paocai (#泡菜, salty cured vegetables). 

Ingredients: 10 radish.  3/8 teaspoon salt.  1 teaspoon Szechuan red chili oil (熟油辣椒) - see my earlier posts. 

1\. Wash and clean radish.  Cut each radish in 2 to 3 pieces, or crush them with the flat side of Chinese cutting knife.  Toss with salt. (2 minutes)  2. Let stay in room temperature till water is extracted.  Then flip once or twice a day to soak each surface.  On second day, adjust saltiness. (2 days)  3. Mix in hot chili oil. 

Unlike Western pickles, the natural acid in Szechuan cured vegetables is produced more by lactobacillus than from vinegar. (My family tradition is to add no vinegar.)  So refrigerator is no good for the preparation.  In what Sichuan people call "bathtub cured vegetables" (洗澡泡菜, xizao paocai), not only is there less time for bacteria to grow, but the open-air environment is also unfavourable to lactobacillus.  As a result, there is less sour taste.  Additionally, short curing leaves some pungency from the raw vegetable, especially with radish. 

Despite the short curing time, however, you can still add some spices to the water, such as ginger root and Chinese prickly ash, in order to add flavour.﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-KVueW0EChWs/UViAefRRxyI/AAAAAAAAlJA/4hHRMlbmEPs/w426-h320/426F971A-AF42-4B91-9844-442B502C4D53.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/108130421983206749402/albums/5669333073485709825/5669333078597650354</link><title>Raw root vegetable salad - shaved gold and red beets, turnip, carrot, and watermelon radish with a citrus vinaigrette from a recipe in Bon Appetit. I'm a little sad that the farmers' market will be over soon :(﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-64j2st9BGZw/Tq2EZccvR7I/AAAAAAAABQA/fUIihS1A9rk/w426-h320/IMG_1460.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/105751452324845051349/albums/5836279057953403777/5836279064144043090?authkey=CObGs6D8l4-aOA</link><title>Traditionally, vegetables and fruits have been seasonal. But research suggests that eating with the season is healthier as there is a variation in the nutrient content of veggies when they are harvested off-season. Radish is traditionally been available during the winter months. 

Radish, a root crop that is pungent or sweet in taste is available in plenty during winter. This root vegetable has a lot of roughage and is a powerhouse of potassium, folic acid and ascorbic acid. Eat it raw, make parathas or Mullangi PindiMiriyam or whatever. 

For Mullangi Pindimiyam recipe text click here http://www.gayatrivantillu.com/recipes-2/chaaru-rasam-perugu-pachhallu-etc/mullangipindimiriyam 

For Video click here Mullangi (Raddish) Pindi Miriam (Godavari Ruchulu)﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-cIwrZCYI6Js/UP6g4wxa3FI/AAAAAAAAAHs/nn7iowLnThY/w426-h320/Mullangi%2BPindi%2BMiriyam.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7259-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/radish%20root/photos/113169736620549602064/albums/6005884332655087969/6005884334204443682?sqi=103312604743377598142&amp;sqsi=74321be4-af4a-44f0-95b3-9a6a375d2162</link><title>Beet, Squash, and Radish Moroccan Stew 
Stew doesn’t need to be thick, meaty, and time-consuming; instead it can be packed with vegetables, healthy, and an easy weeknight meal. Just sauté some onion and garlic with spices, add harissa and root vegetables, and cook for about 45 minutes to infuse all of the flavours and cook the vegetables through. Sweet raisins, honey, and tangy preserved lemons balance things out in this Moroccan-inspired, one-pot, vegetarian dish. Serve it over couscous and top with crunchy almonds and fresh cilantro. http://ow.ly/w7FjX﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7259_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-lpTNDBtSg_Y/U1kv-z5W3CI/AAAAAAAACMY/dpZqlskieAk/w426-h284/Beet%252C%2BSquash%252C%2Band%2BRadish%2BMoroccan%2BStew.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>