<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:16:06" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/117212234762564690546/albums/5989553470412020481/5989553472019502530</link><title>A grassland study, shows that grazing animals can crop fast growing grasses that can out-compete native plants in an over-fertilized world. Excess nutrient from over-fertilizing is a special problem for grasslands, where many plants, like annual wildflowers and others, have adapted to low nutrient levels. 

http://ecowatch.com/2014/03/11/grazing-animals-save-biodiversity-over-fertilized-grasslands/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-6TLZVAHI9zY/Ux8rJhbuFcI/AAAAAAAATAo/aMPxQPkON5E/w426-h256/U01.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/100408006897434710513/albums/5969122541769467281/5969122545567618946</link><title>Fuzzy-tongue Penstemon (Penstemon eriantherus) blooming in grassland habitat of Mount Sentinel (Missoula, MT) for #wildflowerwednesday  and +Bette Kauffman. 
Natural History Notes: The Penstemon genus (belongs to the Snapdragon family) contains 272 species,  the largest group of native flowering plants in North America. Are excellent plants for a xeriscape garden; need plenty of sun and little water, fertilizer. At one time Penstemon was considered for national flower designation (Strickler et al, 1997). 
Conservation Actions: Seed can be obtained via mail order; plant in yard areas that are gravely, rocky or sandy.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Csm8Yjc8uyE/UtaVVFVVV4I/AAAAAAAAEWg/aHeyO3xaoKM/w426-h639/Fuzzy-tongue-Penstemon-WildflowerWednesday.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/104340176530762389758/albums/5833332188590824913/5833332192156632946?authkey=CK-5iJmL8ZCAew</link><title>#geosciences #lipid_biomarkers #olduvai_gorge 

Water, plants, and early human habitats in eastern Africa 

'..Given the magnitude and variability in water availability revealed by our reconstructions, we hypothesize freshwater springs were important for hominin subsistence in highly variable environments..' 

Water and its inﬂuence on plants likely exerted strong adaptive pressures in human evolution. Understanding relationships among water, plants, and early humans is limited both by incomplete terrestrial records of environmental change and by indirect proxy data for water availability. 

Here we present a continuous record of stable hydrogen-isotope compositions (expressed as δD values) for lipid biomarkers preserved in lake sediments from an early Pleistocene archaeological site in eastern Africa—Olduvai Gorge. 

We convert sedimentary leaf- and algal-lipid δD values into estimates for ancient source-water δD values by accounting for biochemical, physiological, and environmental inﬂuences on isotopic fractionation via published water–lipid enrichment factors for living plants, algae, and recent sediments. 

Reconstructed precipitation and lake water δD values, respectively, are consistent with modern isotopic hydrology and reveal that dramatic ﬂuctuations in water availability accompanied ecosystem changes. 
Drier conditions, indicated by less negative δD values, occur in association with stable carbon-isotopic evidence for open, C4-dominated grassland ecosystems. 

Wetter conditions, indicated by lower δD values, are associated with expanded woody cover across the ancient landscape. Estimates for ancient precipitation amounts, based on reconstructed precipitation δD values, range between approximately 250 and 700 mm·y−1 and are consistent with modern precipitation data for eastern Africa. 

We conclude that freshwater availability exerted a substantial inﬂuence on eastern African ecosystems and, by extension, was central to early human proliferation during periods of rapid climate change. 

\- Clayton R. Magill, Gail M. Ashley, Katherine H. Freeman﻿

Meer lezen (41 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_03_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-8S0AsUZ3C2w/UPQouPJYx3I/AAAAAAAAFa4/aVIQPM_3Uhw/w426-h342/Screenshot%2B-%2B1_14_2013%2B%252C%2B11_21_03%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/112820806087024614029/albums/5806297598628605729/5806297604223400562</link><title>Ever since Daniel Eggert first fell in love with pasque flowers, among the first flowers of spring, he had wanted to photograph them covered in hoar frost. Now it was pasque-flower time once again. He had already identified a spot of chalky grassland near his home where the plants grew, on the rim of the Nördlinger Ries crater (a meteor crater) in Bavaria, Germany. So as soon as a cold, frosty, sunny dawn was forecast, Daniel headed up the hill. "I found the ideal flowers to photograph, but I didn't have much time," he says, "because I knew that as soon as the sun rose, the frost would quickly melt." He took this image just as the rising sun began to bathe the hill in a wonderful orange light. "I love the colors," he says, "and the contrast between the warm background and the cold ice." 
(Daniel Eggert/Veolia Environnement Wildlife Photographer of the Year 2012) 
For #hqspflowers curated by +HQSP Flowers +Carina Marsh +Delcour Eric ﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-h3zvvk8LNzE/UJQc6G_v-nI/AAAAAAAAcFA/Ifx6WO-rH3A/w426-h276/s_w03_rfection.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/115601680394653074259/albums/5819952351922086625/5889684278022935922?authkey=CP-QnMbN7Y-gRg</link><title>Sunset Sheep +Landscape Photography curated by +Margaret Tompkins +Carra Riley +paul t beard +David Heath Williams +Bill Wood +Jim Warthman +Ben T #LandscapePhotography +#RuralSaturday #ruralsaturday Curated by +Mario Cerroni +linda stokes +Sunset Saturday #sunsetsaturday Curated by +Dennis Hoffbuhr :- Beacon Hill sits between the ancient villages of Rottingdean and Ovingdean (they are both listed in the Domesday Book which was compiled and written in 1086) on the south coast of England. In 2004 it was created a Local Nature Reserve (LNR) to protect the habitat of the endangered skylarks by supporting a range of plants and butterflies associated with chalk grassland, as well as controlling areas of scrub and investigating archaeological features. From time to time sheep are allowed to graze on the hill and this is a shot I captured during the glow of sundown while they were all busy eating their supper! 

Photography by Justin Hill ©﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-rGKwIYW1saI/UbxcpV7ClXI/AAAAAAAAuq8/Sb0hT5CwcjM/w426-h320/Sunset%2BSheep.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/110582671305643479452/albums/6005560440056619745/6005560442607537042</link><title>WASHINGTON—U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) scientists and their colleagues have conducted research showing the potential response of rangeland plants in arid regions of the United States to the conditions that will occur with climate change, according to a paper published today in Nature. 
Agricultural Research Service (ARS) biological technician Melissa Reyes-Fox and Fort Lewis College assistant professor Heidi Steltzer were the lead co-authors on the paper. ARS is USDA's chief intramural scientific research agency, and the research supports the USDA priority of responding to climate change. 
"Agricultural producers want to know how global climate change is affecting their production and management practices," said ARS Administrator Chavonda Jacobs-Young. "This work is one example of how ARS scientists are helping producers meet climate change challenges and continue the cost-effective and environmentally sustainable production of food and feed." 
In a 5-year investigation, the researchers assessed the effects of increased temperatures and carbon dioxide levels on plants growing in a native mixed-grass prairie. For their study, they used a field system called Free-Air CO2 Enrichment to elevate current levels of carbon dioxide to 600 parts per million, the level of atmospheric carbon dioxide that is expected in the latter half of this century. Outdoor heaters in the fields kept air temperatures at current levels and at day and night temperatures that were 2.7 and 5.4 degrees Fahrenheit warmer than ambient temperatures. 
The scientists tracked leaf emergence, flower production, seed maturation, and canopy senescence in four grasses, a shrub, and a forb common to northern mixed-grass prairie plant communities. The resulting yearly data trends indicated that the plants responded to warmer temperatures with earlier leaf emergence and flowering. Some species also responded with earlier seed maturation and canopy senescence. On average, the growing season for plant communities exposed to higher temperatures began five days earlier and lasted six days longer. 
However, when plants were exposed to a combination of warmer temperatures and elevated carbon dioxide levels, the growing season began seven days earlier and lasted 14 days longer. The researchers believe that elevated carbon dioxide levels prompt greater water conservation in some of the grassland plants, which in turn delayed early plant senescence and death. 
A plant community gets a jump-start on its growing season when the first species leafs out earlier in the spring, and the growing season continues until the last species enters senescence in the fall. So while warming temperatures can increase the length of the growing season in some grasslands communities by promoting earlier spring growth, elevated carbon dioxide levels can help plants conserve water and delay fall senescence.﻿

Meer lezen (43 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-21maOkhqjlc/U1gJZ1rCi5I/AAAAAAAALt4/0wmju9CdQOo/w426-h286/grassland.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/106496383313057281612/albums/5781846491276789281/5781846494694539522</link><title>Grasses, or more technically graminoids, are monocotyledonous, usually herbaceous plants with narrow leaves growing from the base. They include the "true grasses", of the Poaceae (or Gramineae) family, as well as the sedges (Cyperaceae) and the rushes (Juncaceae). The true grasses include cereals, bamboo and the grasses of lawns (turf) and grassland. Sedges include many wild marsh and grassland plants, and some cultivated ones such as water chestnut (Eleocharis dulcis) and papyrus sedge (Cyperus papyrus). Uses for graminoids include food (as grain, sprouted grain, shoots or rhizomes), drink (beer, whisky, vodka), pasture for livestock, thatch, paper, fuel, clothing, insulation, construction, sports turf, basket weaving and many others. 
. 
www.ny007ny.com 
.﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-u9NzpcYPlX0/UD0-wN4bAQI/AAAAAAAAOdc/lQHPSNoXzTw/w426-h566/56.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/115353929242802906395/albums/5960864874256418577/5960864874935413730</link><title>Ranger Pete and the volunteers carried out grassland restoration last week at Jacksons’ Brickworks in Higher Poynton. An area of scrub and trees were removed and the stumps treated to prevent re-growth. Unimproved Grassland is a rare and declining habitat, both regionally and nationally, many scarce plants and animals are dependent on this habitat. Jacksons’ Brickworks is one of the few remaining areas of Unimproved Grassland in Cheshire, and a variety of methods are used to preserve and enhance the site’s value for wildlife. This management will expand the grassland and encourage wild flowers and associated invertebrates. A new 6m x 3m pond will also be excavated in this area and hopefully provide breeding habitat for the great crested newt. It was great to have a fire to clear the brash and keep warm!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-fnhn7SDZXic/Urk_BZCg6-I/AAAAAAAAAUU/jmw7oeWCMEk/w426-h320/42fa1433-2989-4d6e-a7aa-a2775d90f253</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/112366408951548473324/albums/5764000461569832545/5764000461797736738</link><title>Nebraska Sandhills, Nebraska. 
The Nebraska Sandhills is the largest sand dune formation in the Western Hemisphere. After the last ice age, wind blew the loose sand into vast dunes covering around one quarter of the state. Precipitation allowed grassland plants to take root in the shifting sand, eventually stabilising the dunes and today it's a region of mixed-grass prairie. 
Another unique aspect of the Sandhills is that it is resting on on of the largest aquifers in the world. The Ogallala Aquifer consist of 1 billion acre-feet of ground water and comes above the surface at the base of many dunes meaning the Sandhills is a region of dry and sandy grassland dunes with many thousand lakes and wetland scattered between them. 
© 2012 Peter Misfeldt - license CC (Creative Commons) BY-NC-ND 
#bwlandscapewednesday by +Francesco Gallarotti 
#widewednesdaypanorama by +Lucille Galleli +Ken McMahon +Andrew Marston +WideWednesdayPanorama 
#travelpanowednesday  by +Rolf Hicker 
#LandscapePhotography  by +Margaret Tompkins +Carra Riley +paul t beard +Landscape Photography﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XYR2cR33_Lk/T_3X4YqkQSI/AAAAAAAACyM/b-bfbKa-Tko/w426-h237/sandhills.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7265-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/grassland%20plants/photos/117857429833041902177/albums/6000180309902912193/6000180312759278354</link><title>The John Muir Country Park is an area of woodland, grassland and coastline near Dunbar in East Lothian, Scotland. It is named after John Muir, a famous naturalist and geologist who was born in Dunbar. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Muir The park is home to a diverse collection of life, including several species of butterfly, moth and over 400 species of plants. Pond in the dunes: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Muir_Country_Park﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7265_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MTZz7fxZYGk/U0TsNEJPGxI/AAAAAAAACmQ/7D4l1-aaCaw/w426-h640/399px-Pond_in_the_dunes%252C_John_Muir_Country_Park_-_geograph_org_uk_-_1231145.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>