<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:11:13" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/110786039618216658852/albums/5768346729377019313/5768346726460685074</link><title>23 July 1967 – the Detroit Riot | Dorian Cope presents On This Deity 
http://www.onthisdeity.com/23-july-1967-%e2%80%93%c2%a0the-detroit-riot/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_01_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-2FmrZHe9C4Y/UA1IySP5-xI/AAAAAAAADhU/4w01Z2unx5c/w426-h279/193ncmsrzr529.png.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/116092759539395527636/albums/5979343284621641921/5979343289605330994?sqi=116813065938031213617&amp;sqsi=8387a530-c5e3-4d1e-bd6f-6e3f45234615</link><title>Belle Isle Detroit race riot 1943 Ariel view.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-icFXfI591kE/UvrlCr8KmDI/AAAAAAAALO4/uYhF5I1V82I/w426-h264/Belle_Isle_Detroit_race_riot_1943.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/104938227603686091839/albums/6000987161960228209/6000987163746572946</link><title>Moment in time: April 11, 1981 -- Rioting erupts in Brixton 

It was a riot waiting to happen. Brixton was far from tourist London, a noisy neighbourhood rooted in postwar immigration from the Caribbean where police routinely stopped and searched residents simply because they were black. One Friday afternoon, an officer tried to grab a young man who'd been bloodied in a fight. The subsequent chase started a riot that turned into a conflagration. Within a day, prim and proper London looked more like Detroit - buildings were gutted, overturned police cars burned on the street, shops were looted and hundreds of bused-in officers had been injured. Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher refused to accept policing and youth unemployment as underlying causes, but subsequent investigations curbed the inflammatory tactics and denounced the London force's institutional racism. -- John Allemang 

Photo: Press Association ﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-N5E8lZj6mIc/U0fKB-TLGpI/AAAAAAAAG1A/OcyO6NxpHYw/w426-h285/mit-brixton10nw1.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/107153404522022102183/albums/5842613658061381473/5842613656994294210?authkey=CJblwdumkY-ZhQE&amp;sqi=107997920815626896441&amp;sqsi=7444363c-56ea-4936-9b42-4ba632c72bac</link><title>"If nothing else, democracy is a very messy business. And with all of these problems it is remarkable that labor-management matters soon cooled down and production exploded to the point where Detroit was declared the “Arsenal of Democracy.” The Willow Run plant was turning out 600 B-24 bombers a month by the end of the war. Pilots slept on cots waiting for takeoff as the B-24′s rolled off the assembly line. M5 tanks, jeeps, artillery pieces and myriad  war materials spilled out of other factories in Detroit. Sadly, racial tensions were not resolved and the 1943 Detroit race riot killed 25 blacks, 9 whites and wounded 433 over 36 hours. Federal troops were brought in to restore order. Following the violence, Japanese propaganda officials incorporated the event into materials encouraging black soldiers not to fight for the U.S. In spite of the Detroit’s job discrimination, housing discrimination, police brutality and frequent animosity from Detroit’s white population, blacks served loyally and with distinction in all of America’s Armed Services." 

Read more http://bit.ly/11uHWl1 #history #blackhistory #wwii #worldwarii #1940s ﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-VZgp-_IO8mA/URUiKmD9qcI/AAAAAAAADPQ/Dtony_3ONC4/w426-h387/2-8-2013%2B10-04-26%2BAM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/115260129877170686825/albums/5638825456462883505/5638825455812235618</link><title>According to the author Philip Womack the London riots "are not Ballardian" despite the fact that J.G. Ballard wrote about social breakdown in Kingdom Come and High Rise. Womack writes that Ballard's concern was the middle classes - a group Womack clearly believes are different in kind from the young rioters looting London for the past three nights. "What Ballard pointed up was just how thin that layer is. And it's a layer that is completely absent from these rioters... They have no consciences to be removed in the first place." Womack believes, "the only way to solve this is to get in there and talk, and show that every action, mindless or not, has its equal and opposite reaction. We need to show unity, and show these children that their actions are not a form of freedom." I don't find Womack credible. We don't talk to people we believe are "mindless." 

The blogger, Penny Red, is far more credible when she asserts that, "Violence is rarely mindless. The politics of a burning building, a smashed-in shop or a young man shot by police may be obscured even to those who lit the rags or fired the gun, but the politics are there. " Perhaps the riots are Eugenidesisn - in his book Middlesex, Jeffery Eugenides asks if what happened in 1967 in Detroit "was a riot or a guerrilla uprising?" He answers his questions with a series of questions: "After the riot was over, were, or were there not, caches of weapons found all over the neighborhood? And Were these weapons, or were they not, AK-47s and machine guns? And why had General Throckmorton deployed his tanks on the East Side, Miles from rioting? Was that the kind of thing you did to subdue an unorganized gang of snipers? Or was it more in keeping with military strategy? Was it like establishing a front line in a war?" 

2011 is not 1967. I suspect that we are not calling a revolution a riot, but that does not mean that those dismissing the violence on the streets of London "as ‘pure criminality,’ as the work of a ‘violent minority’, as ‘opportunism.’" aren't also making a categorical error. I agree with Penny Red: "This is madly insufficient." 

What questions should we be asking about the implosion of London? Do we have to credit the looters and muggers with political intent to ask if what is happening is a riot or an uprising? Are the social networking tools being used to coordinate actions? Will authorities in England use tactics simular to those used in the Middle East to restore order? Is the lack of any ideological intent the same mindlessness? If middle class political commentators like +Ezra Klein can advocate "anything that works," what should we expect from a spontaneous youth uprising? 

I don't imagine that we are witnessing a Anglo Spring. I am worried for my British friends and very sad that a great city is in flames. But as Nate Silver pointed out on twitter yesterday "High unemployment and lack of homeownership among minority communities are historically correlated with riots." As the gap between rich and poor continues to widen throughout the english speaking world, I do find myself wondering what it is we are witnessing.﻿

Meer lezen (48 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-q4t3TbLt5co/TkEh4FQeUWI/AAAAAAAABv4/awUnQB-vHfE/w426-h418/a-woman-can-be-seen-jumping-from-a-burning-building-in-surrey-street-pic-wenn-604844033.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/118284117222706268262/albums/5738458639001703809/5738458645092232146</link><title>Tell us a little about yourself,and your race relations tales of Detroit. 

Interview with Gregory A.Fournier author of Zug Island A Detroit Riot Novel. 

2.Why dredge up Detroit's painful race history. 

Is this a story that needs to be told?Set in 1967 against a backdrop of industrial blight and urban decay,Racism on the mean streets of Detroit comes in every shade of color. 

3.Will African-Americans find the race language of Zug Island offensive?. 

I use profanity and racial slurs to give my dialogue the ring of truth. It is a blue collar story about the workplace. I hope everyone who reads my novel is offended by that language. That was my intention. 

4.How did you get the idea for writing Zug Island and how long did it take you? When I was walking off the island and was "punching out" at the time clock for the last time, an an man named "Pop" yelled out to me and waved, "Don't forget to write a book about us college boy." I half-laughted and replied, "I will." Mine is a story I've waited over forty-five years to write. 

5.Why do you call Zug Island a novel rather than a memoir? I've changed the names of people and several of the plot race elements. Mainly to avoid litigation. 

6.Is the image on your front cover authentic or is it a stock photograph?It does look Detroit! The cover photo is the exact location which readers of Zug Island will recognize instantly. 

7.Share the coming of age story on chapter 8 race and the Vietnam war. 

Vietnam and the draft was a reality for everyone in the Sixties. It was a turning point for my generation and for our culture. Truth about race and fiction mix heavily in this chapter. I work my way back to college while my friend waits to be shipped out in the morning. Author's note: I mispelled Dina Washington's name in this chapter; I wrote Diana instead. 

8.What race research did you do before and during your writing of Zug Island? Vintage newspaper accounts, the internet, several books on the subject listed on my novel's website and my personal experiences. 

9.What are some marketing tips you can share with us.What would you do different? Get a professional looking website for your book, develop a blogging habit to build an audience, and win some writing contests, even small bragging rights are better than none. Facebook ads did not work for me. Also, instead of making appearances this summer, I will concentrate on web radio and internet opportunities and talk more openly about race in Detroit. 

10.Final comment:What's on your "Bucket List?" Top 5 things you'd still like to do? 

Finish my next project about serial killer John Norman Collins called In the Shadow of the Water Tower, help my children get into the housing market, live to see my grandchildren grow and prosper, and see American leave its legacy of racism on the trash heap of history and the end of negative race talk as we know it.﻿

Meer lezen (60 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-O4hi5SBKMV0/T6MZu-r969I/AAAAAAAAArY/wpc7fKwOOHY/s426/Greg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/115584325734610338186/albums/5891534578360404737/5891534576259720674?authkey=CKz3g7rZoISYSA</link><title>This day in history: 
1214 – The University of Oxford receives its charter. 
1782 – The U.S. Congress adopts the Great Seal of the United States. 
1837 – Queen Victoria succeeds to the British throne. 
1943 – The Detroit Race Riot breaks out and continues for three more days. 
1948 – Toast of the Town, later The Ed Sullivan Show, makes its television debut. 
1972 – Watergate scandal: An 18½-minute gap appears in the tape recording of the conversations between U.S. President Richard Nixon and his advisers regarding the recent arrests of his operatives while breaking into the Watergate complex.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-q-WRL0Gx2kA/UcLve3_kZeI/AAAAAAAAAU0/arvxz_aBoz4/w426-h284/2nCj6.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/113776382996486725967/albums/5784517429111967937/5784517436230292450</link><title>Kevin Alfred from FB 

During the oil boom of the 1910s, the area of northeast Oklahoma around Tulsa flourished, including the Greenwood neighborhood, which came to be known as "the Negro Wall Street" (now commonly referred to as "the Black Wall Street")[3] The area was home to several prominent black businessmen, many of them multimillionaires. Greenwood boasted a variety of thriving businesses that were very successful up until the Tulsa Race Riot. Not only did African Americans want to contribute to the success of their own shops, but also the racial segregation laws prevented them from shopping anywhere other than Greenwood.[4] Following the riots, the area was rebuilt and thrived until the 1960s when ((((((desegregation allowed blacks to shop in areas that were restricted before)))))). 
Detroit Avenue, along the edge of Standpipe Hill, contained a number of higher-end houses belonging to doctors, lawyers and business owners. Also, the buildings on Greenwood Avenue housed the offices of almost all of Tulsa’s black lawyers, realtors, doctors, and other professionals.[5] In Tulsa at the time of the riot, there were fifteen well-known African American physicians, one of whom, Dr. A.C. Jackson, was considered the “most able Negro surgeon in America” by one of the Mayo brothers.[6] Dr. Jackson was shot to death as he left his house during the riot.[2] Greenwood published two newspapers, the Tulsa Star and the Oklahoma Sun, which covered not only Tulsa, but also state and national news and elections. Buildings housing the two papers were destroyed during the riot.[2] 
Greenwood was a very religiously active community. At the time of the riot there were more than a dozen African American churches and many Christian youth organizations and religious societies. 
In northeastern Oklahoma, as elsewhere in America, the prosperity of minorities emerged amidst racial and political tension. The Ku Klux Klan made its first major appearance in Oklahoma shortly before the worst race riot in history.[7] It is estimated that there were about 3,200 members of the Klan in Tulsa in 1921 .﻿

Meer lezen (35 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-gomJBH7A9U4/UEa79eePU-I/AAAAAAAABuU/kct45KgTWcM/w426-h237/376611_458411307513521_989012826_n.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/102041115633546292589/albums/5975585471089822017/5975585471584970082</link><title>Use of Deadly Force, Detention and Interrogation of U.S. Civilians 

According to a variety of sources, Garden Plot has been activated a number of times since the 1960s. In fact, up until 1971 there were multiple standing brigades stationed in the U.S. for domestic civil disturbance operations. According to GlobalSecurity.org, Garden Plot was activated during the Los Angeles riots in 1992, during the Detroit riots in 1967, and following the assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. in 1968. After the creation of USNORTHCOM in 2002, Garden Plot was replaced with CONPLAN 2502 (now referred to as CONPLAN 3502). There are only a few known references to this CONPLAN in the military literature we can find. One of the most significant resources when trying to learn about the CONPLAN is the Domestic Operational Handbook for Judge Advocates, “a resource for operational lawyers involved in domestic support operations” that helps them understand “the legal issues inherent in such operations”. The Domestic Operational Handbook for 2010 includes many references to CONPLAN 3502, including notes that indicate that the plan contains information on the formation of detention facilities for imprisoning U.S. citizens during Civil Disturbance Operations (CDO). Because of the inherent limitations of the Posse Comitatus Act, only police can lawfully detain and hold civilians. However, page 77 of the 2010 Domestic Operational Law Handbook states: 

If available civilian detention facilities cannot accommodate the number of detained persons who are awaiting arraignment, the Joint Civil Disturbance Task Force commander must seek the approval of the SCRAG and Combatant Commander to set up a temporary detention facility. 

Should the Task Force be required to operate a detention facility, the detention facility standards and operations should conform, to the maximum extent possible, to current DoD confinement facility operations and will be under the professional supervision and control of Military Police personnel. The establishment and operation of military detention facilities is a temporary expedient and is authorized only until such time as the custody of detained persons can be transferred to civil authorities. 

A footnote for this passage indicates that CONPLAN 3502 is to be referenced for further instructions on the construction of these facilities and for related legal issues. The note goes on to say that USNORTHCOM “CONPLAN 3502 . . . specifies that detention facilities be under the control of U.S. Army MP Corps personnel. Due to base closure and increased joint nature of operations it is possible that U.S. Navy and U.S. Air Force confinement facilities could be used.” The handbook also describes how “Military forces have the authority to detain rioters, looters or other civilians committing criminal offenses” and that “If civilian police are not available, CID agents or military police may conduct interrogations only if the interrogation is essential to the civil disturbance mission”, indicating that military forces are capable of detaining, holding and interrogating U.S. citizens depending on the exigency of the circumstances. 

The 1991 version of Garden Plot, the precursor to CONPLAN 3502, includes instructions on the use of deadly force against U.S. citizens. Here is a basic listing of the requirements for deadly force found on page C-1-8: 

1 THE USE OF DEADLY FORCE IS AUTHORIZED ONLY WHERE ALL THREE OF THE FOLLOWING CIRCUMSTANCES ARE PRESENT: 

A LESSER MEANS HAVE BEEN EXHAUSTED OR ARE UNAVAILABLE; 

B THE RISK OF DEATH OR SERIOUS BODILY HARM TO INNOCENT PERSONS IS NOT SIGNIFICANTLY INCREASED BY USE; 

AND 

C THE PURPOSE OF ITS USE IS ONE OR MORE OF THE FOLLOWING: 

1-SELF DEFENSE TO AVOID DEATH OR SERIOUS BODILY HARM; SELF DEFENSE AGAINST A HOSTILE PERSON OR FORCE TO AVOID IMMINENT DEATH OR SERIOUS BODILY INJURY POSED BY THE HOSTILE PERSON; (’96 Change) 

2-PREVENTION OF A CRIME WHICH INVOLVES A SUBSTANTIAL RISK AN IMMIMENT DANGER (’96 Change) OF DEATH OR SERIOUS BODILY HARM (FOR EXAMPLE, SETTING FIRE TO AN INHABITED DWELLING OR SNIPING), INCLUDING THE DEFENSE OF OTHER PERSONS, WHERE DEADLY FORCE IS DIRECTED AGAINST THE PERSON THREATENING TO COMMIT THE CRIME; OR (’96 Change); 

3-PREVENTION OF THE DESTRUCTION OF PUBLIC UTILITIES OR SIMILAR PROPERTY CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE (’96 Change) VITAL TO PUBLIC HEALTH OR SAFETY, DAMAGE TO WHICH WOULD IMPERIL LIFE (’96 Change); OR 

4-DETENTION OR PREVENTION OF THE ESCAPE OF PERSONS WHO HAVE COMMITTED OR ATTEMPTED TO COMMIT ONE OF THE SERIOUS OFFENSES REFERRED TO IN SUBPARAGRAPHS 1, 2, AND 3 IMMEDIATELY ABOVE, BUT ONLY IF ESCAPE OF THE PERSONS WOULD POSE AN IMMINENT DANGER OF DEATH OR SERIOUS PHYSICAL INJURY TO MILITARY OR LAW ENFORCEMENT PERSONNEL OR TO ANY OTHER PERSON (’96 Change). 

Page C-8-9 of the same document describes criteria for conducting warrantless searches of people and property, seizure of property, as well as detention operations. Page E-4 specifically describes the role of CONPLANs: “Civil disturbance contingency plans governing the employment of federal forces will include provisions for providing detention assistance to civilian authorities. Plans for this assistance will cover the full range of possible support, from assisting police in guarding detainees to operating detention facilities. Such assistance will be predicated on the turnover of this responsibility to civil authorities as soon as practicable.” 

The 2010 Defense Support to Civil Authorities (DSCA) Handbook clarifies the current policy on the use of force, providing templates for soldiers engaged in civil support missions under Title 10 authority. The Handbook provides a relatively complex description of situations where the use of force is authorized, while also describing arming orders for vehicles and soldiers engaged in civil support missions. 

U.S. Army Field Manual 3-19.15 gives complex instructions on searching and detaining individuals, conducting riot control operations, as well as creating “temporary detention facilities”. These detention facilities are to be located on “the nearest military installation or on suitable property under federal control” and “should be close enough to the disturbance area to minimize transportation and escort needs”. The manual emphasizes that these facilities should be built on “existing structures” that are “adapted for this use, but construction may be needed to provide segregation for ensuring effective control and administration.” In Chapter 7, there are even instructions for quelling riots and other disturbances inside these confinement facilities: 

Civil disturbance doctrine is usually written for quelling disturbances that occur in large open areas where the size of the responding force or the type of formation employed is not hampered by a lack of space. However, in the military confinement environment, inmate disturbances often occur in small, closed areas, such as an inmate’s housing unit, a gymnasium, a dining facility, or a chapel where maneuver space and equipment limit the size of the element that may be employed. The layout of each facility is different and presents its own unique problems when employing forces. This chapter covers the use of small military police teams, forced cell move teams (FCMTs), and the formations used to move an unruly inmate from one cell to another﻿

Meer lezen (145 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_09_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-VcZyKXjgZ98/Uu2LU47OpWI/AAAAAAAACwU/07e7RMpPfMA/w426-h469/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7274-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/detroit%20riot/photos/106968887180620203232/albums/6001909437140179489/6001909443918849282</link><title>The Detroit Race Riot, 1943 

For three days in June, 1943, blacks and whites in Detroit fought a battle that killed 34 people, wounded 433, and destroyed more than $2 million in property. The United States has a long history of racial discrimination which periodically erupts in violence such as the Detroit Race Riot. 

The Detroit riot began at a popular and integrated amusement park known as Belle Isle. On the muggy summer evening of June 20, 1943, the playground was ablaze with activity. Several incidents occurred that night including multiple fights between white teenagers who set upon black teenagers. White teenagers were often aided by sailors who were stationed at the Naval Armory nearby. 

As people began leaving the island for home, major traffic jams and congestion at the ferry docks spurred more violence. On the bridge which led back to the mainland, a fight erupted between a total of 200 African Americans and white sailors. Soon, a crowd of 5,000 white residents gathered at the mainland entrance to the bridge ready to attack black vacationers wishing to cross. It didn't take long before they started killing... 

Turn the tables and see how we like it. Labels do not just work one way, they can be used equally by those demonised by us. 

This historical event is meant to be used as a reminder, not because of any hatred for us white people, But to throw back in the faces of white Muslim hating supremacists the pain of labelling so that they may understand how the Muslims feel, when we do it to them!﻿

Meer lezen (27 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7274_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_IlI2O2Dijs/U0sQ1vrYZQI/AAAAAAAAiB8/jRjmzwlpsco/w426-h552/10173710_10152064147601173_1161933059242153165_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>