<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7294">assumption of mary</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:36:56" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/116376477740775922737/albums/5912127720019505121/5912127722198923138?authkey=CLTmo7a345780QE</link><title>Assumption of Mary 

“One glance at a daily newspaper or a television news show will tell you that some people do not value human life. But this is not news. During the Holocaust of World War II, millions of people were tortured and killed. This terrible tragedy led many people to wonder about human life. How valuable is a single human life? How valuable are the lives of the elderly, the unborn, the terminally ill? Are their lives worth as much as those of people who are healthy and active, working, and raising families? 

“God creates human life and gives it value. And Jesus gave his life on the cross to redeem each individual human person. By doing this, Jesus said, ‘Your life is worth my dying to save you.’ Through his own Resurrection, Jesus showed us the glory of our resurrection and of our living in the Holy Spirit. Jesus promised that the body and soul of a person, separated at death, will be joined together again in glory at the Last Judgment. The person will be whole for all eternity. 

“The feast of Mary’s Assumption is a preview of what our lives will be. At the end of her earthly life, Mary was assumed, or taken up, into heaven body and soul. She did not have to wait for the end of the world, as we do. God granted her this special privilege because of her sinlessness and her fullness of grace. 

“The Church has always believed in Mary’s assumption into heaven. But on November 1, 1950, Pope Pius XII focused the attention of the whole world on the Assumption of Mary as a dogma and mystery of our faith. This mystery shows us that God wants every human person, body and soul, to be in glory forever, just as Mary is now. This dogma shows how important every single human life is. Pope Plus XII hoped that by thinking about Mary’s Assumption, people all over the world would develop a deeper respect for their own lives and their own bodies. He also hoped that people would grow in respect for the lives of others.” 

Hat tip: Loyola Press; Excerpted from Saints and Feast Days, by Sisters of Notre Dame of Chardon, Ohio 

\- See more at: http://www.loyolapress.com/assumption-of-mary.htm#sthash.HT0otIeQ.dpuf 
:. 

For Thursday: 19th week in ordinary time. Readings: Revelations 11:19; 12:1-6, 10; Psalm 45:10, 11, 12, 16; 1 Corinthians 15:20-26; Luke 1:39-56. Hours: of the solemnity. Night Prayer II of Sunday. 

For August 15: Assumption of Mary 

Remember, O most gracious Virgin Mary, that never was it known that anyone who fled to your protection, implored your help, or sought your intercession was left unaided. Inspired by this confidence, we fly unto you, O Virgin of virgins, our Mother! To you we come, before you we stand, sinful and sorrowful. O Mother of the Word incarnate, despise not our petitions, but in your mercy hear and answer us. Amen. 
 :. 

Angel of God, my guardian dear, 
to whom God’s love entrusts me here, 
ever this night be at my side, 
to light and guard, to rule and guide. Amen. 

I pray for the people I love; 
I love the people I pray for. 
I promise to pray for you. (=^_^=)﻿

Meer lezen (62 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-eJv1qLri5os/UgwY1uxn94I/AAAAAAAAJW8/4f5lzg9E06I/w426-h578/Assumption-Palma_il_Vecchio_-_Assumption_of_Mary_-_WGA16930.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/107700027720351417295/albums/5776774072460767665/5776774072256938722</link><title>Good Morning Google+ 
today we celebrate not only the Assumption of Mary, but also the anniversary of Woodstock, which started on August 15th 1969. 
Julie Lomoe's painting, Jimi Hendrix was exhibited there and captures the spirit of the time quite well. 
Have an inspired day, and tread lightly 
#art   #breakfastclub  +Breakfast Club  #treadlightly  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_02_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-rtZi8vOUfQI/UCs5aXyPwuI/AAAAAAAAJwA/GqIou0Htc_w/s426/2012-08-15++Julie+Lomoe+-+Jimi+Hendrix.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/115616874270150115780/albums/5992654986080625985/5992654983674134338?sqi=116591399122314614004&amp;sqsi=789343fd-11fe-472e-a8cb-b8554d4ae2e2</link><title>Fourth Glorious Mystery - ASSUMPTION OF MARY 

The Most Holy Virgin, twelve years after the Resurrection of Our Lord Jesus Christ, passed from this life, and was assumed by the angels into heaven. 

\- Hail Mary 

#rosary  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-G4U8cIhdYhw/Uyov9Qte_0I/AAAAAAAAIZE/kDT06l3lz4s/w426-h630/assumption-203x300.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/115263836993710889888/albums/5917178653328262769/5917178767552585714</link><title>Fresco Assumption of Mary﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-qL3WtE6VaRU/Uh4KvRB0n_I/AAAAAAAACo4/4i5XQVQvf7s/w426-h296/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/111586938013783489135/albums/5907142965153157937/5907142964982917730?authkey=CMyn4NrR74amSQ</link><title>We are holding an Assumption of Mary Miraculous Medal Sale from now until the Assumption on August 15th! Save 20% by using the code from the image below at checkout! #Catholic #sale﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-a5E_eYRRU5w/UfpjOrFBKmI/AAAAAAAAAhg/MuAao0dbxjk/w426-h285/facebook+miraculous+medal+sale.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/113329686749433162673/albums/5935002234889105713/5935002237993126130?sqi=115498623068861010577&amp;sqsi=d36e8fd5-e127-4992-8218-b491cb77bbf1</link><title>Assumption of Mary Pilgrimage Church at sunrise, Lake Bled, Slovenia ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-UwKwK9r4TEw/Ul1dFyi6iPI/AAAAAAAAJFA/0E3M3LwWZR8/w426-h639/07ba87037f38a63df59a6e77f485e3cb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/108584290911157456909/albums/5912321138665657329/5912321138070677666?authkey=CKGt6cmhqLrwLw</link><title>The Assumption of the Virgin Mary into Heaven.The feast day of the Assumption of Mary, also known as #Assumption #Day, celebrates the day that God assumed the Virgin Mary into Heaven following her death, according to popular Christian belief. It is the principal feast day of the Virgin Mother.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-GfFzuN0R9YQ/UgzIwBC8aKI/AAAAAAAACNY/eMPmx_IS4kc/w426-h274/2P2wm.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/115345616279564046845/albums/5892007002920438609/5917584636919625314</link><title>Assumption Parfaits (Genevieve was born on Aug 15th, the Assumption of Mary)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-v3oVyNOXSLI/Uh973-PnNmI/AAAAAAAAHlA/TB5tavUM0Es/w426-h320/036.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/112485864191995902890/albums/5780375826187891185/5780375830233378050</link><title>Church of the Assumption of Mary - Lake Bled - Slovenia﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-qu9ytJU0d-8/UDgFMR1QbQI/AAAAAAAACEs/k9rsWx0MaIk/w426-h283/Churches,+Church+of+the+Assumption+of+Mary.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7294-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/assumption%20of%20mary/photos/110375258839459596730/albums/5918555603970975681/5918555601526085730?authkey=CIn1mqqaornVkwE</link><title>Tomales, Marin County, California 

     Church of the Assumption of Mary, a Roman Catholic church, is located at 26825 Shoreline Highway (Hwy 1) in Tomales, California. It is just south of Dillon Beach Road. The Catholic Cemetery is not located at the Church, but rather about 1 mile west of town near the corner of Dillon Beach Road and Middle Road. 
     "In 1860 the Church of the Assumption was built in Tomales on land donated by John and Kate Miller Keys. Archbishop Joseph Alemany, first Archbishop of San Francisco, dedicated the church that same year with first pastor, Father Louis Rossi. 
      "Contractors were Peter Morrissey and Andrew Fisher but records do not disclose the name of the architect. Style of architecture for the redwood frame building is Carpenter’s Gothic. 
      "In 1897, a stone church designed by architect Frank Shea was built during the pastorate of Father John Rogers but it was destroyed by the 1906 earthquake (image). Parishioners then returned to the redwood frame building they continue to pray in today. The white marble baptismal font, a marble statue of Mary holding the Christ Child and a stained glass window of the Presentation of Jesus in the Temple were retrieved from the newer church. Other windows installed during the 1920s show the influence of Tiffany Glass." 
Source: Catholic San Francisco, The Weekly Newspaper of the Archdiocese of San Francisco, March 26, 1999.﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7294_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-iKBLjXt_LrE/UiLu9jRcWGI/AAAAAAAACdM/3hODX4CYnjA/w426-h320/158.JPG</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>