<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7299">row row row your boat lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 18:10:05" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/117498129729552439039/albums/5903860471410215041/5903860474559694642?authkey=COeOyKKayfH2EA&amp;sqi=100453920415382664577&amp;sqsi=db5a577b-7c6f-417e-b86a-9cf811106c37</link><title>Khor Bayu Boy Bege is one of the most dynamic songs ever written by Rabindranath Tagore, and like most other works by Tagore, it also has a multitude of explanations. The lyrics of the song, translated by Anjan Gangopadhaya from Bengali, are: 

The wind is high, clouds dark, 
O the boatman, Row your boat. 
You give it the direction, while I prepare the sail high- 
Row, Row your boat. 
Resonance of the chains, time and again, Isn’t the yell for despair 
Unbearable are the bounds, its oscillations are hence. 
Row, Row your boat. 
Do not ask, whether or not to venture, 
The day, time just or not, anxiously. 
If your luck runs against, roughness beyond control, 
Smashing storm, sea waves even higher, 
Be confident, adjust to the rhythm, 
Chanting His name merrily. 
Row, Row your boat. 

A most significant aspect of the song is, as many say, it was an invocation to the people of India as a whole to rise together against oppression of the British imperialism. ﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-eOnWo63tDI4/Ue650lWZhzI/AAAAAAAAEmc/3dLQ8YDsW9w/w426-h283/images%2B%252823%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/101983474019961328651/albums/5737365996595055649/5737365996383413554</link><title>APRIL 1977 (35 YEARS AGO) 
Van Morrison: A Period of Transition is released. 
# ALL THINGS MUSIC PLUS+ 4/5 
# allmusic 3/5 
# Rolling Stone (see original review below) 

A Period of Transition is the ninth album by Van Morrison, released in April, 1977. It was his first album in two and a half years, largely forgotten or looked over by most casual fans. 

Morrison had appeared in The Last Waltz with Mac Rebennack (Dr. John) who was a co-producer on this album as well as playing keyboards and guitar. 

Not that there was much competition, but with this album, Morrison made a convincing case for his being the Irish Al Green. The classic Memphis soul sound he adopts here is a logical extension of the R&amp;B roots he had expanded on since the beginning of his career. Helped out here by Dr. John, he presents a group of songs that are among his most visceral and immediate. Miles from the dreamy minstrelsy of Veedon Fleece, this recording is based around solid, propulsive R&amp;B grooves that lay an undeniable claim to dancing feet while the lyrics still address the kind of spiritual concerns that have become a Morrison trademark. Van at his funkiest. 

ORIGINAL ROLLING STONE REVIEW 
It's been a long haul for both the Band and Van Morrison; they have made their livings as rock &amp; rollers for close to 20 years now. To judge solely by their new albums (Morrison's is his first release since 1974) time is catching up with them, though whether they will again outdistance it remains an open question. Morrison made better music in '64 and '65 with Them, the first (and last?) great Irish rock &amp; roll band; as the Hawks, the Band made better music in '63, covering Bobby Bland and Muddy Waters tunes at the tail end of a Ronnie Hawkins session. Not that rock &amp; roll has ever had anything to do with "progress." 

There is a lot of neo-R&amp;B huffing and puffing on A Period of Transition (from what to what?), but Morrison's performances rarely find a focus, almost never hit a groove. The grand gestures of Morrison's style at its most rhetorical ("We are Them, take it or leave it," he snarled during his 1964 sessions) fade in the air. The emotion that would justify those gestures, that would put a little terror into borrowed lines like "From a whisper to a scream," is just out of reach: Transition is "Jackie Wilson Said" without the bite. 

The key to the album's sluggishness is the dullness of the horn charts. Van is the most inventive and lyrical arranger of horns rock &amp; roll has known since the heyday of Stax-Volt, but "Flamingos Fly" is the only tune to which the horns add anything but sound; there, they add wit and a sense of fun. This is "Jackie Wilson Said" and something more; the album's finest number by a long distance. The groove is irresistible, and it capsizes the rest of the album. 

Van Morrison once sang "Listen to the Lion" and made you feel as if you'd been cornered by one; he will do it again, but he doesn't do it on Transition. This is by no means a bad album, but it lives up to its title all too well. 

"I'm not really here, I just stick around for my friends," Captain Beefheart used to say, and that sums up what I hear on Islands — which is not nothing. To be sure, there's not a grand gesture on it. I can't imagine this album meaning anything to someone who does not feel that his or her successes and failures are somehow reflected in the Band's. If one does feel that, Islands is anything but hollow — it may sound like an unassuming last word, if hardly a last stand. 

Since the members of the Band have not moved to Hawaii, it's the album's title, and the specter of the Band's recent farewell concert, that implies that last word. Rick Danko and Levon Helm have signed solo recording contracts, and Helm is already working with Dr. John and Paul Butterfield; the thinness of the material on Islands suggests they may be keeping their best songs for their own albums, and the inclusion of a couple of oldies doesn't make up the difference. "Ain't That a Lotta Love," a barband staple that a couple of years ago on a San Francisco stage Levon, Garth Hudson, Danko, Neil Young, Tim Drummond and Ben Keith stomped out as if they meant to stop the sun in its tracks, is on Islands the stiffest excuse for R&amp;B I ever want to hear; too many of Robbie Robertson's tunes offer cracker-barrel banalities without the music that could redeem them — or disguise them. "You don't know what you want 'til you find out what you need" might be true and it might not be, but the point is it isn't interesting. 

Save for a couple of Richard Manuel's vocals, I was ready to give up on this record. Then I began to hear it on the radio, and it sounded fresh. Now, while the first side of the LP passes pleasantly and tiresomely enough, side two seems like real people talking: that last word. "Islands," the title instrumental, is slight and pretty — it disarms one's desire for grand gestures, and it sets a tone. The tone is one of moderation; that is almost what the best songs here are about, in their music, in the feeling they get across. Manuel's version of "Georgia on My Mind" recalls the heart he put into "Whispering Pines," almost eight years ago. "Knockin' Lost John," a fine, unprofound ditty about the Great Depression of the Thirties, simply speaks to the present, and again, Manuel, without ever reaching for a note, gives the piece its authenticity; his voice carries the authority of an old man who can put up with anything but who'd just as soon not. "I went through it once," he seems to be saying. "I'm damned if I'll go through it again." 

And then there is "Livin' in a Dream," which closes out the set: a rewrite of "Row Row Row Your Boat." Well, it is the best song on Islands — a perfect cut. I hear it as a leave-taking, but then I have finales on my mind. The beat could not be less hurried, nor could the lines Levon sings, nor the way he sings them: 

I'm gonna buy buy buy you 
A sheepskin coat 
I'm gonna string red rubies round your throat 
Gently down the stream I will row your boat 
'Cause you know we're only livin' in a dream. 

There's no languor in the song, only pleasure; there are no promises that can't be kept, and the promises Levon makes seem to have been kept when the tune ends. That spirit doesn't sell records, but it may keep them in mind, when the time is right. 

Still, in rock &amp; roll a little modesty goes a long way. These are not the worst albums Van Morrison and the Band have made, but except for Morrison's "Flamingos Fly" and the Band's "Livin' in a Dream" they make the best almost inexplicable. One cannot think of the power of "Chest Fever" and easily understand the triviality of "Ain't That a Lotta Love"; one can't quite pin down the fatal difference between the urgency of "St. Dominic's Preview" or "You Don't Pull No Punches but You Don't Push the River" and the unconvincing strain of most of Transition. What you do, if you are committed to these artists, is wait. 
~ Greil Marcus (May 19, 1977) 

TRACKS: 
All songs written by Van Morrison unless noted. 
Side one 
"You Gotta Make It Through the World" – 5:10 
"It Fills You Up" – 4:34 
"The Eternal Kansas City" – 5:26 

Side two 
"Joyous Sound" – 2:48 
"Flamingos Fly" – 4:41 
"Heavy Connection" – 5:23 
"Cold Wind in August" – 5:48﻿

Meer lezen (137 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-X9v0fp4XVOQ/T583-dDWpTI/AAAAAAAAK9Y/-WrqgCSudIA/s426/vanmorrison.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/115472308326022353224/albums/5881836232957579809/5919276543543805410?authkey=CPGg7obL8rapWA</link><title>we haven't sung for a while, have we? heh! ;) 
ok now everyone sing along! 
Row Row Row Your Boat 

nursery super sound rhymes ;) ... sorry, couldn't find a punk rock version, only some crappy metal and dubstep releases^^ ;) 

at #bajuwarmeetsfischkopp2013  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-QMqcf-dV4pg/UiV-p5k7BeI/AAAAAAAAnnk/1lwTn2MG5q4/w426-h284/BmF_2013_row_row_row.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/112801448828869860546/albums/5830730587647424241/5830730591616564338?authkey=CJ_HgbH6md3ZHw</link><title>Learning English on Google Plus  especially for +Robert Redl ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-eWeNehLbLOY/UOrqlJ5O_HI/AAAAAAAAHqg/keXKN-VjDCY/w426-h310/Learn%2BEnglish.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/116002676446487541587/albums/5964727423360655617/5964727425210622930</link><title>"Let me say for the record, I am not a gangster and never have been. I'm not the thief who grabs your purse. I'm not the guy who jacks your car. I'm not down with the people who steal and hurt others. I'm just a brother who fights back." Tupac Amaru Shakur 
#2pac﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4CU0wD_17kg/Usb3_aG1o9I/AAAAAAAAGnM/W1WAFlw-_Po/w426-h610/2pac.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/106875406055259294656/albums/6009753062662582497/6009753059588069154</link><title>Cool, the first sighting, and story of the Loch Ness monster. Now I know why he/she doesn't eat, or hurt people :). St. Columba (also known as "Columcille") was born of the O'Donnell Clan in Garten, County Donegal, Ireland, on December 7, 521; he died on 9 June, 597. In between, he founded monasteries in and evangelized Ireland and Scotland. The story of his meeting Nessie -- said to have taken place in A.D. 565 -- was first recorded by Adamnan in "The Life of Saint Columba" sometime in the late 7th Century. An excerpt: 

CHAPTER XXVIII 

How an Aquatic Monster was driven off by Virtue of the Blessed Man's Prayer. 

On another occasion also, when the blessed man was living for some days in the province of the Picts, he was obliged to cross the river Nesa; and when he reached the bank of the river, he saw some of the inhabitants burying an unfortunate man, who, according to the account of those who were burying him, was a short time before seized, as he was swimming, and bitten most severely by a monster that lived in the water; his wretched body was, though too late, taken out with a hook, by those who came to his assistance in a boat. 

The blessed man, on hearing this, was so far from being dismayed, that he directed one of his companions to swim over and row across the coble that was moored at the farther bank. 

And Lugne Mocumin hearing the command of the excellent man, obeyed without the least delay, taking off all his clothes, except his tunic, and leaping into the water. 

But the monster, which, so far from being satiated, was only roused for more prey, was lying at the bottom of the stream, and when it felt the water disturbed above by the man swimming, suddenly rushed out, and, giving an awful roar, darted after him, with its mouth wide open, as the man swam in the middle of the stream. 

Then the blessed man observing this, raised his holy hand, while all the rest, brethren as well as strangers, were stupefied with terror, and, invoking the name of God, formed the saving sign of the cross in the air, and commanded the ferocious monster, saying, "Thou shalt go no further, nor touch the man; go back with all speed." Then at the voice of the saint, the monster was terrified, and fled more quickly than if it had been pulled back with ropes, though it had just got so near to Lugne, as he swam, that there was not more than the length of a spear-staff between the man and the beast. 

Then the brethren seeing that the monster had gone back, and that their comrade Lugne returned to them in the boat safe and sound, were struck with admiration, and gave glory to God in the blessed man. And even the barbarous heathens, who were present, were forced by the greatness of this miracle, which they themselves had seen, to magnify the God of the Christians. 

The following comes from "Loch Ness in the Highlands of Scotland": 

Once upon a time, when Saint Columba was traveling through the country of the Picts, he had to cross the River Ness. When he reached the shore there was a group of people, Picts and Brethren both, burying an unfortunate guy who had been bit by a water-monster. Columba ordered one of his people to swim across the river and get the boat on the other side so that he might cross. On hearing this, Lugneus Mocumin stripped down to his tunic and plunged in to the water. 

But the monster saw him swimming and charged to the surface to devour poor Lugneus and everyone who was watching was horrified and hid their eyes in terror. Everyone except Columba who raised his holy hand and inscribed the Cross in the empty air. Calling upon the name of God, he commanded the savage beast, saying: "Go no further! Do not touch the man! Go back at once!" 

The monster drew back as though pulled by ropes and retreated quickly to the depths of the Loch. Lugneus brought the boat back, unharmed and everyone was astonished. And the heathen savages who were present were overcome by the greatness of the miracle which they themselves had seen, and magnified the God of the Christians.﻿

Meer lezen (75 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-JrBfbJcPjRM/U2bukRCQVyI/AAAAAAAACKY/lnqmMF3o6EE/w426-h240/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/107450567841519364885/albums/5737366665627514673/5737366663453345506</link><title>APRIL 1977 (35 YEARS AGO) 
Van Morrison: A Period of Transition is released. 
# ALL THINGS MUSIC PLUS+ 4/5 
# allmusic 3/5 
# Rolling Stone (see original review below) 

A Period of Transition is the ninth album by Van Morrison, released in April, 1977. It was his first album in two and a half years, largely forgotten or looked over by most casual fans. 

Morrison had appeared in The Last Waltz with Mac Rebennack (Dr. John) who was a co-producer on this album as well as playing keyboards and guitar. 

Not that there was much competition, but with this album, Morrison made a convincing case for his being the Irish Al Green. The classic Memphis soul sound he adopts here is a logical extension of the R&amp;B roots he had expanded on since the beginning of his career. Helped out here by Dr. John, he presents a group of songs that are among his most visceral and immediate. Miles from the dreamy minstrelsy of Veedon Fleece, this recording is based around solid, propulsive R&amp;B grooves that lay an undeniable claim to dancing feet while the lyrics still address the kind of spiritual concerns that have become a Morrison trademark. Van at his funkiest. 

ORIGINAL ROLLING STONE REVIEW 
It's been a long haul for both the Band and Van Morrison; they have made their livings as rock &amp; rollers for close to 20 years now. To judge solely by their new albums (Morrison's is his first release since 1974) time is catching up with them, though whether they will again outdistance it remains an open question. Morrison made better music in '64 and '65 with Them, the first (and last?) great Irish rock &amp; roll band; as the Hawks, the Band made better music in '63, covering Bobby Bland and Muddy Waters tunes at the tail end of a Ronnie Hawkins session. Not that rock &amp; roll has ever had anything to do with "progress." 

There is a lot of neo-R&amp;B huffing and puffing on A Period of Transition (from what to what?), but Morrison's performances rarely find a focus, almost never hit a groove. The grand gestures of Morrison's style at its most rhetorical ("We are Them, take it or leave it," he snarled during his 1964 sessions) fade in the air. The emotion that would justify those gestures, that would put a little terror into borrowed lines like "From a whisper to a scream," is just out of reach: Transition is "Jackie Wilson Said" without the bite. 

The key to the album's sluggishness is the dullness of the horn charts. Van is the most inventive and lyrical arranger of horns rock &amp; roll has known since the heyday of Stax-Volt, but "Flamingos Fly" is the only tune to which the horns add anything but sound; there, they add wit and a sense of fun. This is "Jackie Wilson Said" and something more; the album's finest number by a long distance. The groove is irresistible, and it capsizes the rest of the album. 

Van Morrison once sang "Listen to the Lion" and made you feel as if you'd been cornered by one; he will do it again, but he doesn't do it on Transition. This is by no means a bad album, but it lives up to its title all too well. 

"I'm not really here, I just stick around for my friends," Captain Beefheart used to say, and that sums up what I hear on Islands — which is not nothing. To be sure, there's not a grand gesture on it. I can't imagine this album meaning anything to someone who does not feel that his or her successes and failures are somehow reflected in the Band's. If one does feel that, Islands is anything but hollow — it may sound like an unassuming last word, if hardly a last stand. 

Since the members of the Band have not moved to Hawaii, it's the album's title, and the specter of the Band's recent farewell concert, that implies that last word. Rick Danko and Levon Helm have signed solo recording contracts, and Helm is already working with Dr. John and Paul Butterfield; the thinness of the material on Islands suggests they may be keeping their best songs for their own albums, and the inclusion of a couple of oldies doesn't make up the difference. "Ain't That a Lotta Love," a barband staple that a couple of years ago on a San Francisco stage Levon, Garth Hudson, Danko, Neil Young, Tim Drummond and Ben Keith stomped out as if they meant to stop the sun in its tracks, is on Islands the stiffest excuse for R&amp;B I ever want to hear; too many of Robbie Robertson's tunes offer cracker-barrel banalities without the music that could redeem them — or disguise them. "You don't know what you want 'til you find out what you need" might be true and it might not be, but the point is it isn't interesting. 

Save for a couple of Richard Manuel's vocals, I was ready to give up on this record. Then I began to hear it on the radio, and it sounded fresh. Now, while the first side of the LP passes pleasantly and tiresomely enough, side two seems like real people talking: that last word. "Islands," the title instrumental, is slight and pretty — it disarms one's desire for grand gestures, and it sets a tone. The tone is one of moderation; that is almost what the best songs here are about, in their music, in the feeling they get across. Manuel's version of "Georgia on My Mind" recalls the heart he put into "Whispering Pines," almost eight years ago. "Knockin' Lost John," a fine, unprofound ditty about the Great Depression of the Thirties, simply speaks to the present, and again, Manuel, without ever reaching for a note, gives the piece its authenticity; his voice carries the authority of an old man who can put up with anything but who'd just as soon not. "I went through it once," he seems to be saying. "I'm damned if I'll go through it again." 

And then there is "Livin' in a Dream," which closes out the set: a rewrite of "Row Row Row Your Boat." Well, it is the best song on Islands — a perfect cut. I hear it as a leave-taking, but then I have finales on my mind. The beat could not be less hurried, nor could the lines Levon sings, nor the way he sings them: 

I'm gonna buy buy buy you 
A sheepskin coat 
I'm gonna string red rubies round your throat 
Gently down the stream I will row your boat 
'Cause you know we're only livin' in a dream. 

There's no languor in the song, only pleasure; there are no promises that can't be kept, and the promises Levon makes seem to have been kept when the tune ends. That spirit doesn't sell records, but it may keep them in mind, when the time is right. 

Still, in rock &amp; roll a little modesty goes a long way. These are not the worst albums Van Morrison and the Band have made, but except for Morrison's "Flamingos Fly" and the Band's "Livin' in a Dream" they make the best almost inexplicable. One cannot think of the power of "Chest Fever" and easily understand the triviality of "Ain't That a Lotta Love"; one can't quite pin down the fatal difference between the urgency of "St. Dominic's Preview" or "You Don't Pull No Punches but You Don't Push the River" and the unconvincing strain of most of Transition. What you do, if you are committed to these artists, is wait. 
~ Greil Marcus (May 19, 1977) 

TRACKS: 
All songs written by Van Morrison unless noted. 
Side one 
"You Gotta Make It Through the World" – 5:10 
"It Fills You Up" – 4:34 
"The Eternal Kansas City" – 5:26 

Side two 
"Joyous Sound" – 2:48 
"Flamingos Fly" – 4:41 
"Heavy Connection" – 5:23 
"Cold Wind in August" – 5:48﻿

Meer lezen (137 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-yx53MEvdb8U/T584lSFOBuI/AAAAAAAAEgQ/Sa9A1cGpQC0/s426/vanmorrison.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/117498129729552439039/albums/5952834752515966513/5952834754873273842</link><title>Khoro Bayu Boy Bege is my most favourite song ever. It's the greatest one possibly ever written by any author, if you ask me. 

Original lyrics, in my mother tongue Bengali: 

খরবায়ু বয় বেগে, চারি দিক ছায় মেঘে, ওগো নেয়ে, নাওখানি বাইয়ো। 
তুমি কষে ধরো হাল, আমি তুলে বাঁধি পাল-- হাঁই মারো, মারো টান হাঁইয়ো॥ 
শৃঙ্খলে বারবার ঝন্ঝন্ ঝঙ্কার, নয় এ তো তরণীর ক্রন্দন শঙ্কার- 
&lt;del&gt;বন্ধন দুর্বার সহ্য না হয় আর, টলমল করে আজ তাই ও।&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;হাঁই মারো, মারো টান হাঁইয়ো॥ &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;গণি গণি দিন খন চঞ্চল করি মন বোলো না, 'যাই কি নাহি যাই রে'।&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;সংশয়পারাবার অন্তরে হবে পার, উদ্বেগে তাকায়ো না বাইরে।&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;যদি মাতে মহাকাল, উদ্দাম জটাজাল ঝড়ে হয় লুণ্ঠিত, ঢেউ উঠে উত্তাল, হোয়ো নাকো কুণ্ঠিত, তালে তার দিয়ো তাল-&lt;/del&gt; জয়-জয় জয়গান গাইয়ো। 
হাঁই মারো, মারো টান হাঁইয়ো॥ 

English translation by Mr. Aninda Ganguly 

The wind is high, clouds dark, O the boatman, Row your boat. 
You give it the direction, while I prepare the sail high- 
Row, Row your boat. 
Resonance of the chains, time and again, 
Isn’t the yell for despair 
Unbearable are the bounds, its oscillations are hence. 
Row, Row your boat. 
Do not ask, whether or not to venture, 
The day, time just or not, anxiously. 
If your luck runs against, roughness beyond control, 
Smashing storm, sea waves even higher, 
Be confident, adjust to the rhythm, Chanting His name merrily. 
Row, Row your boat. 

I will be making a music video on it soon 

#Rabindranath #Tagore #Song #Bengali #Culture  ﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-o4jOuIBOYsc/Upy3q4rSLfI/AAAAAAAAItQ/GRGozmNOQAc/w426-h520/images.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/108705174211639807508/albums/5801514825870515105/5801514826412610594</link><title>Raindrops keep falling on my head... 

...but that doesn't mean my camera batteries are all dead. 

Feel free to continue the lyrics!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uTXRydyLyvA/UIMe_zN8VCI/AAAAAAAAbGM/6niE4yDcPRs/w426-h237/12%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7299-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/row%20row%20row%20your%20boat%20lyrics/photos/113941082974646341584/albums/5869369745646011393/5869369743628777714</link><title>While cleaning the garage found one of my childhood toys. Fisher Price tv that I got at the end of 70's from an aunt as a souvenir from USA. And it still worked! Talk about quality...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7299_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-dVfjqZswx5w/UXQwr0BrOPI/AAAAAAAALO4/w-zGVWY1Yvk/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>