<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:38:18" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/100383106820819832535/albums/6005039701969045745/6005039699385342306</link><title>The land of terrorists controlling the FBI, crooks and thieves walk into anyones homes and rape anyone after they get injected with Sodium Pentothalal after the person goes to sleep in their own home's bedroom or normal sleeping area, the woman never knowing anything ever happened, or maybe she suspects something did, and blames on her husband,or she might blame a relativr or close friend of the family, herself likely never suspecting that earlier in the week when she was in the area of 7th St and Mission St in San Francisco, she happened to make eye contact with an fbi police officer, and the officer ( or previously the fbi police officer) has the right to search her without her consent, while she is asleep in her own home or place of residence, assisted by the use of a United States government national network is hidden cameras already built in an active in every home and business in the United States, and the FBI's expert ability at opening any type of lock or safe, with an injection of sodium pentothal (not felt by the sleeping) the males, often 2 if fbi duty agents(?), then have a person unconscious, unsuspecting and unknowing, who might be beautiful and nude, with the backyard area ground wire(s?) used to switch off the hidden cameras at that particular location. Without being noticed entering the location, or not being noticed entering suspiciously, and if they ever were noticed and became reported to the police, the dispatcher might already know that secretly, they're not accepting any calls about any house in that area ? The men inside, with someone unconscious and unable to wake up, supposedly perform a body cavity search, supposedly one area of the uterus is shadowed by the pelvic bone and is not always clear on x rays when using magnetic resonance imagery? 
What might the men be looking for that could be so desperately urgent ? What are some examples (besides drugs) of something the males might find inside of the vaginal cavity of a woman ? What were they supposed to do if they found something ? Since the attacks of 9/11/2001 and the introduction of NT terror legislation called the USA PATRIOT ACT, The Act is believed to allow the FBI/FBIPD to make triple overtime when there is a suspected terrorist in the area. One possible problem is that with triple overtime, how is a person supposed to ever prove her/his innocence ? If the person was to go back to not being a suspected terrorist, the salaries would return to normal ? Because the USA Patriot Act provides Law Enforcement with "Special Tools(and) Abilities" to counter any type of "Terrorist Type Activity" that might be encountered, it is also very easy to turn into a one sided unlimited offensive weapon with only one dishonest person ( terrorist employed as Police Officer and or FBI duty agent?) to almost take over the country ( behind the scenes control of the Office of the President ? ) and secretly terrorize the People of the United States of America by using taxpayer money to bank roll ( counter ) acts of terrorism, that may not have originally happened ? One sided Lies (osl) turns the Patriot Act into an uncontestable and unknown of unlimited offensive weapon, with only one person being dishonest. I know because I've been a victim of terrorism for 10 years in San Francisco, California. The fbi here participate in and/or allows what would normally be considered acts of terrorism, they also discredit people without the victims knowing it, and fabricate a false psychiatric history, change your dental records, replace, alter or remove your medical history, install a tiny microphone that has the ability to transmit information from inside of your neck to the persons left of their Addams Apple, approximately, and can record your normal speaking in everyday conversations and eventually collect enough of your common vocabulary to have experts separate each word ( it's probably edited almost as it is recorded) ( if it's someone's voice they want to use ) the clear recorded individual words are then loaded into another computer program so they can be triggered externally as another person speaks what the recorded voice taking the place of the actual person speaking, for example calling your wife or your husband and speaking to them as if they were you, or calling a friend and insulting them ? Hints of infidelity in the speech could cause a wife to cheat ? The use of electronics, computer hacking, remote monitoring and hidden camera masturbation, locksmithing, alarm defeating, nightly unknown of trespassing, burglaries occurring nightly- sometimes twice- once in the night during sleep and once during the day while the victim is away. Myself as a victim nicknamed one type of activity a "Charged Particle Atmosphere" 
The use of strands of ions as flowing energy ( research operational theory of: ionic breeze by the sharper image company catalog showrooms), caused with flows of ions ( created by electrons traveling towards protons ( the attraction from a positively coated surface) causes a "breeze of energy" without using any moving parts, and might also be noticed as a mist, with the mist actually bring some type of chemical ( it couldn't be radon or argon could it ? those are radioactive gasses and are both expected to be semiconductors), that cause some type of drugging effect ? 
Also common use of a (rat?) poison that causes a hard boiled egg taste in the burp thar is horribly foul before during and after vomiting, and remains very painful, sometimes the sickness might last for a day, sometimes maybe more, the foul hard boiled egg burping taste taking a few days to get rid of, I know because I was sick last week and had to go to the emergency room at the hospital recently and I'm sick with it again today from eating two butterfingers ( that somebody replaced without my knowledge) that had a slightly soaked in sea water taste? a little bit like an aquarium smells ? 
Previously I've had to go to the hospital 6 times in a row in an ambulance. This has caused me to run up a hospital bill of maybe fifteen thousand dollars, myself unemployed and next in line to inherit the family home from my mother who recently you came the only owner when my father became the victim of a natural causes death that:s actually a homicide in disguise. the nightly exposure to energy that starts each night after a victim is asleep, and turns off before the victim is awake. it's believed to be called cycling energy. CE ? And is believed to eventually cause internal organ failure, that is actually a homicide disguised as a natural causes death. It also seems hinted of within the name "Cold War" ? cold changed to 
3old = PI•E ? Compare each as an inverted copy of the other, upside down backwards? 
compare again: 
C is the third letter of the English alphabet, so alphanumerically the C is replaced with the number 3. This changes the word '"cold" to "3old" ? The abbreviated formula (to find the amount of electrical power in a circuit) is shown without quotation marks as 
"P = I x E" or abbreviated even shorter as 
"PI•E". 3old = PI•E ? 
What this means : 
When a victim is exposed to harmful amounts of energy while asleep, one of the types of exposure might be from something called wattage, also called watts, named after the person who discovered it. it is a measurement of something called Power. Power measured as watts, is what cooks food in a microwave oven, it's also the energy that comes from a radio stations antenna. the formula for determining the amount of power is simple. To determine the amount of Power, multiply Amperes x Volts. 
The simple way to remember the formula is the word "PIE". 
The letter X can be replaced with a large dot shown here • that is the symbol for multiplication. 
The symbol for electrical Power is abbreviated with upper case letter P. 
Of the many ways it can be written ( abbreviated ) here's two of them. 
Translated: 
"Power is equal to Amperes multiplied with Volts" 
abbreviated: 
"P = I × E" 
The same thing abbreviated with a multiplication dot: 
"PI•E" 
Power ( equals ) Amperes Dot Volts. 
In scientific notation the symbol for amperes is the uppercase letter I the symbol for Volts is the uppercase letter E. 
The word "cold" of "Cold War" might have more hidden within it than a way of making thousands of strategic kills since 1949 and us here in the United States just thinking people died from internal organ failures, labeled as natural causes deaths ? 
Without a homicide that was caused by energy ever being known of, no alarm was ever sounded, no warnings were issued, no safety measures were taken. An enemy might have picked out every single person they wanted to kill and then replace with their own people or a look alike or resemblance of the person using the person's actual identification itself. Thus identity theft was born. This is something I call theory of the Dead Agent (CIA= 3old ) CIA = CnIIA = cold = hId ? h+I+d=R+4=22=V ? hIdV ? 
Written by Michael A.Fain﻿

Meer lezen (143 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-tB7WDksPjyM/U1Yvyl_7WWI/AAAAAAAAG8E/pB7qyslDI0I/w426-h237/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/109050870493159376152/albums/5974443207872154193/5974443207644494546</link><title>Talk about a cold war: This is the scene at Eglin Air Force Base in the Panhandle after that winter storm swept through. 

MORE PICS: http://www.myfoxtampabay.com/story/24571932/2014/01/29/winter-storm-causes-problems-in-the-panhandle﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-jyW4AMx6Iqo/Uul8cYJlOtI/AAAAAAAABQo/FKpkEATtuP4/w426-h283/3226677_G.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/103229710127416513028/albums/5822959829312804593/5822959835756465218</link><title>~ OPERATION DELIRIUM ~ 

"This Shall Be The Story Of The Fall Of A Human Soul— A Fall Which Is Great." 

Colonel James S. Ketchum dreamed of war without killing. He joined the Army in 1956 and left it in 1976, and in that time he did not fight in Vietnam; he did not invade the Bay of Pigs; he did not guard Western Europe with tanks, or help build nuclear launch sites beneath the Arctic ice. Instead, he became the military’s leading expert in a secret Cold War experiment: to fight enemies with clouds of psychochemicals that temporarily incapacitate the mind—causing, in the words of one ranking officer, a “selective malfunctioning of the human machine.” 

For nearly a decade, Ketchum, a psychiatrist, went about his work in the belief that chemicals are more humane instruments of warfare than bullets and shrapnel—or, at least, he told himself such things. To achieve his dream, he worked tirelessly at a secluded Army research facility, testing chemical weapons on hundreds of healthy soldiers, and thinking all along that he was doing good 

Within the Army, and in the world of medical research, the secret clinical trials are a faint memory. But for some of the surviving test subjects, and for the doctors who tested them, what happened at Edgewood remains deeply unresolved. Were the human experiments there a Dachau-like horror, or were they sound and necessary science? As veterans of the tests have come forward, their unanswered questions have slowly gathered into a kind of historical undertow, and Ketchum, more than anyone else, has been caught in its pull. In 2006, he self-published a memoir, “Chemical Warfare: Secrets Almost Forgotten,” which defended the research. Next year, a class-action lawsuit brought against the federal government by former test subjects will go to trial, and Ketchum is expected to be the star witness. 

The drugs under review ranged from tear gas and LSD to highly lethal nerve agents, like VX, a substance developed at Edgewood. Ketchum’s specialty was a family of molecules that block a key neurotransmitter, causing delirium. The drugs were known mainly by Army codes, with their true formulas classified. The soldiers were never told what they were given, or what the specific effects might be, and the Army made no effort to track how they did afterward. Edgewood’s most extreme critics raise the spectre of mass injury—a hidden American tragedy. 

Ketchum, an unreconstructed advocate of chemical warfare, believes that people who fear gaseous weapons more than guns and mortars are irrational. He cites approvingly the Russian government’s decision, in 2002, to flood a theatre in Moscow with a potent incapacitating drug when Chechen guerrillas seized the building and took eight hundred theatregoers hostage. The gas debilitated the hostage takers, allowing special forces to sweep in and kill them. But many innocent people died, too. “It’s been looked at by some skeptics as a kind of tragedy,” Ketchum has said. “They say, ‘Look, a hundred and thirty people died.’ Well, I think that a hundred and thirty is better than eight hundred, and it’s also better, as a secondary consideration, not to have to blow up a beautiful theatre.” 

Edgewood had been built in a fit of urgency during the First World War, when weaponized gas—chlorine and, later, mustard—was used to devastating effect in the trenches of Europe. Fritz Haber, the German scientist who pioneered the rise of chemical weapons, proclaimed, “In no future war will the military be able to ignore poison gas. It is a higher form of killing.” The U.S. Army took the threat seriously, and launched a program to study the chemicals, building laboratories and gas chambers in order to test human subjects. “We began to hear about the terrors of this place,” a private wrote in 1918. “Everyone we talked to on the way out here said we were coming to the place God forgot! They tell tales about men being gassed and burned.” 

After the Second World War, intelligence reports emerged from Germany of chemical weapons far deadlier than mustard or chlorine. The new compounds, which had evolved out of research into insecticides, were called nerve gases, because they created a body-wide overflow of the neurotransmitter acetylcholine, often triggering organ failure and near-sudden death. The Reich had invested primarily in three—tabun, soman, and sarin—and the victorious powers rushed to obtain them. The Soviet Union secretly dismantled an entire nerve-gas plant and relocated the technology behind the Iron Curtain. The American government, for its part, acquired the Nazi chemical formulas—and, in some cases, the scientists who developed them—and brought them to Edgewood. 

The Army decided to pursue sarin. The chemical was about twenty-five times as deadly as cyanide, and readily made into an aerosol. It was virtually impossible to handle without casualties; in one year, seven technicians required immediate treatment following accidental exposure. As the vapor was released after tests, birds passing over the flue of the gas chambers fell dead, and had to be cleared off the roof. In experiments that the arsenal contracted at Johns Hopkins University, researchers gave sarin to healthy volunteers in cups of water over three days. Some of the subjects were severely poisoned; they twitched, vomited, and had trouble breathing. 

Early nerve-gas experiments focussed on the extreme lethality of the chemicals, and on antidotes, but researchers at Edgewood also began to take note of the chemicals’ cognitive side effects. Subjects often felt giddy at first, then deeply anxious. Some had nightmares or lost sleep and became depressed. A secret 1948 study on the poisoned Edgewood technicians noted that “the outstanding feature of these cases appears to be the psychological reactions,” and its author wondered how “young men having no experience or knowledge” of the chemicals would react. A senior official at the arsenal had observed that men exposed to highly diluted tabun “were partially disabled for from one to three weeks with fatigue, lassitude, complete loss of initiative and interest, and apathy.” 

I spoke to a former Edgewood test subject who was given the nerve agent VX, which, when applied to the skin, is a hundred times as deadly as sarin. An officer came to his bedside to draw a small circle on his arm, and then a doctor with a syringe squirted on a drop of liquid. The effect was rapid. The subject heard other people groaning—one man said, “Oh, shit”—but he felt only a calm disassociation from his environment. There was a radio on in the room, but the words made little sense. When he was given food, he didn’t know what to do with his utensils. “I was not in control,” he told me. “It was incredible. This tiny drop had rendered me helpless.” As the test continued, he was seized by an agonizing wave of tension, as if each nerve ending were being crushed in a vise. “It was intense,” he told me. “My body was clenched. All of my nerves were tight, physically and mentally.” 

In 1949, L. Wilson Greene, Edge wood’s scientific director, typed up a classified report, “Psychochemical Warfare: A New Concept of War,” that called for a search for compounds that would create the same debilitating mental side effects as nerve gas, but without the lethality. “Throughout recorded history, wars have been characterized by death, human misery, and the destruction of property; each major conflict being more catastrophic than the one preceding it,” Greene argued. “I am convinced that it is possible, by means of the techniques of psychochemical warfare, to conquer an enemy without the wholesale killing of his people or the mass destruction of his property.” 

In its broad strokes, “Psychochemical Warfare” fit within the evolving ethos at Edgewood: better fighting through chemistry. The first commanding general of the Army’s Chemical Warfare Service had extolled the “effectiveness and humaneness” of gases: they killed quickly, and kept infrastructure intact. Psychochemical warfare certainly promised a form of conflict less deadly than clouds of sarin—even more humane, in that sense, perhaps. But Greene did not want to elevate consciousness; he wanted to debilitate, in ways that would inspire terror. As he put it, “The symptoms which are considered to be of value in strategic and tactical operations include the following: fits or seizures, dizziness, fear, panic, hysteria, hallucinations, migraine, delirium, extreme depression, notions of hopelessness, lack of initiative to do even simple things, suicidal mania.” 

Greene drew up a list of chemicals to investigate, ranging from barbiturates to carbon monoxide, and he urged a deeper inquiry into the psychological effects of nerve gas. Enoch Callaway, a Navy psychiatrist who arrived at Edgewood in 1950, recalled, “I was told that I needed to measure ‘nervousness,’ because nerve gas was supposed to make you nervous.” So he designed a test: people given sarin were blasted with noise to measure how much they jumped. “We figured out that nerve gas actually reduced anxiety in doses that did not cause convulsions.” The work, he insisted, was conducted responsibly, with a sense of urgency now hard to understand: “We didn’t know that chemical warfare was going to disappear so thoroughly.” 

In the mid-nineteen-fifties, psychochemical warfare was formally added to Edgewood’s clinical research, and approval was granted to recruit soldiers from around the country for the experiments, in a systematic effort called the Medical Research Volunteer Program. The Army assured Congress that the chemicals were “perfectly safe” and offered “a new vista of controlling people without any deaths”—even though early efforts to make weapons from mescaline and LSD were dropped, because the drugs were too unsafe or too unpredictable. Congressional overseers, terrified of Soviet military superiority, were ready to lend support. The Red Army had an extensive chemical-warfare program, and evidence suggested that it had an interest in “psychic poisons,” used to trigger mental illness. “Some foreign enemy could already be subjecting us in the United States to such things,” one panicky legislator proclaimed during a hearing. “Are we the ones receiving it now? Are we the rabbits and guinea pigs?” 

Edgewood began reviewing hundreds of chemicals, many provided by pharmaceutical companies. One officer remarked, “The characteristics we are looking for in these agents are in general exactly opposite to what the pharmaceutical firms want in drugs, that is the undesirable side effects.” Starting in 1959, the arsenal aggressively pursued phencyclidine—or PCP—which Parke, Davis &amp;amp; Company had marketed as an anesthetic but abandoned because patients were having hallucinations and delusions. Edgewood doctors tested it as an aerosol and surreptitiously gave it to soldiers to see if they could then “maintain physical security over simulated classified material.” One subject—who had been exposed to sarin gas a week earlier—was handed a glass of whiskey laced with twenty milligrams of PCP. “Manic reaction and much hostility,” a doctor observed. The subject passed out, and began breathing in a pattern associated with neurological trauma or cardiac stress. 

Rioch told Ketchum that another volunteer had ended up in the hospital for six weeks. “He had a paranoid reaction that didn’t go away after the drug wore off,” Ketchum recalled. The trials with PCP were eventually dropped, but stories of other problem cases circulated. A military advisory council decided that the arsenal was ill equipped for the newer line of research. “It seems important to undertake immediately a program to develop sound, fundamental techniques of assessing abnormal behavior,” its members noted. “The services of people trained in this field, such as psychologists, psychiatrists and neuro-physiologists should be obtained.” Edgewood, in other words, needed young doctors just like Jim Ketchum. 

The psychochemical-warfare program was a small part of the over-all research, and in many respects it was the strangest. Once, Ketchum walked into his office and found a barrel the size of an oil drum standing in a corner. No one explained why it was in his office, or who had put it there. After a couple of days, he waited until evening and opened it. Inside, he found dozens of small glass vials, each containing a precisely measured amount of pure LSD; he figured there was enough to make several hundred million people go bonkers—and later calculated the street value of the barrel to be roughly a billion dollars. At the end of the week, the barrel vanished just as mysteriously as it had appeared. No one spoke about it. He never learned what it was for. 

After receiving a security clearance, Ketchum was told that EA 2277 was 3-quinuclidinyl benzilate, or BZ—a pharmaceutical, intended as an ulcer therapy, that was rejected after tests found it unsuitable. Infinitesimal amounts could send people into total mental disorder. BZ is an anticholinergic, similar to atropine or scopolamine, which are used in medicine today. At high doses, such drugs trigger delirium—a dreamlike insanity usually forgotten after it subsides. Sim, one of the first doctors to try BZ, later proclaimed that it “zonked” him for three days. “I kept falling down,” he said. “The people at the lab assigned someone to follow me around with a mattress.” 

For years, Sim had been overseeing secret intelligence experiments at Edgewood. At one point, he did research for the C.I.A. on a BZ-type drug, called the Boomer, that causes delirium for as long as two weeks. The agency wanted to know if it could be administered through the skin. Could a Soviet agent brush some on silverware at a diplomatic party and cause an American official to go crazy? Could an operative dose an adversary with a handshake? Sim initiated trials at the arsenal and at Holmesburg Prison, in Pennsylvania, with which Edgewood had contracted to conduct experiments on inmates. 

Testing psychochemicals for intelligence purposes, Sim appeared to believe, required a uniquely loose protocol: the goal was to control the mind, and the subject’s expectations of the drug’s effect mattered. He often gave LSD to people without warning. 

Not long after arriving at Edgewood, Ketchum took to playing tennis with a commanding officer at the arsenal, who, after a match one day, described how Sim had spiked his morning coffee with LSD. “He was pissed off as hell,” Ketchum told me. LSD had been mixed into cocktails at a party, and into an Army unit’s water supply. Some men handled it fine; some went berserk. A test subject in 1957 exhibited “euphoria followed by severe depression, anxiety, and panic—feeling he was going to die,” according to his chart. Another test involved intelligence specialists who were blindfolded and placed in an isolation chamber. “Only one subject was in a condition to undergo extended interrogation,” a report concluded. “A second subject fled from interrogation in panic.” 

Ketchum later wrote of Sim’s “hare-brained experiments” and his “lack of scientific (and ethical) judgment.” The Army had apparently reached the same conclusion. In 1959, responsibility for the volunteers was taken from Sim—who was eventually given the new title of chief scientist—and transferred to Lindsey, a more capable leader, though not immune to bouts of recklessness himself. To demonstrate the effects of VX, he was known to dip his finger in a beaker containing the lethal agent, then rub it on the back of a shaved rabbit; as the animal convulsed and died, he would casually walk across the room and bathe his finger in a Martini to wash off the VX. “I thought they were crazy,” a doctor who served under him told me. “I was going to New York, and Colonel Lindsey tells me, ‘How about taking a vial of nerve gas to New York to make a demonstration.’ And I am looking at the guy and thinking, If I have an accident on the Thruway, I could kill thousands of people—thousands of people. I said, ‘No. It’s that simple.’ ” 

Sim appeared to believe that personally sampling every chemical agent made him free to circumvent conventional standards; “I have to live with myself,” he once said. Lindsey had an officer’s protectiveness for the enlisted men. Many of the Army doctors—draftees, like the volunteers—who worked under both men strove to reconcile their military obligations with their medical commitments. “As doctors, we are used to treating people who are sick, not making them sick,” one told me. “I did not like the idea of what I was doing with individual human beings. But I understood what I was doing in the context of the defense of this country.” 

Exposed soldiers exhibited bizarre symptoms: rapid mumbling, or picking obsessively at bedclothes and other objects, real or imaginary. “Subjects sometimes display something approaching wit, not in the form of word-play, but as a kind of sarcasm or unexpected frankness,” he wrote in a report for Sim. The drug’s effect lasted for days. At its peak, volunteers were totally cut off in their own minds, jolting from one fragmented existence to the next. They saw visions: Lilliputian baseball players competing on a tabletop diamond; animals or people or objects that materialized and vanished. “I had a great urge to smoke and, when I thought about it, a lit cigarette appeared in my hand,” a volunteer given a drug similar to BZ recalled shortly after the experiment. “I could actually smoke the cigarette.” 

Soldiers on BZ could remember only fragments of the experience afterward. As the drug wore off, and the subjects had trouble discerning what was real, many experienced anxiety, aggression, even terror. Ketchum built padded cells to prevent injuries, but at times the subjects couldn’t be contained. One escaped, running from imagined murderers. Another, on a drug similar to BZ, saw “bugs, worms, one snake, a monkey and numerous rats,” and thought his skin was covered in blood. “Subject broke a wooden chair and smashed a hole in the wall after tearing down a 4-by-7-ft panel of padding,” his chart noted. Ketchum and three assistants piled on top of the soldier to subdue him. “He was clearly terrified and convinced we were intending to kill him,” his chart said. 

“These soldiers are not really informed at all,” he told Malcolm Bowers, an Edgewood medical officer who later became a professor at Yale. Little was known about the long-term effects of the experiments, and yet the volunteers, after a stay at the arsenal, were blindly pushed back into the Army at large, with no follow-up care. In a self-published memoir, “Men and Poisons,” Bowers recalls Lindsey wondering if the lack of follow-up stemmed from the Army’s fear that such a program would disclose concern about lasting health effects. Sim later offered a more mundane reason: insufficient funding 

The Medical Research Volunteer Program initially had difficulty attracting volunteers, so monthly quotas were established to insure a steady supply of research subjects. Recruiters fanned out to Army facilities across the country; some commanders even ordered men to attend the sessions. People who attended the sessions came away with an uncertain sense of what they were being asked to do. 

A number of them told me that recruiters advertised the program in vague terms, as human behavioral studies, or equipment testing, or medical research. Inducements were offered, too. Soldiers could spend time near several large East Coast cities, and would be given three-day weekend passes to explore them. There would be extra pay, and few responsibilities, aside from showing up at a test. Many men spent much of their stay playing Ping-Pong and watching movies. When it came time for volunteers to leave—at first, they were asked to serve for a month, later two months—a letter of commendation would enter their file. In the sixties, the arsenal offered an even more powerful incentive: time away from Vietnam. 

Once the volunteers arrived at Edgewood, they were given medical and psychological examinations, and were divided into four groups. The least healthy would be used to test equipment. The top twenty-five per cent—the Astronaut Class, as Ketchum once called them—would typically be prepared for the most dangerous chemicals. Doctors informed the volunteers in generalities and asked them to sign a consent form—usually long before any specific test was announced. The forms were designed to offer few details; as one version was drafted, the words “mental disturbance or unconsciousness” were replaced with “discomfiture.” Sometimes a little more information would be provided just before the test began, but not always. Van Sim later confessed that researchers testing nerve gas would tell volunteers that the drug might give them a “runny nose” or a “slight tightness of the chest.” In 1961, a volunteer from Kansas, named John Ross, was given soman, a highly persistent nerve agent. Only when the needle was in his arm did he overhear the doctors saying that he had been given something lethal. “I started having convulsions,” he told me. “I started vomiting. One of the guys standing over me said, ‘We gave you a little too much.’ They told me to walk it off. I started to panic. I thought I was going to die.” Ross became rigid and was rushed to Walter Reed. For years afterward, he suffered from insomnia and depression. 

Test subjects had a right to decline an experiment—assuming that they knew they were part of one—but they almost never did. “There was no question that they would participate,” Bowers recalled. Withdrawing from a test required backing down from a commitment to one’s superior, which was anathema in the Army. “In the military, if you don’t do something you will be ostracized,” a soldier given LSD in 1958 told me. “I believe they did give us the option to leave, at first, but you didn’t really have a choice once you were in.” 

The same day Elbin was given BZ, Ketchum gave the drug to Teddie Osborne, who had been stationed at the Yuma Test Center, in Arizona, where he was using a crude detector and a caged rabbit to look for chemical leaks. Osborne thought that his work would not change much at Edgewood. “It wasn’t really explained,” he told me. At the arsenal, he was assigned to help manage the recruits; he liked the work and volunteered again. 

The second time, he was told that he was going to be a subject. He felt tricked. “I could not have said no,” he told me. “You are dealing with professionals. We were very gullible.” One Wednesday, Osborne was injected with BZ, and ushered into a padded room. He had no idea what the drug was or what it would do. “I don’t remember anything until Saturday,” he told me. “That was so disturbing. Later, it still haunted me.” 

By this time, the Army was running a “crash program” to turn BZ into an operational weapon. 

Even as it became reasonable to suspect that BZ could cause serious injury on the battlefield, the military was pushing to put it into use. In November, 1964, an Army major travelled to Edgewood on an urgent mission from Lieutenant General William Dick, the chief of Army research. Soviet trawlers had been spotted off the coast of Alaska, and Dick wanted to know if a projected cloud of BZ could disable the crew. Senior officers at the arsenal told the major that such a thing was out of the question—the chemical had not even been field-tested. Eventually, the major came to see Ketchum, who was leading a newly created group called the Psychopharmacology Branch. “The plan didn’t make a whole lot of sense, and it offended me on a rational level,” he wrote in his memoir. “On the other hand, the challenge ruthlessly tickled my imagination. 

The Soviets were not ignorant of BZ, after all. Vil Mirzayanov, a chemist who conducted secret weapons research for the Soviet Union, told me that Moscow never had more than a halfhearted interest in LSD, and that its interest in BZ was strictly to keep up with Ketchum’s program. “We knew the West had developed this weapon, and we were trying to copy it,” he said. Soviet scientists, who called the formula Substance 78, conducted their own clinical trials with it and manufactured tons of the drug at a plant in Volsk. 

By the late sixties, the high point of the Cold War had sloped into a murkier geopolitical condition; half a million Americans were in Vietnam, and though the Army had freely used defoliants and tear gas there, it decided not to use BZ. Popular sentiment was turning against the idea of deploying psychochemicals in war. “There are moral imponderables, such as whether insanity, temporary or permanent, is a more ‘humane’ military threat than the usual afflictions of war,” E. James Lieberman, a psychiatric resident at Harvard, wrote in The Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists. In 1965, Sidney Cohen, a well-regarded LSD researcher, argued that “such degradation of a person’s mind is worse than his physical death and can hardly be considered humane warfare.” 

A physician named Mark Needle told me that he thought Ketchum’s human experiments were run like the Keystone Kops. “There was nobody qualified,” he said. “And the fact that they were allowed to do it without people who knew what they were doing was very, very scary. There was no humanity in it. There was no morality in it. If anything happened to the volunteers, we could say, ‘You were offered an out,’ but then we were also telling them, ‘Listen, this is the Army, and we are at war.’ Our view was that this was a terrible thing to do to these kids, because who the hell knew what could happen?” 

When Ketchum sought to orchestrate a field test with a new version of BZ, four doctors wrote in dissent. He overruled them. Another version, called EA 3834, appeared to cause microscopic hematuria—tiny amounts of blood in urine—and other renal problems. One soldier was sent to Walter Reed. “This is a dangerous drug,” a psychiatrist named George Leib insisted. Leib, who worked on the arsenal’s annual budget, had come to think that tests of a baroque nature and questionable design were being funded merely to sustain the program. His office was across from the toxic-aid station, and he was sure that records were being manipulated to disguise problem cases. 

In April, Matthew Meselson, a Harvard biologist, argued in congressional testimony that non-lethal chemical weapons would only make war more savage, because armies would use them to flush out enemies and then slaughter them. 

The lasting health effects of the research were difficult to judge. Records were either messy or incomplete, and no experiment had collected data to determine how a drug might affect lives in the long term 
. 
The Nuremberg Code established an ethical framework for medical experiments. The code begins with a clear premise: 

“The voluntary consent of the human subject is absolutely essential.” That consent must flow from an “enlightened decision,” shaped by a true understanding of the test’s medical risks. Moreover, human experiments must be preceded by animal studies, and conducted in pursuit of a greater social good—with risks never exceeding “the humanitarian importance of the problem.” If a subject is unable to endure the experiment, or if a researcher believes there is a probability of injury, the test must end. 

GIF Via: http://gifmovie.tumblr.com/ 

Complete Article @:http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2012/12/17/121217fa_fact_khatchadourian?currentPage=all﻿

Meer lezen (481 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_03_thumb.gif">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3FOGWEt3lak/UM9PHoehjEI/AAAAAAAA4jI/QVnM03goEHk/w426-h240/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/103743711516936697517/albums/6005619121417632849/6005619125409447858</link><title>http://www.themanyfacesofspaces.com/MFS-StrangeButTrue-ThingsOther13.html 
#armeniangenocide 

The Armenian Genocide (Armenian: Հայոց Ցեղասպանություն, translit.: Hayoc’ C’eġaspanowt’yown; Turkish: Ermeni Soykırımı), also known as the Armenian Holocaust, the Armenian Massacres and, by Armenians, as the Great Calamity (Մեծ Եղեռն, Meç Eġeṙn, Armenian pronunciation: [mɛts jɛˈʁɛrn]), was the deliberate and systematic destruction (genocide) of the Armenian population of the Ottoman Empire during and just after World War I. It was characterised by the use of massacres, and the use of deportations involving forced marches under conditions designed to lead to the death of the deportees, with the total number of Armenian deaths generally held to have been between one and one-and-a-half million. Other ethnic groups were similarly attacked by the Empire during this period, including Assyrians and Greeks, and some scholars consider those events to be part of the same policy of extermination. 

It is widely acknowledged to have been one of the first modern genocides, as many Western sources point to the systematic, organized manner in which the killings were carried out to eliminate the Armenians.[9] Indeed, the word genocide was coined in order to describe these events. 

The date of the onset of the genocide is conventionally held to be April 24, 1915, the day that Ottoman authorities arrested some 250 Armenian intellectuals and community leaders in Constantinople. Thereafter, the Ottoman military uprooted Armenians from their homes and forced them to march for hundreds of miles, depriving them of food and water, to the desert of what is now Syria. Massacres were indiscriminate of age or gender, with rape and other sexual abuse commonplace. The Armenian Genocide is the second most-studied case of genocide after the Holocaust. 

The Republic of Turkey, the successor state of the Ottoman Empire, denies the word genocide is an accurate description of the events. In recent years, it has faced repeated calls to accept the events as genocide. To date, twenty countries have officially recognized the events of the period as genocide, and most genocide scholars and historians accept this view. The majority of Armenian diaspora communities were founded as a result of the Armenian genocide. 

Prelude 

Life under Ottoman rule 

Armenian-populated regions in central and eastern Anatolia and the Transcaucasus before the genocide. 
The majority of the Armenian population was concentrated in the east of the Ottoman Empire.In the Ottoman Empire, in accordance with the Muslim dhimmi system, Armenians, as Christians, were guaranteed limited freedoms (such as the right to worship), but were treated as second-class citizens. Christians and Jews were not considered equals to Muslims: testimony against Muslims by Christians and Jews was inadmissible in courts of law. They were forbidden to carry weapons or ride atop horses, their houses could not overlook those of Muslims, and their religious practices would have to defer to those of Muslims, in addition to various other legal limitations. Violation of these statutes could result in punishments ranging from the levying of fines to execution. 

The three major European powers, Great Britain, France and Russia (known as the Great Powers), took issue with the Empire's treatment of its Christian minorities and increasingly pressured the Ottoman government (also known as the Sublime Porte) to extend equal rights to all its citizens. Beginning in 1839, the Ottoman government implemented the Tanzimat reforms to improve the situation of minorities, although these would prove largely ineffective. By the late 1870s, Greece, along with several countries of the Balkans, frustrated with conditions, had, often with the help of the Powers, broken free of Ottoman rule. Armenians, for the most part, remained passive during these years, earning them the title of millet-i sadıka or the "loyal millet." 

Reform implementation, 1860s–1880s 

In the mid-1860s to early 1870s, Armenians began to ask for better treatment from the Ottoman government. After amassing the signatures of peasants from eastern Anatolia, the Armenian Communal Council had petitioned to the Ottoman government to redress the issues that the peasants complained about: "the looting and murder in Armenian towns by [Muslim] Kurds and Circassians, improprieties during tax collection, criminal behavior by government officials and the refusal to accept Christians as witnesses in trial." The Ottoman government considered these grievances and promised to punish those responsible. 

Following the violent suppression of Christians in the uprisings in Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria and Serbia in 1875, the Great Powers invoked the 1856 Treaty of Paris by claiming that it gave them the right to intervene and protect the Ottoman Empire's Christian minorities. Under growing pressure, the government declared itself a constitutional monarchy (which was almost immediately dissolved) and entered into negotiations with the powers. At the same time, the Armenian patriarchate of Constantinople, Nerses II, forwarded Armenian complaints of widespread "forced land seizure ... forced conversion of women and children, arson, protection extortion, rape, and murder" to the Powers. 

After the conclusion of the 1877–1878 Russo-Turkish War, Armenians began to look more towards Tsarist Russia as the guarantors of their security. Nerses approached the Russian leadership during its negotiations with the Ottomans in San Stefano and in the eponymous treaty, convinced them to insert a clause, Article 16, that stipulated that Russian forces occupying the Armenian provinces would only withdraw with the full implementation of Ottoman reforms. Great Britain was troubled with Russia holding on to so much Ottoman territory and forced it to enter into new negotiations with the convening of the Congress of Berlin on June 13, 1878. Armenians also entered into these negotiations and stated that they sought autonomy, not independence from the Ottoman Empire. They partially succeeded as Article 61 of the Treaty of Berlin contained the same text as Article 16 but removed any mention that Russian forces would remain in the provinces; instead, the Ottoman government was to periodically inform the Great Powers of the progress of the reforms. 

Hamidian Massacres, 1894–1896 

Hamidian massacresIn 1876, the Ottoman government was led by Sultan Abdul Hamid II. From the beginning of the reform period after the signing of the Berlin treaty, Hamid II attempted to stall their implementation and asserted that Armenians did not make up a majority in the provinces and that Armenian reports of abuses were largely exaggerated or false. In 1890, Hamid II created a paramilitary outfit known as the Hamidiye which was made up of Kurdish irregulars who were tasked to "deal with the Armenians as they wished." As Ottoman officials intentionally provoked rebellions (often as a result of over-taxation) in Armenian populated towns, such as the Sasun Resistance of 1894, these regiments were increasingly used to deal with the Armenians by way of oppression and massacre. Armenians successfully fought off the regiments and brought the excesses to the attention of the Great Powers in 1895 who subsequently condemned the Porte. 

The Powers forced Hamid to sign a new reform package designed to curtail the powers of the Hamidiye in October 1895 which like the Berlin treaty, was never implemented. On October 1, 1895, 2,000 Armenians assembled in Constantinople to petition for the implementation of the reforms but Ottoman police units converged towards the rally and violently broke it up.Soon, massacres of Armenians broke out in Constantinople and then engulfed the rest of the Armenian populated provinces of Bitlis, Diyarbekir, Harput, Sivas, Trabzon and Van. Estimates differ on how many Armenians were killed but European documentation of the violence, which became known as the Hamidian massacres, placed the figures from anywhere between 100,000–300,000 Armenians. 

Although Hamid was never directly implicated for ordering the massacres, he was suspected for their tacit approval and for not acting to end them. Frustrated with European indifference to the massacres, Armenians from the Dashnaktsutiun political party seized the European managed Ottoman Bank on August 26, 1896. This incident brought further sympathy for Armenians in Europe and was lauded by the European and American press, which vilified Hamid and painted him as the "great assassin" and "bloody Sultan." While the Great Powers vowed to take action and enforce new reforms, these never came into fruition due to conflicting political and economic interests. 

Dissolution of the Empire 

Young Turk Revolution, 1908 

On July 24, 1908, Armenians' hopes for equality in the empire brightened once more when a coup d'état staged by officers in the Turkish Third Army based in Salonika removed Hamid II from power and restored the country back to a constitutional monarchy. The officers were part of the Young Turk movement that wanted to reform administration of the decadent state of the Ottoman Empire and modernize it to European standards. The movement was an anti-Hamidian coalition made up of two distinct groups: the secular liberal constitutionalists and the nationalists; the former was more democratic and accepted Armenians into their wing whereas the latter was more intolerant in regard to Armenian-related issues and their frequent requests for European assistance. In 1902, during a congress of the Young Turks held in Paris, the heads of the liberal wing, Sabahheddin Bey and Ahmed Riza, partially persuaded the nationalists to include in their objectives to ensure some rights to all the minorities of the empire. 

Among the numerous factions of the Young Turks also included the political organization Committee of Union and Progress (CUP). Originally a secret society made up of army officers based in Salonika, the CUP proliferated amongst military circles as more army mutinies took place throughout the empire. In 1908, elements of the Third Army and the Second Army Corps declared their opposition to the Sultan and threatened to march on the capital to depose him. Hamid, shaken by the wave of resentment, stepped down from power as Armenians, Greeks, Arabs, Bulgarians and Turks alike rejoiced in his dethronement. 

Adana Massacre, 1909 

An Armenian town left pillaged and destroyed after the massacres in Adana in 1909.A countercoup took place on April 13, 1909. Some Ottoman military elements, joined by Islamic theological students, aimed to return control of the country to the Sultan and the rule of Islamic law. Riots and fighting broke out between the reactionary forces and CUP forces, until the CUP was able to put down the uprising and court-martial the opposition leaders. 

While the movement initially targeted the nascent Young Turk government, it spilled over into pogroms against Armenians who were perceived as having supported the restoration of the constitution. When Ottoman Army troops were called in, many accounts record that instead of trying to quell the violence they actually took part in pillaging Armenian enclaves in Adana province. 15,000–30,000 Armenians were killed in the course of the "Adana Massacre". 

Armenian Genocide, 1915–1917 period 

In November 1914, the Ottoman Empire entered World War I on the side of the Central Powers. Minister of War Enver Pasha developed a plan to encircle and destroy the Russian Caucasus Army at Sarıkamış, to regain territories lost to Russia after the Russo-Turkish War of 1877–1878. Enver Pasha's forces were routed at the Battle of Sarikamis, and almost completely destroyed. Returning to Constantinople, Enver publicly blamed his defeat on Armenians living in the region actively siding with the Russians 

Labor battalions, February 25 
Further information: Labour battalions 
On February 25, 1915, The War minister Enver Pasha sent an order to all military units that Armenians in the active Ottoman forces be demobilized and assigned to the unarmed Labour battalion (Turkish: amele taburlari). Enver Pasha explained this decision as "out of fear that they would collaborate with the Russians". As a tradition, the Ottoman Army drafted non-Muslim males only between the ages of 20 and 45 into the regular army. The younger (15–20) and older (45–60) non-Muslim soldiers had always been used as logistical support through the labor battalions. Before February, some of the Armenian recruits were utilized as laborers (hamals), though they would ultimately be executed. 

Transferring Armenian conscripts from active field (armed) to passive, unarmed logistic section was an important aspect of the subsequent genocide. As reported in "The Memoirs of Naim Bey", the extermination of the Armenians in these battalions was part of a premeditated strategy on behalf of the Committee of Union and Progress. Many of these Armenian recruits were executed by local Turkish gangs. 

Events at Van, April 1915 
Further information: Van Resistance 

Armed Armenian civilians and self-defense units holding a line against Turkish forces in the walled city of Van in May 1915On April 19, 1915, Jevdet Bey demanded that the city of Van immediately furnish him 4,000 soldiers under the pretext of conscription. However, it was clear to the Armenian population that his goal was to massacre the able-bodied men of Van so that there would be no defenders.Jevdet Bey had already used his official writ in nearby villages, ostensibly to search for arms, which had turned into wholesale massacres. The Armenians offered five hundred soldiers and to pay exemption money for the rest in order to buy time, however, Djevdet accused Armenians of "rebellion," and spoke of his determination to "crush" it at any cost. "If the rebels fire a single shot," he declared, "I shall kill every Christian man, woman, and" (pointing to his knee) "every child, up to here." 

On April 20, 1915, the armed conflict of the Van Resistance began when an Armenian woman was harassed, and the two Armenian men that came to her aid were killed by Turkish soldiers. The Armenian defenders protected 30,000 residents and 15,000 refugees in an area of roughly one square kilometer of the Armenian Quarter and suburb of Aigestan with 1,500 able bodied riflemen who were supplied with 300 rifles and 1,000 pistols and antique weapons. The conflict lasted until General Yudenich came to rescue them. 

Arrest and deportation of Armenian notables, April 1915 

Armenian intellectuals who were arrested and later executed en masse by Ottoman authorities on the night of April 24, 1915.By 1914, Ottoman authorities had already begun a propaganda drive to present Armenians living in the Ottoman Empire as a threat to the empire's security. An Ottoman naval officer in the War Office described the planning: 

In order to justify this enormous crime the requisite propaganda material was thoroughly prepared in Constantinople. [It included such statements as] "the Armenians are in league with the enemy. They will launch an uprising in Istanbul, kill off the Committee of Union and Progress leaders and will succeed in opening the straits (of the Dardanelles)." 

On the night of April 24, 1915, the Ottoman government rounded-up and imprisoned an estimated 250 Armenian intellectuals and community leaders. This date coincided with Allied troop landings at Gallipoli after unsuccessful Allied naval attempts to break through the Dardanelles to Constantinople in February and March 1915. 

Temporary Law of Deportation (the "Tehcir" law) 

In May 1915, Mehmed Talat Pasha requested that the cabinet and Grand Vizier Said Halim Pasha legalize a measure for relocation and settlement of Armenians to other places due to what Talat Pasha called "the Armenian riots and massacres, which had arisen in a number of places in the country." However, Talat Pasha was referring specifically to events in Van and extending the implementation to the regions in which alleged "riots and massacres" would affect the security of the war zone of the Caucasus Campaign. Later, the scope of the immigration was widened in order to include the Armenians in the other provinces. On 29 May 1915, the CUP Central Committee passed the Temporary Law of Deportation ("Tehcir Law"), giving the Ottoman government and military authorization to deport anyone it "sensed" as a threat to national security. The "Tehcir Law" brought some measures regarding the property of the deportees, but during September a new law was proposed. By means of the "Abandoned Properties" Law (Law Concerning Property, Dept's and Assets Left Behind Deported Persons, also referred as the "Temporary Law on Expropriation and Confiscation"), the Ottoman government took possession of all "abandoned" Armenian goods and properties. Ottoman parliamentary representative Ahmed Riza protested this legislation: 

It is unlawful to designate the Armenian assets as “abandoned goods” for the Armenians, the proprietors, did not abandon their properties voluntarily; they were forcibly, compulsorily removed from their domiciles and exiled. Now the government through its efforts is selling their goods... If we are a constitutional regime functioning in accordance with constitutional law we can’t do this. This is atrocious. Grab my arm, eject me from my village, then sell my goods and properties, such a thing can never be permissible. Neither the conscience of the Ottomans nor the law can allow it. 
On 13 September 1915, the Ottoman parliament passed the "Temporary Law of Expropriation and Confiscation", stating that all property, including land, livestock, and homes belonging to Armenians, was to be confiscated by the authorities. 

Deportation and extermination process 

With the implementation of Tehcir law, the confiscation of Armenian property and the slaughter of Armenians that ensued upon the law's enactment outraged much of the western world. While the Ottoman Empire's wartime allies offered little protest, a wealth of German and Austrian historical documents has since come to attest to the witnesses' horror at the killings and mass starvation of Armenians. In the United States, The New York Times reported almost daily on the mass murder of the Armenian people, describing the process as "systematic", "authorized" and "organized by the government." Theodore Roosevelt would later characterize this as "the greatest crime of the war." 

The Armenians were marched out to the Syrian town of Deir ez-Zor and the surrounding desert. A good deal of evidence suggests that the Ottoman government did not provide any facilities or supplies to sustain the Armenians during their deportation, nor when they arrived. By August 1915, The New York Times repeated an unattributed report that "the roads and the Euphrates are strewn with corpses of exiles, and those who survive are doomed to certain death. It is a plan to exterminate the whole Armenian people." 

Ottoman troops escorting the Armenians not only allowed others to rob, kill, and rape the Armenians, but often participated in these activities themselves.Deprived of their belongings and marched into the desert, hundreds of thousands of Armenians perished. 

Naturally, the death rate from starvation and sickness is very high and is increased by the brutal treatment of the authorities, whose bearing toward the exiles as they are being driven back and forth over the desert is not unlike that of slave drivers. With few exceptions no shelter of any kind is provided and the people coming from a cold climate are left under the scorching desert sun without food and water. Temporary relief can only be obtained by the few able to pay officials. 

It is believed that 25 major concentration camps existed, under the command of Şükrü Kaya, one of the right hand-men of Talat Pasha. The majority of the camps were situated near Turkey's modern Iraqi and Syrian borders, and some were only temporary transit camps. Others, such as Radjo, Katma, and Azaz, are said to have been used only temporarily, for mass graves; these sites were vacated by autumn 1915. Some authors also maintain that the camps Lale, Tefridje, Dipsi, Del-El, and Ra's al-'Ain were built specifically for those who had a life expectancy of a few days. 

Although nearly all the camps, including the primary sites, were open air, the remainder of the mass killing in minor camps was not limited to direct killings, but also to mass burning. Eitan Belkind was a Nili member, who infiltrated the Ottoman army as an official. He was assigned to the headquarters of Camal Pasha. He claims to have witnessed the burning of 5,000 Armenians. Lt. Hasan Maruf, of the Ottoman army, describes how a population of a village were taken all together, and then burned. The Commander of the Third Army Vehib's 12-page affidavit, which was dated 5 December 1918, was presented in the Trabzon trial series (March 29, 1919) included in the Key Indictment, reporting such a mass burning of the population of an entire village near Mush. that in Bitlis, Mus and Sassoun, The shortest method for disposing of the women and children concentrated in tile various camps was to burn them. And also that, Turkish prisoners who had apparently witnessed some of these scenes were horrified and maddened at the remembering the sight. They told the Russians that the stench of the burning human flesh permeated the air for many days after. The Germans, Ottoman allies, also witnessed the way Armenians were burned according to the Israeli historian, Bat Ye’or, who writes: The Germans, allies of the Turks in the First World War, ...saw how civil populations were shut up in churches and burned, or gathered en masse in camps, tortured to death, and reduced to ashes,... 

During the Trabzon trial series of the Martial court, from the sittings between March 26 and May 17, 1919, the Trabzons Health Services Inspector Dr. Ziya Fuad wrote in a report that Dr. Saib caused the death of children with the injection of morphine. The information was allegedly provided by two physicians (Drs. Ragib and Vehib), both Dr. Saib's colleagues at Trabzons Red Crescent hospital, where those atrocities were said to have been committed. Dr. Ziya Fuad and Dr. Adnan, public health services director of Trabzon, submitted affidavits reporting cases in which two school buildings were used to organize children and send them to the mezzanine to kill them with toxic gas equipment . 
The Ottoman surgeon, Dr. Haydar Cemal wrote on the order of the Chief Sanitation Office of the IIIrd Army in January 1916, when the spread of typhus was an acute problem, innocent Armenians slated for deportation at Erzican were inoculated with the blood of typhoid fever patients without rendering that blood ‘inactive’.Jeremy Hugh Baron writes : Individual doctors were directly involved in the massacres, having poisoned infants, killed children and issued false certificates of death from natural causes. Nazim's brother-in-law Dr. Tevfik Rushdu, Inspector-General of Health Services, organized the disposal of Armenian corpses with thousands of kilos of lime over six months; he became foreign secretary from 1925 to 1938.The psychiatrist, Robert Jay Lifton, writes in a parenthesis when introducing the crimes of Nazi doctors Perhaps Turkish doctors, in their participation in the genocide against the Armenians, come closest, as I shall later suggest. Oscar S. Heizer, the American consul at Trabzon, reports: This plan did not suit Nail Bey.... Many of the children were loaded into boats and taken out to sea and thrown overboard. The Italian consul of Trabzon in 1915, Giacomo Gorrini, writes: I saw thousands of innocent women and children placed on boats which were capsized in the Black Sea. Hoffman Philip, the American Charge at Constantinople chargé d'affaires, writes: Boat loads sent from Zor down the river arrived at Ana, one thirty miles away, with three fifths of passengers missing. The Trabzon trials reported Armenians having been drowned in the Black Sea. 

Teşkilat-i Mahsusa 

The Committee of Union and Progress founded a "special organization" (Turkish: Teşkilat-i Mahsusa) that participated in the destruction of the Ottoman Armenian community. This organization adopted its name in 1913 and functioned like a special forces outfit, or the later Einsatzgruppen. Later in 1914, the Ottoman government influenced the direction the special organization was to take by releasing criminals from central prisons to be the central elements of this newly formed special organization. According to the Mazhar commissions attached to the tribunal as soon as November 1914, 124 criminals were released from Pimian prison. Little by little from the end of 1914 to the beginning of 1915, hundreds, then thousands of prisoners were freed to form the members of this organization. Later, they were charged to escort the convoys of Armenian deportees.Vehib Pasha, commander of the Ottoman Third Army, called those members of the special organization, the “butchers of the human species. 

Contemporaneous reports and reactions 

Of this photo, the United States ambassador wrote , "Scenes like this were common all over the Armenian provinces, in the spring and summer months of 1915. Death in its several forms—massacre, starvation, exhaustion—destroyed the larger part of the refugees. The Turkish policy was that of extermination under the guise of deportation." 
Hundreds of eyewitnesses, including the neutral United States and the Ottoman Empire's own allies, Germany and Austria-Hungary, recorded and documented numerous acts of state-sponsored massacres. Many foreign officials offered to intervene on behalf of the Armenians, including Pope Benedict XV, only to be turned away by Ottoman government officials who claimed they were retaliating against a pro-Russian insurrection. On May 24, 1915, the Triple Entente warned the Ottoman Empire that "In view of these new crimes of Turkey against humanity and civilization, the Allied Governments announce publicly to the Sublime Porte that they will hold personally responsible for these crimes all members of the Ottoman Government, as well as those of their agents who are implicated in such massacres." 

The American Committee for Relief in the Near East (ACRNE, or "Near East Relief") was a charitable organization established to relieve the suffering of the peoples of the Near East. The organization was championed by Henry Morgenthau, Sr., American ambassador to the Ottoman Empire. Morgenthau's dispatches on the mass slaughter of Armenians galvanized much support for ACRNE. 

U.S. mission in the Ottoman Empire 

The United States had several consulates throughout the Ottoman Empire, including locations in Edirne, Kharput, Samsun, Smyrna, Trebizond, Van, Constantinople, and Aleppo. The United States was officially a neutral party until it joined with the Allies in 1917. As the orders for deportations and massacres were enacted, many consular officials reported to the ambassador what they were witnessing. In September 1915 the American consul in Kharput, Leslie Davis, reported his discovery of the bodies of nearly 10,000 Armenians dumped into several ravines near Lake Göeljuk, later referring to this region as the "slaughterhouse province". 

A telegram sent by Ambassador Henry Morgenthau Sr. to the State Department on 16 July 1915 describes the massacres as a "campaign of race extermination." 
Fundraising poster for the American Committee for Relief in the Near East - the United States contributed a significant amount of aid to help Armenians during the Armenian Genocide. 
An article by the New York Times dated 15 December 1915 states that one million Armenians had been either deported or executed by the Ottoman government. 
Workers of the American Committee for Relief in the Near East in Sivas. 
Similar reports reached Morgenthau from Aleppo and Van, prompting him to raise the issue in person with Talaat and Enver. As he quoted to them the testimonies of his consulate officials, they justified the deportations as necessary to the conduct of the war, suggesting that complicity of the Armenians of Van with the Russian forces that had taken the city justified the persecution of all ethnic Armenians. In his memoirs, Morgenthau wrote, "When the Turkish authorities gave the orders for these deportations, they were merely giving the death warrant to a whole race; they understood this well, and, in their conversations with me, they made no particular attempt to conceal the fact..." 

In addition to the consulates, there were also numerous Protestant missionary compounds established in Armenian-populated regions, including Van and Kharput. In memoirs and reports, their staff vividly described the brutal methods used by Ottoman forces and documented numerous instances of atrocities committed against the Christian minority. 

The events were reported regularly in newspapers and literary journals around the world. Many Americans spoke out against the Genocide, including former president Theodore Roosevelt, rabbi Stephen Wise, William Jennings Bryan, and Alice Stone Blackwell. The American Near East Relief Committee helped donate over $110 million to the Armenians. In the United States and the United Kingdom, children were regularly reminded to clean their plates while eating and to "remember the starving Armenians". 

Allied forces in the Middle East 

On the Middle Eastern front, the British military engaged Ottoman forces in southern Syria and Mesopotamia. British diplomat Gertrude Bell filed the following report after hearing the account of a captured Ottoman soldier: 

The battalion left Aleppo on 3 February and reached Ras al-Ain in twelve hours... some 12,000 Armenians were concentrated under the guardianship of some hundred Kurds... These Kurds were called gendarmes, but in reality mere butchers; bands of them were publicly ordered to take parties of Armenians, of both sexes, to various destinations, but had secret instructions to destroy the males, children and old women... One of these gendarmes confessed to killing 100 Armenian men himself... the empty desert cisterns and caves were also filled with corpses... 

Reacting to numerous eyewitness accounts, British politician Viscount Bryce and historian Arnold J. Toynbee compiled statements from survivors and eyewitnesses from other countries including Germany, Italy, the Netherlands, Sweden, and Switzerland, who similarly attested to the systematized massacring of innocent Armenians by Ottoman government forces. In 1916, they published The Treatment of Armenians in the Ottoman Empire, 1915–1916. Although the book has since been criticized as British wartime propaganda to build up sentiment against the Central Powers, Bryce had submitted the work to scholars for verification before its publication. University of Oxford Regius Professor Gilbert Murray stated of the tome, "...the evidence of these letters and reports will bear any scrutiny and overpower any skepticism. Their genuineness is established beyond question." Other professors, including Herbert Fisher of Sheffield University and former American Bar Association president Moorfield Storey, affirmed the same conclusion. 

Winston Churchill described the massacres as an "administrative holocaust" and noted that "the clearance of the race from Asia Minor was about as complete as such an act, on a scale so great, could well be. [...] There is no reasonable doubt that this crime was planned and executed for political reasons. The opportunity presented itself for clearing Turkish soil of a Christian race opposed to all Turkish ambitions, cherishing national ambitions that could only be satisfied at the expense of Turkey, and planted geographically between Turkish and Caucasian Moslems. 

Joint Austrian and German mission 

As allies during the war, the Imperial German mission in the Ottoman Empire included both military and civilian components. Germany had brokered a deal with the Sublime Porte to commission the building of a railroad stretching from Berlin to the Middle East, called the Baghdad Railway. 

Among the most famous persons to document the massacres was German military medic Armin T. Wegner. Wegner defied state censorship in taking hundreds of photographs of Armenians being deported and subsequently starving in northern Syrian camps.[90] 

German officers stationed in eastern Turkey disputed the government's assertion that Armenian revolts had broken out, suggesting that the areas were "quiet until the deportations began." 

Germany's diplomatic mission was led by Ambassador Baron Hans Freiherr von Wangenheim (and later Count Paul Wolff Metternich). Like Morgenthau, von Wangenheim received many disturbing messages from consul officials around the Ottoman Empire. From the province of Adana, Consul Eugene Buge reported that the CUP chief had sworn to kill and massacre any Armenians who survived the deportation marches. In June 1915, von Wangenheim sent a cable to Berlin reporting that Talat had admitted the deportations were not "being carried out because of 'military considerations alone.'" One month later, he came to the conclusion that there "no longer was doubt that the Porte was trying to exterminate the Armenian race in the Turkish Empire." 

When Wolff-Metternich succeeded von Wangenheim, he continued to dispatch similar cables: "The Committee [CUP] demands the extirpation of the last remnants of the Armenians and the government must yield.... A Committee representative is assigned to each of the provincial administrations.... Turkification means license to expel, to kill or destroy everything that is not Turkish." 

German engineers and laborers involved in building the railway also witnessed Armenians being crammed into cattle cars and shipped along the railroad line. Franz Gunther, a representative for Deutsche Bank which was funding the construction of the Baghdad Railway, forwarded photographs to his directors and expressed his frustration at having to remain silent amid such "bestial cruelty".[95] Major General Otto von Lossow, acting military attaché and head of the German Military Plenipotentiary in the Ottoman Empire, spoke to Ottoman intentions in a conference held in Batum in 1918: 

The Turks have embarked upon the "total extermination of the Armenians in Transcaucasia... The aim of Turkish policy is, as I have reiterated, the taking of possession of Armenian districts and the extermination of the Armenians. Talaat's government wants to destroy all Armenians, not just in Turkey but also outside Turkey. On the basis of all the reports and news coming to me here in Tiflis there hardly can be any doubt that the Turks systematically are aiming at the extermination of the few hundred thousand Armenians whom they left alive until now 

Similarly, Major General Friedrich Freiherr Kress von Kressenstein noted that "The Turkish policy of causing starvation is an all too obvious proof... for the Turkish resolve to destroy the Armenians."Another notable figure in the German military camp was Max Erwin von Scheubner-Richter, who documented various massacres of Armenians. He sent fifteen reports regarding "deportations and mass killings" to Germany's chancellor in Berlin. His final report noted that fewer than 100,000 Armenians were left alive in the Ottoman Empire; the rest had been exterminated (German: ausgerottet). Scheubner-Richter also detailed the methods of the Ottoman government, noting its use of the Special Organization and other bureaucratized instruments of genocide. 

Some Germans openly supported the Ottoman policy against the Armenians. As Hans Humann, the German naval attaché in Constantinople said to U.S. Ambassador Henry Morgenthau: 

I have lived in Turkey the larger part of my life ... and I know the Armenians. I also know that both Armenians and Turks cannot live together in this country. One of these races has got to go. And I don't blame the Turks for what they are doing to the Armenians. I think that they are entirely justified. The weaker nation must succumb. The Armenians desire to dismember Turkey; they are against the Turks and the Germans in this war, and they therefore have no right to exist here. 

                                                                                                            – Hans Humann, Ambassador Morgenthau's Story 

In a genocide conference in 2001, professor Wolfgang Wipperman of the Free University of Berlin introduced documents evidencing that the German High Command was aware of the mass killings at the time but chose not to interfere or speak out. 

Russian military 

The Russian Empire's response to the bombardment of its Black Sea naval ports was primarily a land campaign through the Caucasus. Early victories against the Ottoman Empire from the winter of 1914 to the spring 1915 saw significant gains of territory, including relieving the Armenian bastion resisting in the city of Van in May 1915. The Russians also reported encountering the bodies of unarmed civilian Armenians in the areas they advanced through.In March 1916, the scenes they saw in the city of Erzerum led the Russians to retaliate against the Ottoman III Army whom they held responsible for the massacres, destroying it in its entirety. 

Swedish Embassy and Military Attaché 

Sweden, as a neutral state during the entire World War I, had permanent representatives in the Ottoman Empire, able to continiously report on the ongoing events in the country. The Swedish Embassy in Constantinople, represented by Ambassador Per Gustaf August Cosswa Anckarsvärd, along with Envoy M. Ahlgren, and the Swedish Military Attaché, Captain Einar af Wirsén, closely followed the development throughout the empire, reporting, among others, on the Armenian massacres. On July 7, 1915, Anckarsvärd dispatched a two page report to Stockholm, beginning with the following information: 

The persecutions of the Armenians have reached hair-raising proportions and all points to the fact that the Young Turks want to seize the opportunity, since due to different reasons there are no effective external pressure to be feared, to once and for all put an end to the Armenian question. The means for this are quite simple and consist of the extermination (utrotandet) of the Armenian nation. 
During the remaining of 1915 alone, Anckarsvärd dispatched six other reports entitled "The Persecutions of the Armenians". In his report on July 22, Anckarsvärd noted that the persecutions of the Armenians were being extended to encompass all Christians in the Ottoman Empire. Quoting the statement of the Greek chargé d'affaires: 

the deportations can not be any other issue than an annihilation war against the Greek nation in Turkey and as measures hereof they have been implementing forced conversions to Islam, in obvious aim to, that if after the end of the war there again would be a question of European intervention for the protection of the Christians, there will be as few of them left as possible. 

On August 9, 1915, Anckarsvärd dispatched yet another report, confirming his suspicions regarding the plans of the Turkish Government: 

It is obvious that the Turks are taking the opportunity to, now during the war, annihilate [utplåna] the Armenian nation so that when the peace comes no Armenian question longer exists." 

When reflecting upon the situation in Turkey during the final stages of the war, Envoy Alhgren presented an analysis of the prevailing situation in Turkey and the hard times which had befallen the population. In explaining the increased living costs he identified a number of reasons: "obstacles for domestic trade, the almost total paralysing of the foreign trade and finally the strong decreasing of labour power, caused partly by the mobilisation but partly also by the extermination of the Armenian race [utrotandet af den armeniska rasen]." 

Wirsén, when writing his memoirs from his mission to the Balkans and Turkey, Minnen från fred och krig (“Memories from Peace and War”), dedicated an entire chapter to the Armenian genocide, entitled Mordet på en nation (“The Murder of a Nation”). Commenting the deportations as a result of accusing the Armenians for collaboration with the Russians, Wirsén concludes that the subsequent deportations were nothing but a cover for the extermination: "Officially, these had the goal to move the entire Armenian population to the steppe regions of Northern Mesopotamia and Syria, but in reality they aimed to exterminate [utrota] the Armenians, whereby the pure Turkish element in Asia Minor would achieve a dominating position." 

In conclusion, Wirsén made the following note: "The annihilation of the Armenian nation in Asia Minor must revolt all human feelings...The way the Armenian problem was solved was hair-raising. I can still see in front of me Talaat’s cynical expression, when he emphasized that the Armenian question was solved." 

Aftermath 

Turkish courts-martial 
Main article: Turkish Courts-Martial of 1919-20 
In 1919, Sultan Mehmed VI ordered domestic courts-martial to try members of the Committee of Union and Progress (CUP) (Turkish: "Ittihat Terakki") for their role in taking the Ottoman Empire into World War I. The courts-martial blamed the members of CUP for pursuing a war that did not fit into the notion of Millet. The Armenian issue was used as a tool to punish the leaders of the CUP. Most of the documents generated in these courts were later moved to international trials. By January 1919, a report to Sultan Mehmed VI accused over 130 suspects, most of whom were high officials. The military court found that it was the will of the CUP to eliminate the Armenians physically, via its special organization. The 1919 pronouncement reads as follows: 

The Court Martial taking into consideration the above-named crimes declares, unanimously, the culpability as principal factors of these crimes the fugitives Talat Pasha, former Grand Vizir, Enver Efendi, former War Minister, struck off the register of the Imperial Army, Cemal Efendi, former Navy Minister, struck off too from the Imperial Army, and Dr. Nazim Efendi, former Minister of Education, members of the General Council of the Union &amp; Progress, representing the moral person of that party;... the Court Martial pronounces, in accordance with said stipulations of the Law the death penalty against Talat, Enver, Cemal, and Dr. Nazim. 

The term Three Pashas, which include Mehmed Talat Pasha and Ismail Enver, refers to the triumvirate who had fled the Empire at the end of World War I. At the trials in Constantinople in 1919 they were sentenced to death in absentia. The courts-martial officially disbanded the CUP and confiscated its assets, and the assets of those found guilty. At least two of the three were later assassinated by Armenian vigilantes. 

International trials 

Following the Mudros Armistice, the preliminary Peace Conference in Paris established "The Commission on Responsibilities and Sanctions" in January 1919, which was chaired by U.S. Secretary of State Lansing. Based on the commission's work, several articles were added to the Treaty of Sèvres, and the acting government of the Ottoman Empire, Sultan Mehmed VI and Damat Adil Ferit Pasha, were summoned to trial. The Treaty of Sèvres (August 1920) planned a trial to determine those responsible for the "barbarous and illegitimate methods of warfare... [including] offenses against the laws and customs of war and the principles of humanity". Article 230 of the Treaty of Sèvres required the Ottoman Empire "hand over to the Allied Powers the persons whose surrender may be required by the latter as being responsible for the massacres committed during the continuance of the state of war on territory which formed part of the Ottoman Empire on August 1, 1914." 

Various Ottoman politicians, generals, and intellectuals were transferred to Malta, where they were held for some three years while searches were made of archives in Constantinople, London, Paris and Washington to investigate their actions.However, the Inter-allied tribunal attempt demanded by the Treaty of Sèvres never solidified and the detainees were eventually returned to Turkey in exchange for British citizens held by Kemalist Turkey. 

Trial of Soghomon Tehlirian 

Grand Vizier Talat Pasha who was assassinated by Soghomon TehlirianOn March 15, 1921, former Grand Vizier Talat Pasha was assassinated in the Charlottenburg District of Berlin, Germany, in broad daylight and in the presence of many witnesses. Talat's death was part of "Operation Nemesis", the Armenian Revolutionary Federation's codename for their covert operation in the 1920s to kill the planners of the Armenian Genocide. 

The subsequent trial of the assassin, Soghomon Tehlirian, had an important influence on Raphael Lemkin, a lawyer of Polish-Jewish descent who campaigned in the League of Nations to ban what he called "barbarity" and "vandalism", and, in 1943, coined the word genocide. 

Armenian deaths, 1914 to 1918 

While there is no consensus as to how many Armenians lost their lives during the Armenian Genocide, there is general agreement among western scholars that over 500,000 Armenians died between 1914 and 1918. Estimates vary between 300,000 (per the modern Turkish state) to 1,500,000 (per modern Armenia, Argentina,and other states). Encyclopædia Britannica references the research of Arnold J. Toynbee, an intelligence officer of the British Foreign Office, who estimated that 600,000 Armenians "died or were massacred during deportation" in the years 1915–1916. 

Memorials 

Over 135 memorials, spread across 25 countries, commemorate the Armenian Genocide. 

In 1965, the 50th anniversary of the genocide, a 24-hour mass protest was initiated in Yerevan emanding recognition of the Armenian Genocide by Soviet authorities. The memorial was completed two years later, at Tsitsernakaberd above the Hrazdan gorge in Yerevan. The 44 metres (140 ft) stele symbolizes the national rebirth of Armenians. Twelve slabs are positioned in a circle, representing 12 lost provinces in present day Turkey. At the center of the circle there is an eternal flame. Each April 24, hundreds of thousands of people walk to the genocide monument and lay flowers around the eternal flame. 

Another memorial, at Alfortville, Paris, was bombed on May 3, 1984, by a hit-team headed by Grey Wolves member Abdullah Catli and paid by the Turkish intelligence agency (MİT) 

Other interesting websites about The Armenian Genocide: 

http://genocide-museum.am/eng/ 
http://www.armenian-genocide.org/ 
http://www.teachgenocide.org/ 
http://www.armenian-history.com/Nyuter/HISTORY/ARMENIA20/armenian_genocide.htm 

Genocide-museum.am 
Armenian-genocide 
Teachgenocide 
Armenian-history 

Source: 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Armenian_Genocide﻿

Meer lezen (893 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-qCQ0Bup_dQU/U1g-xoJSf7I/AAAAAAAAA2E/NgkPUmdLZhY/w426-h322/Armenian_Genocide_16.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/105638737223007338699/albums/5992316073553081329/5992316042215404610</link><title>Ooooh I did a handstand right for the first time since I turned 9 :) but then I fell and curled up on the floor and laughed for an hour 
Hey hey guyssss can you help me come up with a topic for a social studies project? Or not? I want to do the Cold War because I love the way the countries were like "hey I still hate you but no more war hmm? k" or any war except Civil (even though the death rate is like wow project worthy I'm a bad person oops) because my teacher suggested that already and I don't want to be a copycat. But what part of the war like the influence? Or the causes? Or something please help!!! 
I used too much punctuation and I hate when people do that it's annoying and that's exactly why I did it GETTING YOUR ATTENTION IN THE WORST WAY HELP ME PLEASE﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_ZO-tUj6I7k/Uyj7sRYftEI/AAAAAAAAaR8/ePavso7q5rQ/w426-h237/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/103333429938529668020/albums/5983504595613814401/5983504601501344658</link><title>WarGames 

Has anyone else watched this for, oh, say, 100 times? It's one of the ultimate movies for geeks. Pure joy with this film! 

"Shall We Play a Game?" 

WarGames is a 1983 American Cold War science-fiction film written by Lawrence Lasker and Walter F. Parkes and directed by John Badham. The film stars Matthew Broderick, Dabney Coleman, John Wood, and Ally Sheedy. 

The film follows David Lightman (Broderick), a young hacker who unwittingly accesses WOPR, a United States military supercomputer programmed to predict possible outcomes of nuclear war. Lightman gets WOPR to run a nuclear war simulation, originally believing it to be a computer game. The simulation causes a national nuclear missile scare and nearly starts World War III. 

Favorite quotes from the film? 

#wargames   #matthewbroderick   #geek   #classicfilm   #g33k #globalthermonuclearwar 

via/ http://www.hark.com/clips/rptftxrwmn-shall-we-play-a-game 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WarGames﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-1J5ZGx-uqsU/Uwmtu6xnI5I/AAAAAAABnR4/niFGJgDO4Sk/w426-h237/original.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/102667755095811918645/albums/5978383536559047201/5978383545201069570</link><title>In the early 1900s, Yellowstone's administration declared war on wolves and coyotes. In addition to shooting and trapping, officials resorted to biological warfare and introduced into Yellowstone a parasitic mite that causes mange. Mange leads to fur loss and that can lead to a slow and painful death due to the ravages of winter. 

The coyote pictured here has mange--is another victim of that introduction a century ago. Mary and I met him as we skied the Blacktail Deer Plateau road. The groomed surface is perfect for cross country skiers or for a coyote with mange that wants to travel without getting snowy and cold. 

The coyote was coming towards us and saw us, but made no move to avoid us. To give him room, Mary and I stepped off the road and sunk into knee-deep snow. The coyote, head down, padded by. Its tail devoid of fur looked like a rat's tail. Its rear legs were streaked with blood from incessant scratching. Mary and I stood silent, our breath billowing in the cold, almost feeling the coyote's pain. 

My new best-selling book has two chapters about coyotes--one recounts how these intelligent little survivors won the war against them. To "Look Inside" or buy the book: 
http://amzn.to/Jpea9Q﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-snBeyLY2hRc/Uvd8KNbADgI/AAAAAAAABDk/RJtuhrZYyuw/w426-h359/coyote%2Bw%2Bmange.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/118189369395446106037/albums/5782011064378416577/5782011062146296242</link><title>It's been only 70 years since World War II, and the mad scientists from companies like I.G. Farben, BASF, Hoechst, Dow and Bayer, who created the gas chambers and tested dangerous vaccines on innocent Jews, didn't just go away. In fact, they went to work for U.S. corporations and pharmaceutical companies that run the vaccine industry today. At least a dozen of these cold blooded killers were hired fresh out of prison, just 4 to 7 years after the Nuremberg trials found them guilty of mass murder and enslavement. (http://frank.mtsu.edu/~baustin/trials3.html) 

In fact, at the close of WWII, the IG Farben building in Frankfort was protected from allied bombings by the highest levels of military command. Why? IG Farben was the FDA/CDC type of "pharmaceutical arm" of Hitler's 4th Reich, and the Rockefellers had a financial interest in maintaining and controlling this pharmaceutical empire, which would soon be catapulted on U.S. soil. Research reveals that Hitler also invested heavily in Merck and other pharmaceutical companies. 

Nazi convicted mass murderers became executives for major U.S. chemical and pharmaceutical companies 

Fritz ter Meer, found guilty of slavery and mass murder at Auschwitz, served only seven years in prison and became Chairman of the Board at Bayer in 1956. Still trust U.S. vaccines? 

Carl Krauch, Executive Member of IG Farben and Head of Military Economics for Hitler, found guilty of slavery and mass murder, served just 6 years in prison, then became Chairman of the Board for BASF in 1952. Still want to get those flu shots? How about that HPV shot for your daughter or son? 

This is the same vaccine industry today which protected and employed Nazi war criminals. The very industry that produced the Nazi gas chambers was purchased by Bayer. So, exactly whom are you trusting with your children's health and welfare? 

Currently, the U.S. Government and the CDC rely solely on the manufacturers of vaccines to report problems, injuries and deaths. This atrocity is like letting murderers be their own judges in court! Where are the checks and balances this country was founded upon? Vaccines have economic and political agendas now, and the FDA does absolutely no testing of their own before making decisions to release vaccines to the masses. 

Want more research before you or your child get injected with a new concocted disease for which there is no cure? Listen to stunning admissions by vaccine industry experts, including Dr. Maurice Hilleman (formerly w/Merck), who admitted to the deadly nature of the most trusted vaccines. (http://www.naturalnews.com/033584_Dr_Maurice_Hilleman_SV40.html) 

Today's vaccines not only contain live versions of the diseases you DO NOT WANT, but also contain GMOs, hormones from infected cows, pigs, chickens and monkeys, untested virus combinations (like H1N1), aluminum, mercury, emulsifiers, and crossbred bacteria from animals, mosquitoes, and diseased humans: 

Measles Live Virus Vaccine: (Attenuvax) Made by Merck. Two injections are given; one at 1 year and another at 4 years old. Contains gelatin, sorbitol, sodium chloride, bovine cow serum, egg protein and human albumin. 

Measles and Mumps Live Virus Vaccine: (M-M-Rvax) Made by Merck. Injected into one year old babies. Contains gelatin, sorbitol, sodium chloride, bovine cow serum, and human albumin. 

Diptheria, Tetanus and Polio Vaccine: Five injections given between 2 and 6 years of age, plus boosters "recommended" every 10 years. Contains formaldehyde, phenoxyethanol and aluminum phosphate. 

DTaP, IPV, HBV and Hib*: (Diphtheria, tetanus, polio, hepatitis B and Haemophilus influenza type B) Given to infants 2 to 12 months with boosters less than a year later. Contains aluminum hydroxide, formaldehyde, and bovine cow serum. 

Gardasil HPV: Human Papillomavirus Vaccine Made by Merck. "Recommended" 3 intramuscular injections; given at birth, 2 and 6 months of age. Re-administered to children as young as 9 years of age for a rare sexually transmitted disease. Contains polysorbate 80, sodium chloride, aluminum, and a "denatured" (fragmented and weakened) form of the virus. 

Toxic vaccine ingredients and their adverse effects: 

• Bovine cow serum: Extracted from cow skin. When injected causes connective tissue disorders, arthritis and lupus; also shortness of breath, low blood pressure, chest pain and skin reactions. 

• Sorbitol: Synthetic sweetener which metabolizes very slowly and aggravates IBS and gastrointestinal issues. 

• Gelatin: Derived from the collagen inside animals' skin and bones. Injecting gelatin poses the risk of infection from synthetic growth hormones and BSE infectivity (mad cow disease). 

• Sodium chloride: Raises blood pressure and inhibits muscle contraction and growth. 

• Egg protein: Vaccines are prepared in eggs (certainly not organic). May contain growth hormones, antibiotics, and salmonella bacteria. 

• Thimerosal: A neurotoxic mercury which causes autism: There are 25 mcg in one average flu vaccine, and the EPA safety limit is 5 micrograms, so children who are vaccinated simultaneously with multiple* vaccines receive over 10 times the safety limit of mercury in one day. 

• Human albumin: The protein portion of blood from pooled human venous plasma; when injected causes fever, chills, hives, rash, headache, nausea, breathing difficulty, and rapid heart rate. Injecting "pooled blood" can result in a loss of body cell mass and cause immunodeficiency virus infection, or contain SV40, AIDS, cancer or Hepatitis B from drug addicts. 

• Formaldehyde: Highly carcinogenic fluid used to embalm corpses. Ranked one of the most hazardous compounds to human health; can cause liver damage, gastrointestinal issues, reproductive deformation, respiratory distress and cancer. Plus, formaldehyde has been known to fail to deactivate the virus the vaccine is intended to cure, thus enabling a live virus to enter your blood and infect your system. 

• Phenoxyethanol: A glycol ether/chemical; highly toxic to the nervous system, kidneys, and liver. The FDA warns "can cause shut down of the central nervous system (CNS), vomiting and contact dermatitis" in cosmetics; imagine when injected into your blood. 

• Aluminum phosphate: Greatly increases toxicity of mercury, so caution about minimum mercury tolerance is therefore severely underestimated. CDC scientists and all doctors are well aware of this. 

• MSG (monosodium glutamate): When injected becomes a neurotoxin, causing CNS disorders and brain damage in children. 

If you especially enjoy being lied to, visit vaccinateyourbaby.org, where they tell you formaldehyde is safe because it is "present in the environment and is a byproduct of metabolism, so it is already present in the human body." They also inform you that aluminum is good for you, because "[a]luminum is also commonly found in food, water, infant formula and even breast milk." Hey, if it's in the environment, it must be safe to inject into your veins (so why not use snake venom, bleach, and plutonium?). 

Want the ultimate alternative to vaccines that prevents disease? Buy organic vitamins, minerals, antioxidants, amino acids, and enzymes! (Dr. Joel Wallach - The Best of Dead Doctors Don't Lie) 

Sources for this article include: 

http://www.naturalnews.com/033584_Dr_Maurice_Hilleman_SV40.html 

http://vaxtruth.org/ 

Dr. Joel Wallach - The Best of Dead Doctors Don't Lie 

http://frank.mtsu.edu/~baustin/trials3.html 

http://www.novaccine.com/vaccine-ineffectiveness/ 

http://www.novaccine.com/pdffiles/gardasil_information_HPV.pdf 

http://www.vaccinesafety.edu/components-MMR.htm 

http://www.fda.gov/cber/efoi/approve.htm 

http://www.tetrahedron.org/ 

http://www.supernutrient.com/articles/fibromyalgia/taf.html 

http://www.whale.to/b/nazi_allopathy.html 

http://www.vaccinateyourbaby.org/about/ingredients.cfm 

http://heinonline.org/ 

http://www.earthclinic.com/CURES/mad_cow.html 

Learn more: http://www.naturalnews.com/035431_vaccine_ingredients_side_effects_MSG.html#ixzz24sf4x8i8 — with Charles William O'Connor, Oswaldo Rodriguez, Kristin Dawn Ribbans, Aaron Adams, Jared Sacco, Jeremiah Forman and Fred Lawson.﻿

Meer lezen (182 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MOAKUY9AXnI/UD3UbTab6bI/AAAAAAAAArg/2gk9OPtzqyo/w426-h511/66D348A0-817C-413F-8B18-1174A13CE95E.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/117148843313168230209/albums/5842968684888144481/5842968689863204914?authkey=CM_bzPPP6uTVbw</link><title>#NDAA 2012 ‏@NDAA2012 
Yup, There're no accidents, only causes. I served 1981-86 during the Cold War, imagine my shock when OBL was named. pic.twitter.com/DCs7oTzM﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-X1nCwCcuyns/URZlEOkGoDI/AAAAAAAAA9g/F4MF9WqvQho/w426-h318/OBL-Hero-what-93.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7307-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/causes%20of%20the%20cold%20war/photos/111190792066661220034/albums/6004161966751890993/6004161965510579442?sqi=104191988121507435081&amp;sqsi=544704b7-5e28-4e4f-80af-1d9ce5451ef1</link><title>2008 The Iran Symbol, The Falsifiers and the Republican Prophecy 
LayDayWatchers 

The May 15th Prophecy like a lone voice in the wilderness have been telling you the Beast would rise up from Iran before transferring his seat of power to Iraq, and there would be no European Roman Empire or Gog and Magog happening, because the False Prophets have prophesied things unto you that are False, Fallacious and Fictitious. 

However God is manifesting the truth of the May 15th Prophecy 

Ahmadinejad's visit to Iraq is the first ever by an Iranian president since the end of the bloody war in the 1980s between the two coutnries that left one million people dead 
Iraq and Iran having been deadly enemies, and (Ahmadinejad's visit) shows they have turned a page," said Rand Corp. analyst and former U.S. diplomat James Dobbins.Iraq's Shiite power bases — both in top posts and on the streets — will be the most closely watched barometers for any possible changes following the visit. 

Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki, a Shiite, and President Jalal Talabani, a Kurd, may now have a more direct pipeline to Tehran for dialogue on Shiite trouble spots. 

LastDayWatchers this is the type of information you need to focus on because it revels how God is working the nations, by allowing Satan to establish his Son Kingdom; to fulfill his Word in scripture 

There came up among them another little horn, before whom there were three of the first horns plucked up buy the roots. 

The May 15th Prophecy have been saying what the Prophets of old have been saying about Iran coming to power to dominate from Iraq take a look at this video because it give a glimpse and foreshadow of what the May 15th Prophecy have already prophesied about. 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eEEvhilOZ8c 

When you have the power you don't need to come under the cover of darkness as the Iranian President pointed out all to well! 

Ahmadinejad: US power crippling in Iraq 

Unlike Bush's trips to Iraq, Ahmadinejad announced his journey in advance, drove in a motorcade down Baghdad's airport road_ once known as "The Highway of Death 

The visits should be declared and open. And all those who come on stealth visits, we should ask them why they visit this country in a stealth manner?" Ahmadinejad 

This is another hint or example that shows the failure of the "surge" 

A head of state is a symbol of a nation power, the Iranian President visit proves the United States power hold on Iraq is so tenuous their own head of state had to come under the cover of darkness and theirs officials wearing helmets and flat jackets! 

Speaking Of symbols LastDayWatchers did you notice the Iranian symbol?, how many of you know that much of God's Word is better understood by symbols, which is why God uses symbols and symbolism. 

Satan is no stranger to the use of symbols and the important thereof, which is why you see nations throughout history good or bad use symbolism to portray their ideology, advance their cause and promote their culture and systems. 

Take for instance one of the most powerful symbolism of the Cold War and ultimate fall of Communism was made by U.S. President Ronald Reagan. 

With his speech in front of the Berlin Wall he uttered forth the famous word "Tear Down This Wall", the Berlin Wall which symbolized the smothering entrapment of communism and the division between democracy and communism. 

The symbol of a democratic head of state to go inside another nation (Germany) who stood at the heart of the cold war divide; to advance the cause for democracy was profound,  it goes without saying that the Berlin Wall came crumbling down AFTER that symbol was made. 

Anyone doing a historical documentary on Ronald Reagan would have done a piss poor job if they didn't included this moment. 

TEAR DOWN THE WALL 

The same is true of the historic visit of Iran President to Iraq, it has been played down in the West because of propaganda that is being used in the false "war on terror". 

However spiritually, historical and biblical LastDayWatchers it is of enormous important, with this scriptural and "facts on the ground" symbolism; is more proof of God keeping his word to Abraham, Isaac and Jacob by reason of the Prophets especially Habakkuk and Daniel. 

Did not the May 15th Prophecy tell you back on 06-13-07 in the post titled 
(See:The Beast, The Anti-Christ and The Little Horn (The Hidden Iman) 

Iraq by reason of the coming up among the bear position of Iran. 

Is none other then that same demon-spirit through the Uammah; which has been taken over by the same spirit that possessed Alexander the Great, is now in the deception in the form of the Hidden Imam. 

Also remember I warn back on 07-03-07 in the post titled 
(See:Iran and The 3 Horns, No European Roman Revival) 

But Iran is “up among them” horn" Daniel 7:8 

Iran is “The other which came up, and before whom three fell" Daniel 7:20 

Iran is the bear with “three rib in it month between the teeth of it" Daniel 7:5 

Iran is “behold there shall stand up yet three king in Persia" Daniel 11:2 

Iran is the “Then shall stand up in his estate a raiser of taxes in the 
glory of the kingdom” Daniel 11:20 

That a description of the monarchy rule of Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran 

He shall be destroyed, neither in anger nor in battle” Daniel 11:20 

That a description of his fall to the revolution led by Ayatollah Khomeini to replace the monarchy with a Islamic Republic controlled by the mullahs. 

It is that religious mullah government rule that Daniel is referring to when he says 
And in his estate shall stand up a vile person, that vile person is the Anti-Christ 

Just like he did with Alexander the Great he will do with Anti-Christ by starting off in one place before moving his capital and headquarters to Iraq. 
Also back on 07-12-07 in the post titled(See:Iran-Iraq and the 10 who give power to the Hidden Imam) 

The May 15 Prophecy pointed you to the fact that Iran from it “bear” feet position noted in Revelation 13:2" 

And his feet were as the feet of a bear 

Would rise up and strike with its paws 3 nations that are part of the 10-horn kingdom which are Horn-Rib #1 Iraq" 

LastDayWatchers can you see how correct the May 15th Prophecy have been because it is the truth of God Word, equally can you also see how false and fallacious a Gog and Magog (which Iraq have no part of) is full of lies repeated by the false prophets 

(See:May 15th chronicle, the Armenian Genocide and Woe to the False Prophets) 

Do you actually think that U.N General Secretary Ban Ki Moon is leading a conspiracy to unite a European Union to bring down Israel? (lol), if so how can we "Watch" such action?, can you see how absurd God's Word get treated by these false prophets? 

(See:The Fire Starter, The Perfect Position and The Ominous Reminder) 

The May 15th Prophecy ask you to read the book of Lamentations, if you did your homework you would know that Lamentations is the voice of Israel (The House of Judah) during the Great Tribulation, it describes the characteristics of these false prophets relationship to them. 

Thy prophets have seen vain and foolish things for thee 
The Septuagint translate it 

Thy Prophets saw vanities and follies for thee 
The Bible an American translation (J.M.Powis Smith and Edgar Goodspeed) translate it 

Your Prophets have divined for you stuff and nonsense 
The living Bible Paraphrased (Kenneth Taylor) translate it 

Your Prophets have said so many foolish things, false to the core 
The New English Bible translate it 

The vision that your prophets saw for you were false and painted sham 

LastDayWatchers it will be the Spirit of Iniquity that will possess the False Prophet and the spirit of the Son of Satan will posses Anti-Christ and these two in unison will deceive the worlds 

The May 15th Prophecy will go into more detail of the difference of these two entity and will show you exactly who the False Prophet is just as I shown you who the Beast is in future post. 

But now I want to know that the Spirit of Iniquity who the May 15th Prophecy have shown is the working force behind the Ummah 
(See:Ummah and Shadows of the Uprooting) 

The spirit is not limited to the activity of the Ummah put is also the primary and driving force behind the Religious Right Conservatism. 

You can discern them by their lies and false since of support for Israel (the House of Judah). 

They will tell you things like Judah is surrounded by "Islamic Fascists” that why you must stand against this evil. (Hint: support war on terror) 

They will tell you Israel is good, and "Radical Islam" is bad, and God is on the side of Israel. 

That why they preach the false doctrine of Gog and Magog to promote the idea that God is going to wipe out Iran and Russia while still leaving Israel standing. (Hint: the war on terror will achieve victory over Islamic fascism) 

Then they tell Israel itchy ear that Islam will be defeated and their only worry is a "European" Rome empire but that threat is far in the future, they do this all in the name of "Patriotism" to win the false "war on terror" 

Thus saith the Word of God  "All who preach this false doctrine shall drink the water of gall" 

The real truth of God's Word is in the May 15th Prophecy which have already declared unto you that Israel (the house of Judah) will be overran and plunder by the kingdom of the Beast they will utterly lose the "war on terror" 

The continuation of the Lamentation 2:14 verse declare the difference between the May 15th Prophecy and the falsifying false prophets (Hal Lindsey, John Woolvard, Tim LeHaye, John Hagee , Jack Van Empee and Joel Rosenberg, Benny Hin...est.) just to name a few. 

Listen to what Lamentation have to say about these false prophet who scratch the ear of Israel (the House of Judah) 

They have not discovered thine iniquity, to turn away thy captivity; but have seen for thee false burdens and causes of banishment. 

The New International Version translate it 

They did not expose your sin, to ward off your captivity. The oracles they gave you were false and misleading 

The New Living Translation Tyndale Charitable Trust translate it 
They did not try to hold you back from exile by pointing out your sins. Instead, they painted false pictures, filling you with false hope. 

The Jerusalem Bible translate it 
They never pointed out your sin to ward off your exile, the visions they proffered you were false, fallacious, misleading 

And the American bible (Kenneth Taylor) translate it best 
They have not tried to hold you back from slavery by pointing out your sins, they lied and said all was well 

There you have it LastDayWatchers now you see why the hypercritical bastards preach a Gog and Magog and European Rome to sell you painted shams and raise money for support of Israel (the House of Judah) 

However the May 15th Prophecy declares what will shortly occur with 100% accuracy, you LastDayWatchers already know that God has cursed the United States (the House of Manasseh) by reason of George W Bush. 

The Lord of Host has cursed him, his household (including his political house affiliation), the White House and the entire Nation. 

Thus saith the Word of Gods 

There will be no peace for the house of Judah, only violence during your Administration as a testimony against you 

Your political house will suffer defeat as a testimony against thine unclean hands, they will suffer defeat in the House, they will suffer defeat in the Senate 

And because John McCain has embraced thine unclean hands he will be utterly defeated a testimony against you 

Before you democrats get to giddy let the May 15th Prophecy also remind you that the Lord of Host curse is still in affect which says from Gods own mouth 

You shall be only oppressed and plundered continually, and no one shall save you. 

Until we blog again "watch" more proof of the 100% accuracy of the May 15th Prophecy about the dark cloud that is brewing over Lebanon. 

USS Cole 'ordered to position off Lebanese coast' 

BEIRUT: A US Navy warship has been ordered to take up station off Lebanon's coast as a "show of support" as the standoff between Prime Minister Fouad Siniora's government and the opposition continues 

Lebanon: What are they waiting for? 

It's just time-wasting until a war happens," said Amal Saad- Ghorayeb, a Hezbollah expert at the Carnegie Endowment Middle East Centre in Beirut. 

There's a regional war coming and things are going to change dramatically." A meeting at the weekend between Mubarak and King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia appeared calculated to up the pressure on Syria and show a united front. 

Posted 10th March 2008 by Leon Davis  http://lastdaywatchers.blogspot.com/2008/03/iran-symbol-falsifiers-and-republican.html﻿

Meer lezen (327 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7307_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-d1-cKpmPZsU/U1MRfwgrVPI/AAAAAAAAPTU/C5Yz7KMalvY/w426-h320/h%26m.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>