<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7320">cayenne pepper plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:26:11" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/101695584591678584936/albums/5807007507728229121/5807007509815361026</link><title>Put a little spice in your life! 

The cayenne pepper, or Capiscum annum, derives its proper name from a Greek word meaning “to bite,” a clear allusion to the pungent properties of the plant and its seeds. However, it’s the many medicinal benefits of cayenne pepper that earned it the nickname “The King of Herbs”. 

Read more: http://undergroundhealthreporter.com/benefits-of-cayenne-pepper-for-your-health#ixzz2BH6tFe00 

#naturalremedies   #healthyliving   #pepper  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-5dNCgty5bUM/UJaikDaR_gI/AAAAAAAAAfU/f0bPOxGcnr4/w426-h283/cayennepepper.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/115156430764417129923/albums/5941465436885824401/5941465435513406082</link><title>For Details: http://plantcaretoday.com/amazing-healing-powers-of-cayenne-pepper.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SMRG7kAPsXs/UnRTVZkJwoI/AAAAAAAARp8/XN3yPpNx3TM/w426-h319/3ADkM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/106702324621449002266/albums/5988915463732323297/5988915462888243250</link><title>Potato Cat in Cayenne Mushroom Pepper Cream Sausage Sauce 

Sunlight is not edible directly, but through the deliciousness of plants and the animals that eat them. 

Eating is the fuel that keeps us alive. Water maintains our balance with the cosmos, but the reactions from a billion-year-old-fusion-plant are what truly allow us to keep existing 

#spacepriest   is a real thing, at least on the Internet.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2yJh90_9rsg/Uxzm4gNMQDI/AAAAAAAAloo/v44s-vF_LB0/w426-h282/DSC_4725%255B1%255D.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/114171292862435225130/albums/5868215464041702609/5868215462355131554?authkey=CNTHyPeA5-feAQ&amp;sqi=111369486666269185136&amp;sqsi=e8b1743e-be16-49dc-be6e-c1409bd863a1</link><title>The Cayenne Peppers in my Vertigro Stacks are setting on and growing so fast!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Yw1IgmdbyMo/UXAW3zMh3KI/AAAAAAAABcI/ucMRfLd0GwU/w426-h568/CayennePeppers4-18.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/112756859469531650254/albums/5692793595192720593/5748767297063364146</link><title>Day 152of my 366Project for 2012: 

I swear, "It's like wash, rinse, repeat" when it comes to my finding these Lil' buggers on my garden plants... this one just happened to be on my Cayenne Pepper marker. However, I was being continuously pelted by grasshoppers and leafhoppers while working in the garden this morning into the afternoon. 

They are cute, but omg they seriously need to go elsewhere. (: 

#366SPR2012 #UnearthedFotografi #creative366project #G+365project #sooc #leafhopper #grasshopper﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-YLTYBHQ76k8/T8e5Zf3YJjI/AAAAAAAAExI/-orCo1Bf28A/w426-h638/152_31May2012_G%252B_UnearthedFotografi.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/112785334848925353945/albums/5740867993602789281/5740867993423214802</link><title>We will have some new items this Saturday, May 12, at Farmers Market in downtown McMinnville. New items will include petunias in hanging baskets and potted aloe vera. As usual we will have a nice selection of pepper plants as well as dried peppers for use in your cooking. 

Dried Cayenne (aka Chili Arbol or Red Pepper) 
These are the thin red peppers your grandma used to have hanging in the kitchen on a string of thread. They are also the crushed pepper you see at pizza restaurants to give your pizza an extra kick. 

I always have some on hand for cooking. Just drop one into your pot of chili or soup. Crush one up to add to your spicy recipes, or just sprinkle onto omelets, casseroles, mashed potatoes or any dip to eat with tortillas. Yum! 

Come on down this Saturday to get fixed up for Mother's Day!﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-SUEricIDxqY/T6upBgpmeNI/AAAAAAAAASs/xaSoBxmwucE/w426-h320/chili%2Bcayenne%2Bdried.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/114850458271885487101/albums/5929793093636436433/5929793090621134674</link><title>Brought my plants in for the winter. Still have several different types of peppers ripening and they should do well indoors. Peppers still going are tabasco, red marconi, cubanelle, jalapeno, kung pao, cajun bell and cayenne.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-mboiH99nYtU/UkrbZgYJ11I/AAAAAAAACic/o1FIvPQD05g/w426-h320/IMG_20130930_221500.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/117011250208698355705/albums/6004215204680831521/6004215201650111698?sqi=109797356189435459567&amp;sqsi=b9d7d06e-2707-4bc7-b1ad-4eba043c040e</link><title>The tomato and pepper seedlings I ordered from Burpee have arrived! Varieties include: 

Amish Paste Tomato 
Baby Boomer Cherry Tomato 
Hot Cheyenne (Cayenne Pepper) 
Big Guy Jalapeno (x2 plants) 
Sweet California Wonder Bell Pepper 

Weather permitting, these will all be planted in the garden within the next 48 hours.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-spy0w-qS9i0/U1NB6gla9NI/AAAAAAAAAxA/jvn2KjiCYqU/w426-h320/2014-04-19%2B21.35.30.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/109336424142741953770/albums/5853446962629418545/5853446960175037090?authkey=CKmQv-r9wuzNdw</link><title>soon all these tiny plants will be vibrant and flourishing again. pictured are bell peppers, jalapeno peppers, sweet banana peppers, carrots, strawberries,white seedless grapes, cayenne peppers, and four seedlings for sweet snap peas. and a few florals sago palm , ponytail palm and whatnot, i may add yellow squash cucumber and eggplant next weekend, and possibly collards, broccoli, and romaine.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4elDrAmXSFs/UTue_1TSuqI/AAAAAAAACS0/9fXXDfydD3A/w426-h318/DSCF0059.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7320-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cayenne%20pepper%20plants/photos/117433248989819064267/albums/5993798699945234241/5993798699395623554</link><title>25 Helpful Tips: 

1\. Take your bananas apart when you get home from the store. If you leave them connected at the stem, they ripen faster.. I didn't know that! 

2\. Store your opened chunks of cheese in aluminum foil. It will stay fresh much longer and not mold! 

3\. Peppers with 3 bumps on the bottom are sweeter and better for eating. Peppers with 4 bumps on the bottom are firmer and better for cooking. 

4\. Add a teaspoon of water when frying ground beef. It will help pull the grease away from the meat while cooking. 

5\. To make scrambled eggs or omelets rich add a couple of spoonfuls of sour cream, cream cheese, or heavy cream in and then beat them up. 

6\. Add garlic immediately to a recipe if you want a light taste of garlic, and at the end of the recipe if you want a stronger taste of garlic. 

7\. Reheat Pizza Heat up leftover pizza in a nonstick skillet on top of the stove, set heat to med-low and heat till warm. This keeps the crust crispy. No soggy micro pizza. I saw this on the cooking channel and it really works. 

8\. Easy Deviled Eggs: Put cooked egg yolks in a zip lock bag. Seal, mash till they are all broken up. Add remainder of ingredients, reseal, keep mashing it up mixing thoroughly, cut the tip of the baggy, squeeze mixture into egg. Just throw bag away when done easy clean up. 

9\. Expanding Frosting: When you buy a container of cake frosting from the store, whip it with your mixer for a few minutes. You can double it in size. You get to frost more cake/cupcakes with the same amount. You also eat less sugar and calories per serving. 

10\. Reheating refrigerated bread: To warm biscuits, pancakes, or muffins that were refrigerated, place them in a microwave with a cup of water. The increased moisture will keep the food moist and help it reheat faster. 

11\. Newspaper weeds away: Plant your plants in the ground, work the nutrients in your soil. Then wet newspapers, put layers around the plants overlapping as you go, cover with mulch, and forget about weeds. Weeds will get through some gardening plastic they will not get through wet newspapers. 

12\. To keep squirrels from eating your plants, sprinkle your plants with cayenne pepper. The cayenne pepper doesn't hurt the plant and the squirrels won't come near it. 

13\. Flexible vacuum: To get something out of a heat register or under the fridge add an empty paper towel roll or empty gift wrap roll to your vacuum. It can be bent or flattened to get in narrow openings. 

Click here for the rest: http://buff.ly/1l0QmJZ﻿

Meer lezen (55 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7320_11_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-6tmk6BBrioM/Uy5AKRysqoI/AAAAAAAAEDo/b4yLCXP_2Iw/w426-h237/905bf3c9-821a-4110-9f64-1b7d2b6f86e7</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>