<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:49:03" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/101364458217110170867/albums/6005213058877805745/6005213067636625954</link><title>"A Swell New View: Satellites Can Monitor Volcanoes" 

+Inside Science: "Predicting when a volcano will blow its top takes constant monitoring. Researchers are now looking to satellites as a valuable eye in the sky, since they can observe the ground around volcanoes for signs of deformation." 

"Ground deformation can indicate that molten rock, or magma, is flowing. This sometimes hints at an eruption to come -- but it's not a sure sign." 

"Just because we detect deformation at a volcano, it doesn't mean that eruption is imminent," said Susanna Ebmeier, an earth scientist at the University of Bristol, in the U.K. "Lots of different processes can cause that." 

"Even if the deformation is caused by magma, it doesn't provide an exact eruption time. The magma can accumulate slowly underground, remaining dormant for years before the volcano finally explodes." 

"To clarify the link between deformation and eruption, researchers looked at 18 years' worth of satellite data." ... 

via: http://www.insidescience.org/content/swell-new-view-satellites-can-monitor-volcanoes/1615 

Image credit: NASA Goddard Photo and Video via flickr | http://bit.ly/1qKreHg 
Rights information: http://bit.ly/cGotEb 

#volcanoes   #satellite  ﻿

Meer lezen (27 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-HcKZ5t0U3SQ/U1bNd9ED0iI/AAAAAAAAPxE/F62_44wQZic/w426-h237/volcano1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/111480413428119678209/albums/5649876178060765585/5649876184252449890</link><title>Erupting volcanoes photographed from space 
An image taken by astronauts aboard the International Space Station (ISS) of a large plume of smoke, steam and ash erupting from the Sarychev volcano on the Kuril Islands, Russia. It is thought that the eruption has caused a hole to form in the cloud layer above it.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_02_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4lmNZJA-Z3o/TmhkdItOhGI/AAAAAAAAKu4/4MzixY0Aju8/w426-h427/Screen%2BShot%2B2011-09-07%2Bat%2B11.44.27%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/114025394629117977284/albums/5989626549472815601/5989626547292128370</link><title>Researchers Found Why Volcanoes Scream Before Eruption. Read more: http://ttj.pw/1ke4nRt﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-oytfAZUVei4/Ux9tnECYxHI/AAAAAAAAOxM/j3qraPUdc58/w426-h283/38fec845-aa56-41ef-82d8-26bf762bdc76</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/113507009175485747967/albums/5815856995734365281/5815856997616437394</link><title>Image: Karymsky Volcanic Eruption on the Kamchatka Peninsula As Seen From The Space Station 

An eruption plume from the Karymsky volcano on the Kamchatka Peninsula in the Russian Federation is visible in this image photographed by an Expedition 33 crew member on the International Space Station. The Karymsky stratovolcano stands 1,536 meters above sea level, with most eruptions and occasional lava flows originating from the summit. Karymsky is the most active of Kamchatka's eastern volcanoes, with almost constant (on a geologic time scale) volcanism occurring since at least the late 18th century when the historical record for the region begins. In light of the high levels of volcanic activity on the Kamchatka Peninsula, the Kamchatka Volcanic Eruption Response Team (KVERT) monitors the activity levels of several volcanoes and issues updates including aviation alerts and webcams. 

KVERT reported moderate seismic activity at Karymsky during 2-9 Nov. 2012; such activity can indicate movement of magma beneath or within a volcanic structure and can indicate that an eruption is imminent. The Tokyo Volcanic Ash Advisory Center (VAAC) subsequently reported an explosive eruption at Karymsky on Nov. 9, 2012 at 22:15 GMT. This photograph of the resulting ash plume was taken approximately one hour and 35 minutes after the eruption began. The plume extends from the summit of Karymsky (bottom center) to the southeast, with brown ash deposits darkening the snow cover below the plume. 

The Akademia Nauk caldera -- now filled with water to form the present-day Karymsky Lake - is located to the south of Karymsky volcano. Calderas are formed by explosive eruption and emptying of a volcano's magma chamber -- leading to collapse of the structure to form a large crater-like depression. Akademia Nauk last erupted in 1996. ISS033-E-019822 (9 Nov. 2012) - high res (0.8 M) low res (80 K) 
Source: SpaceRef 
http://spaceref.com/news/viewsr.html?pid=42712﻿

Meer lezen (32 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-OhyM2j5O33k/ULYTICdlyJI/AAAAAAAAAQc/0aEi2u_dEhQ/w426-h284/Karymsky%2BVolcano%2Bon%2Bthe%2BKamchatka%2BPeninsula%2Bvia%2BISS.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/111348202787498563348/albums/6005766612514114993/6005766613190596786</link><title>Did you know Kilauea Volcano on Hawaii's Big Island has been continuously erupting for about 30 years, making it one of the world's most active volcanoes? Have you witnessed this volcano first hand? If so, tell us about your experience.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-b7fkbVQaHyk/U1jE6i8gWLI/AAAAAAAABHY/bbh1y_KJCGc/w426-h284/5evJv.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/114562168945437357579/albums/5995275988730865937/5995275991842571170</link><title>Puyeue Volcano eruption in Chili. 
Puyehue volcano is one of four located in the Puyehue-Cordon Caulle volcano chain in southern Chile. 
"Volcanic lightning: Electrifying sights from erupting volcanoes" 
http://www.nydailynews.com/news/volcanic-lightning-electrifying-sights-erupting-volcanoes-gallery-1.1100739?pmSlide=1.1100732 

#volcanoes   #volcanophotography   #lightning   #lightningphotography 
#chile   #landscapephotography  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_06_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ShRBm0jD4-g/UzN_wBA0Q6I/AAAAAAAAcSE/V749mzeBwu4/w426-h267/Puyeue%2BVolcano%2BEruption.%2BChili.%2BPhoto%2Bby%2BCarlos%2BGutierrez%252C%2BReuters..png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/110702015089501404917/albums/5978265512496503297/5978265515746038530</link><title>[ObjectName]=YEARENDER 2006-PNG-VOLCANO-RABAUL-ERUPTION 
[Urgency]=5 
[Category]=DIS 
[DateSent]=075513+0000 
[DateCreated]=203500+0000 
[OriginalTransmissionReference]=AFP Reporters 
[Byline]=AFP 
[BylineTitle]=STR 
[City]=Rabaul 
[CountryCode]=PNG 
[CountryName]=PAPUA NEW GUINEA 
OriginalTransmissionReference]=PNG07 
[Credit]=AFP 
[Source]=AFP 
[Caption]=Evacuated Matapit Islanders watch Tavurvur volcano erupt sending ash and rocks over the already devastated city of Rabaul on New Britain Island in Papua New Guinea, 07 October 2006. Tavurvur (also spelt: Tuvurvur) erupted violently, sending a plume of ash 18 kms into the air, causing some 2,000 residents to flee as lava flowed from the caldera into Simpson Harbour. AFP PHOTO/Bruce ALEXANDER 
[CaptionWriter]=tb/TA/mo 
[Imagetype]=3S﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_QDz25N0yfg/UvcQz_cCkwI/AAAAAAAAEjs/Ix9DoSm0cxk/w426-h307/1175488929.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/105071181644612789958/albums/6004757606928364865/6004757605766660786</link><title>Gunung Merapi. 
1 of the active volcanoes before erupting.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ieoU3pPLy0c/U1UvOlYMArI/AAAAAAAAAqw/6pZ9dUtwir0/w426-h288/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/113725245271712610655/albums/6005466996246821249/6005467007118257762</link><title>Arenal Volcano, CostaRica 

It was thought to be extinct until an eruption in 1968. Out of the 6 live volcanoes, it is the most active volcano of #costarica. It entered into a resting phase in 2010, means its eruptions have taken pause for the time being. 

#travel﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Po2InY8zq8Y/U1e0bLWcrmI/AAAAAAAAIFs/AFCl-kGy_dY/w426-h469/Arenal%2BVolcano%2Bin%2BCosta%2BRica1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7326-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/volcanoe%20eruption/photos/101987700269894001742/albums/5848644631046531121/5848644628053310002?authkey=CMH4zJ6AquS3Zg</link><title>The Manam Volcanoe erupting in Papua New Guinea looks like that from the air, how would you describe it?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7326_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-0ZEZJUSk7S8/USqPTUCdOjI/AAAAAAAAAec/OEaR_BWzcdY/w426-h419/papauyeniginef4.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>