<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 13:17:39" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/112375123015014637680/albums/6005862597898169345/6005862607766504834</link><title>Infamous map of the "Post-War New World Moral Order" constructed shortly before Pearl Harbour by Maurice Gomberg or what happens when an American redraws the world from a shower in Philadelphia :) 
You can see a proposal to re-arrange the world after an Allied victory against the Axis forces. Its title refers to a ‘New World Order’, a vague concept which you can go ahead and define for yourself. 
At the core of the NWO,  as always , is the idea that a small group of powerful individuals, institutions, industries and/or nations must lead the world in the right direction . This may be against the world’s own will (and therefore done covertly) but ultimately it is for its own good. 

The footer of the above map reads as follows: 

•The United States of America (USA): the US, Canada, all Central American and Carribean states, most Atlantic islands (including Greenland and Iceland), most Pacific islands, Taiwan, Hainan, the Philippines and several now Indonesian islands, including Sulawesi. This was to be the dominant power in the world, military and otherwise. 

•The Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR): the Soviets were to be rewarded with Persia (Iran), Mongolia, Manchuria, Finland, and all of Eastern Europe, which subsequently would form part of the Eastern Bloc (excluding Albania, but including the real-life maverick state of Yugoslavia, socialist but anti-Soviet) . All of theses states were simply to become member-states of the USSR. Austria and most of Germany, although ‘quarantained’ are shown within the Soviet sphere. 

•The United States of South America (USSA): including all South American states, with the three Guianas as a single constituent state and the Falkland Islands part of the USSA. 

•The Union of African Republics (UAR): All of Africa as a federation of republics. 

•The Arabian Federated Republics (AFR): covering Saudi and all other states now occupying the Arabian Peninsula, plus present-day Iraq and Syria. 

•The Federated Republics of India (FRI): Present-day Afghanistan, Pakistan, India, Nepal, Bhutan, Bangladesh and Birma (Myanmar). 

•The United Republics of China (URC): A federation including all parts of present-day China, Korea, the erstwhile French colony of Indochina (now Vietnam, Laos and Cambodia), Thailand and Malaya. 

•The United States of Scandinavia (USS): Norway, Sweden, Denmark. 

•The United States of Europe (USE): the Benelux countries, the German Rhineland, France, Switzerland, Spain, Portugal and Italy. 

•And finally the British Commonwealth of Nations (BCN), including Great Britain, Australia, New Zealand, Sri Lanka, Madagascar and most of Indonesia. 

Smaller entities include Eire (the whole of Ireland), Greece (including Albania), Turkey (excluding European Turkey), Hebrewland (the Holy Land plus Jordan) and Japan. The three axis states (Germany, Italy and Japan) were to be ‘quarantained’ until they could be readmitted in the family of nations. 

Mr Gomberg possibly took his cue for this map from US president Franklin D. Roosevelt, whose speech about Four Freedoms and a Moral Order (from his State of the Union to the 77-th Congress) he quotes, before outlining his own vision (at the bottom of the map): 

“As the USA with the cooperation of the Democracies of Latin-America, the British Commonwealth of Nations and the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, assumes world leadership for the establishment of a New World Moral Order for permanent peace, justice, security and world reconstruction.” 

“OUR POLICY SHALL BE THIS: 

1\. We, the U.S.A., in cooperation with our allies, for reasons of our national safety and in the interests of international morality, are determined to crush and completely destroy the military power of the Axis aggressors, and their satellites regardless of cost, effort and time necessary to accomplish this task. 

2\. The old world order of colonial oppression, exploitation of dominions, rival imperialism and mercenary balance of power diplomacy; of majesties, dictators, privileged minorities, plutocratic monopolists and similar social parasites; the corrupted order responsible for the present world cataclysm, endangering our national safety and peaceful process, shall never rise again. 

3\. A New World Moral Order for permanent peace and freedom shall be established at the successful conclusion of the present war. 

4\. For reasons of history, economic structure, favorable geography and the welfare of mankind, the U.S.A. must, altruistically, assume the leadership of the newly established, democratic world order. 

5\. To reduce the burden and criminal waste of armaments expenditures everywhere in the world, the U.S.A., with the cooperation of Latin-America, the British Commonwealth of Nations, and the U.S.S.R. shall undertake to guarantee peace to the nations which will be permanently disarmed and demilitarized after the conclusion of the present war. 

6\. In order to be able, in the fulfillment of our obligations, to effectively prevent the possibility of a recurrence of another world cataclysm, the invincibility of the U.S.A. as a military, naval and air power, shall be the major prerequisite. 

7\. For realistic considerations of strategy and our invulnerability, it is imperative that the U.S.A. shall obtain relinquishment of controls of their possessions from all foreign Powers in the entire Western Hemisphere, it’s surrounding waters and strategic island outposts as outlined on accompanying map. 

8\. For considerations of hemispheric defense and in the spirit and tradition of the new Monroe Doctrine of hemispheric solidarity and the “Good Neighbor” policy, the U.S.A. with the consent of the Latin-American Republics, shall obtain control and protectorate rights of the relinquished territories. 

9\. To strengthen our position in the Caribbean area which is of obvious importance to hemispheric defense, all possible inducements shall be offered to our neighbors of Central America and the West Indies to facilitate their entrance as equal states of the U.S.A. as outlined on map. 

10\. To fortify the politico-economic unity of the Western Hemisphere, the U.S.A. shall promote and assist the unification of South America into a well organized, democratic, federated “United States of South America.” 

11\. The liberated British, French and Netherlands Guiana shall be reorganized as one state of the U.S.S.A. 

12\. All Powers shall relinquish their controls of their colonial, mandate and strategic island possessions everywhere in the world. 

13\. The British Commonwealth of Nations, the second military and naval Power of importance cooperating in a binding compact with the U.S.A. as a Power for freedom, shall retain and acquire control such territories, peace-security bases and strategic islands outposts essential for the maintenance of world peace and freedom as outlines on the map. 

14\. The U.S.S.R., the third military Power of importance cooperating with the U.S.A. as a Power for freedom and the maintenance of world peace, shall acquire control of the liberated, disorganized adjacent areas and those of Germany-Austria to be re-educated and eventually incorporated as equal republics of the U.S.S.R., as approximately outlined on map. 

15\. A world League of Nationalities with arbitration and supervision powers shall be organized. 

16\. A World Court with punitive powers of absolute boycott, quarantine, blockade and occupation by international police, against lawbreakers of international morality shall be organized. 

17\. The U.S.A. with the close cooperation of the United States of South America, the British Commonwealth of Nations, the U.S.S.R. and the World League of Nationalities, shall promote and assist in the unification of the relinquished territories and the areas at present unsoundly divided into well organized democratic and absolutely demilitarized republics as approximately on the map. 

18\. The areas known as Netherlands, Belgium, Luxemburg, Switzerland, France, Spain, Portugal, the island of Corsica, and eventually Italy and the islands of Sardinia and Sicily shall be unified as a demilitarized, federated “United States of Europe.” 

19\. The areas known as Sweden, Norway, Denmark and the Spitsbergen islands shall be unified as a demilitarized, federated “United States of Scandinavia.” 

20\. The continent of Africa shall be reorganized and unified as a demilitarized, federated “Union of African Republics.” 

21\. The areas of Saudi Arabia, Syria, Lebanon, Iraq, Hejas, Aden and Oman, shall be unified as a demilitarized union of “Arabian Federated Republics.” 

22\. The areas known as India, including Afghanistan, Baluchistan, Nepal, Bhutan and Burma shall be unified as a demilitarized “federated Republics of India.” 

23\. The areas known as China, Inner Mongolia, Tibet, Thailand, Malaya, Indo-China and Korea, shall be unified as a demilitarized, federated “United Republics of China.” 

24\. The areas known as Greece, Macedonia, Albania, Crete, Dodecanese and adjacent islands in the Aegean sea shall be unified as a demilitarized “Federal Republic of Greece.” 

25\. The areas known as Eire and Northern Ireland shall be unified as a demilitarized independent republic of “Eire.” 

26\. The area of the Holy Land of the ancient Hebrews, at present known as Palestine and Trans-Jordan, and the adjacent requisite regions as outlined on map, for considerations of history and the imperative necessity to alleviate a post war refugee problem, shall be unified as a demilitarized republic of “Hebrewland.” 

27\. The area known as European Turkey, adjacent to the Dardanelles, sea of Marmora and Bosporus, for considerations of realistic peace strategy shall be placed under joint control of the U.S.S.R. and Turkey. 

28\. The area known as Turkey shall be a demilitarized independent republic of “Turkey.” 

29\. All problems of exchange, transfer and repatriation of populations shall be administered by the World League of Nationalities. 

30\. The criminal perpetrators and their partners in guilt of this hideous war shall be brought to justice and unforgettable punishment administered. 

31\. All subjects of Japan and all persons of Japanese origin of doubtful loyalty shall be expelled from the entire Western Hemisphere, U.S.A. protectorates and strategic island outposts and their property confiscated for post-war reconstruction needs. 

32\. All subjects of Germany and Italy and all persons of German and Italian origin known as active supporters of Nazi and fascist ideologies shall be treated similarly. 

33\. German, Italian, Japanese immigration to the Western Hemisphere, its protectorates and island outposts shall be indefinitely stopped. 

34\. All persons of German origin in East Prussia and the Rhineland shall be transferred to inner Germany and the regions permanently de-Prussianized. 

35\. All persons of German, Italian and Japanese origin shall be permanently expelled from their now conquered territories and their property confiscated for post-war construction needs. 

36\. To cleanse the populations of the defeated Axis aggressors of the intoxication of military chauvinism; to effectuate the removal and destruction of their potential military establishments; to recover the accumulated loot and to re-educate them for their eventual membership in the Family of Nations, the areas of Germany-Austria, Italy and Japan shall be hermetically and indefinitely quarantined and administered by appointed Governors subject to supervision by the world League of Nationalities. 

37\. All resources, industrial and labor capacity of quarantined areas shall be employed for the post war restoration and reconstruction needs. 

38\. To reduce the numerical power of the aggressor nations, as a potential military advantage, a Population Control Policy shall be elaborated and applied in the quarantined area. 

39\. In the New World Moral Order which we seek to establish, besides the essential political freedoms, the following fundamental economic changes are imperative: 

(a) Nationalization of all natural resources and equitable distribution of same to all nations…everywhere in the world; 

(b) Nationalization of international banking, foreign investments, railroads and power plants….everywhere in the world; 

(c) Nationalization of all armaments producing establishments by all military powers; 

(d) Federal control of foreign commerce and shipping; 

(e) The establishment of a world common monetary system; 

(f) World wide limitations of interest rates to a maximum of two percent; 

40\. To retain the victory and leadership of our united democratic effort….the aim of which is not vengeance or exploitation, but freedom and security to all nations for peaceful progress….the unified “Supreme War Command of the United Nations” at the conclusion of the present war, shall be recognized and transformed into a permanent “Supreme Military and Economic Council” collaborating with the World League of Nationalities in post war construction and to enforce world peace. 

41\. The “Supreme Military and Economic Council” shall appoint the Governors to administer the quarantined areas until their eventual parole. 

For this purposeful beginning we must fight until absolute victory.”﻿

Meer lezen (291 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-d_k3NsfC_I0/U1kcOKm5RYI/AAAAAAAAe_g/k8Pl-g-PSUA/w426-h304/infAM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/100207590405557337712/albums/5974168048285420993/5974168049739446450</link><title>Current picture of the US 

Or a map of the United States superimposed over a map of Antarctica for scale. One or the other. 

From Amazing Maps: https://twitter.com/Amazing_Maps﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_02_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-qhsm2zc6YB0/UuiCMFE1OLI/AAAAAAAA5Oc/fqw_-feJas4/w426-h284/ankarctica.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/114077525644661833984/albums/5963885072487477809/5964041794600651970</link><title>Map of 124 United States of America  by Andrew Shears 
Source &amp; Credit: http://andrewshears.com 

http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-fix/wp/2013/12/31/the-124-states-of-america/?hpid=z4﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_03_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-tyziuDDTa4c/UsSIadDBTMI/AAAAAAAHCNA/V1dehA2tUWw/w426-h293/1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/113507009175485747967/albums/6004928508164889489/6004928513850231362</link><title>The Global Map of Mars: Viking Orbiter 
This is the most accurate color global mosaic of Mars to date, produced in 2014, based on NASA Viking Orbiter data from the 1970s: the Viking Orbiter Colorized Mars Digital Image Model (MDIM) version 2.1. The full-resolution map, available from the USGS, is 256 pixels per degree (232 m/pixel) as a 12-GB data set: 
http://astrogeology.usgs.gov/search/details/Mars/Viking/MDIM21/Mars_Viking_MDIM21_ClrMosaic_global_232m/cub 

Credit: NASA/JPL/United States Geological Survey (USGS) 

+NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory 
+USGS News: Everything We've Got 

#NASA   #Mars   #Viking   #Orbiter   #Geology   #Map #Color   #USGS #JPL﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_04_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-OjqBqhOOUOs/U1XKqvmoSkI/AAAAAAABBU8/4dSmSwYw3tU/w426-h237/Mars_Viking_MDIM21_ClrMosaic_global_2500m%2B%2528med2%2529.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/117762635025576128070/albums/5942460027828813105/5942460043722728002</link><title>A map of the United States with each state’s name replaced with its etymological root translated into English. 

Idaho LOL﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Vftn6Dj_MDQ/Unfb7N4LokI/AAAAAAABP-8/D_VUPymy38Y/w426-h279/tumblr_mebl40EjC61qz98hlo1_500.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/115433406081833536712/albums/5980040244392044593/5980040248136392018</link><title>Here's a wind map of the United States. The storm responsible for the mess in the south and now east coast is shown to the right. The tighter, brighter colored lines indicate stronger winds where it is wrapping around the front, which is a blue area off the east coast of Maryland and NJ. 

I've included a link to the website where I got this picture from... http://goo.gl/j7gzSM (it's called "Earth Wind Map" and has a lot of nice information and features). #weather  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Unj7zRm02bw/Uv1e7Ay1XVI/AAAAAAAAGPQ/8MONIL4v5BY/w426-h237/earth%2Bwind%2Bmap.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/105212181263201049085/albums/5918564307152122497/5918564311353526450?authkey=COH4y5636JP_-AE</link><title>The Racial Dot Map - One Dot Per Person for the Entire United States 

http://demographics.coopercenter.org/DotMap/index.html 

A beautiful cartographical resource! The map displays 308,745,538 dots, one for each person residing in the United States at the location they were counted during the 2010 Census. Each dot is color-coded by the individual's race and ethnicity. 

It has many possible uses linked to the IB DP Geography syllabus including: 

Patterns and Change: Origin of disparities - Explain disparities and inequities that occur within countries resulting from ethnicity, residence... 

Global Interactions: Sociocultural integration - Examine the role of diasporas in preserving culture in one country and the adoption of minority traits by host societies. 

Urban Environments: Urban land use - Explain the location of residential areas in relation to wealth, ethnicity...﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_07_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zkhYZe3Wr4E/UiL24h6ICLI/AAAAAAAABVQ/FdMdmdfsPyg/w426-h237/The_Racial_Dot_Map__One_Dot_Per_Person_for_the_Entire_U.S..png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/100207590405557337712/albums/5953492007698386545/5953492015576056386</link><title>Another gif of a changing United States map 

While this may not be as historically interesting as the map +Lars Fosdal shared yesterday, it definitely does demonstrate big changes in the US. (heh, big changes.) 

This map demonstrates the rapidly growing obesity epidemic. (heh, rapidly growing.) 

source: http://www.policymic.com/articles/70457/watch-america-grow-fatter-in-one-scary-gif 

mapsmapsmapsmaps,  owl? no owls, just maps.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_08_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-8s0bxRf0mFw/Up8NcfmJAkI/AAAAAAAAzxA/jM1bpIPQnFQ/w426-h247/obesity.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/102939525100717806392/albums/5948531535379095729/5948531542066708802</link><title>United States Population Growth 

This is a very interesting map. 

Source: goo.gl/AM6WHN 

#maps   #driving  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_09_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-nbBRJWBW6mY/Uo1t67wXwUI/AAAAAAAAA7s/EgDxKN7LXqU/w426-h261/Screen%2BShot%2B2013-11-20%2Bat%2B9.19.19%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7348-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/map%20of%20the%20united%20states/photos/103863989923615589024/albums/5949852956202271633/5949852957763336114</link><title>This future map of the United States is way cooler than any current map of the United States. (We know this may not happen soon, but it'd be pretty cool one day…) http://u.pw/18vzYdq — +Adam Mordecai   #rail 

Share if you have a need for speed.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7348_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-2zIb2jivQc4/UpIfvc1Kd7I/AAAAAAAAGL4/Q32acaGnejo/w426-h237/83805a1e-3f0c-45d3-967d-5374a66cb1e6</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>