<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:33:36" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/104696459135303205735/albums/5864838120020054353/5864838125694424562?authkey=CKTrhJS7y-6-Ag</link><title>Little Johnny's next door neighbor had a baby. Unfortunately, the little baby was born with no ears. When they arrived home from the hospital, the parents invited Little Johnny's family to come over and see their new baby. 

Little Johnny's parents were very afraid their son would have a wise crack to say about the baby. So, Little Johnny's dad had a long talk with Little Johnny before going to the neighbors. He said, "Now, son...that poor baby was born without any ears. I want you to be on your best behavior and not say one word about his ears, or I'm really going to spank your butt when we get back home." I promise not to mention his ears at all," said Little Johnny. 

At the neighbors home, Little Johnny leaned over the crib and touched the baby's hand. He looked at it's mother and said, "Oh, what a beautiful little baby!" The mother, who had braced herself for Johnny's comment, was pleasantly surprised and said, "Thank you very much, Little Johnny." He then said," This baby has perfect little hands and perfect little feet. 

Why, just look at his pretty little eyes! Did his doctor say he can see good? The mother a bit bewildered, hesitantly replies "Why, yes... his doctor said he has 20/20 vision, why do you ask?" 

Little Johnny said, "Well, it's a good thing, cause he'd be screwed if he needed to wear glasses"﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-CtO0KA44qmM/UWQXM7svFfI/AAAAAAAA_QA/o9IVtIa9hxY/w426-h523/images.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/110836827667548335516/albums/5701870141137970257/5701870141653062290</link><title>LITTLE JOHNNY STRIKES AGAIN 
The teacher asked the class to use the word 'fascinate' in a sentence. 

Molly put up her hand and said, 'My family went to my granddad's farm, and we all saw his pet sheep. It was fascinating.' 

The teacher said, 'That was good, but I wanted you to use the word 'fascinate, not fascinating'. 

Sally raised her hand. She said, 'My family went to see RockCity and I was 'fascinated.' The teacher said, 'Well, that was good Sally, but I wanted you to use the word 'fascinate.' 

Little Johnny raised his hand. The teacher hesitated because she had been burned by Little Johnny before. 

She finally decided there was no way he could damage the word 'fascinate', so she called on him. 

Johnny said, 'My aunt Gina has a sweater with ten buttons, but her boobies are so big she can only fasten eight.' 

The teacher sat down and cried.﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-OjmEFh0Q_28/TyEcrxyjEpI/AAAAAAAAGE0/AJGfYIchDJI/w426-h436/crying+teacher%21.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/108992007110283236440/albums/5841291697196933825/5841291695323740418?authkey=CNrk6v7a0J3T8AE</link><title>Little Johnny is always being teased by the other neighborhood boys for being stupid. Their favorite joke is to offer Johnny his choice between a nickel and a dime -- Little Johnny always takes the nickel. 

One day, after Johnny takes the nickel, a neighbor man takes him aside and says, "Johnny, those boys are making fun of you. Don't you know that a dime is worth more than a nickel, even though the nickel's bigger?" 

Johnny grins and says, "Well, if I took the dime, they'd stop doing it, and so far I've made $20!"﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vZZq-UfEpcs/URBv2TE1-QI/AAAAAAAAcPg/EeLtFIqdbIE/w426-h642/24464_420443204696382_1133835799_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/115997114756428816858/albums/5944394712375734161/5944394714525829234</link><title>The BEST Little Johnny joke I have ever heard! 

                            The kids filed into class Monday morning. They were all very excited.. 
                            Their weekend assignment was to sell something, then give a talk on 
                            salesmanship. 
                            Little Sally led off. "I sold Girl Scout cookies and I made $30" she said proudly, 
                            "My sales approach was to appeal to the customer's civil spirit and 
                            I credit that approach for my obvious success." 

                            "Very good", said the teacher. 

                            Little Debbie was next. "I sold magazines" she said, "I made $45 and 
                            I explained to everyone that magazines would keep them up on current events." 
                            "Very good, Debbie", said the teacher. 

                            Eventually, it was Little Johnny's turn. The teacher held her breath. 

                            Little Johnny walked to the front of the classroom and dumped a box 
                            full of cash on the teacher's desk. "$2,467", he said. 

                            ; "$2,467!" cried the teacher, "What in the world were you selling?" 

                            Toothbrushes", said Little Johnny. "Toothbrushes", echoed the teacher, 

                            "How could you possibly sell enough tooth brushes to make that much money?" 

                            "I found the busiest corner in town", said Little Johnny, "I set up 
                            a Dip &amp; Chip stand and I gave everybody who walked by a free sample." 
                            They all said the same thing, "Hey, this tastes like dog poop!" Then I would say, 
                            "It is dog poop. Wanna buy a toothbrush? I used the President Obama method 
                            of giving you some crap, dressing it up so it looks good, telling you it's free and 
                            then making you pay to get the bad taste out of your mouth." 

                            Little Johnny got fi ve stars for his assignment. 
                            Bless his heart.﻿

Meer lezen (49 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-TR7gxS9gPSo/Un67f4QFiHI/AAAAAAAABYA/ycvSvOpvaM8/w426-h240/c56b02f56c804be386b7c7616bd3e750.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/117299772725703017626/albums/5745882670067616817/5745882672387917890</link><title>Little Johnny: 

If it’s time for women doe’s that mean that I won’t be able to like Lady Ga Ga And Brittany Spears and the other lady’s anymore. 

No it doesn’t because you’re be dead like all the other men and you won’t then be able to like Lady Ga Ga, Brittany Spears And all the other lady’s, because your dead, and I will beable to have all the lady's to my self. 

Said the lady that took Little Johnny without his mothers permission 

Match On A Book:﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ACOrs9lcv0I/T7152PjBCEI/AAAAAAAABac/5oXi6XrMy-s/w426-h320/Match%2BOn%2BBook.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/102666600573503665457/albums/5956924794072808737/5956924797564731378</link><title>With a frown wrinkling his forehead, little Johnny was working hard at his father’s desk scratching a pen along a page of his paper. His mother asked, “Are you writing a letter to your little girlfriend, Son?” 
“Nope,” he grunted, “It’s a letter to myself.” 
“Well,” she smiled, “What are you going to write about?” 
“How should I know?” he squeaked, “I haven’t received it yet.”﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-fy_YkuRnM-8/Uqs_itCPv_I/AAAAAAAAMrI/fLlyodsu67A/w426-h284/40NSw.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/107889816939032412666/albums/5674624401787749681/5674624400764011858</link><title>Little Johnny﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_07_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Xo8jxzdF6bk/TsBQ07lNhVI/AAAAAAAAC_A/wwNfDuZ4NT4/w426-h579/farm.PNG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/104696459135303205735/albums/5789705681836442289/5789705687862909186</link><title>Goodnight All 

Little Johnny sees his Daddy's car passing the playground and going into the woods. 

Curious, he follows the car and sees Daddy and Aunt Jane kissing. 

Johnny finds this so exciting and can barely contain himself as he runs home and starts to tell his mother excitedly. 

"MOMMY, MOMMY, I WAS AT THE PLAYGROUND AND DADDY AND...." 

Mommy tells him to slow down, but that she wants to hear the story. 

So Johnny tells her. "I was at the playground and I saw Daddy's car go into the woods with Aunt Jane. I went to look and Daddy was giving Aunt Jane a big kiss, then he helped her take off her shirt, then Aunt Jane helped Daddy take his pants off, then Aunt Jane laid down on the seat, then Daddy...." 

At this point, Mommy cut him off and said, "Johnny, this is such an interesting story, suppose you save the rest of it for dinner time. I want to see the look on Daddy's face when you tell it tonight." 

At the dinner table, Mommy asks Johnny to tell his story. 

He describes the car into the woods, the undressing, laying down on the seat, and, "Then Daddy and Aunt Jane did that same thing Mommy and Uncle Jeff used to do when Daddy was in the Army."﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1E7TX-VUouY/UFkqpd8gmQI/AAAAAAAAYPU/l4VqjEpB4oc/w426-h560/229275_10152095692335702_1575770989_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/107483599783818929646/albums/5785696789697312993/5785696787951217650</link><title>Little Johnny.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ttyyylStBKs/UErskx_za_I/AAAAAAAAAPo/bnz-_xtAOe4/w426-h568/12%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7402-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny/photos/111139905254421432447/albums/5764931852634541825/5764931855792447730</link><title>Back to School Joke: 

Summer vacation was over and Little Johnny returned back to school. 

Only two days later his teacher phoned his mother to tell her that he was misbehaving. 

"Wait a minute," she said. "I had Johnny with me for three months and I never called you once when he misbehaved!; couldn't you show me the same courtesy?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7402_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-kIj_g5rW9J4/UAEm-prXoPI/AAAAAAAAAHw/vwJ0AfF14Xw/w426-h415/246880_10150218678472611_3365066_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>