<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:11:27" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/115833201340797801649/albums/5990215346866652513/5990215349867808162</link><title>what is #led #LIGHT #THERAPY 
The word is an abbreviation for Light Emitting Diodes. LED’s are tiny light bulbs that emit non-thermal specific wavelengths of light from the visible spectrum. LED Light Therapy is a non-invasive method of light therapy that stimulates the skins natural repair and rejuvenation processes making it safe for all skin types and effective in the treatment of a wide range of skin conditions. 
@viaproskinsite﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-wa-JolqTCRE/UyGFH4j2haI/AAAAAAAAARI/_NsgueeARzQ/w426-h603/2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/105229351202504968662/albums/5866372176712394641/5866372176575774274?authkey=CImZ5ITw_4DN1wE</link><title>BiontologyArizona - Light Therapy﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-NUatq1iaRyA/UWmKackIvkI/AAAAAAAAADM/ZVoD3IEVU78/w426-h320/Biophoton+Light+-+Johan+Boswinkel.mp4</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/115833201340797801649/albums/5985486260566988321/5985486266328379538</link><title>CLEANE BLUE #ANTI   #ACNE led Therapy- Light Therapy 
#device   #cosmetic  www.cleane.it 
Blue light and thermal shock therapy technology 
Clinically proven to treat acne 
usable in anywhere and anytime 
Rechargeable system ( Adaptor and USB cable ) 
Rapid treatment effect within 24 hours 
Personal and home care 
#Beauty care device﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-EuXzsPIABdo/UxC4C_h7cJI/AAAAAAAAANQ/ZiwtDSZOA44/w426-h859/cleane+eng.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/110678303231765978559/albums/5938371972936725697/5938371975886033506</link><title>Blue Light Therapy VS Full Spectrum – Which One Works Better for SAD? 

http://www.light-therapy-reviews.net/blue-light-therapy-vs-full-spectrum/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-rstybsv9EcA/UmlV2WbSUmI/AAAAAAAAAQE/Rf8G3Hf2Yjg/w426-h371/blue%2Blight%2Btherapy%2Bvs%2Bfull%2Bspectrum.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/113595424311323604894/albums/5771031228494670481/5771031230508330402</link><title>Blue Light Therapy 

“Blue light has been shown to be antibacterial against P. acnes, the bacterium associated with acne, heat may help lower levels of this bacterium, and vibration can loosen sticky skin cells that block pores,” explains Dr. Zeichner. Share this if you would like to treat your acne from the comfort of your home! http://shout.lt/bSpc﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Uc3LD4shGtQ/UBbSU_IibaI/AAAAAAAAAfg/SWatPHx6uS8/s426/564581_10151119874475568_548971183_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/111174284979888465116/albums/5774961233323672721/5774961233208260962</link><title>Red LED light therapy fascinates movie stars. 
http://beautyneeds.infiniteinfo.net/2012/08/10/red-led-light-therapy-fascinates-movie-stars/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-3CXJ1DZrE3U/UCTIpQEHuWI/AAAAAAAAGrQ/QLq_5yxhd2w/w426-h513/Red%2BLED%2Blight%2Btherapy.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/114077525644661833984/albums/5816596578834913489/5816596589362447362</link><title>Sweden Offers Light Therapy At The Bus Stop 

Interesting idea .... 

http://www.thelocal.se/44690/20121127/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_07_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-XkuhcGD-kl0/ULizx8ayhAI/AAAAAAACz0w/8HErWL54Fg0/w426-h329/1.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/113595424311323604894/albums/5776231841015191585/5776231840356391442</link><title>Red Light Therapy 

HKI’s (HueKnewIt) view impressive pieces of consumer-friendly machinery that puts the power of anti-aging into your hands and out of the hands of expensive dermatologists. ( the Tanda Luxe) "Like" this if you would like to make one less appointment with a dermatologist! http://www.hueknewit.com/journal/2012/8/2/editors-picks-anti-aging-beauty-tools.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-GCGwwl78Nus/UClMQUi-WhI/AAAAAAAAAlw/UqeIYuPI-TM/s426/185535_10151151784235568_1083648789_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/107942694530932018707/albums/5992897243878321713/5992897247462178402</link><title>Infrared light therapy also is used to treat acne. The increased production of ATP helps eliminate any bacteria in the pores. This includes the bacteria that cause pimples. Improved collagen production also helps heal any scars that might have formed. 

Not all infrared light is safe for use, however. Short-wave infrared light can bypass the body's nerve receptors, causing patients to feel nothing. For this reason, there is no way that the patient can tell if the heat is actually causing more damage than good. When considering infrared light therapy, then, it is important for one to consult both a physician and the technician first.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-e1soBHYEHTU/UysMS3pmPmI/AAAAAAAAAlw/aa52FwFHP38/w426-h237/images.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7405-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/light%20therapy/photos/115337148988005892196/albums/5828966822284984289/5828966826188269522?authkey=CJ_43JmA2e2GIw&amp;sqi=117022908558730334854&amp;sqsi=8d388b83-2979-4f66-b151-bbb1c3e651bb</link><title>SUNLIGHT HEALS -- One Hour of Light Therapy Reduces Depression 

Written By: Case Adams, Naturopath 

Researchers from the University of Maryland's School of Medicine have determined that just one hour of bright light therapy significantly reduces depression and depressed moods. 

Depressed patients were given one hour of bright light therapy or an hour of dim light therapy as a placebo. The researchers found that the patients given bright light therapy had reductions in their depression scores ranging from 120% to 130%, using two different depression-testing systems. 

The research is significant because it applied a placebo test against the light therapy system - something previous light therapy studies have not done. 

In a related study, some of the same researchers tested 15 depressed patients who were diagnosed with seasonal affective disorder. They administered different lengths of 10,000 lux of white cool fluorescent light for 20 minutes, 40 minutes and 60 minutes and compared the depression scores with the depression scores of the patients prior to treatment. 

The researchers found that 40 minutes of the light therapy significantly improved moods among the patients, and reduced their depressed states. The improvement was greater than the 20 minutes of therapy. But surprisingly, the 60 minutes of light therapy did not result in significantly better improvement of depression than either the 20 or the 40 minutes of therapy. 

Depression levels in the latter study were measured using the 24-item NIMH scale, a standardized measurement of depression symptoms. The level of seasonal affective disorder depression was gauged using the SIGH-SAD scale (Structured Interview Guide for the Hamilton Depression Rating Scale). They also used Wilcoxon Signed Rank testing. Other studies have used the Profile of Mood States-Depression-Dejection subscale and the Beck Depression Inventory II. 

The researchers used a 10,000 lux light box made by Sunbox for the bright light therapy. The patients starred at the center of the light box to receive their therapy. 

The findings are consistent with other studies, most that utilized both synthetic light, but some that used natural light. In one, McGill University researchers found that natural bright light significantly reduced acute tryptophan depletion-related depressed moods. 

Still other studies have shown that bright light increases cognition, improves sleep and has a myriad of other benefits. 

Learn more about light therapy and why the sun is not the enemy (next post). 

\---------------------------------- 

REFERENCES 

Virk G, Reeves G, Rosenthal NE, Sher L, Postolache TT. Short exposure to light treatment improves depression scores in patients with seasonal affective disorder: A brief report. Int J Disabil Hum Dev. 2009 Jul;8(3):283-286. 

Reeves GM, Nijjar GV, Langenberg P, Johnson MA, Khabazghazvini B, Sleemi A, Vaswani D, Lapidus M, Manalai P, Tariq M, Acharya M, Cabassa J, Snitker S, Postolache TT. Improvement in depression scores after 1 hour of light therapy treatment in patients with seasonal affective disorder. J Nerv Ment Dis. 2012 Jan;200(1):51-5. 

aan het Rot M, Benkelfat C, Boivin DB, Young SN. Bright light exposure during acute tryptophan depletion prevents a lowering of mood in mildly seasonal women. Eur Neuropsychopharmacol. 2008 Jan;18(1):14-23. 

Case Adams is a California Naturopath and holds a Ph.D. in Natural Health Sciences. His focus is upon science-based natural health solutions. He is the author of 20 books on natural health and numerous print and internet articles. His work can be found at http://www.caseadams.com.﻿

Meer lezen (79 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7405_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-TN9HWeU3JjY/UOSmcfp859I/AAAAAAAAFuw/iENro_wgeiU/w426-h546/485040_10151341861858185_603356086_n.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>