<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:42:30" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/103836659420959768085/albums/5930284787288653089/5930284791975835346</link><title>Does my child have ADHD or is she just rambunctious? More about ADHD from UC Davis MIND Institute experts: http://bit.ly/17u0SkL﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-YqYyL7NKSCk/UkyamSqe9tI/AAAAAAAAAYI/RZ1o2iNkuDo/w426-h282/school-classroom.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/117546643132134165396/albums/5895456391373785537/5895456392269956018?authkey=COOg_tnHksD1FA</link><title>#ad Do you have a child with ADHD? Know someone who does? Here are some tips that I have personally used with my own son on dealing with ADHD in Children. http://generationsofsavings.com/2013/06/some-tips-on-dealing-with-adhd-in-children.html #lifescript﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-5o0b9AT2pN8/UdDeWnIOg7I/AAAAAAAAAD8/wg5NM1SoG_4/w426-h675/IMG_5839.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/106947464970880961126/albums/5938473006223402113/5938473010120274754</link><title>My son confirms &lt;3 

It gets better as he gets older, but he said it was like having different CDs playing all day. The attention fights to focus on just one; once finally focused on the one ... the attention bounces around again! 

***** CLICK SHARE ***** 

Share for people that may not understand that ADHD is real and this is what they deal with!!! Talk with your child with ADHD. He / She can be taught to clarify things the way YOU need to understand and help. &lt;3 

***** SOME TIPS &amp; REAL DEAL ***** 

Here's a tip I received from an AWESOME doctor that believed in food and behavior modification for ADHD instead of bullying me to put him on meds: 

Give children with ADHD 1 to 3 step directives. Do not bombard with a bunch of instructions and long lectures they will tune out in a sec ... "I want you to ONE - brush your teeth, TWO - clean up behind yourself, THREE - turn off the light" if you want your child to empty the dishwasher and have 1/2 hour of TV time thereafter, then you need to wait until after step one, two and three are done and give the next instructions. Some can do more of less at different times, but this is a nice way to help them focus and structure - to develop the pattern when they are younger - to make things easier on the child with ADHD, teacher, other family members, friends and yourself. 

Another useful tip was not to address things when he came home from school. Let them settle in for a while before starting homework and evening activities. 

I'm really glad the doctor cared enough to point this out because school was no longer fun for him once he transferred from pre-school to grade school; the first 5 years of school was extremely stressful for my son. Not so much his personal challenges with ADHD and other issues he had,  but because non-support teachers, staff and other kids had no clue that his mind was all over the place even when his body was where it should be. They did not know not to give him certain foods or that he needed something to fidget with at his desk or that he needed a points / reward system from the first day of school or ... that the music teacher was mean to him because he couldn't follow along at the back of the class or that he didn't know what to do with himself on the playground  and during other unstructured activities ... art teacher and private violin instructors are wonderfully patient but english and math teachers always assume avoidance ... 

Another useful tip was that some people with ADHD / ADD respond well to medications and REALLY need them despite anything in order to achieve even close to the mild clarity that another person with ADHD has naturally / not medicated, therefore don't judge a parent trying to give their child a chance to stop that chaos in their head. 

Also, children with ADHD not only need but will express (demand) the need for structure, so pay attention when they do. 

I could go on and on with tips on ADHD, ADD, Neurological Tics, Asperger's, ODD, etc. I have been to more doctors, specialists, EKGs, IEPs / ESEs meetings, and read it all! 

THE POINT BEING that you meet people each day (not just children) who are dealing with ADHD and other disorders that are not outwardly apparent. They are real and function according to what types of tips their parents, family and friends followed ~ as well as what they carried out on their own as they became adults. 

***** HERE'S THE POINT ***** 

So, when that one co-worker ALWAYS leaves a mess in the break room (no matter how many times reminded) ... or the other co-worker is like dealing with a toddler (not really but maybe at times) ... or that chick at the fast food register just does not seem to be "all there" ... or your cousin stares off into space every so often and it TRIPS YOU OUT ... or that dude that almost got himself hit crossing the street last week ... or that lady at the grocery store that takes forever to count back the change ... or that woman's kid that's always all over the place ... that man that talks about the same interest all of the time ... 

Or like in my homw, the teenage son that always leaves something clean in the dishwasher when emptying it; or mixes up where things go in the kitchen and makes me feel mixed up &lt;3 ... 

&lt;del&gt;-&lt;/del&gt;&gt; Regardless, YOU NEVER KNOW WHO IT WILL BE THAT HAS ADHD, ADD, NEUROLOGICAL TICS or some other disorder in your life. &lt;\--- 

They aren't slow or "out there" - some people with ADHD deal better than others and / or "grow out of it" maybe even just A BIT as they get older - sometimes they can't help it or know better; and sometimes they choose to ignore and do what is easier (people that can't read do this all of the time, so do people with disorders) ... sometimes they don't take medicines because they make them sick or don't work any better than their trying to deal with it on their own - sometimes parents / doctors give it to them despite all because they genuinely think that medicine is their best chance to help ... some can learn to function well with food and behavior modification ... some will go to college and others will do better to start learning a trade or trades from a very young age ... 

YADADA YADADA YADADA ... 

Regardless, ADHD and the related ARE REAL disorders with common effects, though unique to the individuals (i.e. he may struggle with this where she may struggle with that); since your attention is "all there", please be mindful to be aware of the 3 step directives and some of the tips mentioned for guiding children with ADHD! 

When dealing with an adult that has ADHD or related disorder, it's sometimes hard to tell who has it or not; who received "good rearing" or not; who developed defense mechanisms, disability adaptations, etc; who took medications or not while growing up; who takes them now and what they are like when they wear off, but do your best not to take offense, speak ill or deface people with ADHD as we all make mistakes in life; there is always a person that annoys you in life. People with ADHD are prone to do the same ones again and again, hopefully they will catch on as a behavior is mentioned or tactfully dealt with non-verbally ... all you can do is pray that life experiences will be their best teacher. 

There is so much more to learn and know about certain behavioral disorders like AHDH; 

GOOGLE SOME OF THE FOLLOW SEARCH TERMS AND READ FOR YOURSELF - I AM TOUCHING ON SOMETHING IMPORTANT ... 

"adhd characteristics in children" 

"adhd characteristics in adults" 

"adhd make the same mistakes over and over again" 

"adhd over and over again" 

"adhd same impulses over and over again" 

"living with ADHD" 

EVEN IF JUST FOR YOUR NERVES IN THE WORK PLACE ... People are so busy following zombie trends and celebrity diets ... ADHD is something real that affect you each day and little do you really know why you should not HATE that annoying manager or coworker of yours ... or maybe even why you should offer to take your niece or nephew to blow off some steam at the park every once in a while :) 

For more health tips, natural solutions, advice &amp; friendships, join us at: 

http://www.facebook.com/groups/organicfoodnaturalhealth﻿

Meer lezen (149 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-8SVxEHwym8U/UmmxvUR2s0I/AAAAAAAADx4/nQlgpWI2sFM/w426-h425/adhd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/104190332112493422074/albums/5972101756830693985/5972101758584914226</link><title>Via Leslie~This is my story on how Plexus Slim has helped my 8 year old with ADHD. Since my son was about 3 years old, I knew he had a problem. Then, and over the years I would notice that he was overly hyper, could not concentrate, liked things to be routine, would lie and believe it, had anger issues, uncontrollable noise would shut him down. Examples, radio, vaccums, tv, people talking loudly or laughing loudly. It hurt his ears so bad he would be in fetal position. I say uncontrolable because, if he was the cause of the noise, it didnt bother him. I was told from 3 yrs. old that hes just being a little boy, he needs discipline, theres nothing wrong!! I fought with his teachers because for little things he would get in a world of trouble. If he needed to tell his teachers something important, he would try and tell them and they would very rudly tell him to sit down and to shutup (not in MS schools!!). He would argue with them so he could say what he needed to say because, if he didnt say it, he would forget it. Then that would upset him. He needs one on one and eye to eye. Comeing from a family of teachers, I know thats hard with a class full, but not impossible! 
His self esteem started slipping away. As parents, we try so hard to build our children up. Because of getting in trouble at home for things he couldnt help and for getting in trouble at school for trying to tell a teacher something, he was going down. Thought the world hated him. I actually found that on a piece of paper in his room,"Why does everyone hate me"! Not cool yall, just not cool!! 
I am a parent who does not like medication. Thought if I could get teachers, friends parents and who everelse, to understand and to help me, I could get away with no medication. Everyone was awesome, but the teachers. Again, not the MS teachers. I get so angry just thinking about how this one teacher did him. 2 years ago, my huband and I broke down and had him tested for ADHD. Doc confirmes our thoughts and he is put on Adderall 10mg twice a day. Ofcourse it started helping him and I was ecstatic. I did not like what he was or the side effects of it, but with the doctors assurance, we stayed with it. Plexus came into my life a few months back. I have used it, never thought in a million years of having my boy take it for ADHD. He has been on Plexus for less than a week. AND thy hyperness has cut down, but hes not a zombie! The arguements have cut down, the tantrums have cut down, his stress is gone, self-esteem is coming back up, he is sleeping at night, he can sit at the computer and play a game with out bounceing in the chair. He no longer has the dry look in his eyes. They sparkle and his smile just shines, his laugh is one of the best sounds I have heard in a long time. 
When your child struggles with ADHD, ADD, Autism, etc. You, as a parent, start doubting yourself. What could I have done different, what am I doing wrong, why cant people just accept my child. Just like its not their fault, its not your fault. Be aware of the issue at hand, and do your best to help. A child with either of the above or more, is not spoiled, does not lack discipline, they are loveing and careing children, they are smart beyond their years. Give them a chance. Learn from them. Heaven knows, I have learned so much from my 8 yr. old. But please, if you dont want your child on harsh prescriptions, if you dont want them to go through the world feeling unwanted or unloved, etc. Please give Plexus a try. From mother to mother, from parent to parent IT WORKS!!﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-IZdYpXSIfb8/UuEq6GrwgTI/AAAAAAAAA04/YyOEN4XY8Sk/w426-h639/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/113117251731252114390/albums/5716519843505601057/5716519843411998146</link><title>Children born in December more likely to be diagnosed with ADHD. 

A study has found that children who are younger than most of their classmates are far more likely to be diagnosed with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) and put on drugs. 

In other words, children are being diagnosed with ADHD simply because they're younger and therefore less mature than older peers. 

At any given grade level, kids' age can be up to a year apart. The age cut-off is typically December 31 in Canada, where the study was conducted. So a Canadian child born in December will enter into the school system as one of the youngest kids in her class, whereas a child born in January will wait a year and enter school as one of the oldest. 

A new study published in the Canadian Medical Association Journal found that the youngest children in any class are 39% more likely to be diagnosed with ADHD and 48% more likely to be prescribed drugs for it. 

To oversimplify: The medical-industrial complex has decided that being born in December (or whatever the cut-off date is in the country of your choice) is now a medical condition that requires becoming a customer of the pharmaceutical industry. 

What will they pathologize next? 

http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2012-03/cmaj-yci022812.php﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_05_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AK-G5ArIREc/T1UogpoLNcI/AAAAAAACHoM/0RWQjMjANGg/w426-h282/Screen%2BShot%2B2012-03-05%2Bat%2B12.55.07%2BPM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/107468649033915515591/albums/5829045734406601633/5864646459246010722?authkey=COfMsMnKufDSag</link><title>How I Knew My Son Had Sensory Processing Disorder If I were to tell you that both of my sons have Sensory Processing Disorder (SPD), you might: a) ask, what is that? b) ask, how did you know that they have it? or c) not believe me unless you had met them — especially my older son — a few years ago. 
I believe that they are mostly recovered because of occupational therapy (OT) interventions over the course of a year and a half and because of ongoing naturopathic medicine and dietary changes. 
My goal here in this article is to help other parents understand what SPD is and what can be done about it. 
To answer the first question, people with SPD have a problem with the wiring from their nervous system to their brain; SPD is a neurological disorder.  SPD is usually more noticeable in kids; most adults have learned to compensate. 
Sensory Seekers and Sensory Avoiders 
There are two kinds of people with SPD: sensory seekers and sensory avoiders.  Sensory seekers are the kids who are constantly seeking stimulation. They like to crash hard into things or people, or they won’t stop spinning or swinging. 
My sons are both sensory avoiders, so I can tell you more about that because of my personal experience. The most mundane things can overstimulate sensory avoiders. Lights are too bright, sounds are too loud, the lightest touch can hurt, food textures can bother them, and motions can make them dizzy or sick. From what I understand, many autistic children also have SPD. 
So, how did I come to know that they had SPD? I’m going to focus here on my older son because he’s the one that had the most pronounced symptoms and because I had learned from him to see those symptoms in my younger son. 
I’m also going to tell you that not all of his symptoms were SPD symptoms but those of gut dysbiosis and immune dysregulation as Beth Lambert details in her book, A Compromised Generation. 
The more you know about neurological disorders such as SPD, autism, and ADD/ADHD, the more you understand that there are many comorbid symptoms that result from the same root causes. I’ll explore the root causes and how I discovered them in a later article. 
Something Was Wrong 
Here are the major signs that I had that something was wrong: 
When my older son was a baby, he would constantly projectile vomit. 
His weight gain was OK until he started eating solid food around five months of age. It was incredibly hard (no, “TORTURE” is the right word here) to feed him any solid food. 
It got so bad that I (being a former Wall Street analyst) made a spreadsheet to show the doctor that he was only eating ten cheerios and one ounce of yogurt a day. The rest of his calories came from my breast milk.  Any food or breast milk I managed to get in him was typically vomited up immediately. 
He didn’t crawl when he should have. Instead, he slithered backwards at eight months of age. 
He would always cry when going for a ride in the car. Looking back now, I’m sure it was motion sickness; he would vomit a lot when going for a ride. 
Loud or unexpected noises would make him cry. I had to remove the batteries from any toy that made noises because he would always cry when the toys made sounds. 
He army crawled until he was 18 months old. 
At his 18-month checkup, the pediatrician discovered that my older son had lost weight. He recommended taking him to McDonald’s and giving him Pediasure. I’ll go over why this was such bad advice in a later article. 
He didn’t walk until he was 20 months old. This was extremely hard for me because he didn’t walk until three weeks before his little brother was born, and I had to carry him everywhere while I was 8+ months pregnant. 
I couldn’t take him anywhere because he would get sick without fail. This scenario continued until we started seeing a naturopathic doctor when he was four years old. Trust me, the Prevacid for his acid reflux and the antibiotics for his ear infections weren’t helping at all. I’ll discuss that in a later article. 
He would always sleep way more than other kids his age. At three years of age, he needed 15 hours of sleep a day; most kids get 10-12 hours at that age. People used to call me “the sleep nazi” because I was so committed to making sure that he got his naps; my life revolved around his sleep schedule. What those people didn’t know is that there was hell to pay from a relentlessly crying child if I didn’t ensure that schedule. 
He was like a little limp rag doll. It was so sad to see other kids happily and busily playing and climbing while my son sat there like a lump on a log. I’ll talk about why this was so in a later article. 
Even as a baby, he would cry if I put him in a swing. He refused to go on slides or merry-go-rounds. This became a real concern for me when he started preschool. I realized that if he were always to play in the sandbox while other kids played on the playground, he would never be able to make friends. I don’t think any mother would want a lifetime of social isolation for their child. 
We couldn’t take him anywhere! While other kids were having fun going to birthday parties and social events, we’d try to go and then have to leave because he would cry at all the overstimulation. Even being around a lot of people would be overstimulating because of all the movement and noise. 
I couldn’t even take him grocery shopping. Sure enough, halfway through the store, the bright fluorescent lights, eye-catching colors, different smells, and loud, echoey noises would get to him, and he would start crying. If I was lucky and had my husband with me, he could take him out to the car to calm down while I finished shopping. If I didn’t, we’d have to suffer through. 
He was a barnacle. I felt as if he were permanently physically attached to me. It wasn’t so bad when he was younger, but after his brother was born, it was extremely difficult to deal with two small, crying children at the same time, who both wanted to be picked up and held at the same time. 
I would feel so guilty about neglecting his little brother, and then I would get angry because it just wasn’t right that the older one’s needs should be taking away from the little one’s. He was older, all of his peers were becoming more self-sufficient, why wasn’t he? 
He had an incredible amount of anxiety. I’ll explore the reason for this and what was done to help him overcome this in a later blog. This is probably one of the more interesting and unknown aspects of neurological disorders. 
He was incredibly withdrawn with his peers. He would usually open up a little more to adults over time. 
It is my understanding that the earlier the intervention occurs, the better, as children’s brains are constantly growing and rewiring themselves. Intervention causes the brain to rewire itself so that the brain properly processes signals from the nervous system. 
My older son’s intervention began when he was 3-1/2 years old. If you were to meet him today, you would have no clue that this is the same child I’ve discussed here. He is happy; he’s social; he’s even extremely outgoing! 
Who knew that this was the child that was really hiding inside this damaged body? Sorry, I’m crying when I write this because this feeling of peace and recovery and health is what I so wished for ever since I was first pregnant with him — doesn’t every mom want that? 
Sign up for our newsletter and find out why this epidemic of children’s chronic illnesses is occurring and what you can do about it.  div.maxbutton-1-container { } a.maxbutton-1 { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; font-family: Arial; font-size: 16px; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold; padding-top: 15px; padding-right: 25px; padding-bottom: 15px; padding-left: 25px; background-color: #2271df; background: linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -moz-linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -o-linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(.45, #2271df), color-stop(1, #12285d)); border-style: solid; border-width: 1px; border-color: #0f2557; border-radius: 4px; -moz-border-radius: 4px; -webkit-border-radius: 4px; text-shadow: -1px -1px 0px #12285d; box-shadow: 0px 0px 2px #333333; -pie-background: linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); position: relative; behavior: url("http://www.epidemicanswers.org/wp-content/plugins/maxbuttons/pie/PIE.htc"); } a.maxbutton-1:visited { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; } a.maxbutton-1:hover { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; background-color: #2270df; background: linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -moz-linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -o-linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(.45, #2270df), color-stop(1, #12295d)); border-color: #0f2557; text-shadow: -1px -1px 0px #12295d; box-shadow: 0px 0px 2px #333333; -pie-background: linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); position: relative; behavior: url("http://www.epidemicanswers.org/wp-content/plugins/maxbuttons/pie/PIE.htc"); }Sign Up Now! 
This document is not a substitute for medical advice, treatment, diagnosis, or consultation with a medical professional.  It is intended for general informational purposes only and should not be relied on to make determinations related to treatment of a medical condition.  Epidemic Answers has not verified and does not guaranty the accuracy of the information provided in this document. 
Maria Rickert Hong can be contacted at maria[at]epidemicanswers[dot]org 
Maria Rickert Hong is a Certified Holistic Health Counselor who received her training from the Institute for Integrative Nutrition.  She specializes in recovery from symptoms of autoimmune, neurological, behavioral and digestive disorders, as she has recovered her own sons from Sensory Processing Disorder, asthma and acid reflux.  She is also a board member, social media director and blogger for Epidemic Answers, a non-profit whose goal is to let parents know recovery is possible from autism, ADHD, SPD, allergies, asthma, autoimmune, Lyme and more.﻿

Meer lezen (164 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-MygNnixjlNM/UWNo4eicYWI/AAAAAAAAAew/RTuxe5W9lHY/w426-h320/DSC01498_2-300x225.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/107468649033915515591/albums/5829045734406601633/5865369481200487906?authkey=COfMsMnKufDSag</link><title>The New Normal By Ashley Morgan, mother of 2 chronically ill children (Leo and Sydney) 
It’s official according to the CDC and other government bodies. The rate of autism has increased no matter what.  The numbers are now 1 in 50. 
Will these new numbers be the tipping point that will cause change in the way we take care of our children?  Will it change how we live? 
Over reporting? Even Michael Kogan, lead author of the HRSA study states there are unaccounted for percentages in the rise. I didn’t get a call, did you? 
Doubtful Leo’s former pediatricians didn’t account for him. And how about those that say we must “proceed with caution?”  What?  Cautiously treat children that desperately need services?  When a very small percentage get the level of services they need already? 
Do we treat the statistics or do we treat what we see before us? 
I was sitting at dinner the other night with new friends after Leo’s baseball game. Our first social dinner out since our move. 
For the day I forgot all about health: Sydney and Leo were having a good health weekend. The day was extraordinary beautiful, a perfect game day.  Leo’s bun-free order didn’t even register.  It was so nice! 
Come to think of it, it has been a break to not know almost every single child in Leo’s 5th grade like I did at our old community.  That constant reminder of our New Normal. 
My bubble burst as somehow the topic of the uneaten bun comes up.  The mom offers that the restaurant has a gluten-free menu available upon request. I smile widely and say all the right things back. 
The dad joins the conversation and says they “used to think Taylor had a gluten problem, but that wasn’t it. They still don’t know what it is.” 
Usually this is my cue to go off about the toxic load, how we are all bearing children with GI and immune problems from the get go.  But, I was tired.  I was bummed.  I didn’t even say something sympathetic or ask more.  Not me!  Did I subconsciously think our new community was immune to the New Normal? 
And what is the New Normal anyway?  The secret isn’t out yet, it’s not okay to openly talk about it.  Doesn’t register with most parents, as they often think they are the ONLY ones with sick kids. 
Many parents don’t even KNOW their kids are chronically ill because their friends, their pediatricians, don’t phrase these problems as chronic illness. 
I’ve gone through 4 pediatricians.  They all didn’t show concern when I asked them, “Aren’t you concerned that all these kids are sick once a month?”  Isn’t that abnormal? 
All 4 say the same thing, like good little soldiers courtesy of the American Academy of Pediatrics. Why think for yourself when you are protected to say and BELIEVE the party line? 
Here is the new normal that I SEE EVERY DAY and I have consistently seen since Leo was born almost 11 years ago. 
Just this summer my good friend Janice that had a girl in Leo’s class and I sat down and looked at the lovely 4th grade class of “typical” children in our affluent public classroom. I knew all the boys, and Janice knew the girls since our kids have grown up with them. 
Just a handful, on average, 5 out of 22 children per class (or 20 out of 88 children) were “normal.” 
These 5 kids did NOT have: ADHD, ADD, an ASD, a mood disorder, an LD, Sensory Integration, chronic eczema, constipation, asthma, allergies (food, environmental), P.A.N.D.A.S., Lyme disease and/or co-infections, a behavior plan, ODD, chronic colds, bronchitis. (See more statistics about the “new normal” on Ashley’s blog here: www.hiddenrecovery.com) 
About 5 out of 22 children per class. That gives you roughly 22% of health. Is it just me or does that not scare the crap out of you? 
Sign up for our newsletter and find out why this epidemic of children’s chronic illnesses is occurring and what you can do about it.  div.maxbutton-1-container { } a.maxbutton-1 { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; font-family: Arial; font-size: 16px; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold; padding-top: 15px; padding-right: 25px; padding-bottom: 15px; padding-left: 25px; background-color: #2271df; background: linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -moz-linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -o-linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); background: -webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(.45, #2271df), color-stop(1, #12285d)); border-style: solid; border-width: 1px; border-color: #0f2557; border-radius: 4px; -moz-border-radius: 4px; -webkit-border-radius: 4px; text-shadow: -1px -1px 0px #12285d; box-shadow: 0px 0px 2px #333333; -pie-background: linear-gradient(#2271df 45%, #12285d); position: relative; behavior: url("http://www.epidemicanswers.org/wp-content/plugins/maxbuttons/pie/PIE.htc"); } a.maxbutton-1:visited { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; } a.maxbutton-1:hover { text-decoration: none; color: #ffffff; background-color: #2270df; background: linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -moz-linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -o-linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); background: -webkit-gradient(linear, left top, left bottom, color-stop(.45, #2270df), color-stop(1, #12295d)); border-color: #0f2557; text-shadow: -1px -1px 0px #12295d; box-shadow: 0px 0px 2px #333333; -pie-background: linear-gradient(#2270df 45%, #12295d); position: relative; behavior: url("http://www.epidemicanswers.org/wp-content/plugins/maxbuttons/pie/PIE.htc"); }Sign Up Now! 
This document is not a substitute for medical advice, treatment, diagnosis, or consultation with a medical professional.  It is intended for general informational purposes only and should not be relied on to make determinations related to treatment of a medical condition.  Epidemic Answers has not verified and does not guaranty the accuracy of the information provided in this document. ﻿

Meer lezen (92 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-bKLNmzLMvMU/UWX6d5NfTeI/AAAAAAAAAfQ/u6YnurbcHfI/w426-h639/girl-on-seesaw-200x300.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/103207155632371173811/albums/5943926890066835009/5943926891363642354</link><title>Many people think ADHD is some made up mental health diagnosis. That it doesn't really exist? 
TODAY'S QUESTION: If you believe that, why? And if you've been diagnosed with ADHD or have a child with an ADHD diagnosis, what are your thoughts about this? Comment below. 

Does ADHD Exist? http://ow.ly/qBHxI 
What is ADD, ADHD? http://ow.ly/qBHBj 
What is Adult ADHD? http://ow.ly/qBHCj #adhd #add #adultadhd #adhddiagnosis #mentalhealth #mentalhealth﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ivj9MiW28Lw/Un0SA_KfK_I/AAAAAAAAIKY/J7g-ffBNdao/w426-h538/3EYf4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/117318520570949674407/albums/5937280917504172545/5937280921300540786</link><title>My son has ADHD, SPD and exec functing issues so I know the benefits of having good resources -- (Stock Photo used below)  Does your child have trouble with motivation, flexible thinking or working memory?  www.LD.org has created an infographic to help understand a day in the life of a child with executive functioning issues. You can get an even deeper understanding of how executive function relates to learning and attention issues through their Executive Function 101 e-book. see more http://www.ncld.org/types-learning-disabilities/executive-function-disorders/what-is-executive-function﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_09_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Pu_iJEsAGxc/UmV1inXSnXI/AAAAAAAAIqQ/lkuQqWaLUXM/w426-h300/Screen%2Bshot%2B2013-10-21%2Bat%2B11.41.53%2BAM.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7406-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/does%20my%20child%20have%20adhd/photos/114273135512064179236/albums/6006163543637366817/6006163546857158898</link><title>A Killer In Your Fridge ~ Sweet Poison... A MUST READ 

September 2, 2013 

tags: aspartame, diabetes, dizziness, fibromyalgia, headaches, 
lupus, migraines, ms, muscle spasms, nutra-sweet 

In October of 2001, my sister started getting very sick She had 
stomach 
spasms and she was having a hard time getting around. Walking was a 
major chore. It took everything she had just to get out of bed; she 
was in so much pain. 

By March 2002, she had undergone several tissue and muscle biopsies 
and was on 24 various prescription medications. The doctors could not 
determine what was wrong with her. She was in so much pain, and so 
sick she just knew she was dying. 

She put her house, bank accounts, life insurance, etc., in her 
oldest daughter's name, and made sure that her younger children were 
to be taken care of. 

She also wanted her last hooray, so she planned a trip to Florida 
(basically in a wheelchair) for March 22nd. 

On March 19, I called her to ask how her most recent tests went, 
and she said they didn't find anything on the test, but they believe 
she had MS. 

I recalled an article a friend of mine e-mailed to me and I asked 
my sister if she drank diet soda? She told me that she did. 
As a matter of fact, she was getting ready to crack one open that 
moment. 

I told her not to open it, and to stop drinking the diet soda! I 
e-mailed her an article my friend, a lawyer, had sent. My sister 
called me within 32 hours after our phone conversation and told me 
she had stopped drinking the diet soda 
AND she could walk! The muscle spasms went away. She said she 
didn't feel 100% but, she sure felt a lot better. 

She told me she was going to her doctor with this article and would 
call me when she got home. 

Well, she called me, and said her doctor was amazed! He is going to 
call all of his MS patients to find out if they consumed artificial 
sweeteners of any kind. In a nutshell, she was being poisoned by the 
Aspartame in the diet soda..and literally dying a slow and miserable 
death. 

When she got to Florida March 22, all she had to take was one pill, 
and that was a pill for the Aspartame poisoning! She is well on her 
way to a complete recovery. And she is walking! No wheelchair! 
This article saved her 
life. If it says 'SUGAR FREE' on the label; DO NOT EVEN THINK ABOUT 
IT! 
I have spent several days lecturing at the WORLD ENVIRONMENTAL 
CONFERENCE on 'ASPARTAME,marketed as 'Nutra Sweet,' 'Equal,' and 
'Spoonful. 'In the keynote address by the EPA, it was announced that 
in the United States in 2001 there is an epidemic 
of multiple sclerosis and systemic lupus. It was difficult to 
determine exactly what toxin was causing this to be rampant. 
I stood up and said that I was thereto lecture on exactly that 
subject. 

I will explain why Aspartame is so dangerous: When the temperature 
of this sweetener exceeds 86 degrees F, the wood alcohol in 
ASPARTAME converts to formaldehyde and then to formic acid, which in 
turn causes metabolic acidosis. 
Formic acid is the poison found in the sting of fire ants. The 
methanol toxicity mimics, among other conditions, multiple sclerosis 
and systemic lupus. 

Many people were being diagnosed in error. Although multiple 
sclerosis is not a death sentence, Methanol toxicity is! 

Systemic lupus has become almost as rampant as multiple sclerosis, 
especially with Diet Coke and Diet Pepsi drinkers. The victim usually 
does not know that the Aspartame is the culprit. He or she continues 
it's use; irritating the lupus to such a degree that it may become a 
life-threatening condition.  We have seen 
patients with systemic lupus become asymptotic, once taken off diet 
sodas. 

In cases of those diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis, most of the 
symptoms disappear. We've seen many cases where vision loss returned 
and hearing loss improved markedly. 

This also applies to cases of tinnitus and fibromyalgia. During a 
lecture, I said, 'If you are using ASPARTAME (Nutra Sweet, Equal, 
Spoonful, etc) and you suffer from fibromyalgia symptoms, spasms, 
shooting, pains,numbness in your 
legs, 
Cramps, 
Vertigo, 
Dizziness, 
Headaches, 
Tinnitus, 
Joint 
pain, 
Unexplainable depression, anxiety attacks, slurred speech, blurred 
vision, or memory loss you probably have ASPARTAME poisoning!' 
People were jumping up during the lecture saying, 'I have some of 
these symptoms. Is it reversible?' 

Yes! 
Yes! 
Yes! 
STOP drinking diet sodas and be alert for Aspartame 
on food labels! Many products are fortified with it! This is a 
serious problem. 
Dr. Espart (one of my speakers) remarked that so many people seem 
to be symptomatic for MS and during his recent visit to a hospice; a 
nurse stated that six of her friends, who were heavy Diet Coke 
addicts, had all been diagnosed with MS. This is beyond coincidence! 

Diet soda is NOT a diet product! It is a chemically altered, 
multiple SODIUM (salt) and ASPARTAME containing product that actually 
makes you crave carbohydrates. 

It is far more likely to make you GAIN weight! 

These products also contain formaldehyde, which stores in the fat 
cells, particularly in the hips and thighs. Formaldehyde is an 
absolute toxin and is used primarily to preserve 'tissue specimens.' 

Many products we use every day contain this chemical but we SHOULD 
NOT store it IN our body! 

Dr. H. J. Roberts stated in his lectures that once free of the 
'diet products' and with no significant increase in exercise; his 
patients lost an average of 19 pounds over a trial period. Aspartame 
is especially dangerous for diabetics. We found that some physicians, 
who believed that they 
had a patient with retinopathy, in fact, had symptoms caused by 
Aspartame. The Aspartame drives the blood sugar out of control. 
Thus diabetics may suffer acute memory 
loss due to the fact that aspartic acid and phenylalanine are 
NEUROTOXIC when taken without the other amino acids necessary for a 
good balance. 

Treating diabetes is all about BALANCE.. Especially with diabetics, 
the Aspartame passes the blood/brain barrier and it then deteriorates 
the neurons of the brain; causing various levels of brain damage, 
Seizures,Depression, Manic depression, Panic attacks, Uncontrollable 
anger and rage.  Consumption of Aspartame causes these same symptoms 
in non-diabetics as well.  Documentation and 
observation also reveal that thousands of children diagnosed with 
ADD and ADHD  have had complete turnarounds in their behavior when 
these chemicals have been removed from their diet. 

So called 'behavior modification prescription drugs' 
(Ritalin and others) are no longer needed. Truth be told, they were 
never NEEDED in the first place! 
Most of these children were being 'poisoned' on a daily 
basis with the very foods that were 'better for them than sugar. 
'It is also suspected that the Aspartame in thousands of pallets of 
diet Coke and diet Pepsi consumed by men and women fighting in the 
Gulf War, may be partially to blame for the well-known 
Gulf War Syndrome. 

Dr. Roberts warns that it can cause birth defects, i.e. mental 
retardation, if taken at the time of conception and during early 
pregnancy.  Children are especially at risk for neurological 
disorders and should NEVER be given artificial sweeteners. 

There are many different case histories to relate of children 
suffering grand mal seizures and other neurological disturbances 
talking about a plague of neurological diseases directly caused by 
the use of this deadly poison.' 

Herein lies the problem: There were Congressional Hearings when 
Aspartame was included in 100 different products and strong objection 
was made concerning its use. Since this initial hearing, there have 
been two subsequent hearings, and still nothing has been done. The 
drug and chemical lobbies have very deep pockets. 

Sadly, MONSANTO'S patent on Aspartame has EXPIRED! There are 
now over 5,000 products on the market that contain this deadly 
chemical and there will be thousands more introduced. Everybody 
wants a 'piece of the Aspartame pie. 'I assure you that MONSANTO, 
the creator of Aspartame, knows how deadly it is. 

And isn't it ironic that MONSANTO funds, among others, the 
American Diabetes Association, the American Dietetic Association 
and the Conference of the American College of Physicians? 

This has been recently exposed in the New York Times. These 
[organizations] cannot criticize any additives or convey their link 
to MONSANTO because they take money from the food industry and are 
required to endorse their products.  Senator Howard Metzenbaum wrote 
and presented a bill that would require label warnings on products 
containing Aspartame, especially regarding pregnant women, children 
and infants. 

The bill would also institute independent studies on the known 
dangers and the problems existing in the general population regarding 
seizures, changes in brain chemistry, neurological changes and 
behavioural symptoms. The bill was killed. It is known that the 
powerful drug and chemical lobbies are responsible 
for this, letting loose the hounds of disease and death on an 
unsuspecting and uninformed public. Well, you're informed now!﻿

Meer lezen (224 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7406_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-vouwU6GdDS4/U1ot7IFSOPI/AAAAAAAAAjU/edxXONREl4Y/w426-h695/0.11.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>