<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7411">lenin mausoleum open</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:59:59" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7411-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lenin%20mausoleum%20open/photos/100849377590089256360/albums/5788355372300333409/5788355372694424482</link><title>In Moscow - Take a hike 
Begin on the cobblestones of Red Square, site of Tsarist executions and Soviet parades, to see the mummified body of Vladimir Ilyich Lenin. There are constant whispers about removing him, but for now the hero of the October Revolution is still in his marble mausoleum and open for business from 10am to 1pm daily except Mondays and Fridays (free entry). 
Soak up the austere beauty of the square before walking down Ilinka and the lanes of Kitai Gorod, dotted with ancient churches and low-rise buildings. Emerge on Lubyanka Square, the monolithic base of the KGB and its successor, the FSB. Head back down the hill to the Soviet-era Russian parliament and you'll be back at the other side of Red Square. Head up Tverskaya, Moscow's main thoroughfare, passing the mayoralty and a statue to Yury Dolgoruky, the city's founder. You'll end up at Pushkin Square, from where you can cut through to Patriarch's Pond, where the Devil first appears in Mikhail Bulgakov's The Master and Margarita.﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7411_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-jRrpr-TktZg/UFReix8sy6I/AAAAAAAAQQk/5IyOYQRGoMU/w426-h320/Moscow_-_Entrance_of_Red_Square.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7411-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lenin%20mausoleum%20open/photos/103213146979013791133/albums/5843723510745826913/5843723512958128850?authkey=CPXMkpelmOrc1gE</link><title>A Short History of Interest in the Communist Hypothesis and the Maoist Revolution in Nepal 

My interest grew in contemporary revolutionary events. I was most attracted to the Maoist revolution in Nepal. This was about 2002 - an added benefit was, that at this time, I had relocated to China. Earlier, in the 1990s I had been in the Former Soviet Union during its demise, and lived several years in the fledgling new republic of Kazakhstan. Engaged during that period in projects of a humanitarian/business nature, it was only slowly that study of socialist history became amusing. 

For me, anarchism meant the purist form of socialism - the spiritual dimension so to speak of socialism, the pure egalitarian essence constituting the evolution of new humanity becoming. Taking into account, as we must, the historical actuality of human nature within the coordinates of our selfishness and violence, I nonetheless fail to dismiss the apparent Utopian vision of the evolution of human nature required for self-organization of society without the imposition of authority, either by a communist vanguard "democratic" parties or the "democracy" of parliamentarian multiparty elites. 

So it was in China that I discovered the early relationship of anarchistic influences on the group of young people in Paris in 1921 who were eventually subsumed, so to speak, by the Marxist-Leninist faction in the formation of the Chinese communist party, there at that time in Paris. My reading therefore extended from anarchists (Classics: Bakunin, Kropotkin, Proudhon, Rocker, then Noam Chomsky mainly) to Marxist-Leninist thought (Marx and Lenin of course, but a lot through Althusser), then reading on Maoism - and eventually, following the scent, to opening my study of Alain Badiou and Savoj Zizek. 

I started writing about the Maoists in Nepal in an earlier blog, Nepal: Ending of Sorrow 2005-6, dedicated to that topic, because it seemed actual engagement in the world struggle should be attempted somehow - then, being "nearby" in China, I went to Nepal in 2006 to feel something for myself and interview a few people about the Maoists, mainly journalists and NGO groups. My focus in the blog was the child-soldier issue. 

The Maoist movement grew out of a spontaneous uprising against an elitist Indian and Monarchist oppression - an almost feudal society, within which the rebellion emerged from among the poor, an under-caste, and also from among powerless indigenous groups. This spontaneity and its self-organization had, I thought, an anarchist flavor. 

Of course, a vanguard Marxist-Leninist Maoist intellectual and authoritarian leadership of the revolution emerged and declared the "official" revolution in 1996. The Maoists now control the majority of elected positions, though certainly not the entire situation (for example, the former rebel army is in cantonment with easy access to UN containers of their weapons, while the former Royal Army is far from disarmed). The whole story of the Maoist revolution, and now their participation in government, is fascinating. To what extent the "Maoists" are now becoming counter-revolutionary, or simply engaged in a modern strategy of revolution, is a compelling story. 

I went to Nepal in 2006 and 2009 for the purpose of interviewing Maoist leaders and developing blog posts on the revolutionary movement and political philosophy issues: 

http://stefandav.blogspot.com/2008_11_01_archive.html 

 2009 (57) 
 November (3) 
Koirala Assured Prachanda of Nepal Government Fall... 
Interview with Bhattarai: Fusing People’s War &amp; In... 
Basanta Interview: Possible Victory or Collapse in... 
 October (5) 
Democracy Now: Savoj Zizek October 15, 2009 
Nepal: Comrade Gaurav speaks on Democracy and Cult... 
Interview of Prachanda, Chairman, UCPN (Maoist) 
Chomsky: Coups, UNASUR, and the U.S. 
Haiti: Dialogues With Tim Ives (1) - Activist Auth... 
 September (9) 
Tick-Tock What’s on the Clock? 
Himalayan Consensus - Spiritual Revolution 
2-Line Struggle At Paris Height: Report from Key M... 
Nepal: Interview with Comrade Binod 
Peter Hallward: The Will of The People: Notes Towa... 
Hallward Reviews Alex Dupuy's "The Prophet and Pow... 
Haiti: The Deluge (Lenin's Tomb) 
Nepal: Maoists launch UNPM 
Announcement Regarding My Blogs 
 July (2) 
Commentary: CPI (Maoist) Open Letter on Nepal Maoi... 
Rosa L. Blanc: Rebuttal of RCPUSA on Nepal Maoists... 
 June (7) 
Indian Maoists Speak: On Intern’l Controversies Am... 
Revolution in Nepal: Presentation to Union of Iran... 
Savoj Zizek: Will the Cat Above the Precipice Fall... 
A Question Over Iran: Can the People Make History ... 
Revolution in Nepal: A Debate 
New Left Review - Slavoj Zizek: How to Begin from ... 
June Maobadi Bookmarks 
 May (7) 
Interview: Chandra Prakash Gajurel 
“Revolution and State Power in Nepal” (Kasama) 
May Maobadi Bookmarks 
Nepal’s Gajurel: State Power is Our Goal (Kasama) 
Nepal: General State of Uncertainty (The Economist... 
Nepal May Day Photos 
Revolution Reports from Nepal - 4 
 April (11) 
April Maobadi Bookmarks 
Revolution Reports from Nepal - 3 
Revolution Reports from Nepal - 2 
Revolution Reports from Nepal - 1 
Ferment in Nepal: Dynamic Vortex of Revolutionary ... 
Baburam Bhatarrai: New Revolutionary State 
On Badiou's Idea of Communism Plus Maobadi Revolu... 
Maobadi: The State of Things Today 
Nepal Army: Serving Impirialism in Afghanistan 
Badiou 101 for the RCP,USA « Kasama 
John Steele: Revolutionary Faithfulness 
 March (5) 
March Nepal Maoism Bookmarks 
Reply to RCPUSA Badiou Polemic 
Aussie Invades Nepal 
Nepal: Revolution Reports (Prologue - Section 3) 
Nepal: Revolution Reports (Prologue - Section 2) 
 February (4) 
 January (4) 
 2008 (23) 
 December (5) 
 November (4) 
The Maoist Debate in Nepal - Part 3 
The Maoist Debate in Nepal - Part 2 
The Maoist Debate in Nepal – Part 1 

Here is an extensive set of photos taken in Nepal in 2009: 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/photos/103213146979013791133/albums/5272059762990390497?authkey=CPye4dSx076gdQ﻿

Meer lezen (132 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7411_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-n8cFTvAh2KI/URkTktt3ktI/AAAAAAAAAqg/pP-tEVat04E/w426-h308/and%2Btheir%2Boff.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7411-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lenin%20mausoleum%20open/photos/111732375221065535359/albums/5686515219227449873/5686515219333568242</link><title>Vladimir Lenin meets YC :)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7411_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-x4uhKj2r4Sk/TuqPdqo61vI/AAAAAAAAHn4/Y46mEm2N8TU/w426-h320/IMG_6199.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7411-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lenin%20mausoleum%20open/photos/102744407669548081722/albums/5853126519518015425/5853126520391278898</link><title>Hugo Chávez in the News 

Censored Media Images to match the one sided exaggerations and divisive propaganda that keeps the masses arguing over things that don't exist, except as vague and ill-defined idealisms. 

Isn't it time we make a real Science out of Economics and Politics, and leave these 19th century emotional assertions and claims behind? 

2 Million people have passed by the casket of the late Hugo Chavez, and millions more will pass in the coming 7 day extended viewing.  Is that how people act when their evil oppressor dies? 

This post will seem one-sided as well, but it is that way simply to give light to the other side of the story.  Truth is something that must be sought out.  He was no saint, but neither was he a devil. 

Some excerpts from an article last year  ( http://goo.gl/guACx ) 

"As a matter of fact, of the 92 elections that we've monitored, I would say that the election process in Venezuela is the best in the world." - Jimmy Carter, who won a Nobel prize for his work through the election-monitoring Carter Center, which has observed and certified past Venezuelan elections said. 

..Venezuelan state TV has only about 5-8% of the country's audience. 

..the opposition still has most of the media, including radio and print media – not to mention most of the wealth and income of the country. 

Since 2004, when the government gained control over the oil industry and the economy had recovered from the devastating, extra-legal attempts to overthrow it (including the 2002 US-backed military coup and oil strike of 2002-2003), poverty has been cut in half and extreme poverty by 70%. 

Millions have access to healthcare for the first time, and college enrollment has doubled, with free tuition for many students. Inequality has also been considerably reduced. By contrast, the two decades that preceded Chávez amount to one of the worst economic failures in Latin America, with real income per person actually falling by 14% between 1980 and 1998. 

Social &amp; Economic charts:  http://goo.gl/ZnONC 

All this while the US is spending millions of dollars within the country, in addition to unknown covert funds – to undermine, de-legitimise, and destabilize democracy in Venezuela (as in many other places). 

If you've read this far, and wish to comment about some terrible thing about Venezuela or Chavez, please provide a link to a credible source. 

#hugochavez #funeral #millionsofsupporters #government #politics #economics #socialism #capitalism #communism #imperialism #propaganda #corporatocracy #oligarchy #plutocracy #ratm  ﻿

Meer lezen (57 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7411_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-PM6IF5125N0/UTp7jyFXITI/AAAAAAAAA7U/Jvmlx681vMI/w426-h288/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7411-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/lenin%20mausoleum%20open/photos/107406362655011292240/albums/5753566754469186865/5753566752479032306</link><title>Communism and Mysticism 

In 1961, from the 17th to the 31st of October, there was the 22nd Congress of Communist Party. 
During this congress numerous interesting things happened. Mainly, it was the split between soviet communism and chinese communism trigerred by Kroutshev open critics of the stalinist doctrine and even of late comrade Stalin. 

One person stood up and spoke: 
"My name is Darya Lazurkina. I was one of the companions of Lenin, I fought with him, he honored me with his friendship. In 1937, during a purge ordered by Stalin, I was arrested and then deported. I was 19 years in a labor camp. 19 years! If I could survive, it's because Lenin was with me, advised me, supported me with His loving presence. When I returned from this hell, I have to own Him. 
Even yesterday he appeared to me and told me: how hard it is to stand next to Stalin who suffered us so much!" 

The old militant finished with his face scarlet, sat down again and then, fell a deep silence in the hall. 

The Isvetzia ignored the fact but, shortly afterwards, the body of Stalin was removed from the mausoleum in Red Square.﻿

Meer lezen (20 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7411_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-SaLFEv_YiCQ/T9jGekkCs_I/AAAAAAAAChs/YIbhwU1SUH0/w426-h237/stalin-lenin-mummies.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>