<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7413">alkan piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:08:29" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/102780081909349586182/albums/5740418687296924305/5740418685789819394</link><title>WAVES (CHILLY GONZALES PIANO REMAKE) 
Erol Alkan &amp; Boys Noize 
http://www.stereomood.com/song/23903 
Photo by Sarah Lee, winner of the week at "YOUR photo &gt;&gt; new stereomood background | CHALLENGE " group on flickr.com 
http://www.flickr.com/groups/your_stereomood_bkg — con Sarah Lee Photography.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-bzsEe2aAktQ/T6oQYXSEUgI/AAAAAAAAAGY/glvlX3zCITI/w426-h283/bgwave.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/103952325840612339342/albums/5969533744411386113/5969533744792840050</link><title>Today is the anniversary of the birth of the Kazakhstani climber Anatolij Nikolaevich Bukreev (16 January 1958–25 December 1997). 

http://grooveshark.com/s/Sonata+In+B+Minor/3MHI3U?src=5 

Bukreev made 18 successful ascents on peaks above 8000 meters. He died in an avalanche on Annapurna in 1997. He was the lead climbing guide for Scott Fischer's ill-fated Mountain Madness Everest expedition in May 1996. He saved three of Fischer's clients, and this was said about Bukreev not long after: "One of the most amazing rescues in mountaineering history performed single-handedly a few hours after climbing Everest without oxygen by a man some describe as the Leonidas [a Greek hero-king of Sparta] of Himalayan climbing." 

Franz Liszt's B Minor Sonata is widely considered to be the Mount Everest of the Romantic piano repertoire, . This work is acknowledged to be the crowning achievement of Liszt’s solo piano output. Many in the classical music world believe this work to be the summit of the entire Romantic era of piano composition. 

The Sonata has four movements, although there is no gap between them. Although Liszt never said that it was a programmatic piece, some people think that it could be based on the Faust legend or perhaps the story of the Garden of Eden; it could even be autobiographical. 

Liszt dedicated the Sonata to his good friend Robert Schumann. Unfortunately, Schumann never had a chance to play it, as by the time the manuscript was delivered to his house he had already been committed to a sanatorium. Clara Schumann thought that it was just a bunch of noise and never played it, either. The German critic  Eduard Hanslick said, "Anyone who has heard it and finds it beautiful is beyond help." But Richard Wagner was very enthusiastic about it, and by the beginning of the 20th century it was recognized as a masterpiece. 

The Sonata is one of Liszt's most analyzed and discussed works. There have been dozens of articles published on the symbolism used throughout. As Jonathan David Keener said, "Many composers, particularly in the 19th century, have attempted to write 'autobiographical' music. Although Franz Liszt never explicitly mentioned that any of his works were autobiographical, the facts we have about his life and the symbolism within his Sonata in B Minor suggest that this piece may serve this purpose, either intentionally or subconsciously. Liszt, having strong ties to the Catholic Church, may have also consciously or unconsciously incorporated religious symbolism into the work. Works that exerted influence on the formal structure and the possible extra-musical meaning of the Sonata in B Minor include Charles-Valentine Alkan's Grande Sonate , Robert Schumann's Fantasy, Op. 17, and Franz Schubert's 'Wanderer' Fantasy. In the end, although there is no written evidence that Liszt intended his Sonata to be autobiographical, . . . the Sonata in B Minor is at very least an unintentional archetype of a spiritual struggle within Liszt's life. Liszt's Sonata in B Minor is an image of a soul laid bare, struggling against sin and guilt, but with hope and joy as well. There is no more complete picture of the many layers of Liszt's personality and beliefs than in his Sonata in B Minor." 

My classical music post for today is Franz Liszt's B Minor Sonata.﻿

Meer lezen (55 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-nR01TCKr0a0/UtgLUB0Vp3I/AAAAAAAAArg/Erj4IPxU8VQ/w426-h237/boukreev%2Bon%2Beverest.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/118153264997029884851/albums/5869641753362821617/5869641757781791026?authkey=CJSh4qbutJPj8AE</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-yxXhFi16BlU/UXUoFHtiETI/AAAAAAAAAzs/p5IW3xkX8NM/w426-h286/22_11_piano.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/112075914100713734066/albums/5809705761971718385/5809705763522858866</link><title>#cool  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_04_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-CBsoSZyCK_4/UKA4nFxRz3I/AAAAAAAAYF0/4VOpLJJJTgM/w426-h319/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/110788105777643761839/albums/5751249499476051441/5751249497320747090</link><title>güzel İstanbul'un﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-HUIwNCnWuhM/T9CK8kZycFI/AAAAAAAAbTg/35E6kCIt8GQ/w426-h320/istanbul.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/106660876363786203340/albums/5816612937515446609/5816612937502517954</link><title>Daily Classical Music Post 

Today is the anniversary of the birth of the French composer and pianist Charles-Valentin Alkan (30 November 1813–29 March 1888). 

http://classical-music-online.net/en/listen/57768 

Alkan was one of the greatest pianists of his day, and many consider him to be a forgotten genius now. He was a child prodigy; he began his studies at the Paris Conservatoire at the age of six, and was part of the Eugène Delacroix–Franz Liszt–Frédéric Chopin social set in the early 1800s. However, he became more and more reclusive, and basically withdrew from society and stopped performing after 1848. In 1861, he wrote to Ferdinand Hiller, "I’m becoming daily more and more misanthropic and misogynous . . . nothing worthwhile, good or useful to do . . . no one to devote myself to. My situation makes me horridly sad and wretched. Even musical production has lost its attraction for me for I can’t see the point or goal." Alkan never married, but there is evidence that the painist Élie-Miriam Delaborde (1839–1913) may have been his illegitimate son. 

Douglas Purl says of Alkan, "He is widely thought of as an eccentric par excellence. In his later years he became intrigued with the pedalier, a pedal board that attaches to the piano and enables full performance of organ literature on the piano. He was fond of playing the compositions of Bach on this device, and composed copiously for it. His piano works require the utmost of skills, attesting to Alkan's own. Few performers care to attempt the difficulties of the Alkanian oeuvre in public, though some display their uncommon prowess by means of his works. The name of Alkan even now remains one capable of engendering vigorous debate in musical circles." 

Alkan wrote almost exclusively for the piano and organ, and his works are at the same time virtuosic and beautiful. (You can hear many of his best piano works here: http://grooveshark.com/#!/album/Laurent+Martin+Piano/6610026.) 

He also had a great sense of humour; his Funeral March on the Death of a Parrot brings to mind Monty Python, of course. This work was written for mixed voices and wind instruments, and it could have been written by P D Q Bach. 

Fred Flaxman says, "Alkan starts with an introductory bogus funeral march. Then the singers enter with 'As-tu déjeuné, Jacot?' Jacot is the French equivalent of Polly; 'As-tu déjeuné'—which means 'Have you eaten?'—is what the French say to their parrots when we would say 'Polly wants a cracker?' The only other words in the piece are: 'Et de quoi?'—literally, and of what? What did you eat?" 

 I could not resist sharing this as my daily classical music post for today. So here, in all its wonderful glory, is Alkan's Funeral March on the Death of a Parrot.﻿

Meer lezen (48 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-xd8Zdf8DO1s/ULjCph_HasI/AAAAAAAALWo/2Bmg3HP5l0w/s426/alkan.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/102442570267394714463/albums/5830636601079754593/5830636601416594914?authkey=CLaG6PWzsoK_eg</link><title>FIVE SONGS YOU MUST HEAR THIS WEEK: JUJU &amp; JORDASH 

Part Seventy-Eight. Juju &amp; Jordash met over a decade ago in Haifa. They each had their own lives going on at the time, but found one another through weekly be-bop jams, with Juju AKA Gal Aner on guitar and Jordash AKA Jordan Czamanski on piano… 

http://erolalkan.co.uk/?p=11274﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1I8I6xvtzOg/UOqVGNHTteI/AAAAAAAABjY/X0nm0IgOLZg/w426-h284/juju%2526jordash.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/114464565015090878153/albums/5820248296814708561/5820248302488578338?authkey=CLqirLC3hP6jYw</link><title>Nature Beautiful....﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-gudvkI7xeJ0/UMWs_n5m6SI/AAAAAAABIHA/mj35Yu-Mtgs/w426-h320/561003_388700661215867_1628299620_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/102361078944455275911/albums/5904651252130093777/5904651252429693698</link><title>The Silence Bellows Through 
Flavel House Astoria, Oregon USA 

Taken with my iPhone 5 I am now headed back from my coast adventure. I can't wait to bring you some of the images from the last couple if days! Have a great day y'all! Edited with +Nik Photography's Snapseed! 

#goonies #flavelhouse #snapseed #nikphotography﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MlzebY0K_gw/UfGJB6ejIwI/AAAAAAAAYBA/wjWDk40CH88/s426/13%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7413-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/alkan%20piano/photos/104572582455810423891/albums/5802345861235239489/5941002260229787042</link><title>DOS GRANDES PIANISTAS DE 1813: ALKAN Y HELLER 

Carlos Tena Tamayo 

Se termina el Festival Internacional Cervantino edición 41, durante el cual se recordó, en el bicentenario de su nacimiento, a dos clásicos de la música. Si se trata de reconocer a músicos que nacieron en 1813, no habría que hacerlo solo con Verdi y Wagner, sino también con otros que fueron grandes en su tiempo aunque poco conocidos en el actual. 

Es el caso del francés, de origen judío, Charles Valentin Alkan uno de los más destacados pianistas de su época. Fue niño prodigio. A los seis años ingresó al Conservatorio de París. Su conocimiento de la música y habilidad para tocar el piano le permitió a los catorce años de edad componer su opus 1 y dar el primer concierto. 

Rivalizó con Liszt, a pesar de ello, este llegó a opinar que Alkan tenía la técnica más formidable de todos cuantos conocía. Con Chopin tuvo gran amistad y también fue muy admirado por Schumann. Alkan dedicó más de seis años solo a escribir varios estudios, opus y un concierto. Sus composiciones son complejas en su ejecución y muy interesantes. 

El pianista que lo intenta interpretar requiere gran destreza para hacerlo, pues la velocidad con que se deben tocar varias de sus composiciones las tornan difíciles. Estoy seguro que para los afectos al piano, tendrán una grata sorpresa cuando escuchen la obra de Charles-Valentin Alkan, pero si observan a un buen ejecutor, será doble el gusto. 

Se sabe que Alkan dejó de dar conciertos en público por dedicarse a traducir al francés la biblia desde su idioma original. Su muerte ocurrida a los 74 años (marzo 1888) se convirtió en una leyenda, se dice que un librero cayó sobre él en su casa, al tratar de alcanzar de la parte más alta, el Talmud, libro sagrado de los judíos. 

Otro pianista importante nacido en mayo de 1813 fue el húngaro Stephen Heller. También un niño prodigio. A los nueve años tocó un concierto para dos pianos con su maestro, F. Brauer. En París se convirtió en concertista, compositor y profesor. Su producción musical fue muy extensa. Tuvo influencia en compositores románticos como Rachmaninov.  También tuvo amistad con Chopin, Liszt y Brahms. A pesar de haber sido un grande del piano, falleció en el olvido el mismo año que Alkan, aunque ocho meses después (noviembre 1888). 

Alkan y Heller son un buen ejemplo de grandes pianistas compositores que van quedando en el abandono de la mayoría, eclipsados por los grandes que han tenido la fortuna de ser promovidos o tal vez auspiciados por mecenas o promotores con mayor poder económico. Buena idea la del FIC de recordar a los grandes en el aniversario de su nacimiento, pero vale la pena unas líneas para los que fueron famosos y ahora ya no lo son, aunque no por ello dejan de ser genios de la música. ﻿

Meer lezen (51 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7413_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4gV1t971EIw/UnKuFDLKDaI/AAAAAAAAAZM/J7AQFpMjQVs/w426-h320/Diapositiva1.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>