<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7421">story magic flute</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:42:21" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/112349041503767076030/albums/5973208323906159025/5973208325679940674</link><title>It's Mozart's 258th birthday today. Read the story about his famous Masonic #Opera 'The Magic Flute' http://yovisto.blogspot.de/2012/09/mozarts-famous-masonic-opera-magic-flute.html 
#music #Vienna #classicism ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-FfS9OnG0M1A/UuUZUyWPBEI/AAAAAAAACmI/-I7VcBBUfE8/w426-h551/mozart-cartoon.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/100212613856984996154/albums/5958443308169273905/5958443311663395682</link><title>Your daily Exalted inspiration! And some setting neep. 

Warning: TOO LONG. 

It's 2013, almost 2014. There have been a number of stuffs released since Exalted hit the shelves in 2001. In the core book for the 1st edition it mentions some media that might help inspire the reader, including Tanith Lee's Flat Earth and Final Fantasy VII. It happened again in 2006 with 2nd edition, updating the list with the video game Dynast Warriors and a few others. 

Those are great, in their own way. Big swords and big combat and big magic. But Exalted doesn't cleave to those inspirations alone. My affection for the gameline has very little to do with a single hero standing against a tide of foes, or the size of her daiklave. 

This is my list. 

Books: 

Tanith Lee's Night's Master 

This is a point both editions of Exalted try to drive home, and they're right. This is epic fantasy at is most fantastic. Just read it. It's amazing, and is undisputably Exalted. 

&lt;swoon&gt; Azhrarn. &lt;/swoon&gt; 

Stephen King's The Waste Lands 

Remnants of an advanced civilization, "old" high technology, characters from vastly different worlds, wandering experiments from a lost age, a lynchpin of realities, a chosen group with great power long since fallen from their authority. Travel. So. Much. Travel. Exciting, interesting, exploration-filled travel. Even the dreadful Blaine the Mono could be a spirit-intelligence from the forgotten age. 

Brandon Sanderson's The Way of Kings 

It has an essence equivalent that powers martial artists and a magical panoply and insane sorcery. It has the big combat and big swords and big magic, but also a great example of codifying that power in an unkind authority. This is what Exalted would be with more western influences. 

Movies: 

The Adjustment Bureau 

Fate and it's agents, destiny and the fight against a story already told. Mysterious, fickle authorities and the power of human hearts to change immortal minds. Divine power with an artificed look. Great flick. Though modern, it's an amazing example of Sidereals in action. 

The Man with the Iron Fists 

Not, uh, the best film in the universe, but it has so much visual Exalted appeal. Artifacts and naming conventions you could steal wholesale. One character even uses Invulnerable Skin of Bronze, I shit you not. 

Hero 

The CG was dated when it hit theaters, but goddamn the storytelling in this movie is delicious. The memories of combat, the landscape of an intense mental conflict, the styles of combat. This barely beats out Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon for best Exalted wuxia, because it isn't as driven by a macguffin. 

Painted Skin 2: The Resurrection 

This movie has an example of almost every Exalted type. It's the story of a Solar who falls for a wood aspected Dragon-Blood, and befriends an Infernal -- whose Lunar friend finds her humanity in a mortal sorceror. They battle an Abyssal who demands the Solar's hand in marriage. Totally awesome film. 

Half of Studio Ghibli's films: Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind, Spirited Away, Princess Mononoke 

I can't even say how much Spirited Away and Princess Mononoke have colored my perceptions of Creation and its spiritfolk. Fickle, crazy, arrogant, insulting, confusing and sometimes weirdly kind, spirits are best when they've got weird greeds and bizarre motives. Also, San is an amazing Lunar, and makes not-shapeshifting somehow awesome. Ashitaka is a fantastic Solar, wormy anima visuals aside. He even limit breaks! 

Nausicaa otVotW, on the other hand, has an amazing example of a Zenith in Nausicaa herself, and the empire that accosts their village is either the Realm, or Lookshy. The wildlife is also great megafauna for the deserts nearer to Creation's southernmost Elemental Pole. 

Escaflowne: the Movie 

The visuals in this movie are ridiculously fun. It looks so good! It has so much Exalted in it it's hard to list it all. A powerful, supernatural empire hunting the last remnants of the previous empire. A "wild hunt" of sorts. Beastmen. Ancient, life-force-driven machines. Over-the-top swordplay. Even without the warstrider analogs, this movie is among my favorite action-focused animes. 

Video Games: 

Shadow of the Colossus 

Forget the titular colossi (though they're wonderful inspiration themselves), the zeal of the hero and the fearlessness of his noble steed are way more Exalted than the casual army-slaying attitude of other games. A dubious contract with a faceless voice, a magical sword of light, a forbidden civilization in ruin, a caste of warrior exorcists, and a quest for love? AW YISS. And that's to say nothing of the music. Holy shit. 

Vagrant Story 

Dark powers, high drama, and powerful skills and sorcery from a previous life? Improbable armor on the dudes? Power exhanged for limbs and hearts? Supernatural conspiracies? A city-sized spellbook? Battle-blacksmith spy-magician? "Have a bit more respect for faery tales[...]" 

Journey 

At first glance, Journey doesn't have much of a tale to tell. No word is spoken. No word written (in an actual langauge). But there's a narrative, and it's beautiful and heartbreaking. The story of a great civilization brought to ruin by its own strife, and the spiritual path its remaining few must make through the terrible ruins of history. 

Asura's Wrath 

I'm of two minds on this one. It's so over the top I can barely speak to its scale. You punch a dude who is literally twice as big as the planet to atoms. That's specifically not why I think it's Exalted, though. There's a style here that's amazing. A mixture of technology and traditional Buddhist art that is totally fantastic. Clay and gold. Artifacts and Alchemicals. 

Final Fantasy XIII 

Individuals with a terrible, misunderstood power. An authority spreading misinformation and hunting those chosen few down like dogs. Great and awful magics. It isn't my favorite system in the world, but I love the cast (yes, even Hope and certain totally batshit pseudo-accents) and the way the world works. Which is Exalted inspiration on its own! 

Comics: 

Saga 

Maybe the best comic on shelves. Magic with weird rules and technology indistinguishable from magic. War and love and violence and consequences. The single greatest familiar in the universe. It's Exalted because it's a story about exceptions and oddities, and the colorful cast sings of god-blooded, wyld mutations, beastmen and Extigents. It's political fantasy, weird scifi, and a dozen other things. 

Yoshitaka Amano's Mateki: The Magic Flute 

It's only sort of a comic, but the story is almost as captivating as the art. Closer to Amano's work on Sandman than Final Fantasy. Amano's work always reminds me of the Fair Folk. 

Music: 

Takenobu 

An awesome, cello-filled clash of east and west, folk and classical. Just lovely and haunting. His first album is best. 

The Kill Bill vol. 1 &amp; 2 soundtracks 

Not every track is appropiate, but those that are? Damn. 

Art source: andrewryanart.deviantart.com﻿

Meer lezen (174 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vdiyR43-6_g/UrCkn23_s2I/AAAAAAAAPTA/uYJTKuckfkQ/w426-h237/showdown_by_dunechampion-d5e39wn.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/109084046155091816356/albums/5998058058615143985/5998058059152493682</link><title>Soprano Layla Claire featured by +WQXRClassical Operavore as a 'Singer to Watch': ""The Canadian soprano Layla Claire is fast developing a reputation as a #Mozart interpreter. Having played Fiordiligi in the +Canadian Opera Company’s Cosi fan tutte this winter, she's now gearing up to sing Pamina in the MinnesotaOpera Opera's The Magic Flute; this summer she'll be Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the +Glyndebourne Festival." read on here: http://www.wqxr.org/#!/story/singer-to-watch-layla-claire/ #opera   #pr   #interview  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-mNk8UFw4rAM/Uz1iBpX0DHI/AAAAAAAADHE/qcsk-6u5eAE/w426-h511/layla-lowres.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/100422114511957026168/albums/6002712141564339377/6002712144928835858</link><title>Jai Shree RadheyKrishna 
A True Divine Love Of Shree RadhaKrishna, Though Physically Different but Spiritually One and Inseparable. 
Here Is A Story Of Last Meeting Of Shree RadhaKrishna, Though Last Meetintg, but yet They were Always Present in each other. 

Part 1 
Krishna went to his mother, Yashoda, and turned on the full force of his charm. "Mother," he said, "I want you to send a message to Radha's family, asking for her hand in marriage." Yashoda thought this was another of Krishna's pranks. But when Krishna persisted she replied firmly and clearly. 
She said, " You cannot marry Radha for several reasons. She is engaged to Aiyyan. You are the son of a chief and her family is much lower in status. She is older than you. And she is a brazen girl, totally unfit to be a wife." 

Krishna then used his final weapon. He threatened that his mother would not only lose a lovely daughter-in-law if she refused, but also her son. Yashoda then asked him to settle the matter with his father. So Krishna went to Nand and repeated his request. His father said with a wink, "I have noticed that you are spending more and more time with the girls lately. No wonder you want one for yourself. There are many chieftains who would willingly wed their daughters to you." Krishna interrupted and said that he wanted to marry Radha and not a chieftain's daughter. The arguments were repeated. Finally Nand said he was no match for Krishna in a debate. Their family priest, Sage Garg, was arriving the next day and Nand would refer the matter to him. 
Krishna told Sage Garg that since he and Radha desired each other, they should get married. Garg replied that desire as a reason for mating is the way of animals. The matching of temperaments, family backgrounds and future plans should be considered while selecting a spouse. Krishna stated that even as per these considerations he could not find any fault with his choice. Radha's temperament was perfectly matched to his, their family backgrounds were similar and both of them would be spending the rest of their lives in Vrindavan doing what the men and women of Vrindavan had always been doing. 
Sage Garg then said, "I think it is time to tell you the truth about your birth. You are the eighth son of Prince Vasudev and Devaki. It was prophesied that you would kill your maternal uncle Kansa and deliver the Yadava race from his tyranny. Hence you were secretly brought to Gokul and were brought up as the son of Nand and Yashoda. The great sage Vyasa has foretold that you will be the leader of the Yadava race and the saviour of all humanity. Hence I have brought Sage Sandipani with me, who is to begin your education in the scriptures, procedures of governance and the art of warfare. We all have great expectations of you. Radha is a village girl. She will not be a suitable companion in this endeavour. That is why we are against this marriage." 
Krishna quietly digested what had been said and then replied softly but firmly. "First of all I would like to aver that Nand and Yashoda are my parents and I will always look upon them as such. Then I would request you to keep the story of my birth a secret from the people of Vrindavan till it is time for me to leave. If they learn the truth then their attitude towards me will change and this I will not be able to bear. You say that I am to deliver all humanity from suffering. I cannot begin this formidable task by thrusting the person who loves me the most into unbearable suffering. 
From the moment Radha saw me tied to the mortar eight years ago, there has not been a single day that she has not waited for me. With every breath that she has drawn she has taken my name. For her spring comes when I come to meet her and winter begins when I leave her. If I had died fighting Kaliya, the poisonous snake, many in Vrindavan would have been heart broken. Mother would have never stopped crying and father would have lost his smile forever. But Radha would have given up her life there and then. Radha lives for me and in me and I live for her and in her. If you prevent this marriage, you will be depriving me of the right and power to carry out the great tasks you want me to. I beseech you with folded hands to grant your consent." 
Sage Garg was overcome by the rationality and intensity of this speech. He gave his consent. Radha's joy knew no bound. And in the celebrations that followed Aiyyan was forgotten. 

\--------- 
Part 2 
The news that Krishna was leaving spread like wildfire throughout Vrindavan. The youth sensed that they were losing a staunch friend; the maidens sensed that they were losing a man of their dreams and Radha.... 
Before Radha could even begin to ponder upon the consequences, the melodious sound of a flute wafted throughout the village. The women left what they were doing and ran to the Madhuban. There was no time to wear their ornaments or comb their hair. While running they tried to arrange their clothes to give an appearance of modesty but soon gave up. Radha picked up her anklets and raced ahead of everyone else, her bosom heaving with excitement. Her Kahn was calling her. Krishna was standing in his usual spot, his right leg crossed over his left, and playing his flute with gay abandon. Radha cuddled up to him and began to sway in the rhythm of his music. The other maidens formed circles around them and began to dance. The men folk, the elders and children too had come there, but were watching from a distance, so as not to embarrass the dancers. 
Every maiden wanted Krishna to dance only with her, every maiden imagined that Krishna was dancing only with her and the spectators could see a multitude of Krishnas, each dancing separately with one of the lasses. Such is the power of love; such is the power of faith. This was the Maharasa or the "great dance". When the dancing stopped Krishna and Radha were missing. 
Radha and Krishna were heading for their favourite nook in the Madhuban, near the Yamuna river. Radha was in Krishna's arms, her tousled head resting on his shoulder. 
"Will you always be like this, Kahn?" asked Radha. 
"Always," he replied, "Till the sun and the moon endure." 
But Radha was not satisfied by this assurance. "Will you always remember me?" she asked. 
"How can I forget you," replied Krishna, "You are my Goddess of beauty and joy." 
They reached their destination and huddled close together on the mossy grass. They kissed tentatively at first, but the pent-up passions soon engulfed them and they united in body and soul. After a while Radha got up and began to tie her disheveled tresses into a knot. "Will we always be together after we are married," she inquired uncertainly. Krishna replied that they were inseparable and that they had just got married according to the Gandharva tradition. According to the this tradition, sexual intercourse among consenting couples was tantamount to the marriage rituals provided the male was of royal descent. 
"You will always be my prince," said Radha, "but you are not of royal blood. And I do not regret our love making so you do not have to justify it." Then Krishna narrated the story of his birth, of his being the redeemer and his leaving for Mathura before dawn. Radha let the whole narration sink in and appeared to be forming some decisions of her own. "Is there anything that can make you stay?" she asked. 
"Nothing can hold me from my destiny and my duty." Replied Krishna firmly. "Why do you worry? Are you afraid that I will die at Kansa's hands? It will be over soon and then I will call you to Mathura" 
"No, I am sure that you will kill Kansa. And then you will become the king of the Yadavas. A lot of people will look up to you, will bow down before you, and will depend on you. You will become the saviour of humanity," said Radha. 
"And you will be my queen, by my side always," added Krishna. 
"No," replied Radha surely. "I am a poor cowherd girl. I will be lost in the palace intrigues. There will be many princesses wooing you and wanting you at any cost. I will be awkward and gawky compared to them. This village girl will be a handicap to you in your new avatar. For you will undeniably change. Your life will be filled with politics and manipulations. You will fight wars and participate in destruction. That will be a part of your destiny and I don't pass judgment. But the Kahn I loved was a cowherd boy, whose calling in life was to graze cattle, who played the flute and danced in the woods and whose crown was a peacock feather and weapon was a bamboo staff. I will not be able to see you in any other form." Radha was now sobbing convulsively and Krishna has to take her in his arms to calm her down. 
After regaining her composure Radha continued. "Please listen to me Kahn! Let me stay here and take care of your parents. Here in Vrindavan I will see you in the waters of the Yamuna, the slopes of Govardhan and the trees of Madhuban and hence I will always be with the Kahn I knew." 
They sat silently for a while reflecting on the past, savouring the last moments of togetherness and coming to terms with the future. Krishna broke the silence. "You are right Radha. In Mathura I will have to change and if you come with me then you will have to change as well. I will not be the Krishna you knew and you will not be the Radha I knew. We will not be able to replicate the magic we weaved here. And without either of us here, Vrindavan too will wither away. But if you stay back, then Vrindavan will become an enduring shrine to our love and you will be its deity." Krishna then told Radha that preparations had been made for them to get married in the Vedic manner and since the auspicious moment was drawing near they should return. Radha requested that Krishna leave his flute behind as a gift to her and Krishna readily agreed. 
It was time for the final parting. The villagers had turned out to personally meet Krishna. Radha stood beside her mother in law, dressed in bridal finery, her face covered modestly by her sari. From time to time she looked up at Krishna, each glance a pledge of eternal devotion. Krishna's eyes met Radha's each time and he smiled at her reassuringly. Any other communication in front of the elders would be out of place. So no words were said and no hands touched. Krishna touched his mother's feet and mounted the bullock cart with Nand, Balaram and Akrura. Radha looked without blinking at the cart till it disappeared round the corner and then fainted. Krishna never set foot in Vrindavan again. 

\------------- 

Part 3 
Krishna never set foot in Vrindavan again. But legend has it that he did come face to face with Radha once, later … much later. After he had killed Kansa and become the leader of the Yadavas. After he had shifted his capital from Mathura to Dwarka. After he had married Rukmini and Satyabhama and the others. 
It was at the occasion of a total solar eclipse. A massive congregation had gathered at the field of Kurukshetra to bathe in the holy tank of Syamantapanchaka after the eclipse. (It was said that a dip in this tank after eclipses purified the soul. It was here that the great sage Parshurama had come to atone for killing the evil kings and warriors. He established that all killing is sinful, even when the persons killed are evil and deserve to die, even killing in war. Hence all killings have to be atoned for.) All the major kingdoms were represented. Krishna was leading the Yadavas. Dhritarashtra of Hastinapur was there with his sons the Kauravas and nephews the Pandavas. So were many other kings. Little did they know that soon they would be engaged in a do or die battle on this very field some years later. Many common folk had come as well. Among them was the cowherd community of Vrindavan. 
When Krishna's parents, Vasudev and Devaki learnt of this they wanted to meet Nand and Yashoda. They had never met Krishna's foster parents and wanted to thank them for taking care of their son in his formative years. The meeting was a very emotional one. Balaram met his old cronies and reminisced about old times. 
But when Krishna came face to face with Radha no words were said. No hands stretched to meet each other, no smile played upon lips and no eyes sparkled with delight. Only a million thoughts flashed through each mind and a deluge of tears flowed from each pair of eyes. Radha had promised not to get involved with Krishna's later life and she intended to keep that promise. Krishna did not want to say or do something that would make things difficult for Radha. They stood staring stonily at each other till all the thoughts were exhausted and the eyes were dry. Though Krishna and Radha had been physically separated, they had been inseparable spiritually and would continue to be so till the end of the world. Radha had seen the splendour in which Krishna's wives lived and the joy he lavished on them. But she knew that his tears were for her alone and that each drop was more valuable than all the riches of the world. Krishna knew that Vrindavan would be enshrined forever because of Radha's sacrifice. Both were assured that they had taken the correct decision many years ago. Without saying anything they said everything and went their separate ways. They never saw each other again.﻿

Meer lezen (218 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-XQl5CPEMOko/U03q5F9oCRI/AAAAAAAAHdA/-JXHhU7X6kk/w426-h562/2014+-+1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/111299623601739408634/albums/5804625204465822209/5804625208359374658</link><title>In the words of Bar Mix Master “the blend of the charred oak, spiciness, of Bourbon; the sweet, herbal, and slight caramel flavour of Sweet Vermouth; and the indescribable flavour of bitters combine to make a cocktail like none other.”  This cocktail “is said to have been invented in New York’s Manhattan Club in 1874 at the request of Winston Churchill’s mother, Lady Randolph Churchill to celebrate a newly elected governor” (http://barmixmaster.com). The cocktail still these days is known as the Manhattan. 

  This is a multi-part story of one of the greatest and best-loved groups in the history of soul music, the Manhattans, told by its present end ex-members and many other music business figures, who have been dealing with the group throughout the years.  As to the origin of the name of the group, there have been different recollections.  One member is in favour of the skyline they could see right across the water from the Jersey City - “Manhattan was close to New Jersey.  It was easy to remember, and we just felt we wanted to represent class” – but another member, Mr. Winfred “Blue” Lovett, remembers slightly differently: “We collectively came up with the Manhattans, but we referred ourselves to the alcoholic drink.  Everybody thought the name was from the borough of the New York anyway, so we just grabbed on to that.” 

(The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
The five singers, who became the first members of the Manhattans in the early 60s, went to two Jersey City high schools in the 50s - George Smith and Richard Taylor to Snyder High and Winfred Lovett, Kenneth Kelly and Edward Bivins to Lincoln High. 

(Sonny Bivins pic taken from www.themanhattans.net) 
EDWARD “SONNY” BIVINS 

    Edward Jesse Bivins, Jr. (tenor) is the senior member of the group in terms of his age, as he was born on January 15 in 1936.  Still today he’s best known as “Sonny” - “when I was young, I was always smiling” – but his other nickname used to be “Dip.” Sonny: “I played baseball.  Then I started singing, and I couldn’t sing and play baseball at the same time.”  He played minor league baseball in the Jersey City All-Stars. 

  Sonny was born in Macon, Georgia, to Willie and Edward Bivins.  “My father tap-danced, and I got into music through my father.”  Sonny had two brothers, Donald and James, but no sisters.  In Macon he started singing in a school choir and glee club.  “We moved no New Jersey in 1950, and I went to Lincoln High in 1951.  In school I was two years ahead of Kenny Kelly and Blue Lovett, and we all used to sing around school and on the street corners.” 

  Sonny’s early idol was Sam Cooke, and of the later acts he puts the Temptations first, but thinks highly of the Dells, the Spinners, the O’Jays and B.B. King, too.  His all-time favourite record is To Each His Own by Nat King Cole.  He has five children – Mark, Pam, Doug, Yvette and Kenny – but they’re not active in music.  “They have their own things they wanted to do in life.” 

(On the right: Early Smitty; The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
  Sonny reminisces how he met their future lead singer, George Smith, for the first time during a teen dance night at the YMCA in 1953 in Jersey City.  “I heard somebody playing the piano in the adjacent room from the dance hall.  Slowly I opened the door and peeked my head inside and saw a young, teenage guy about my age playing the piano and singing I Cried in my Mother’s Arms.  I walked over to him and started to harmonize with him.  We looked at each other, smiled and we introduced ourselves.  His name was George “Smitty” Smith.  As time went on, our relationship grew closer and we eventually left high school and went into the military vowing to complete our high school education once we got out of the service.” 

  In 1954 Sonny joined the NG.  “After the National Guard, I was in the Air Force in Germany till 1957.” 

(Smitty at the Apollo; The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
GEORGE “SMITTY” SMITH 

  The second oldest in the first line-up of the Manhattans is George Hoza Smith (tenor), who was born in Florida on December 18 in 1939.  Jeanie Scott: “His mother couldn’t remember his actual birth date.  It was either supposed to be December the 18th, or December the 28th.”  Mrs. Jeanie Scott, formerly McCarthy, who today is the wife of the legendary Jimmy Scott and handles his business (www.jimmyscottofficialwebsite.org ), lived with Smitty until his untimely passing in December 1970.  “We got together in 1969, so I was with him maybe a year and a half.” 

(On the right: Jimmy Scott, The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
  “When Smitty was a toddler, perhaps four years old, his mother and his father separated.  The only thing he could remember about his father is him walking with some dogs (laughing).  His mother moved to Jersey City with Smitty and his oldest sister Marion.  Marion has lived her whole adult life in California.  Eventually his mother married another man, whose last name was Smith, and he became Smitty’s stepfather, and that’s how he got his name.  Smitty’s mother had ten children.  After Marion and Smitty – who they all called ‘Brother’ – she had eight other children, so Smitty had three half brothers and five half sisters.  Tommy was Smitty’s youngest brother and he had a group called 8 Mile High.  The other brothers, Bobby and Joe, had a group of their own, too, Out of Limits.” 

  “Smitty had three children.  When Smitty was fifteen years old, his girlfriend got pregnant with George, Jr., aka ‘Dewberry’, so they got married.  George, Jr. looked exactly like him.  After he came back from the service, she had another baby while he was away, Michelle, which Smitty took as his own.  Later he had his daughter Paula with a girlfriend.” 

  Through his mother, Smitty first sang gospel music in church and then joined his newly-found singing pals, while in Snyder High.  “Smitty and Sonny were close at the time, Blue and Kenny were close”.  After Snyder High, Smitty joined the Air Force and was stationed in California for two years. 

(Smitty &amp; Jeanie; The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
  Jeanie: “My first memory of the Manhattans would be hearing their records on the radio - I’m the one that Love Forgot, Searchin’ for my Baby...  I had been going to all their shows and I kind of had a crush on Smitty, but I was afraid to talk to him.  I had seen him around, and I was peeking around corners at him.  Eugene Pitt of the Jive Five would tease me and say ‘go on and knock on their dressing room door and talk to Smitty’, but I wouldn’t go over there.  It wasn’t until a couple of years later.  They were about to do a show at the Cheetah in New York on 52nd street.  I sent Smitty a message and he called me up and he came over to my house the next day.  We got together, and we were together ever since, and he moved me in his mother’s house until he passed.  As a matter of fact, I stayed with her for a couple of years after that and I remained close to the family throughout the years, especially with Smitty's Mother, brother Bobby - who was like a brother - and Smitty's children George, Jr., &amp; Paula.” 

WINFRED “BLUE “LOVETT 

  Winfred Lorenzo Lovett (bass) was born in Jersey City, New Jersey, on November 16 in 1940 to Lovonia and William Lovett.  “My father was a singer in church, and he made it mandatory that I sing in church on every Sunday also.”  Winfred has two sisters, Billie and Gwendolyn, and today he resides in Phoenix, Arizona. 

  Most know this bass singer extraordinaire best under the simple moniker of “Blue.”  “It’s my so-called nick-name.  If you hung out on streets - and you’re not necessarily bad or are in gangs and nothing like that - you had a nick-name, and because of my complexion and a long hair and a beard “Blue Jesus” was my name.  I naturally dropped the ’Jesus’ and kept the ‘Blue’.”  During his high-school years he was also called “Bacon” for a short while. 

  Blue has seven children: William, Robyn, Tania, Kia, Damon, Marisa and Rico.  “None of them do anything professionally in music, except Rico, who was born in 1986 and who does rapping.  All my kids live on the west coast.” 

  Some of Blue’s favourite recordings of all times include Neither One of Us by Gladys Knight &amp; the Pips and Sexual Healing by Marvin Gaye.  “Also Luther Vandross has come up with some magnificent songs that I like.  I think my all-time bass singer would be Melvin Franklin of the Temptations.  The Temptations started us off.  We patterned us after the Temptations and Curtis Mayfield and the Impressions.” 

  In Lincoln High, Blue played football and baseball.  “Then I couldn’t play sports because of my asthma.  Baseball was out and football was definitely out, so my third choice was music, and I never thought that I would get an opportunity.  If you were from the New York area, it was very hard back then to get a record deal.  You had to be discovered.” 

  “I did locally high school groups, but nothing ever happened.  We just sang to entertain our families, fans, girlfriends... In Lincoln high school Sonny, Kelly and I took part in a singing contest in a variety show and we won.  I forgot the name of our group in high school.”  All five Manhattans boys got to know each other already in the 50s.  “All five of us met during the high school days.  Sonny Bivins, Kenneth Kelly and myself went to Lincoln, and Richard Taylor and George Smith went to Snyder, which were competing high schools in Jersey City.” 

  In the late 50s Blue was drafted.  “I was in the Air Force.  I was in France, but they closed that base and I was transferred to Wiesbaden, Germany.  I was discharged in 1960...’61.  There in Germany I had a group of my own called the Statesmen.  It was me and four other guys, but not Sonny and Richard.  They were stationed in the Air Force in Germany, too, but they were stationed elsewhere.” 

KENNETH “WALLY” KELLY 

  Kenneth Bernard Kelly (tenor) was born on January 9 in 1941 in Jersey City to Eloise and Lloyd Kelly.  Kenny: “My parents are both deceased.  My mother belonged to a chorus, when she was younger.  She sang in a church choir.”  Besides one brother, Adonis, Kenny has three step-brothers and a sister.  His two children are called Kai and Monee. 

  Kenny’s last name is spelt both Kelley, and Kelly.  “My father spelt his last name Kelly.  There happened a vocabulary error somewhere along the line, and my last name got changed to Kelley.  As I grew older, according to certain situations I ran in and out of, they assumed it was supposed to be spelt Kelley.  I didn’t go through the corrections, so there exist two spellings of my last name.  Most of my IDs have Kelly, so I mostly use Kelly.” 

  Kenny’s nickname is Wally.  “We had a guitar player named Charles Reed and he gave it to me, because I was always telling people different little things and answering to their questions.”  Kenny is the only college graduate among the members of the group, and he graduated from Morgan State University in Baltimore, Maryland, in 1963. 

  “Being in a group situation, we idolized a lot of groups – the Spaniels, and later the Temptations and Smokey &amp; the Miracles.  Later I had one idol and that was Ray Charles.”  Kenny’s favourite record is Letter Full of Tears by Gladys Knight &amp; the Pips, and besides singing he plays piano, trumpet and baritone sax. 

  “I played in a high school band in Jersey City.  I started messing around with my neighbour next door, which was Sonny.  He played guitar.  We just started singing together, and he introduced me to some guys, who sang.  It was just something we did, because we liked doing it.  Group singing was popular at that point of time.  We all would cross each other at some point.  We formed different groups, and from that we eventually came in contact with each other.” 

  “Sonny belonged to this one group, and he brought me in to hear what the group sounded like.  I don’t remember the name of the group, but one member kept missing the rehearsals and I – having been there so frequently and knowing his parts – said ‘okay, I’ll do it’.” 

  “I grew up with some of the members of the Manhattans.  We met in the 50s.  I don’t know what groups Richard came out of and I don’t remember what groups Blue was with.  Blue was with several groups.  A lot of the groups didn’t stay together.  They’d form and break up.  One group that I, Sonny, Smitty and somebody else were part of was called the Socialeers.  We sang in local clubs and talent shows.  That group started breaking up, because people had other commitments.”  Right after Lincoln High, Kenny joined the Navy, which was followed by his three-year college period in Baltimore.  He would meet the other fellows again in 1963. 

THE DULCETS 

  One early incarnation of the Manhattans was as lucky as to even cut a record in 1961.  Smitty, Blue, Sonny, Ethel Samuels and Buddy Bell had formed another group and they called themselves the Dulcets.  This quintet under a misspelt name of the Dorsets released a single on a New York label called Asnes.  The plug side, a slowly and heavily swaying post-doowop, novelty type of a song, was titled Pork Chops (Asnes 101), and in style and interpretation it owes a lot to the Olympics or the Coasters of those days.  Blue: “yes, that’s the flavour we had on that.” 

  Smitty is leading on the song that was written by him, Frennie Brooks and John Brown (mistakenly printed as Bowden on the label).  Blue: “I think the owner of Asnes was Frennie Brooks, and those guys, Brooks and Brown, worked at the airport and recorded us.  Nobody heard the record – or perhaps twenty-five people – but nobody bought it.  It didn’t do anything.”  Sonny: “I was laughing, when we did it... but it was okay.”  Backed by an uptempo ditty called Cool It, Pork Chops was re-released four years later in the U.K. on the Sue label (391). 

  Some of the other artists on the short-lived Asnes label were Ernie Johnson (You Need Love) and a “Jamaican doowop” outfit named the Jiving Juniors (Moonlight Lover).  Soon after Pork Chops the Dulcets disbanded, so there was no follow-up record.  Sonny: “Everybody decided to go their own ways.  Ethel and Buddy are still around.  I see Buddy every now and then.  They are here in New Jersey.” 

THE OTHER MANHATTANS 

  Blue: “We had a battle for the name, until I Wanna Be was released.  There was another Manhattans, and the union insisted that whoever came out with the first hit they would be able to maintain the name, and I Wanna Be (Your Everything) came out in ’64 and that was the way we won the name over.” 

  Music history knows many groups, who have used the name ‘Manhattans’.  There are Eli &amp; the Manhattans, Ronnie &amp; the Manhattans and several plain Manhattanses.  In the 50s and 60s singles by these groups have appeared on such labels as Dootone, King, Big Mack, Boss, Colpix, Ransom, Web, Piney, Enjoy, Golden World, Atlantic and Avanti, but not any of them is by our group.  Blue: “From ’61 through ’64 we tried desperately to get a recording deal, but it was impossible.” 

  There was at least one occasion, when they actually entered the studio and were ready for Danny Robinson (Bobby Robinson’s brother) to record them, but nothing came out of it.  Blue: “He never recorded us.  He pretended to record us, but he never did anything with us.” 

  Kenny: “I became a Manhattan as a result of the group I was introduced to.  The members of that group started also not making the rehearsals.  Sonny was part of that group and Smitty was already there.  We wanted this group to come together.  We already knew who we wanted to have as ideal members.  So Sonny brought me in, introduced me to the group and then one of the other members stopped making rehearsals.  He was a truck driver. Then they brought Richie in.  We had to just get a bass voice, and everybody wanted to see if we could get Blue again.  He agreed and that’s how we got together.” 

(The pic courtesy of Mrs. Jeanie Scott) 
JOE EVANS 

  Mr. Joe Evans is a seasoned musician, to say the least.  Throughout decades he has played with a number of jazz, blues and rhythm &amp; blues luminaries, but for the Manhattans he was first and foremost the owner of Carnival Records and the gentleman, who gave them their first record release in 1964. 

  Joe Evans, Jr, was born in Pensacola, Florida, on October 7 in 1916, so this year he’ll turn ninety-four.  He started playing the saxophone in the 1930s in the Ray Shep Band, moved to New York in 1938 and has since played with Jay McShann, Charlie Parker, Louis Armstrong, Cab Calloway, Dizzy Gillespie and Lionel Hampton, to name a few.  All this is documented in a fascinating book titled Follow Your Heart (ISBN-13978-0-252-03303-2; University of Illinois Press, http://www.press.uillinois.edu; 180 pages + 22 with photos; 2008), written by Mr. Evans himself and Christopher Brooks.  It’s an interesting read and contains many remarkable stories starting from Joe’s early days as a musician.  He sheds light on touring the south in the 30s, working with such artists as “Ma” Rainey, Billie Holiday, Al Hibbler, Ivory Joe Hunter, Jackie Wilson and Sam Cooke, running record companies in the 60s and 70s and life after an active and many-sided career in music. 

  Mr. Evans, who today lives in Richmond, Virginia, was kind enough to talk about the Manhattans, Carnival Records and some other points of his career for this article, too.  In the 50s he belonged to the Apollo Theater house band in New York.  “It was very nice.  It wasn’t tough.  We played five shows a day, and one night a week you played a midnight show.  On Wednesday night they had an Amateur Hour.  A lot of the stars were discouraged in that show at the Apollo.  The audience was very responsive.  On Wednesday night, if you weren’t good, they would boo you.  They had a guy called Porto Rico, who would come out in different costumes chasing you off the stage, if they didn’t like you.  But the audience was very good to you, if they liked you.” 

CEE-JAY, TANGERINE, MOTOWN... 

  In the late 50s Joe met with Clarence Johnson, and became a partner with him in running a record label.  “Cee Jay – that was initials for Clarence Johnson.  We called him ‘Jack Rags’.  He’s the man that taught me the record business.  He played trombone and had played in several bands.  He talked me into going into the record business.  He knew it, because he was already in it.” 

  The roster at Cee Jay in 1960 and 1961 included Mike &amp; the Utopians, Sherman Williams, Jay Dee Bryant &amp; the Magic Knights, Little Roy Little, the Four Kings, Jimmy Spruill &amp; his Band, the Vines, Delroy Green &amp; the Cool Gents and Harry Lewis &amp; his Orchestra... but there wasn’t a hit-making unit.  “Most of those artists just gave up.  Then some of them continued to try to be a success, but they never made it.  A lot of them joined other groups, and some of those groups became famous.” 

  “On that label we mostly did r&amp;b stuff.  One big record we had on Cee Jay was a blues record, and it was called I’m a Little Mixed Up by Betty James (583).  Leonard Chess of the Chess Records leased it, took it over and made it a big record.” 

  Clarence Johnson passed away in late 1961, the label ceased to exist and Joe proceeded to work for Ray Charles.  “It was very nice.  I was working as a promotion director.  Ray had a label that was distributed by ABC-Paramount called Tangerine.  I did a lot of work coast-to-coast.  He was a very nice man, very nice to work with.”  Since its start in 1962 Tangerine signed many established artists – Percy Mayfield, Lula Reed, Louis Jordan etc. – but hit-wise it wasn’t a very successful company.  “I believe that Ray had an idea what was good, but it was not the same idea what was happening in the business at the time.  This is just my belief.  He could make hits, but other artists that weren’t as strong couldn’t make hits like that.  The material wasn’t as strong as his and they weren’t as dynamic as he was.  Then he had a band on the road for the people to hear him in person and he could influence people that way.  And he was very good at what he did.  Other artists couldn’t get away with that.” 

  After Ray, Joe worked for a growing Detroit company called Motown after being approached by another saxophone player and a band leader named Choker Campbell.  “I was working and travelling with their show, the Motown Review.  I was playing mostly background for the artists, but I did a lot of recording with them, too.  I recorded with Stevie Wonder, Marvin Gaye, the Temptations, their girl groups, several artists...” 

CARNIVAL RECORDS 

  With Cee-Jay Records Joe had become so attached to the record business that in conjunction with his work at Tangerine he launched and started running a label of his own called Carnival, a name he picked up from a billboard ad.  Joe formed the label in 1962 together with Paul “Hucklebuck” Williams, a saxophonist, bandleader and recording artist in his own right that Joe had met in Detroit already in the 40s.  They also formed Bright Star Publishing Company (with BMI), and Paul’s home address – 605 West, 156th Street, New York – became the company and label address. 

  The first release, Your Yah-Yah Is Gone (501), was by a girl group called the Tren-Teens, who were scheduled to cut the record already for Cee-Jay.  The song owes some to Lee Dorsey’s Ya Ya, released a year earlier on Fury.  The Tren-Teens’ debut single was followed by Delores Johnson’s big-voiced r&amp;b belter titled What Kind Of Man Are You, (502).  You can listen to some mp3’s at www.westwoodmusicgroup.com -&gt; Carnival Records. 

  Joe’s and Paul’s Carnival Records shouldn’t be mixed up with Jerry Moss’ and Herb Albert’s label by the same name in 1961, which turned into A&amp;M a year later.  Also Atlantic’s Herb Abramson’s Carnival is a different label. 

  The third artist for the label was Barbara Brown, who cut in ‘63 a pleading r&amp;b ballad named Send Him to Me (b/w a cute toe-tapper, Sometimes I Wonder), but Barbara’s boyfriend wouldn’t allow her to continue show business career and perform in front of other men, so after one more single a year later she dropped out.  She, however, was an important link in Joe and the Manhattans hooking up with each other. 

THE MANHATTANS TO MOTOWN 

  Barbara told Joe Evans about the group, but there are two slightly different stories as to how the two actually met for the first time.  Sonny: “Richard, Smitty, Kenny, Blue and I felt that we had put in enough time and hard work to compete at Harlem’s famous Apollo Theater’s Amateur Night, which was held every Wednesday night.  So from Jersey City we went to the Apollo and placed 3rd that night.  But as fate would have it, Joe Evans was in the house that night.  And despite coming third, we really won that night, because he signed us to his Carnival Record label.” 

  Blue: “A gentleman called Joe Evans was the one who saw us and liked us.  He played alto sax in Choker Campbell’s orchestra that travelled with the Motown acts.  Joe Evans’ vision was to start a “Motown” in the New York area, and Barbara Brown was one of his first artists.  Barbara told him about us and he caught us at the Apollo.” 

  Joe: “One of the artists on Carnival, Barbara Brown, was responsible for me meeting them.  She gave them my phone number, they called me and then we set up an appointment at the Theresa Hotel.  I had Paul Williams with me.  If I saw them earlier, I didn’t remember them, but I never met them in person until they came into the Theresa.” 

  “The songs that they sang that day were songs that were made popular by other groups during that time.  They sang two or three songs like that.  They sang the songs better than the groups that had recorded them (laughing).  I said to Paul Williams ‘that is a million-dollar group’, and he said ‘oh, you’re crazy’, but later he said ‘you’re right, you knew what you were talking about’.” 

  “I asked them ‘do you want a record contract’, and they said ‘yes’, but then they said that ‘everybody promises to record us but they never get around to it’.  Then they told me that they had been approached by Bobby Robinson’s brother, Danny Robinson.  He was in the record business also (Everlast, Enjoy).  They tell them to come to the record session, but when they get there they’re recording someone else and tell them ‘we’ll get around to you’, and when they would finish late at night everybody would pack up and go home.  They said that happened to them two or three times.  I said ‘well, it won’t happen with me, because if I promise to record you and sign you, I will record you’.” 

  “The next day they signed the contract and brought it back to me.  I asked them had they gone over the contract with their parents or friends, they said ‘no, we don’t need to do that.  We’re over twenty-one and speak for ourselves’.  So we started from there.” 

  Joe was still working for Motown, so he took the first two songs he cut on the Manhattans to Detroit first.  “I put them on tape and I took the recording to Berry Gordy.  He liked it, but he wouldn’t go ahead of Mickey Stevenson.  He put him over that, and I would have to talk to him.  When I spoke with Mickey Stevenson, he wanted to take it over and only put perhaps my name on a record or something like that.  I’ve been in the business too long for that and I wouldn’t go for that, so I didn’t talk to him anymore about them.”  Joe soon left Motown altogether. 

MUSICIANS, STUDIOS, MIXING... 

  Joe put the Manhattans on his own Carnival label.  For his recording sessions he favoured one particular studio and he used a permanent line-up of rhythm section players.  “For most of the recordings I used Talent Masters in New York, because I worked very well with the engineer there.  His name was Bob Gallo, and he was also a guitarist.” 

  “For the rhythm section I had a regular bunch.  There was Bernard Purdie, who was the drummer, and Jimmy Tyrell was the bass player.  Robert Banks was the pianist.  “Snaggs” Allen was the guitarist and Eric Gale was the other guitarist.  They recorded all the Manhattans backgrounds.” 

  “I did the mix.  I would record the track first.  When I record the track, I would let the vocals sing along with it, just to give the musicians the feel of the song.  They didn’t have to be good.  They were not for the record.”  As Mr. Evans tells in the book Follow Your Heart, on four-track tapes that he used those days “track one was for the lead singer, two was for the background singers, three was for the rhythm section and the fourth track was for whatever additional instruments were necessary.” 

  “When I put the strings down – I think there were five or six of them – in the mix I would double them up.  If I wanted a light sound, I would double them once, and if I wanted something heavier, I would record those five or six in one register and then I make another take of them in another music I wrote.  The horns I didn’t double up much.  I used the trumpets and I used the trombone most of the time, but I would blend the trombone into the bass sound, and that blend had a different sound to it.  When I used the girls in the background, I used the Lovettes, especially with the Manhattans.” 

  Kenny: “We used Talent Masters Studios in Manhattan.  Only studios we used in Jersey City was the rehearsal studios.  How many takes we needed?  It all depends on the song.  Some of the songs we did once, and that was it.  We were always told ‘time was money’.  It was no use in going there and not be prepared to go.  So we tried to prepare ourselves as much as we possibly could, before we went in.” 

“FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME” 

  Those two songs that Joe first took to Berry Gordy were finally put out on the first Carnival single (504) by the Manhattans in March 1964.  Sonny: “Our first single, For the Very First Time, was a hit locally in the tri-city area.”  George Smith, their lead singer, also wrote the song, which is a rather typical dancer of those days and actually sounds like it could have been cut a couple of years earlier.  The flip, a mid-tempo and mellow mover titled I’ve Got Everything but You, was written by Joe and his newlywed wife, Anna Moore.  Anna took care of the company’s bookkeeping and her sister, Louise, became an assistant in the firm. 

  Perhaps a local hit, but nationally For the Very First Time didn’t make any waves.  According to Joe, their follow-up, There Goes a Fool/Call Somebody Please (506), did a little better.  Released in August 1964, There Goes a Fool was written by Sonny.  “I had written plenty of songs, but that was the first one recorded.”  It’s an uptempo pop song, which undoubtedly was musically influenced by the British invasion those days.  Smitty is again leading, and you can even hear a short flute solo by the producer himself, Mr. Joe Evans.  Call Somebody Please is a mid-tempo pop ditty, which Blue wrote and he also leads on this side. 

  Those days Paul Williams decided to leave the company to pursue other interests such as managing artists, so Joe now had the company all to himself.  He formed a new publishing company called Sanavan – the name comes from Anna and Evans – and the new Carnival address became 350 Chadwick Avenue in Newark, Joe’s home address. 

OTHER MERRYMAKERS 

  Although the Manhattans eventually became Carnival’s leading act and breadwinner for the company, many other interesting artists had releases on the label, too.  Curly Mayes cut a poppy umptempo ditty called Oh Why (b/w I’m Walkin’ On, Carnival 505) in 1964.  Joe: “He was out west somewhere.  I’m still looking for him now, because I have a chance to put one of the songs on his records on a television movie.” 

  Smitty invited his friend, Curby Goggins, to the company.  Curby also cut only one single (Come Home to Daddy/Love Me If You Want to; 510) in 1965.  Harry Caldwell sang in his high tenor voice a teenage anguish ballad named Nobody Loves Me on Carnival 516 in 1966.  It was backed with another yearning song, this time a mid-pacer titled Nobody Loves Me, co-written by Blue Lovett.  Joe: “I haven’t seen Harry for years.  He’s down in North Carolina somewhere.  He was from Charlotte, North Carolina.  He was also a brick mason, and he travelled around.”  Harry’s second single, a sympathetic “hippie” ballad called A New World Is Just Beginning (547), was released as late as in 1970. 

  The Lovettes had two single releases and both Little Miss Soul (518 in 1966), and I Need a Guy (530 in 1967) were written by Blue.  Blue: “They lived in Jersey City.  We all grew up together wanting to be recording artists, and Joe Evans loved them.  We used them sometimes as female background singers, and we were looking for that Motown thing that Berry Gordy did.  The idea that Joe had was to record these young ladies and hopefully get a hit on them.”  Indeed, Little Miss Soul is like a standard Motown scorcher, whereas the flip, Lonely Girl, is a downbeat tender song.  I Need a Guy is again a motownish mid-pacer, while I’m Afraid (to Say I Love you) on the flip is a poignant beat-ballad. 

  Norma Jenkins recorded Blue’s poignant ballad, Need Someone to Love (528; b/w a stomper called Me, Myself and I) in 1967.  Blue had invited Norma to Carnival.  Blue: “She was very good.”  Male duos were popular throughout the 60s, and one single by Carnival’s own Turner Brothers proved that as singers they were equal to many of their colleagues.  I’m the Man For You Baby (535) is an almost deep soul ballad, while My Love Is Yours Tonight is a more mid-tempo mover.  Joe: “I haven’t seen them recently.  These people are hard to keep up with.  They came from someplace down south.  They were quite active.  They got around.” 

  Kenneth Ruffin stayed at Carnival for one single as well.  I’ll Keep Holding On (536) is a pleading soul ballad with a strong support from the horn section, whereas Cry, Cry, Cry is a blues romp.  Joe: “Kenny was basically a writer, but I recorded him, because some things he sang quite well.  I’ve been searching for him, too.  He wrote several songs that other artists did.” 

  It’s Too Late and I’m Just Gonna Be Missing You (539 in 1968) by Rene Bailey let you know from the opening bars that here we have one big-voiced blues lady.  Joe: “She lives in upstate New York.  I call to Rene all the time.  She’s partly retired.  She sings on most of the weekends, and she’s teaching the school.” 

  In the next part of the story I’ll still feature two other popular Carnival acts – Phil Terrell and Lee Williams and the Cymbals - more in detail and with comments from the artists themselves.  In their roster Carnival also had such familiar names to the fans of genuine soul music as Little Royal, who cut a fine soul ballad titled I Can Tell, and Jimmy Jules, who excelled on an Otis type of a slowie named Nothing Will Ever Change.  Both singles were released in ’67. 

LET’S DANCE FIRST... 

  So far on all four released Manhattans sides on Carnival Records the songs had been dancers, and we had to wait till the fourth single to hear a ballad.  Joe: “Uptempo things were easier to get played.  If you had a name, they’d play anything, but the best way to get new artists played was play an uptempo record.  When you take it to a deejay, they put it on and they don’t listen to the whole song.  They listen to the introduction and a little bit and tell you ‘I’ll play it’.  If you have a slow song, they don’t listen enough, no matter what it is.  So you had to have a little bit of rhythm to the song for them to give you a break with.” 

  The Manhattans’ third Carnival single was also a mover, but it became their first hit and marked the beginning of a remarkable success story.  That song as well as the rest of the Carnival period and DeLuxe period will be covered in the second part of the story. 

Heikki Suosalo 

ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS(so far) 

INTERVIEWEES: Gerald Alston, Edward Bivins, Joe Evans, Kenneth Kelly, Winfred Lovett, Jeanie Scott, Phil Terrell, Lee Williams 

MY OTHER HELPERS: Christopher A. Brooks, Charles Hardy, Vick Kaply, Toye Kates, Jr.﻿

Meer lezen (650 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-domHa3tvyf0/UI4r326Jz0I/AAAAAAAAABs/pJIxCsi0hpo/w426-h272/histor1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/100066708911621958820/albums/5948502997163321041/5948503009821083922?sqi=100486961016255401142&amp;sqsi=8c2e5914-8866-4e81-949a-3715015e97b8</link><title>Warning: Wall of Text and Heavy Character Establishment 
These are my "mane" OCs, oddly enough, six in number. I decided to draw them all together to establish that these are the ones I will consistently use, and also to celebrate the new season! So, here's a rundown: 
     On the bottom left is a purple mare named Synesthesia, who has the condition she shares a name with. Her special talent is using her condition to inspire music, particularly the flute. She teaches band at Stable High in Manehattan. 

     On the bottom right is a red mare named Carolyn Hooves, though she prefers School Spirit. She attends Stable High and plays a wide range of instruments, from bass drum, snare, clarinet, saxophone, flute, and sometimes even the sousaphone. She's the section leader of the flutes and is in her sophomore year. Her special talent is motivation, represented by a tomahawk famously used by the ancient griffons that are her school mascot. 

     In the center is a white mare named Swirl Mist, also known as Misty, and a maroon stallion named Compass Rose. The pair are married, and occasionally act like the young, infatuated couple they once were. Compass Rose is the oldest pony of the group, followed closely by Swirl Mist. Misty's special talent is writing, and she works as a self-employed author, writing epic tales, short stories, and the occasional poem. Compass Rose, meanwhile, is an explorer, or a "professional cartographer", though he prefers the excitement of the former. He travels around the fringes of the mapped world and adds onto it, sometimes forming important alliances with the races he discovers. Sometimes his wife and daughter accompany him on his travels, though he works best alone. He's boasted before that he leads a life "Daring Do herself would be jealous of!" 

     The pegasus is the couple's daughter, Windy Waves. She's the youngest pony in the group, but only by a year. She's excitable but levelheaded and shares her father's enthusiasm for adventure. Despite living with Misty in their sleepy ocean town of Brielle, there's always some sort of magic out there, and Windy will find it! Her special talent, only recently discovered, is swimming, especially acrobatic swimming. This is represented by the happy dolphin on her flank she sometimes resembles. 

     Finally, the dark griffon is named Finner, and he's Windy's best friend. Ever since they were young, Windy has dragged poor Finner into her adventures. He struggles with a deep-seated fear of water, but quickly forgets it when he knows that his friend is there to save him. He's more cautious when it comes to jumping headfirst into some strange scenario. His caution has saved Windy Waves occasionally, but she still likes to tease him about bravery. But when situations get tough and things look bleak, he can step up and face danger headfirst like the bravest warrior. Once he saved Windy and himself from griffon pirates, though Windy swears she was about to break her bonds anyway. He lives with his mother, Laudi, and has no idea who his father is, though one ambassador in Canterlot looks oddly familiar. ﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-D77dmWjlauk/Uo1T-I26SRI/AAAAAAAABd0/xqTDuL60wS4/w426-h329/My%2BSix%2BOCs.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/101983474019961328651/albums/5714220736546593169/5714220743118439506</link><title>ON THIS DATE (42 YEARS AGO) 
February 28, 1970 – Van Morrison: Moondance is released. 
# ALL THINGS MUSIC PLUS+ 5/5 
# Allmusic 5/5 
# Rolling Stone (see original review below) 

Moondance is the third solo album by Van Morrison, released on this date in February, 1970 by Warner Bros. Records. 

Moondance was critically acclaimed when first released and established Morrison as a major artist. The songs on the album quickly became staples of FM radio. It has proven to be Morrison's most famous album, often appearing on many lists of best albums of all time. Among other awards, it was inducted into the Grammy Hall of Fame in 1999. In 2003, it was ranked #65 on Rolling Stone magazine's list of "The 500 Greatest Albums of All Time". 

The single released was "Come Running" with "Crazy Love" as the B-side, which peaked at #39 on the Pop Singles chart. "Crazy Love" was only released as a single in the Netherlands and did not chart. "Moondance", as a single was not released until 1977 and peaked at #92. 

Moondance was a commercial and a critical success with the album charting in the Top 30 in the US and #32 in the UK. While Blowing Your Mind! was recorded and released under Bert Berns's control and Astral Weeks was a commercial failure if lauded by most critics, Moondance represented Morrison's first success as an artist in control of his music and his band and it established him as a top selling singer-songwriter. Said to be an "extraordinary achievement", as of 2010, it had continuously sold well during the forty years since being released. It was listed by RIAA as 3x multi platinum in 1996. 

ORIGINAL ROLLING STONE REVIEW 
Long ago, Van Morrison reached that point where the influences on his music no longer mattered. It is as pointless to attempt to detect those influences as it would be for any musician to try to imitate him. 

Van Morrison's music cannot really be imitated, because, as with Dylan's music, what one hears is not style, but personality. With each record -- Them Again, Astral Weeks, or Moondance -- one gets a sense that Van has achieved some ancient familiarity with his band and with his songs; no matter how the music changes, the long inventions of Van's singing, his full command of the musicians that play with him, and the striking imagination of a consciousness that is visionary in the strongest sense of the word, creat an atmosphere that instantly sets its own terms. Morrison's powers are clear: his strong gift for melody, his ability to move freely within virtually any sort of contemporary instrumentation, his verbal magic as inventive and literate as Dylan's, and most of all, the authenticity of his spirit. 

Moondance is his first album in over a year. Unlike Van's masterful Astral Weeks, this one will be immensely popular; Van's picture already fills the windows of record stores and his new music is getting more airplay on FM stations than anything in recent memory. 

Van's new album might send one back to the bright enthusiasm of "Brown-Eyed Girl" and the magic blues of Them Again; Van now sings with a magnetically full electric band, complete with piano, organ, vibes, and intricately controlled saxophones and flute. The band's performance has a stately brilliance; and if it recaptures some of the feeling of the earlier music, the past is serving as a rite of passage toward the celebrations of Moondance. 

Van opens with "And It Stoned Me," a tale of boys out for a day's freedom, standing in the rain with eyes and mouths open, heads bent back: "Oh, the water, let it run all over me..." The sensuality of this song is overpowering, communicated with a classical sort of grace. "And it stoned me/To my soul/Stoned me just like jelly roll..." There is no strain for meaning in Van's words or in his voice. "Let it run all over me..." -- you feel the exhilaration almost with a sense of astonishment. The band, playing subtle, gentle rock and roll, surrounds the singer; here, as everywhere on Moondance, the horn arrangements are absolutely exquisite, as eloquent as a sermon in a backwoods chapel. 

With "Caravan" one might begin to remember the early Impressions: the instantaneous aura of fantasy and desire that Curtis Mayfield created for "Gypsy Woman" tumbles down again as a fanfare on piano and the roll of drums and guitar open a composition of seductive grandeur. "Caravan" is a strange song; the images are easily real and the music is profoundly comforting, yet there's the edge of a story here that fades without ever revealing all it has to tell. "Now the caravan has all friends/Yes, they'll stay with me until the end...Gypsies...tell me all I need to know..." Woven between the fragments and framed by the textures of the horn with blazing imagination: "Turn up your radio/And let me/Hear the song/Turn on your electric light/So we can get down/To what is really wrong." The singer moves from the gypsy campfire to his lover and back again, with a lovely sort of affection. Van's singing is pure expression, pure sound; the band moves off and then forward again. A graceful soprano saxophone holds notes behind Van's words: "Now, the caravan is painted red and white/That means everyone is staying overnight..." 

"It's a good thing he doesn't have much stage presence," said a friend after watching Van perform this song. "Otherwise it'd be too much to take." 
"Into the Mystic" is the heart of Moondance; the music unfolds with a classic sense of timing, guitar strums fading into watery notes on a piano, the bass counting off the pace. The lines of the song and Morrison's delivery of them are gorgeous: "I want to rock your gypsy soul/Just like in the days of old/And magnificently we will fold/Into the mystic." The transcendent purity of the imagery seems to turn endlessly, giving back one's own reflection. Van's more abstract songs are mosaics of brilliantly chosen metaphors -- ambiguous and instantly recognizable. Morrison communicates directly even when he is most obscure; his visions have power, and the ambiguity of those visions is always unified by the sympathy of the music -- there is no "backup band" on Moondance any more than there is an "Lay Lady Lay." Something's been made; it stands, it won't be broken down. 

Perhaps "Glad Tidings," which ends Moondance, is the song that most makes one want to come back to this album without even thinking about it. "Glad Tidings" is a vital, leaping promenade through the streets of the town; fast, clean rock and roll moves it along as striking horns guide the song, until they cue the chorus into an explosion of real joy: "Yeah, we'll send you glad tidings/From New York/DO DO DO DOOT DO DO/Open up your eyes that you may see/DO DO DO DOOT DO DO/Ask you not to read between the lines/Hoping that you come right in on time." 

Moondance is an album of musical invention and lyrical confidence; the strong moods of "Into the Mystic" and the fine, epic brilliance of "Caravan" will carry it past many good records we'll forget in the next few years. Van Morrison plays on. 
~ Greil Marcus and Lester Bangs, Rolling Stone, 3/19/70 

TRACKS: 
All songs written by Van Morrison. 
Side one 
"And It Stoned Me" – 4:30 
"Moondance" – 4:35 
"Crazy Love" – 2:34 
"Caravan" – 4:57 
"Into the Mystic" – 3:25 

Side two 
"Come Running" – 2:30 
"These Dreams of You" – 3:50 
"Brand New Day" – 5:09 
"Everyone" – 3:31 
"Glad Tidings" – 3:13﻿

Meer lezen (139 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-s1Zx2s4rMEg/T0z9fZm-RFI/AAAAAAAAHLA/w6h3eRcvYg8/s426/van_morrison_moondance.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/111936274817971914273/albums/5855605680805061633/5855605680784034114?authkey=CIKf_brc1MHMhwE</link><title>A night at the opera: The Magic Flute.  The show started off a little lame with video projection during the opening, but soon it picked up steam and the whole show was fantastic. The meshing of aboriginal culture into the story took a little getting used to, but again, it ended up working really well and added a fresh feel to the amazing music and singing.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-BrfrgkUZAfI/UUNKV6PkSUI/AAAAAAAAMMs/Piw51GlOd54/w426-h568/20130314_193056.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/105089427435432204420/albums/5916274739327395697/5916274740610860322</link><title>#AnimeMangaoftheDay 
The anime for today is... 

Anime: Magi: The Labyrinth of Magic 
Genre: Adventure, Shounen, Action, Fantasy 
Number of Episodes: 25 
Short Description: This story is about Aladdin, a boy who has set out to explore the world after being trapped in a room for most of his life. His best friend is a djinn named Ugo who comes from his flute. Soon enough, Aladdin discovers he is a Magi, a magician who chooses kings, and he was born to choose kings who will follow the righteous path, battling against those who want to destroy fate. Follow his adventures with his friends Alibaba and Morgiana as he meets others from the story 1001 Arabian Nights, like Sinbad, and fights to keep the balance of the world! 

My rating: ☆☆☆ [3 stars] 

~Kira﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_09_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-vrlL2ENlpCU/UhrUh-O6BSI/AAAAAAAAAaQ/0Yylw4avYPI/w426-h330/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7421-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/story%20magic%20flute/photos/104202263011113038990/albums/5745424942760590817/5745424942930446050</link><title>Cassandra's Log - Part 1 \- Welcome Aboard the Wormwood! 

“By Besmara’s right ass cheek… what happened?” Cassandra mutters to herself as she stirs from her place on the floor and pushes herself up to her knees to look around. “I remember reading the cards… and then the barmaid…” 

“You’ve been taken like the rest of us to sign up against our will for a little sea cruise,” chuckles a human male with long hair and a moustache sitting on the floor and holding his head. 

Suddenly there is a blinding flash of light as a door from above is opened to briefly reveal the squalor that she was tossed into. “Look alive, land lubbers!” Bellows a voice from above. “The Captain will flog you for dereliction of duty if you don’t report topside!” 

“Come on,” says Cassandra as she offers hands to the others to help them up. “We’re all in this together at the moment.” 

As they stumble upstairs, the dark and damp squalor of below decks gives way to the salty air of the ocean and natural light of the sun. “Blessed Besmara… for she has answered my prayers,” mutters Cassandra before closing her eyes with a smile and inhaling. 

“What… you prayed to be kidnapped into slavery on board a pirate ship? You got some low expectations there, mate.” offers another human to her right, bearing an uncanny resemblance to the human she saw before. 

“But I’m on the ocean…” Cassandra replies. “This is where I’m supposed to be.” 

“I’m Zack and this is my bother Jack, by the way. Perhaps you’ve heard of us?” A human male with long hair and a moutache points to another man who would be near impossible to tell apart if it weren’t for the clothing. 

“Afraid I’m from much farther north than here,” Cassandra says with chagrin. “I wouldn’t mind hearing your stories one day, though.” Cassandra scans around the deck and scans over the greasy Gnome and the other humans gathered around what looks like the captain reading a scroll before falling on a Halfling gemale in a red cloak and a human female with red hair with tattoos very similar to her own. I may not be human… but I am a female… and in a place such as this we should know that we can look out for each other. 

The older man looking at the scroll finally curls it up and hands it to one of the other humans before lumbering his way over to his new “crew” from below decks. “Welcome to The Wormwood! I’ve got two rules on me’ ship: DON’T TALK TO ME! is the first… and the second is DON’T KILL THE CREW! We’ve got a bit of a shortage, we have… and anyone making my life harder by killing off another crewmember I can’t afford to lose will soon find themselves walking a very short plank over shark infested waters. YOU GOT THAT?” 

The man then stomps away and is soon replaced by a tall imposing bald man with many scars and crags pockmarking his skin, carrying a whip. “The name’s Mr. Plug! Don’t wear it out!” The weary group stands to attention as Mr. Plug scans over them all with a snear. “You and the Halfling,” he grunts as he points to Cassandra. “You two start scrubbing the decks. You other two,” he continues as he turns to the twins, “start climbing the rigging! I’ll assign permanent duty when I feel like looking at your lilly-lovin’ faces again.” 

The day passes rather quickly when dealing with the monotony of scrubbing decks and hauling ropes. The Halfling Drogo is soon assigned to rat catching down in the bilges while Cassandra works on scrubbing the decks. She sits up from her scrubbing and pops her back with a sigh as she breathes in the salty air. “Could’ve been worse, I guess.” a female Halfing looks up from her scrubbing with a raised brow. “After getting knocked out at the bar, I wasn’t expecting to wake up at all, honestly,” Cassandra continues with a shrug. “When you’re alive, anything is possible.” 

“All right, all right… I guess I’ve got to look at your faces again, so let’s line up and not make me have to do it for too long!” bellows Mr. Plug with a crack of his whip as they all gather at the base of the rigging. “I’ve got a little test for ye all… it’s called ‘Get your ass to the Crow’s Nest before you get hit with rotten tomatoes!’ GO!” 

Cassandra grins to herself as she launches herself up through the rigging, much to the detrement of the cursing twins below caught surprised by the contest. It’s almost a relief to be able to stretch her legs in the climb, and she wants to be able to try to get a good view from the Crow’s Nest before they call them back down again. “Damn… no landmarks!” she mutters as she catches her breath at the top, and is soon followed by Drogo the halfling. “Impressive work, my friend,” she smiles as she looks down with a chuckle at the twins being pelted with rotten tomatoes. 

“Fun’s over! Get your asses back down here on the double!” bellows Mr. Plug. “All right-y… which of you scurvy dogs knows how to cook worth a damn?” he grumbles as he looks us over. 

“Actually…” Cassandra replies as she raises her hand. Her mother had taught her how to make the best of herbs and spices when one was constantly travelling with their clan. 

Mr. Plug looks at Cassandra with a raised brow. “Fine then, you’re now the cook’s mate. Halfling, you’re a rigger. You two…” he gazes at the twins stained with tomatoes. “Start swabbing the decks. You’ve each been assigned hammocks in the common room as well as your daily ship duties. Do your jobs, keep your nose out of where it doesn’t belong and don’t talk back, and maybe you’ll live to see tomorrow!” 

Cassandra grimaces as she’s escorted past a man bolted to the mainmast for trying to sneak into the Captain’s quarters. “Come on, kitchen’s this way,” mutters one of the crew. Eventually she’s taken to a cramped room stuffed with dishes and boxes from floor to ceiling and covered in cooking grease. In the middle of it all is a rather fat and drunk human currently trying to sleep off a hangover. “So what am I…” Cassandra turns to question her escort only to find that he’s gone back to his own duties. “Well… guess I can aquaint myself with the supplies, at least.” After an hour of crawling over boxes and pans she’s able to find a rather servicible dagger that she tucks into her sleeve… but still no clean pans. 

~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 

The sun sets over their first day on the Wormwood as the bell rings once again on deck. Cassandra grunts at her futile attempts to organize the kitchen area and runs down to join the others lining up in front of a pacing Mr. Plug and a redheaded human covered in muck. 

“It seems this piece of scum was stupid enough to steal from the ship stores! Perfect time to demonstrate to the crew what we call Ship’s Justice, eh?” he cracks the whip towards some men with rope on each side of the deck. “Show them how we clean the barnacles off the hull, boys!” 

Cassandra and the others grimace as ropes are tied to the legs and arms of the man with the ends going over each side. With a pull of the ropes he is taken overboard, his screams turning into gurgles as he’s quickly pulled under to scrape along the barnacles underneath. 

The dull scraping sounds along the hull are nearly enough to make Cassandra’s stomach turn… but instead she bites her lip and breathes deep through her nose as she does her best to remember happier times. The sickening scraping soon comes to an end… only to be replaced by the sounds of excited sharks gathering off portside to feed. 

“Entertainment’s over! Get your ass back to the kitchen and start serving up the stew!” Pug rails at Cassandra before cracking his whip over his head and stomping off. 

Cassandra heads back to the kitchen to the sounds of nausea from some of the crew at eating after such a graphic display. Focus on who you can help, Cassie… some people just have to make their own fate. She soon returns with a large pot full of what can only be called soup, considering how watery it is. “I’m so sorry…” she says to each of the crew as she spoons out the rotgut soup. “When he lets me near the food, I swear I’ll make something better…until then, the rum will kill the taste.” The redheaded female and a few of the crew offer slight smiles at her sincere apology, as no one ever cared about the food before. 

Hmmn… perhaps we can compare tattoos later… Cassandra chuckles to herself as she finishes up and totes the pot back to the kitchen. Since magic is so prized on this ship, though… perhaps sharing knowledge of my skills with her might help her situation with Mr. Plug. In a place like this, people you can trust are the true measure of wealth. 

The evening finds the crew doing their best to stretch out sore muscles and backs as Drago plays a flute alongside a red furry lizard-thing doing a jig… and rather well. 

“I’ve heard tales of summoners and their magical companions… but I must admit this is the first one I’ve seen,” Cassandra comments in awe. “How did your friend come about?” 

“Just something I was born with,” Drago replies with a shrug before going back to his music. 

So much for conversation… Cassandra turns to the female halfling looking rather longingly at Drago’s flute. “Lucky bastard,” the halfling girl named Rosie mutters. “At least he has an instrument… they went and took away my fiddle.” Cassandra opens her mouth to comment, but is interrupted by the clanking of metal as a rucksack is dropped at her feet in front of her by the redheaded female. “It pays to have friends,” she winks. “If you know how to talk to her, sometimes you can get things back from the quartermaster,” she offers before heading into the next room. 

“Thank you,” Cassandra calls after her before opening the sack in joy… because right on top is the worn blue leather cover of her spellbook. Thank the Gods! She whispers thanks to Besmara and tucks the book carefully into her jacket before pulling out a set of wooden armor and two monogramed rapiers that are quickly taken up by the halfling and the twin humans. 

“You know, our grandfather Jareth Teashanks is the one who passed down these swords to us,” begins one of the twin brothers with a smile as others settle in around him for a story. Cassandra can make out something about cannonballs and mechanical body parts before sleep takes her and she passes out on one of the cots. 

Cassandra is woken from a dream of rabbit princes and ant queens by the sounds of the morning bell, signifying a new work day. She mutters a quick cantrip that cleans the remnants of yesterday’s efforts from her clothing before making sure the others are ready in time. No sense starting off the day on a bad foot… 

As she jogs up the steps with the others, however, they find their way blocked by four humans looking to start trouble. “In a hurry?” the slightly bigger one in front asks with a swagger as he shoves Jack down a few steps. Zack quickly moves up to defend his brother as Cassandra pulls the dagger from her sleeve with her best intimidating sneer. 

“Look… I obviously can’t kill you all… but I can certainly make you wish you were dead if you make us late. Maybe if you’re lucky you’ll even get the job of cleaning up your blood afterwards.” 

Three of the thugs back away in fear, leaving the leader who grins and pulls out a dagger of his own. “That butter knife don’t scare me,” he snorts. 

“Try this then,” offers Jack as he unsheaths his rapier. The thug gulps visibly and tries to run up the stairs, but gets cold-cocked in the back of the head by the rapier’s hilt instead. 

“Serves you right trying to make us late,” Zack mutters as he kicks him in the side for good measure before joining the rest of them continuing up the stairs. 

“So glad you all decided to make it!” Mr. Pug growls as they manage to line up before the fading of the last bell ring. “Time to show us how well you can fish, Elf girl!” he waves the hilt of his whip towards some nets along the side of the boat before growling at the others. “The rest of you get back to your duties!” 

After a fruitful day with a decent catch, Cassandra totes the fish back to the kitchen in the hopes of making something less offensive to the stomach for the crew. A search through the shelves doesn’t turn up any spices, unfortunately… but she does find a brace of daggers in a wooden box shoved under some frying pans. Hmmn… I wonder if I can trade these with the quartermaster to get back my cards? She draws a symbol in the air as she mutters a spell, and the air ripples for a moment as her Unseen Servant pops into existance. “Clean and prepare these fish for dinner for me… I’m going to go see if I can conduct some business,” she orders before slipping out the door. 

“GO ’WAY!” growls a sleepy voice as a bottle shatters against the inside of the Quartermaster’s door. Well… so much for that. 

~~~~ 

The fish goes over reasonably well that night, causing the rum to flow a bit more freely as laughs and stories are shared all around. Even Ambrose the cook was more verbose than unconscious, and shared stories of the crew with Cassandra before passing out again. It’s a particular bit of information about the quartermaster that gives Cassandra an idea or two about getting their things back… 

“So what do you say… maybe between my illusion and your hillarious impersonation of Mr. Plug, we can fool that old hag guarding our stuff?” Cassandra asks the human girl next to her with only a slight slur. 

“Oh no,” replies Tilly Bracket with a wave of her hands. “As much as I’d love to pull one over on old Cuthroat Grok, I don’t even want to think what might happen if it doesn’t work. Cool idea, though.” She leans over to Cassandra and whispers, “Besides… I’ve heard that she’s afraid of cursed things, so that’s probably the way to go.” 

“Hey… where’d you get even more daggers?” complains a burly human. On second glance, Cassandra identifies him as the one who pulled a dagger on them on the stairs. 

“Amazing what you can find when you actually bother cleaning around here,” Cassandra replies with a roll of her eyes. 

“I’d start with yourself, Fips,” adds Tilly as she holds her nose and waves for him to go. Fips scoffs and shuffles into the other room with a mutter… soon to be followed by Jack. 

“Hey Sindara, love the tattoos! Want to see mine?” the redheaded female turns at Zack’s voice and laughs heartidly at the sailor bent over with his pants down. 

“Believe it or not, that reminds me of a song,” says Drago as he pulls out his whistle and his creature twirls about in joy. 

~~ 

The next day begins with the now-expected bell ringing… but this time when they line up there’s a young man covered in bilge water with a rather nasty wound on his leg standing by Mr. Pug. “It seems something decided to eat early and take a chunk out of ol’ Jackie-boy here!” he grunts as he waves his whip handle at the boy. “I vollunteer you four to go down into the bilges and take out whatever did it!” 

“Will we have access to any equipment for the task?” Cassandra asks hopefully. 

“Looks to me you’ve been supplying yourself just fine,” sneers Mr. Pug as he lumbers off. “Don’t come back up till it’s done!” 

“That’s one really nasty rat bite,” offers Jack to the others. “Best be careful.” 

Zack nods to his brother and mutters his own incantation before a globe of soft light floats in front of him. “Come on… let’s do this.” 

Cassandra can’t stop the shudder that goes through her at the sight of numerous spiders and webs in the dark dank corners of the bilge. 

“It’s as hot and smelly as an ogre’s armpit in here,” grunts Jack. 

Zack’s ball of light floats forward until it glints off the red eyes of at least six rats some 5 feet long huddled around a pile of garbage. Between the four of them it doesn’t take long before the rats are just one more corpse floating in the bilge water. All but Drago’s pet remain unscathed… but fortunately its hardy constitution seems to have protected it from any disease the creatures might have been carrying. 
“Let’s look around real quick before they call us back up!” exclaims Jack as he discovers a water-tight pouch in one of the crates in the corner. A quick search by the rest of us reveals a suit of leather armor for Zack, as well as a masterwork hand axe and a vial of holy water for Cassandra. 

“Sweet… maybe I can trade this armor to get my hat back!” exclaims Zack. 

“I was going to talk to her too today,” Drago replies. “Good luck to you!” 

Cassandra smiles at the others as she formulates her own plan for the quartermaster in her mind. Curses were the bread and butter of Varisian gypsies… I think I can drum up a few good ones regarding a fiddle… 
#skullandshackles﻿

Meer lezen (333 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7421_10_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-KxLYQfHG1yc/T7vZi4cJxuI/AAAAAAAANJE/ypYX5wcyuWY/w426-h271/pirateflag%255B1%255D.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>