<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:56:14" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/115194439175912065364/albums/5778737391364588129/5778737390894616274</link><title>Cars motion picture stories and coloring books in Arabic and English from Hachette Antoine. Click here: http://goo.gl/c9VC1﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-sSPdiz0AX6Y/UDIzCjqKjtI/AAAAAAAAATs/wHWFMuRHQ0I/w426-h237/SliderCars.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/116761784986758593534/albums/5634157729357326417/5634157727706672242</link><title>Wash that for you, Miss? 

If you were a fish living in the warm turquoise waters off the coast of Bonaire, you may not hear those words, but you'd see the shrimp sign language equivalent. It seems Periclimenes yucatanicus or the Spotted Cleaner Shrimp is doing a booming business in the local reefs by setting up a fish washing service. That's right, a Fish Wash. You'd be hard pressed to find a terrestrial Molly Maid with two opposable thumbs as studious and hardworking as this wee marine beauty. 

This quiet marine mogel is turning out to be one of the ocean's top entrepreneurs. Keeping its host and diet clean and green, the spotted shrimp hooks up with the locals, in this case, local sea anemones and sets up a fish wash... picture a car wash but without the noise and teenage boys. The signage posted is the shrimps natural coloring which attracts fish from around the reefs. 

Wash on, wash off. 

Once within reach, the shrimp cleans the surface of the fish, giving the fish a buff and the shrimp its daily feed. Credit for this lovely photo of the wee spotted cleaner shrimp goes to Paul Sutherland.﻿

Meer lezen (18 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-oQM1FlLrJiE/TjCMmjB6bHI/AAAAAAAAGKg/NIdR_6NaVo0/w426-h297/spotted-cleaner-shrimp-991621-ga.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/115655205216183932495/albums/5821420284921448865/5821420282272158242?authkey=CIme39fOl_vj4wE&amp;sqi=107227825802974578216&amp;sqsi=915a1f3f-716c-48b5-b265-edb82217ef43</link><title>My first success in the Lightbox gallery :D 

Comments from yesterday: 

nicolas outinday 
#save  impressive ! ﻿ 

Angie McMonigal 
Nice toning and energy! #save2  ﻿ 

Chris Shaw 
Shouts power and movement, great selective colour use. #save3  ﻿ 

Michael Roettger 
Very nice clarity. The coloring on the car is nice as well. #save4﻿ 

Dirk Heindoerfer 
Great action shot. Perfect timing, great dust cloud and motion in the wheels. I would just wish for a tad more brightness in the right side of the car. But thats nitpicking already;) #save5﻿ 

Brian W. Downs 
I like the shot but not the processing. 
#delete  ﻿ 

C.J. Sros 
Great shot! 
Killed by processing 
What is it with color selection today?? 
Definitely a sign of the end of days! 
#delete2﻿ 

William D. 
Wish I could be there. I'm with C.J. The washing out of the color really killed it- I feel like either a full-color or a B&amp;W shot would do better, not a desaturated one. #delete3  ﻿ 

Jeff Anderson 
First impression is explosive action and movement. The selective coloring doesn't hurt it for me. #save6﻿ 

Jamie Darrow 
I love the feeling this portrays. Excellent color choice! #save7﻿ 

Cindee Reeder 
Ooooooo I feel the power.  LOVE IT!!!  I feel like racing now.  I like the color and choices you made.   #save7  ﻿ 

Ray Diehr 
Rally Grunge! Great action shot, heavy hand in the post processing but I see where you wanted to go with this. Perhaps a little more color in the dirt... I like it. #save8  ﻿ 

Ricardo Lagos 
100% #save9  ﻿ 

Frank Cava 
The angle of the road, really works here. The image is further enhanced by all of the dust and rocks.  The processing is very effective. I didn't notice the environment was monochrome at first since there's not much color in gravel in the first place. #save9﻿ 

Matt Shalvatis 
Nice shot, handled the processing well. 

Looks like this has 11 saves already.  You can add another if you like.   #save12  ﻿ 

Gerard Charnley 
Thank you all for taking the time to comment.  I 
thought the processing might not be everyone's cup of tea and this proved so... which is fair enough.﻿ 

Seshank Malap 
umm #save13  !.. good job.. love it!﻿ 

Amanda Valverde 
I think your choice of color processing is effective at calling the viewer's eye to the car and not the background which can sometimes be a huge distraction in shots like this. I like it.﻿ 

Salem Salem 
Full of action﻿ 

russ vallelunga 
I'd save it if I needed to; looks like you're already there!﻿ 

William D. 
+Gerard Charnley I know I voted down, but its still an epic looking picture. I actually have since changed my mind on re-viewing it. Is there any chance I can get a full resolution one for a computer wallpaper?﻿ 

Thomas Hawk 
Congratulations +Gerard Charnley   feel free to add this photo to the Light Box.  http://goo.gl/c45MQ.  ﻿

Meer lezen (93 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5XTgNAs4lbE/UMnW500WEiI/AAAAAAAAFjg/funAFoNb3e4/w426-h284/IMG_2324%2BG%252B.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/110483720435337739097/albums/5719011846076331137/5719011847868852978</link><title>Sundown 

The monday rush, coffee, food, upload picture, run to car, speed to work, repeat, fun fun fun….. 

Enjoy a picture! 

#MoodyMonday hosted by +Philip Daly 

#NatureMonday hosted by +Rolf Hicker 

#plusphotoextract hosted by +Jarek Klimek 

#landscapephotography 
Details/Equipment: 
Camera: Canon EOS 7D 
Lens: Sigma 10 mm - 20 mm - F/4.0-5.6 
Tripod: Oben AC-1310 Tripod w/ Ball Head 
Computer: 27" iMac i7 3.1GHz 16GB Ram 
Programs: Photomatix, Photoshop, and Lightroom for final adjustments﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-GUPKPy9tYlg/T14C-Zp5KvI/AAAAAAAADrw/g6IFcaRtj3M/w426-h284/David%2BMorrow-1-2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/105080945612477536738/albums/5704391913630552465/5704391913224790946</link><title>Coloring: Flasn SWF, Vector SVG, Raster PNG. 
www.abc-color.com/color/car/001/car-girl/car-girl-online-coloring-en.shtml﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_05_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-mU9R5jgNEoI/TyoSOM9f46I/AAAAAAAAAe8/U1MOpIGUt9I/w426-h294/car-girl-picture-color.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/116170869855447155410/albums/5912049052034091265/5912049055707458914?authkey=CK3z6LvFhsKSHA&amp;sqi=100136178342216549598&amp;sqsi=ce732535-48d8-4822-a0ad-5dcfa3384b6d</link><title>Generally subjects such as farm fields and corn don't appeal to me much.  Sometimes something more can be found within a subject to make a picture worth shooting.  You know, always keep the eyes open for that one spot of interest.  This was shot in relatively early morning light and the split between the two stands of corn with the open space leading off to who knows where as though it's a path, struck my interest.  Of course the long shadowing and the light coloring added to the appeal as well.  So sometimes we just see something, pull the car off the road and get out, camera in hand.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-UksqCCHhNZE/UgvRSvQgbWI/AAAAAAAADSw/2A5MlEYvDpo/w426-h284/corn_6178.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/103723061331205387934/albums/5939533198860371473/5939533200870271538</link><title>Follow Your Dream (Fiction) 
by Dean Borok 

Niño de Jesus Benitez leaped into action as soon as he heard the door latch fail to catch. The first thing he did was to stick his finger down his throat and puke up his medication. Sticking his head out into the corridor and finding it to be deserted in the madrigal hours before dawn, he made a beeline for the emergency stairwell, and in a matter of moments was out of the building, onto the hospital grounds. He inhaled a deep breath of freedom and it made his head glow gold like a Byzantine icon. 
The frosty chill of the predawn hour crept up his backside as, dressed only in the backless hospital patient’s muu-muu and paper slippers, Niño de Jesus crept stealthily through the woods of Ward’s Island like a Red Indian, dodging the occasional police cruiser and crossing the footbridge that connects to Manhattan at East 103rd Street. 
The creases of his narrow, pock-marked face flowed with tears of prayer and redemption like overflooded streams traversing the parched earth of the Sonora desert during a thunderstorm when the denizens of that inhospitable plain burrow deep in their lairs to escape the consequences of God’s wrath. 
He crept through the streets of Spanish Harlem like a thief or a mugger, concealing himself in the shadows or hiding in basement stairwells where garbage cans were stored behind waist-high wrought iron fences, concealing his presence from all but the rats gorging themselves on the bounty of human refuse that overflowed the bins. 
He crossed himself as he passed a ceramic statuette of the Black Madonna displayed in the window of the Botanica Chango, a religious devotional shop dedicated to Santeria, Candomblé and the African cult sects of Christianity. Western religion accepts that we are created in God’s image. But everybody knows that images are expressions of interpretation. Physically speaking, we may resemble God to the same extent that one of Picasso’s cubist figures or a child’s finger painting resembles us. This possibility of distortion could reach into the metaphysical realm as well. So, Niño de Jesus Benitez’ spirit world, with its little dolls and burning sacrifices could be interpreted as an acceptable alternative to our so-called “rationalism”. As New York continued to evolve more latin, this tendency became more pronounced, percolating up through society as these animist elements gained more economic and social influence. A few steps further along, he reconsidered, went back and fell 
to his knees in devotion to the icon, blubbering in a creepy mix of Spanish and Jivaro, sobbing, praying for redemption, tranquility, comfort. 
At length he rose from his knees and made his way to the subway and down the stairs. The people waiting on the platform, mostly Mexican restaurant workers on their way to begin their pre-dawn cleaning jobs, expressed no astonishment at seeing Niño de Jesus Benitez place a hand on each turnstile and gracefully jump over the gate, though they were rather repulsed and offended at the naked display of his lower torso as the surgical dressing gown surged up above his waist like a billowing sail or a parachute. But he ran down the platform away from them and they went back to perusing their folded tabloid newspapers. 
Niño de Jesus left the train at midtown and began to walk west toward Twelfth Avenue and the Hudson River. This was the witching hour, when the streets were haunted by starkly mad homeless people in shockingly filthy fashion statements pushing around canvas mail carts filled with beer cans and garbage, so nobody, not even the cops so much as took notice of him in his backless cotton nightdress. 
As he approached Eleventh Avenue, his demeanor, already hysterical and delusional, went up an octave like some desiccated movie Mexican driven by thirst towards an anticipation of water. He drove himself desperately to a deserted lot enclosed by a chain link fence just off the West Side Highway. Running up to the fence, he grabbed onto it with both hands and gazed with fascination upon the object of his constant obsession. For the only thing occupying this space was a forklift machine, and not just any forklift but the monster mother of all cargo delivery vehicles. Painted in the most garish purple-fuchsia shade imaginable and standing fifteen feet high with rubber tires almost as tall as a man and forks as long as a New York City taxi, this monster, with its own enclosed, temperature-controlled cockpit, was designed for outdoor pipeline or mineral extraction work. In the relatively more delicate environment of New York, the machine, easily capable of moving a city bus or 
a small house, was used by its owner for transporting shipping containers to industrial sites on the West Side. Niño de Jesus frequently had marveled at it on his way to work and one day, when the proprietor had left the gate unlocked, he snuck in for a closer look. Climbing up the ladder on the side and peering into the control booth, he noticed that they had left the key in the ignition. After all, one might reason, who would steal such a monster? Only a crazy man. 
From that day forward the machine became a constant landmark of his scattered emotional terrain. The idea of it would pop up when he was riding the subway into town from his rented room in Corona, when he was eating beans and rice in the shared kitchen of his boarding house, when he was watching Mexican gangster movies showing smartly tailored guys with mustaches smattering each other into fragments with machine guns. 
If the average person is distracted by thoughts of sex every eight seconds as scientists contend, then Niño de Jesus Benitez, who had not the slightest interest in any form of human contact, who was a fanatical Catholic fundamentalist sober or drunk, had found the ideal vehicle of transferal for all his earthly animal tendencies. The fuchsia forklift took over all his waking thoughts and dreams. He changed his commute so that he could pass it twice each day, crossing himself and uttering a devotional prayer on his way to and from his job as (what else?) a forklift operator. 
The fuchsia forklift came to have a deleterious effect on his job performance at the industrial bakery where he worked. His previously close relationship with the dependable little yellow forklift that he drove became strained, the same way a man might devalue his plain but faithful wife after becoming infatuated with a younger, lovelier woman. He began treating her with contempt and insouciance, letting her battery water run low and forgetting to recharge her when he went on break or ended his shift. Sometimes, out of spite, he intentionally banged her against concrete surfaces, damaging her fiberglass body and exposing her insides. Occasionally he would drive her around without first raising her fork, causing sparks to fly as the prongs scraped painfully across the reinforced cement floor. The yellow forklift, which was named Teresa since its last driver had painted his child’s name on it, sadly deteriorated from her previously spunky self and now dripped tears of 
hydraulic fluid as she dragged herself forlornly about the premises. Finally, the loading dock foreman, Bolivar Marticorena, took notice and stepped in to champion her. 
“It’s a crime the way you abuse this machine,” he asserted. 
“Why don’t you go to hell!” retorted Niño de Jesus with the defensive indignation of somebody who knows perfectly well he is being justly accused. Whether Bolivar was right or wrong was beside the point. Niño de Jesus knew the Mexican foreman had it in for him because he was from Ecuador. Besides, he knew Bolivar’s hideous secret, that he was a demon from the depths of hell who had ascended into the world by way of a stairway behind the furnace in the sub-basement of the factory, a filthy, hellish place where the slops from the drainage system fell into a slop sink which connected it to the city’s sewer system. Niño de Jesus sometimes went down there because the foul odor kept others away, and he could get some peace and quiet while he sipped from a pint bottle of Ronrico to steady his nerves. As the old saying goes, once you get past the smell you’ve got it licked, and Niño de Jesus passed many agreeable solitary moments there, alone except for the occasional water bug 
or garden variety rodent. 
That is, until the day when he heard whistling, chuckling voices coming from behind the giant hundred year-old furnace in a dark corner, towering like a steel mountain behind a blackened lagoon of a cesspool of shiny sewage and putrefied rat carcasses. Intrigued, he squeezed his skinny body into the narrow passage separating the furnace from the wall until he had gotten behind it. There was a solid green door. He tried the handle, but it was locked. 
The voices behind the door had gone silent when they heard somebody trying the handle. There was total silence for several seconds, when suddenly a terrifying chorus of howls and screams startled and frightened Niño de Jesus. Panicked, he tried to scramble back through the narrow passage from which he had come, but in his haste he snagged part of his clothing on a piece of metal protruding from the furnace. Unable to move, he heard the voices come right up behind him, mocking him and threatening him in unknown languages of gibberish. Disembodied faces spun around in the air, laughing and menacing as Niño de Jesus, soaked in sweat and praying to Jesus for salvation from these infernal spirits who, enraged that he had discovered their hiding place, now laughingly taunted and threatened him with destruction and the loss of his immortal soul. 
He passed out, hanging there like a marionette in this dark, stinking subterranean pit of filth and demons for an immeasurable period of time. Once he woke up to find giant water bugs crawling all over his clothing and body, sucking the salt perspiration. At the end of the short passage, rats stuck their heads in curiously, wondering how long it would take for him to die there so they could begin eating him. Passing out again, he retreated into a dream state of delirium. 
At length, he was discovered by the old man, Tato, whose job in the factory it was to search out and kill bugs and rodents, for which purpose he carried with him a little tin first-aid case that he called his “maleta de muerte,” stuffed as it was with the traps and poisons that were his instruments of destruction. He would assemble all the little dead critters he had collected during his shift in a white bakery bag and show them to his boss as proof of his indispensability to the company. His manager, a hardened man of fifty, might very well be biting into a sandwich at the time of such an exhibition, where a glance into the bag would transport him into another little unique dimension of hell, one of water bugs stuck to glue traps, their shells and wings in disarray, many still alive with antennae furiously thrashing about; maggot-ridden corpses of mice stuck to traps with blood flowing out of their mouths and laying in their own droppings. “Muy bueno”, the manager would 
tell the old man as he chewed his sandwich. And he meant it. Tato, with his small body and unabashed enthusiasm for squeezing into dark corners of the factory, flashlight in hand, performed an invaluable function. The manager, although repelled by this little menagerie of loathsome filth, was nevertheless heartened by the knowledge that none of these animals would contaminate the food product or, even more horribly, intrude their pointy little heads during a factory tour by customers or a government inspection. “You’re doing a fine job,” he would compliment the little man in fluent, though heavily anglo-inflected Spanish. “Get out there and kill some more!” The old man, elated by this encouragement, would recommence with renewed ardor. 
Tato found Niño de Jesus Benitez suspended in the narrow passage behind the furnace, his clothes tangled in the machinery, and helped cut him free with a box cutter. After he had cut him loose, the toothless old man cautioned Niño de Jesus in barely comprehensible Spanish, “Never go there. There are bad things.” 
This episode had a major impact on Niño de Jesus’ mind, and he started going down to the sub-basement on a regular basis, not to nip the bottle but to monitor the activity behind the furnace. In the silence, punctuated only by the gurgling and plopping of the rancid, filthy factory waste water flowing through the drainage pipe into the slop sink, he could make out the sounds coming from the green door at the end of the narrow passage, the infernal whistling and chuckling of rats mixed with human voices shrilly screaming and the shouts and pleadings of tortured souls being impaled on spikes, branded with red-hot pokers, having their eyes gouged out. This was the work of the Jews, who ascended a staircase leading from the pit of hell to emerge in modern New York. He formulated a clear picture of this diabolical intrusion of demons and determined that the bakery was a mere front for the methodical infiltration of Jew-demons into the world, a hellish Fifth Column organized to 
deliver humanity into the embrace of Satan. 
Armed with this knowledge, Niño de Jesus Benitez came to develop a clear understanding of the events of September 11, which, though having occurred many years before, were still the major preoccupation of New York society. He came to realize that the buildings’ collapse, while precipitated by the airplanes having collided into them, actually resulted from fissures in the earth’s crust caused by the Jews burrowing underneath them and weakening their foundations. This little scenario he updated to include fiendish masked lesbians violating priests with massive strap-on dildoes. Niño de Jesus, straining to hear, could distinguish over the roar of the furnace and the rushing flop of sewage into the slop sink the barely audible moans and pleas of priests who, stripped naked and chained to posts, bleeding and sweating, their pathetic moans and pleas for mercy and salvation drowned out by the hellish baritone laughter of the lesbians, were flagellated unmercifully with barbed 
wire cat o’ nine tails whips. 
He decided to alert a priest, Father Guzman, a saintly man who ministered to the unfortunate Central American undocumented aliens out of St. Anthony’s Parish in Corona. Father Guzman listened sympathetically to Niño de Jesus’ description of the events taking place behind the green door and wrote him a referral for psychiatric counseling, which Niño de Jesus immediately tore up after leaving the priest’s office. 
“If they think they’re going to get me, they’re crazy!” 
About the only thing that could mitigate these feelings of isolation, conspiracy and rage percolating through the skinny body of Niño de Jesus Benitez was the tranquillizing effect of watching the oozing, gooey blobs of putrefied bakery waste as the plunger forced it into the bowels of the rear-loading garbage truck each morning. The mesmerizing swirls of fermented dough, damaged product, grease, oil, vegetable coloring, purple blueberry, brown cinnamon, egg, whole wheat, brown sugar, pumpernickel, etc., all squished together and molded in texture and shape like a putrid, stinking lava lamp of decay reminiscent of a Jackson Pollock tableau (in actuality, the garbage truck was a vastly more talented artist), aroused in Niño de Jesus feelings of cosmic harmony. The spectacle of all this oozing decayed slop rising, falling and reformulating into kaleidoscopic shapes and textures of filth spoke volumes to him about the cosmic cycle of rebirth, like a pictorial essay in 
National Geographic about the birth of the universe illustrated with photos from the Hubbell satellite telescope. 
As he sat in his forklift, sprinkled with a light layer of the flour blowing out of the back of the garbage truck like a wedding cake ornament dusted with powered sugar and transfixed by celestial reveries of euphoria, the spell was suddenly broken by an insistant klaxoning of a tooty little car horn. 
Stationed directly behind him, a very expensive metallic green German luxury car driven by a well-nourished oriental businessman was insisting on its right of way. This Korean man, impatient and offended to have to have his egress impeded by a dirty, dark-skinned workman riding a battered piece of heavy equipment, felt entirely justified to lean on his horn. 
Though the guy was letting his horn do the talking for him, Niño de Jesus got the message loud and clear. In the Asiatic scheme of things, whoever had the money was on top, and the rest of us were suckers. Calmly, he put the forklift in reverse and smashed it into the front end of the beemer. The guy got out and started screaming horribly. 
Niño de Jesus drove forward, raised the forks, wheeled the machine around so that it was facing the car face nose to nose, smashed into it and lowered the forks, crushing its hood and flattening its suspension so that the tires were flat onto the pavement like seals’ flippers. The great screaming of metal and crunching noise of destruction greeted the cacophony of oriental screams and curses as the car’s owner helplessly witnessed the willful destruction of his expensive vehicle. 
Niño de Jesus jumped off his machine and ran of down the street. He was not arrested until months later, by which time everybody had lost interest in the affair, including the judge who ordered him held in Ward’s Island Sanitarium for psychiatric evaluation. 
You can change a name, but that does not alter the essential nature of a thing. You can call a scumsucking maggot Marilyn Monroe, but it still lives in corrupt decay and thrives on the putrefied bowels of a dead thing. When the city fathers attempted to sanitize the image of Hell’s Kitchen by changing its name to Clinton, it was like putting tooth whitener on a decayed black stump of a broken molar. Nobody was fooled except the genius who initiated the concept. It was still a neighborhood of noxious gases and steam rising up like a bitch’s brew from forlorn, desolate streetcorners. Drug addicts waited behind trucks with guns and baseball bats for likely victims. Hookers lifted their skirts at traffic lights to display their wares. Rats the size of dogs demanded, and got, easement rights through people’s living rooms. 
Meanwhile, you could look down to the end of the street and see, across the river in New Jersey, the heights of Weehawken, where luxury condominium complexes and Victorian mansions held out a tantalizing mirage of American prosperity and order as though peering across a dimensional void from the desolate wasteland of a Salvador Dali tableau into the benign innocence of a Norman Rockwell magazine cover, taunting the damned souls who would never know it like the key to a jail cell hanging just out of reach of the condemned prisoner. 
Niño de Jesus Benitez had occasionally admired that glittering promise, but this night his concentration was fixed on the more attainable goal of the fuchsia forklift with the all-terrain rubber wheels. It was just where he had left it. The sight of it, shining like a purple plum in the moonlight, made his heart leap with joy. All those months that he had been locked in isolation, and the preceding months that he had been free but in an isolation of the soul, the one dream that had kept him from sinking into despair was to get back to this forklift and use what he had learned to confront the defilers of humanity and stop them from dragging our immortal souls through an eternal gauntlet of torment. 
The gate to the yard was closed with a chain and a large brass Master lock. Niño de Jesus had been starving himself for months so that he would be skinny enough to squeeze through the narrow opening allowed by the slack in the chain. 
He wedged himself through, though just barely, his flimsy hospital gown getting snagged in the chain mesh and torn off his body, leaving him just the paper slippers. He ran to the monster machine and, clambering up the ladder to the cockpit, opened the door and installed himself into the contoured operator’s chair. 
His body exploded with an expression of relief as his muscle memory recognized the familiar sensation of being in control of a piece of heavy machinery. The key to the ignition was still there! He turned it and the machine erupted with the rage of life. One lever motivated a chain assembly raising the gigantic forks. Another lever changed their angle of thrust, bringing them closer to the cab. Releasing the air brake, he put the leviathan in gear and aimed it toward the fence, crashing through effortlessly as the gates were torn off their hinges and tossed uselessly into the deserted street. 
He set the thing toward the west, barreling the wrong way down the one-way street in the direction of the Hudson River piers. A car approaching from that direction boldly sounded its horn, then, realizing he meant business, meekly pulled over to the side and ceded him right of way. 
When Niño de Jesus got to the West Side Highway, traffic was sparse in the pre-dawn hour. He turned left and headed toward the 46th Street Pier, where the Aircraft Carrier Intrepid was moored. This overwhelming expression of American imperial majesty was a floating hotel of death. New York mayors have often been berated for having their own foreign policy, and it’s no wonder, considering that they have their own navy with enough firepower to decimate whole countries. 
Crowded onto its flight deck, the Intrepid boasted a dazzling array of technological weaponry: Blackbirds, AWACs, Tomcats, Cobras, HUEYs, Apaches. Berthed opposite it, a nuclear submarine with missle poised in launching position was at the ready. On a barge behind that rested an entire Concorde supersonic jetliner. Deployed on the dock separating the two majestic warships was a little decorative bouquet of tanks, armored vehicles, armored personnel carriers, howitzers and cannon, a little flourish of mayhem displayed like little plaster roses on a child’s birthday cake. 
Toward this massive and indomitable concentration of power sped Niño de Jesus Benitez, naked and in control of a stolen forklift, hellbent for leather and propelled forward like Don Quixote on a desperate mission to save the world from the forces of satanic destruction. 
Unlike Don Quixote, however, Niño de Jesus had no intention of smashing himself against a superior construct. His concept was marginally more sophisticated, a sort of step-by-step methodology in problem solving, as though devised by a chimp moving a box so he can stand on it to reach a banana suspended by a string. 
After he had made the discovery of the satanic demons, lesbians and Jews infiltrating New York by way of the Green Door in the sub-basement boiler room of the bakery, Niño de Jesus Benitez had cast about devising solutions for rescuing humanity’s immortal soul. He spent his lunch breaks squatting on his heels like an Ecuadorian cowboy on the sidewalk in front of the bakery which, as fate would have it, was on the opposite corner facing the mammoth battleship complex. It may seem incongruous, this juxtaposition of imperial might to be facing a cesspool of grease and filth besieged like a frontier outpost by legions of rodents, giant roaches and garbage-eating pigeons, but this has been the condition of imperial might through the ages, grandeur surrounded by decay. Anyway, the Intrepid was a latecomer to this environment, specifically placed there to ignite gentrification of the area. 
Many questions perplexed the mind of Niño de Jesus Benitez as he contemplated the multi-faceted dilemma that confronted him. How is it possible for man to judge evil when he himself is born in original sin? If Satan has no concept of evil, can he be said to be doing evil without having a moral parameter for judging his own actions? After all, one might conjecture, if the snake that bites you is just following his nature, how can he be held guilty for that? 
Niño de Jesus knew that the dark legions of satanic malediction were onto him for discovering their conspiracy. Obviously, they could have destroyed him at any time, so they must have been saving him for a particularly gruesome fate. Nevertheless, they sent him signals that they were watching. Somehow they had gotten into his locker without breaking the lock and pissed into his bottle of rum, this he knew for a fact. They had put dead rodents into his work boots, so that when he put his foot in, he felt the crunch of the little bones and the squishy sensation of blood and guts all over his feet. Maybe they thought these signals would deter him, but if so they had not appreciated the full measure of their adversary and had underestimated his godly nature. Niño de Jesus Benitez would rather be blown to smithereens on the battlefield of Armageddon in the Final Conflict between Good and Evil than be taken whole and roasted on a spit, writhing for eternity in the fires of 
hell, his flesh sizzling in the flames, like some pathetic cringing beast out of a Hieronymus Bosch tableau. 
If he was going to be judged, then let it be by God Himself sitting on a high bench and counseled by a jury of celestial angels! Niño de Jesus floored the accelerator pedal of the mammoth forklift and crashed through the wrought iron fence forming the security perimeter surrounding the aerospace complex. The guards in the sentry booth scattered in panic, barely evading the explosive impact as the rampaging machine smashed it into fragments. They drew their sidearms and started blasting away, but the heavily armored vehicle deflected the bullets like fireflies as they pinged uselessly off its reinforced shell. A cacophony of alarms went off, echoing against the mighty hull of the giant carrier, joined within seconds by the insistent burbling of police cruisers approaching at breakneck speed from the north, south and east as the alarm went out that the Intrepid was under terrorist attack. 
With pandemonium breaking out all around him, Niño de Jesus Benitez calmly put his plan into effect. As alarms roared and flashing lights popped all around, and bullets bounced off his truck, he used the vehicle to gently nudge the artillery piece closest the highway until its nuzzle was facing directly east, right at the beige and brown façade designed to look like an ersatz Disneyland pirate castle or an Iberian seafood restaurant on Calle Ocho. The pinnacle of this fantastical structure boasted an ardent expression of nationalistic exuberance, New York’s biggest Puerto Rican flag. “¡Mi Bandera Querida!” Right below, shining over the highway as the first rays of the sun heralded the approaching daylight, huge block letters announced “San Juan Bagels. The Bagel With Sabór.” 
It was certainly inevitable that in a city where cultural fusion was the spiraling fate of so many conjunctions grinding against each other like screaming gears, that a gastronomic hybrid like the latin bagel would be born. This bagel was the child of Pato Gonzalez, an authentic Puerto Rican Jew who started rolling bagels by hand in the Bronx at age 17 and over the course of many years experimentation developed a product that was more Boricua than Belarus, a bagel that rather than plopping down your gullet like a depth charge, exploded in your mouth with fireworks of spicy flavor and danced a cultivated rumba down your esophagus. It took New York and the world by storm, and was eventually shipped around the planet in frozen containers to Paris, Dubai and Shanghai. It was featured in Tokyo fashion magazines, doctoral theses submitted at Oxford and the Sorbonne, and became local New York color for Hollywood movies. 
All this excitement was naturally lost on the low-wage immigrant workers who actually produced the product, and had Niño de Jesus Benitez actually availed himself of Father Guzman’s offer of psychiatric counseling, he may have come to realize that his true resentment of the place had less to do with flagellating baritone lesbians than the inevitable resentment of being forced to work in a hot, steamy, stinking food processing plant producing a gastronomic luxury bakery product that he couldn’t afford. 
But no matter, all the conjecture in the world cannot explain away the convoluted machinations of his deranged imagination and their resultant consequences. He wanted to blow the place up, and he now had a cannon in place and pointed directly at it. As bullets rained around him and scores of police cars, sirens wailing and lights flashing, blocked all approaches to the Intrepid, Niño de Jesus Benitez, naked as a jaybird, jumped off the forklift, ran to the back of the cannon and began pulling frantically at the levers. 
Naturally, nothing happened. This was the stupidest project ever conceived, by a whack job who had one hour previously escaped from the Ward’s Island Insane Asylum. A pale of silence overtook the whole scenario as the legions of armed cops waited for instructions that would allow them to blow the pathetic little fucker to smithereens, which was pretty much the standard procedure in instances like these. 
However, in this instance they were to be denied this small indulgence. In keeping with the city’s business-oriented Republican administration, which was touting a new “kinder, gentler” approach toward its less privileged citizens in order to advance its proposal to host the Olympic games, the city was toying with new gadgets that would keep the idiots alive long enough to stick them under a jail somewhere upstate, where they would rot for an appropriately long term out of the public eye. 
With this end in mind, they had contracted with Rudy Giuliani Associates to develop a new line of non-lethal applications to restrain fat ladies brandishing cutlery, deranged pot-head rabbinical students wielding hammers, graffiti artists who refused to go along peacefully, African street peddlers with dark wallets in their hands and the other million-and-one inexplicably bizarre human interactions that altogether define a day in the life of the Naked City. 
The latest of these innovations was a remote-control cannon mounted on a kiddie car that fired a weighted net. Naturally, when the device was announced, some cruel soul joked that Giuliani was working on a net large enough to cover the entire city. 
For Niño de Jesus, who was standing at the controls of the artillery piece expecting to be disintegrated at any second, as well as the scores of cops fidgeting behind their squad cars hoping for the command to let loose with their Glock pistols and riot guns, the little toy cannon slowly creeping to the center of the scene was an interminable entre-acte of suspense. All the assembled actors stood breathlessly at their posts like a child’s toy soldiers as the technicians from Giuliani Associates calibrated the trajectory of the shot, knowing that if their first attempt failed it would immediately be follow up by a fusillade of bullets, and that the cannon project (and, not incidentally, their jobs) would face meltdown in a cavalcade of media ridicule. 
The little cannon exploded with a loud BOOM, and Niño de Jesus Benitez and the assembled police, reporters, dignitaries, traffic copters and spectators watched in awe as the net sped at him, entangling him and throwing him to the concrete. The reality of the force, which had all the velocity of a battering ram, knocked the wind out of him, along with all his illusions. Nothing brings you down to earth like getting arrested. Forgotten were the stairwell behind the Green Door, the lesbians, the forklift and all the other ephemeral constructs of his imagination. All the petty slights, the insults, the million-and-one seemingly important little events that bring you to committing the act evaporate like Gorillas in the Mist once you are confronted with the realities of the New York Criminal Justice System and its shackles, the body odor of the other inmates, the filthy floors and toilets reeking of disinfectant, the rancid baloney sandwiches, moralistic prosecutors seeking to 
make points with your ass, greedy judges impatient to get rid of you so that they can make some money. In the instant that Niño de Jesus Benitez’ illusions were peeled away like the layers of an onion, all he was left with was the net, the hard macadam and the blue sky above which seemed to spin ‘round and ‘round in an endless swirl. 
The assembled law enforcement officers surged forward in a blue wave. They surrounded him, the initial disappointment at not being permitted to perforate him replaced by curiosity about the nature of their prey. When they saw him for what he was – a cringing, naked little beaner, crying, delusional, tangled in the net and crawling about helplessly like one of Tato’s little creatures stuck to the glueboard, they laughed. 
One of the officers, a massive motorcycle cop with black jackboots, a fade haircut and a scorpion tattoo on his thick neck spit a huge glob of bubble gum in the direction of Niño de Jesus. It bounced off him. The cop joked, “You’re in deep shit now, Pedro, this is federal property!” 
All the cops laughed. 
THE END﻿

Meer lezen (529 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-eNTMkuxZFxo/Um11-imC6jI/AAAAAAAABLI/40EFZJKa8zg/w426-h568/lorenz+halloween+party+2013+006.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/102771885878475900381/albums/5951364632354955489/5951364634217684322?sqi=106556096081458944318&amp;sqsi=db77444c-15ea-41c0-817b-6733dbae1b5d</link><title>The Grimes Home by Alice Thompson 

My name is Jason Grimes and I am writing this so that when the room is eventually opened people will perhaps understand the things they find within it. And so that I will not be thought of as the madman that part of me already fears I am. 

It all began with the reading of the will. My mother (My only living parent left) had passed away due to a heart attack in her New England home. Her body had been found by one of the women who came to clean every few days and the news had not come as a shock to any of the family. She’d had two previous heart attacks and with her smoking and drinking she wasn't exactly in the best of health. 

It had been a surprise that she wanted me to have the old family home though. I’d never exactly had much love for the place and had moved out the first chance I got. Honestly I hadn't been expecting to get anything in the will, given how long it had been since we’d even spoken, I was surprised that she hadn't written me out, the way she’d tried to write me out of the family’s history by removing any pictures of me from the house. 

I certainly didn’t plan to keep that creepy, rundown old place. But at the same time I knew that there was a chance it could fetch a bit of cash on the market if someone put a little work into fixing it up and as I was currently between jobs it might be a worthwhile use of my time. I got my brother and our cousin to come over and help with fixing it up, which they happily agreed to do. 

There actually wasn’t as much work to do as I had first thought as the house seemed to be in better repair than I remembered it being. I guessed that my mother, cheap as she was, had still finally been forced to actually get someone in to fix up some of the bigger problems the house had. There was still stuff that needed repair and a new coat of paint but it only ended up taking about a week or so in the end. 

It was during this time that I first found it. 

Now I didn’t have the best memories of the old place, given how long it had been since I had stayed there. But one of the first things I noticed while I was walking along the ground floor hallway was that there was a door that hadn't been there before. I stared at it for a few moments, more out of confusion than anything else before trying to push it open. It wouldn’t budge an inch. 

I asked my brother if he knew what might be down there and he shook his head, saying that he’d not even noticed it before now. My cousin said that she’d noticed a big, old fashioned looking key in the keyhole of the door the last time she’d come round to visit but she had no clue where it might be right now. I shrugged, not really thinking much of it at the time, just figuring that I’d had to get someone to bust the door down at some point before I got the house sold. 

The room none of us WANTED to go in was Emerson’s. It was weird, seeing all his old toys and coloring books still there, as if our mother had been trying to bring her son back by clinging on to the past. Emerson had always been our mothers favorite, the one who she’d lavished all of her attention on and I saw that she had stuck his drawings up all over the place. Drawings of pirate ships and odd, comical looking figures with strange designs. 

My brother told me that when he’d stayed for dinner, our mother would still set a place for Emerson as if she expected him to just show up out of the blue. Missing for all these years and she was still expecting him to come wandering through the door… 

That first night I spent alone in the house I didn’t sleep very well. Crazy as it sounds I kept thinking that I heard noises in the house, people talking to each other. I must have checked each and every one of the rooms a good dozen times only to find each and every one of them empty. I even checked to see if I’d left the TV on but it was still unplugged. 

I would go back to bed and then after a little while the noises would start up again. Sometimes I was sure that I could hear music as well. It was around four in the morning that a thought occurred to me and I went to the locked door in the hallway, pressing my ear against it and listening closely. I was sure I heard what sounded like a muffled tune coming from within. 

The next day I went into town to buy some food and after the events of last night I also bought a hammer to knock that old door down. It was while chatting with the cashier that I learned something unsettling about the neighborhood that I had temporarily moved into. 

I had casually brought up where I was staying after he commented on me being new around here and told him that I was planning to try and sell up. He’d let out a short burst of laughter before looking embarrassed about it and when I’d asked him to explain had said the following: 

“No one with sense is gonna buy that dump. No one with half a brain would buy ANY house within ten miles of that place” he said, not looking up from the groceries he was packing away. 

“Why not? It seems like a nice enough neighborhood” I had replied. 

“Because of all them kids going missing, of course” 

He’d gone on to explain that for the past few years there had been a sudden and disturbing rise in the number of children vanishing from their homes in the area. There had been search parties formed, the police and the FBI had gotten involved but nothing had turned up. The kids had vanished from their homes with no signs of forced entry or struggle and no evidence left behind as to who might have been responsible. 

People were trying to move away as fast as possible but there were few who would buy a house in the area once they heard about what was going on. No one wanted to move to a place where a child kidnapper/killer was active. 

I have to admit the story kind of creeped me out. Knowing that something so strange was going on near where I was staying made the odd goings on of the previous night seem even more unsettling to me and so as soon as I got home I decided to bust that door down. My neighbor, a fairly nice young woman named 
Charley who I’d gotten to know, was working on her homes front lawn when I got back and noticed the hammer in my hand as I headed towards the front door of my home. Not really wanting to be alone when I broke the door down I gave her an abridged version of events (Leaving out the odd noises of last night) and asked if she’d like to join me in finding out what was in the room. 

“Mysterious locked door? Very Scooby Doo” she said as I grinned. 

“Sure. I’ll be Fred, you be Daphne” I replied, happy to have someone with me, her presence making the nervousness I had felt while listening to the cashiers story start to fade a little. 

“Trust me; I’m more Velma than Daphne” 

Once inside the house I packed away the various groceries, pouring drinks for myself and Charley before we went to the white door. It only took a few swings from the hammer to smash it open, the lock breaking beneath the assault and the door swinging open. Behind it was a staircase, leading down into a darkened basement below. I stared in confusion at the stairs, not believing what I was seeing. Our house didn’t have a basement, I was sure of that. 

And yet suddenly I seemed to recall seeing this before. I could remember playing with Emerson one day, daring each other. Emerson had always been afraid of pretty much everything and I, in the way of older brothers everywhere, had taken far too much pleasure in tormenting him. I seemed to remember the two of us stood at the top of this staircase, me daring him to go down into the dark while calling him a chicken. 

‘C’mon Emerson’ I had been saying to him. ‘You have to go inside…’ 

Charley and I began to descend the old, creaking steps towards the basement, the hammer still clutched tight in my hands. I didn’t know what we would find but I knew that I felt better being armed with something that could do some damage. As we reached the bottom of the stairs Charley began feeling around for a light switch, finding one after a few moments and flicking it on. The room was instantly illuminated, revealing what was within. 

“Oh my god! LOOK at all this cool stuff!” Charley cried out. 

The basement was full of puppets. 

There was dozens of them, all lined up on various shelves all in very good repair as if they were brand new. There were puppets of all shapes and sizes, some of them being very human looking while others were Muppet-like animal creatures and others were more monstrous. There were props from what looked like the set of a kids show I guess. None of it had any dust on it, as if someone had been down to tidy up just moments before. 

I could guess what all of this was from but what it was doing down here I had no idea. 

“What IS all of this?” Charley asked as she picked up one of the puppets, a guy with a massive mustache and a monocle over one eye. She grinned, playing around with him, moving his limbs up and down. 

“My brother used to work on a kids show, years ago. ‘Pirate Place’ I think it was called. Only ran for a couple of years before it got cancelled. I guess this stuff is all the old puppets and sets from the show” I said as we looked around at the room. My eyes fell on a creepy looking skeleton puppet with a really weird mouth and a top hat upon its head. Ugly looking thing, I thought to myself at that moment. 

“No way! Do you have any idea how much some of this stuff might be worth? Collectors pay a FORTUNE for things like this on eBay” Charley said, setting the puppet down gently on one of the shelves. 

I glanced around at the rest of the contents of the room. Apart from the puppets and the set pieces there was an old sewing machine set on a desk that was otherwise completely bare. There was no sign of anything that could have been the source of the tune that I’d heard before. Deciding that I must have imagined it, probably due to lack of sleep and being back in the old place, I did my best to forget about my fears and concentrate on the opportunity before me now. 

There was just one thing that troubled me as I looked around. On the desk the sewing machine was set on there were several odd red stains spattered over it. As I stared at them I was sure, out of the corner of my eye that the odd looking skeleton puppets head had twitched in my direction. 

The next few days went by without anything odd happening really. I put the puppets up on eBay and had a few people come to view the house. The only thing that was strange was when one couple viewed the basement. All of the color drained out of the husbands face when his eyes fell on the skeleton puppet and he just turned, left the basement and then the house. He went to the car, started it up and sat there until his wife joined him (After apologizing for his rudeness) and the two drove away. 

Later that night I was sure I heard the old sewing machine in the basement. I wanted to go down and check and yet at the same time looking at that darkened doorway I suddenly felt very frightened. And when there was a knock at the door the sudden noise almost made me jump out of my skin, my head jerking to the side towards the source of the noise. Taking a moment to steady my nerves I walked to the door, opening it cautiously to see Charley standing there. 

“We need to talk” she said. 

She explained that she’d mentioned to a friend of hers about the find in the basement a few days ago. When she’d brought up the name ‘Pirate Place’ he’d gone quiet and asked for her to describe the puppets. He looked afraid, she said, as if he’d just seen a ghost. He had told her to move house, to get away from me and from those ‘Damn things’ as he referred to the puppets, growing increasingly hysterical as the conversation had gone on. He’d repeated over and over that it wasn't safe to be around them that ‘They could see you through them’. He’d rambled at length about ‘Physical avatars’ and ‘The signal’ none of which had made any sense to her. 

Apparently he’d used to work in television and had known my brother. He said that he’d sat down with Emerson in what he called ‘The Script Room’ and then started raving about ‘Knowing where the stories came from’. Charley said that she had never seen him like this before, that he seemed to be almost psychotic. His eyes bugging out of his head, his face glistening with sweat. She had been worried that he was about to have some kind of attack. 

“Was your brother involved in anything…weird?” she asked me and I honestly didn’t know how to respond to that. Emerson had always been an odd kid, no doubt about that, but I couldn't imagine him ever provoking such a frightened reaction in anyone let alone a grown man. I asked her if he’d said why the puppets were so awful and she shrugged. 

“All the stuff he was saying wasn't making much sense. He just said ‘It’s not the puppets. It’s what made them’ and then he just got up and said he couldn't be in my house anymore. Just ran out to his car and drove off” 

I decided that as she’d shared her weirdness with me, maybe I could open up about some of the weirdness in my life right now. I explained about the odd noises, the music and the sewing machine seeming to turn itself on. And against my better judgement we decided to descend into that pitch black basement once again. 

I’m not sure what I expected to find but I was sure that something would be wrong. So when we saw that nothing seemed to have changed or been moved I felt an odd sense of almost disappointment. I kind of WANTED for there to be something strange down there, just to prove that I wasn't imagining all of this, to prove to myself that I wasn't going crazy. 

And that’s when Charley spotted the door. 

It was when she flicked off the light as we began to go up, casting one last look back into the darkness and noticed that there was light coming from somewhere. Not very bright but nonetheless a light source. Moving swiftly we shoved aside one of the shelves of puppets and felt along the ‘wall’ behind it, to confirm what Charley had believed to be the case: there was a door behind it. 

“Told you this was all kinds of Scooby Doo” Charley said with a grin on her face, clearly enjoying herself. I smiled, which was something I definitely wouldn't have been able to do if she wasn't’t here. It was nice to have someone to share this insanity with. 

We felt along the wall trying to find some way to open the door, some handle or switch to make it open. From behind it I was sure that I could hear SOMETHING. It sounded almost like music. Circus music, a cheerful, upbeat tune but also off somehow, as if there was something not quite right about it. 

Out of the corner of my eye I was sure that the puppet with the ridiculous mustache and monocle had moved. And I realize how ridiculous that sounds but I was certain of it. It was just the tiniest movement, a twitch of its head toward the skeleton puppet. ‘As if waiting for orders’ I thought to myself, and then wondered why that had popped into my head. 

With a bit of work we managed to strip away the wall paper that was covering most of the door, revealing that it was a bright red in color, the paint chipped and flaking in places, with a small keyhole and no handle. I assumed that it just pushed inwards once unlocked or perhaps slid to the side as there was no place for a handle to have once been either. 

It was then that I noticed that Charley had stopped smiling. In fact she was staring at the door with what looked like a mix of confusion and fear, taking a few steps back from it. When I asked her what was wrong she just shook her head and made excuses to leave. I asked her if she was alright and she just told me she was tired and promised to help me try and find the key to the door in the morning. It was getting late so it was plausible enough but I knew that something was wrong here. 

For the rest of the evening I looked through Emerson’s old things in his room, looking for some clue perhaps as to what it was that had inspired such fear in Charley’s friend. For the most part it was old toys and childhood drawings, nothing of much use. There were a few things that were odd though. 

It was a picture that I guess Emerson had done when he was little. There was a crude drawing of a boy sat in his bed that I think was meant to be Emerson himself. Around him were stood several figures. One was just a stick figure with a hat upon its head. Another was a portly man with a cartoonish mustache and teeth. And there was a third that was…very odd. 

It was just a scribble in the outline of a person, a black, shadowy scribble. There was a circle drawn above the three figures and the boy and lines were shown coming down from it leading to the boys head. For some reason, looking at those lines, the word ‘Tendrils’ came into my head. 

There was a picture of a red door. The words ‘WHERE THEY TAKE THEM’ were scrawled in large letters beneath it. 

And the final picture was of the stick man and the man with the mustache leading several smaller figures towards a third. This one was a woman, a rather well drawn one in comparison to the crude, basic nature of the others except for the face. The face was just two dots for eyes and a line for a mouth. 

The words ‘WHERE THEY TAKE THEM’ were written here as well. 

There was a message on my answering machine from Charley the next day. She said that she’d gone to stay with her girlfriend for a few days ‘Just to clear her head’ and apologized for leaving so suddenly the previous night. Her voice sounded odd, kind of shaky really, and she said not to bother with the door. She tried to sound calm and casual when she said it but there was fear in her voice. She said it was probably best to forget all about the whole thing and just cover up the basement, not even mention it to potential buyers for the house. She said it would be a good idea to take the puppets off of eBay as well. 

I should have just done as she asked. 

Instead I spent the rest of the day ransacking the house, searching for the key to that door. I looked everywhere with little success until, almost on a whim, I decided to search Emerson’s room more thoroughly. And there, hidden in one of his old pillow cases, was a key. 

I poured myself a drink to steady my nerves, sitting down to watch the TV. I remembered the old thing never picking up much when we were little, the channels always being full of static. It seemed to be working better now at least and the news came on, talking about another disappearance in the area. A girl of twelve this time, vanished from her home in the middle of the night. I flipped through the channels looking for something a little less grim while I finished my drink 

Getting up, I headed down the steps into the basement, striding toward the door, ready to open it. 

The skeleton puppet was sat at the sewing machine now. I knew I hadn't moved it and neither had Charley. And the other puppets…their heads seemed to be turned towards it, as if they were waiting for it to do something, to say something. God it was a hideous thing, that awful misshapen mouth looking so awful. God knows why the prop designer had made it look that way. 

At that moment, the words ‘To grind your skin’ popped into my head. 

I put the key into the door and sure enough it unlocked it, the door pushing inward with ease, revealing the room that lay beyond it. It was illuminated by a single dirty bulb, making the contents of the room easy to see. Dear lord the smell…the only thing worse was the sight of what was littered around the room. 

Children’s shoes and clothes, some spattered with old, dried blood were piled in a heap in one corner of the room. The floor was stained with large patches of red, one of which, as I stepped into it, I realized was still somewhat fresh, fresh and sticky like soda spilled on a movie theater floor. The room smelt of spoiling meat and burnt hair and it took all I had not to throw up as I entered it, wondering how the smell hadn't traveled from this room to the basement. 

There was a pile of old video cassettes in one corner of the room, all labelled with things like ‘Emerson’s first bike ride’ and ‘Emerson’s first spelling bee’ all old home movies I guess. But mixed in with them were tapes labelled ‘Candle Cove episode four’ and ‘Season three pilot episode’. I picked up a few and noticed that there were bloody fingerprints on several. 
There was a series of steps leading down further into the blackness at the rear of the room and I felt oddly compelled to go down there. How far down did this go? How was this even here, beneath my family home, without me ever knowing of it? And yet…and yet I felt like I DID know about it. Looking at those steps I felt like I remembered being in this room before. I was a child and it had been empty then and there I stood with Emerson, at the foot of these stairs. 

“Emerson…you have…to go…inside” I had whispered to him, taking delight in how terrified he looked. He had gone down into the dark and… 
And… 

My head throbbed with pain. It actually physically hurt to try and remember, as if something was willing me not to. Had there been someone down there with us? I was sure I remembered there being someone in the room besides the two of us, the more I thought about it. Our mother? No not our mother but another woman. Why couldn't I remember her face? 

I began to take unsteady steps down the stairs; the more I walked the closer I got to another door, another red door. The key fit the lock of this one as well and it opened with ease. There was music coming from within now and the sound of waves crashing against the shore. I felt it pulling me towards it, calling to me like a siren song. 

I had to go inside, I thought to myself. I HAD to go inside. 

I wasn't alone in this room. 

I burned all the puppets later that night. Not that I imagine it matters. 
They've been destroyed before and it hasn't stopped them from coming back. They’re just wood and paint and cloth, nothing but a conduit. They allow them to come through, allow them to walk through the door and come here. Oh god the door…I know where they go now…I know where they go, oh Christ, oh Jesus please help me I know where they go… 

I saw it. They took me there, the way they took my brother when he was a child. They need us. I don’t know why they need us but they need us, that’s what he said. Through that horrible, misshapen mouth, those eyes rolling in his sockets wildly. They needed my brother and they need me. My family is not safe. The signal needs us. The story needs us. 

The ship came to that cave. Emerson was laughing and crying at the same time as he spoke the words I knew were coming. As he told me what I had to do. 

It was waiting for me. 

I saw the 

(The following portion of the letter has been heavily crossed out, making it almost impossible to read. A word that may or may not be ‘Mannequin’ appears at one point in the letter and the words ‘skin’ is visible at several points in the following two paragraphs. What could be ‘Faker’ or ‘Taker’ can also be made out in the second paragraph and ‘ship’ in the final sentence. The letter resumes…) 

I ran. You may think me a coward for not helping them, not even trying to save them. But I know where the ship is taking them now. I know where the voyage leads and I know who is waiting at the end. I would pray to god but know that will do no good. I know now. I know things that no one should ever know. 

I know what Emerson learned, that day the signal found him. I know the things he learned in the dark places, where the music comes from. Music played on instruments crafted of bone and organs, wrapped in flesh. It’s always there now in my head, playing on an endless loop. The signal has found me like it found Emerson that day I made him go down those stairs. Like it found our mother. I know why she did what she did. I know what she knew and I know where Emerson is. I saw him on the ship. 

My god the ship… 

The laughing was the worst. I wish it would stop laughing. 

I have sealed up the basement but know that one day someone will go down there again. I write this so that when they discover the things I know they will find down there they will know neither I nor my mother were responsible. And perhaps so they will have the courage to do what I do not and destroy this terrible place, burn it to the ground. The only thing that holds me back is the fear that perhaps this place is not merely the door to their cage but the cage itself. If the house were to be destroyed perhaps they would be able to spread. 

I wish to apologize to my family. I hope they will forgive me for what I am about to do. I hope they will understand. My brother, if this reaches you please do not go into that house. And don’t sell it. Board it up and let it stand forgotten, a creepy old building for people to stare and wonder at. Maybe that will hold them back at least. 

The sewing machine is going at all hours of the day now. I know that it’s him, sewing himself new additions to that terrible cape. She lets him keep the skin, you see. He gets to keep the skin. 

I am so sorry Emerson. I don’t hate you for the things you did. I wish I could help you or at least put you out of your misery. I know they won’t let you rest. I know you cannot be free of them now. 

I see them out of the corner of my eye sometimes. They’re going to take me to the ship. I won’t let them. I will die the way I choose. The sea will carry my body away, hopefully far from where they can ever find it. 

(This letter was found lying beside a cassette tape. The tape proved to be nothing but static although those who watched it reportedly felt a sense of ‘unease’ and ‘nausea’ when they tried to view it. 

The Grimes home was searched and the belongings of over twenty three children who had gone missing in the local area were discovered within. No trace of the children themselves was found within the house or near it however. 
The basement and the secret room were both as the letter described them. However no stairs leading down to a further sub-basement were found anywhere on the property. The puppets all also appeared to be completely undamaged, despite the claim that they had been burnt. The tapes mentioned in the letter were missing however. 

Two families have since lived in the Grimes home. Neither has stayed for more than a few months, reporting strange smells, odd noises around the house and things going missing. One reported sensing something ‘Terrible’ in the basement and her children spoke of horrible dreams about ‘The ship taking them away’ and ‘The bony man from the TV’ watching them at night. 

The house is now abandoned, having been purchased and then left empty by one Adrian Grimes in early 2011. 

The puppets and set pieces from ‘Candle Cove’ (Mistakenly named ‘Pirate Place’ by Grimes in the letter, an early working title for the show that Emerson Grimes later abandoned) supposedly vanished shortly before Adrian Grimes made the purchase. 

The whereabouts of Jason Grimes remain unknown)﻿

Meer lezen (540 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-nHHDFWkk8SM/Upd-mmdeHWI/AAAAAAAAFBY/awVwnd5nXxM/w426-h239/Candle+Cove.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/112855886072993423409/albums/5730524002327627377/5730523999401231282</link><title>#FBFIND 
His wife is seriously injured. She was hit by a car as she swooped low across the road. 
He brought her food and tended to her with love and compassion. 
He brought her food again but was shocked to find her dead. 
He tried to move her....a rarely-seen effort for swallows. 
Aware that his mate is dead, he cries with adoring love. 
He stood beside her, saddened by her death. 
Finally, he stood beside her body with sadness and sorrow. 
People cried after seeing these pictures when they were published 
in the leading newspaper in France. All copies of the paper were 
sold out on the day the pictures were released. 
And many people think animals don't have emotions.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-gEMY8B3ZG8U/T4bpN0EpQ7I/AAAAAAAA6S4/sbLmY8N2qOk/w426-h424/420151_315986071782189_163735700340561_795293_1926287674_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7425-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/coloring%20picture%20cars/photos/113700935647920525743/albums/5966307904296315521/5966307901230688258</link><title>Indigo is a color that is traditionally regarded as a color on the visible spectrum, as well as one of the seven colors of the rainbow: the color between blue and violet. 
Reference : http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indigo 

For January #ROYGBIVweek 
With +Susan Porter and +Tisha Craw 
Day 6 : #Indigo 

Also for #treetuesday 
With +Christina Lawrie +Shannon S. Myers +Ralph Mendoza +Allan Cabrera +Kim Troutman 

And for me and all of you!! 
There's Indigo in there somewhere... ;)﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7425_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-gaBGH9qnkS4/UsyVbOF2KAI/AAAAAAAAIaU/8XYM0vttk2w/w426-h240/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>