<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:08:36" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/105064358310097610462/albums/5880438759212173345/5880438763340423074?authkey=CMid4KvCoPCtRw</link><title>Crafts for kids on this rainy afternoon: create an online diorama with elements from Vincent van Gogh's paintings and share it with others! Just visit http://www.vangoghmuseum.com/diorama for English or http://www.vangoghmuseum.nl/kijkdoos for Dutch. 

Have fun!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Po69igZL0Y0/UZuD5jxX36I/AAAAAAAAIso/9Usbv7DDHmU/w426-h275/diorama.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/107387192012882144300/albums/5911338553169768353/5911338555938153442?authkey=CMH7xbrf4f32Fg</link><title>My son and I made these cute friends from the zoo on a rainy afternoon with help from +Oriental Trading  Come check them out! Sponsored. http://sparklesandastove.com/animal-crafts-for-kids-an-oriental-trading-giveaway/ #kidscrafts  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-oqm7b7Tpxwg/UglLGNXDo-I/AAAAAAAAJxk/7X-PeDR46B4/w426-h537/Easy+Kids+Craft+Zoo+Friends.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/118177253929143457733/albums/5734173946665331393/5734173948841824130</link><title>SQUAWK for our planet on Earth Day 2012! http://www.earthday.org﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-trhKMynXYGU/T5Pg01UED4I/AAAAAAAARRo/CypOa4oty3E/w426-h237/earth.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/110466688127241330787/albums/5901318874030783137/5901318870450990146?authkey=CMOl5e36_-HlRQ</link><title>Dearest +Google I still love you, but we need to have a talk. 

I met you a little over 2 years ago, and it was love at first sight.  You were clean and fresh, not like the other messy and insensitive networks I had met before.  You've taught me many things, and introduced me to a lot of wonderful people. 

But lately you have changed.  You removed the beautiful clean UI and replaced it with Pinterest.  You took what was pretty simple navigation and made me double or even triple the number of clicks I have to make to get to where I wish to go.  (Such as a specific community or photo album).  At the same time you Pinterestified the layout you introduced animated GIFs that turned my stream into puke.  It gave me such a headache viewing all of them I not only had to uncircle a lot of people, but I only viewed G+ on my phone for a day or two until it started dying down.  I get that people were having fun playing with the new toys, but it would have been so much nicer if they didn't auto play.  Or at least you gave those of us not interested in them the option to disable autoplaying.  Then everyone would be happy. 

A little over a year ago I went to the G+ Photographer's Conference and listened to +Bradley Horowitz speak.  At about the 55:40 mark he speaks of context and relevance on G+.  Google+ Photographer's Conference Opening Keynote  Granted he is speaking about ads, but when the highlighted +1 posts rolled out, I immediately felt betrayed.  This is an unwanted intrusion.  I gave it a few days as many wonderful Googlites requested (+Chris Chabot +Ricardo Lagos  and +Shimrit Ben-Yair to name a few) but it's not any less annoying than the first day.  I either get posts of people I already have circled and in many cases already plussed and/or commented, or posts that I have no interest in.  Again, all G+ had to do was give us the option to disable.  There was an extension that rolled out almost immediately to hide these posts, but sadly it also hides the posts if I have the person circled.  That's no good either.  I can't even see all the posts from people I have circled - people I specifically said I want to see, why show me people I don't have circled instead?? 

I realize this is most likely in response to people requesting more ways to discover people.  And that's great.  But couldn't you just give us a choice to not see it?  Maybe teach newcomers how to search out content and users they are interested in? 

The recurring theme here is choice.  I used to be able to choose how much or how little of someone's posts that I wanted.  I used to be able to arrange what I saw in the left column - even saved searches.  I used to be able to only see content from people I chose in my stream.  Please Google, stop treating me like a lemming.  I liked that you used to treat me as an individual.  That's why I came, and stayed here.  I like that Google employees interact on posts and come out to photowalks.  Without wonderful people like +Chris Chabot , +Ricardo Lagos , +Vincent Mo +Brian Matiash  and +Brian Rose this community wouldn't be what it is.  Please return to being an innovator and stop copying other networks. 

I really am looking forward to our 3 year anniversary.  :-)﻿

Meer lezen (52 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-oNUUIsID0mM/UeWyPwOKbEI/AAAAAAAArKE/-6la1UjrxlE/w426-h284/IHeartG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/115285805034937175151/albums/5992045756083399537/5992045763790737042?sqi=111695236665241870338&amp;sqsi=7d05f517-e0c0-4f39-884a-dbd6918d688e</link><title>Cape Breton Daily Brew Is A Cape Breton Daily Blog For Cape Breton Islanders And Friends 

Morning Cape Breton Islanders and Friends 

Follow Me On Google Plus: 
https://google.com/+TomMacDonald 

Join Cape Breton Daily Brew 
http://caperbuzz.com﻿ 
#glacebay #sydney #northsydney #newwaterford #sydneymines #capebreton #novascotia  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-0A3VX9Ow-5Y/UygF3_yhjpI/AAAAAAACesA/svcF6r8R8yY/w426-h320/glacebaysig.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/109138752796940254668/albums/5828773507193171521/5828773511870623474?authkey=CPzZ5uzquZa_CA</link><title>A Pac Shelf 

I like the idea but as for the image the shelf should have more books in it. 

Good afternoon everyone! 
It's been raining for almost 24 hours and it's cold. Love the weather today, with a book and coffee what could go wrong? =) 

buzzfeed dot com﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-a50oa9Z4EG8/UOP2oHtBLvI/AAAAAAAALsI/eVrmYJpwj6w/w426-h314/enhanced-buzz-9130-1356727188-7.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/106427505879596001328/albums/5895969322751488913/5895969323710525394?authkey=CO-f7qD2uJfp8gE</link><title>Easy little Watercolor Mobile~ This is a great Kids Craft for those rainy summer afternoons~ #hometalktuesday 

SEE IT NOW&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; http://goo.gl/XXSMx 
PIN IT FOR LATER&gt;&gt; http://goo.gl/lWp1g﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-6dTCqrMcD6Q/UdKw3Jpdr9I/AAAAAAAAAhY/xFYhPBoGWoc/w426-h639/watercolor%2Bmobile.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/100157031362421742485/albums/5788769399906059121/5788769404681784482</link><title>New article by yours truly on photofocus.com: 

PERSONAL PROJECTS ARE IMPORTANT 

As professional photographers, our craft pays for the bills, sends our kids to school, and puts food on the table, but often, what we produce on a daily base it not what inspires us, or what made us pick up the camera in the first place. 

The same applies to amateur photographers as well. We love photography, we go out, and we point our cameras at whatever we see as half way interesting. We end up with images of trees, walls, people in the streets, dogs and cats, our friends and family. We get better at our craft, we learn how to handle our cameras, we improve on our technical skills to a certain point, but to really get to the next level, we have to stop "documenting", and start "creating". We have to start thinking about our artistic vision, concepts and ideas. 

I often hear the argument from amateurs that " you pro's have access to the great gear, the models, the money ". The truth is, when it comes to producing an idea, both amateurs and pro's are in the exact same boat: We don't have a budget, no client to pay for models, sets, travel, locations or catering; we start with an empty canvas, and gear doesn't matter. 

At whatever stage of our photographic journey, there come times when we have to put the camera aside, sit down, and think about what makes us happy. What inspires us, what we would love to do, not for money, social media response, not for our friends or family, just purely for our photographic heart. When asking the question "what would you love to do" however, many new shooters have no real answer for it, and quickly slide into the "get paid" response. "More beauty, or fashion would be cool" is an answer I hear often too, but when talking about personal project, I think much more specific than that. 

Let your inner producer, artist and personal ego take over, sit down and think of ways, how you can create what you'd love to shoot. The more detailed you do so, the easier it will be to find ways to actually do it. Create your own story. 

Every photographer I know, regardless of how experienced or successful they might be, are all working on personal projects. Because we create our personal vision, these images are important to us, they represent who we are as artists. Some might not turn out the way we envisioned, and they will never see the light of day, others will end up in their portfolio. As a result, more often than not, clients will end up booking us for exactly what we showed them, what we love. 

The other side of personal projects is learning. I would never try anything new at a paid gig, unless I am 200 percent certain, I have all the images (plus a few extras) the client expects, and I still have plenty of time to fool around. Even then however, I am well aware that my client, the art directors, everyone on set, will judge me how I work, I have to maintain being confident, people hire us because we know what we are doing. On personal projects however, I have all the time in the world, no paying client breathing down my neck, no expectations. I can communicate openly with models, makeup artists, or whoever I might invite to join me to collaborate, we all know, we will try, play, learn, have fun, for a great outcome. 

On personal projects, I expect mistakes to happen. We analyse, learn, and improve. Once we get the results we imagined, we have to ask ourselves: can we replicate it, how can we apply what we just achieved in other scenarios, in a studio instead of on location, can we pull this off in different lighting scenarios. The more we try, the more we learn, and the more confident we will go into our next shoot. 

In the process, we might discover what we truly love to photograph, sometimes we even re-discover our love for photography all together. In any case, there is nothing wrong with listening to our own inner artistic diva from time to time, indulge in ideas, and learn along the way. 

… 

Find all of my articles also on my website: 
http://www.stephanbollinger.com/category/articles/ 

Photo below: "The Ego Trip" with Film-maker Evan Burrows. 
Photo: Stephan Bollinger. 

#photography   #photofocus  ﻿

Meer lezen (80 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-iLUZfV8O3j4/UFXXGnS1DKI/AAAAAAAAEos/uaiMPygn-m4/w426-h310/egotrip.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/117520666412794415990/albums/5857796046551543713/5857796050985629154</link><title>Walking for Water \- already fetched fresh water today? 

World Water Day - March 22.  #worldwaterday2013  While we often take water for granted, many cannot. By 2025, it is expected that more than 2.8 billion people in 48 countries will face water stress, or scarcity conditions. By 2050, the number of countries could rise to 54, with a combined population of four billion people - about 40% of the projected global population - goo.gl/N51wZ \- Water Risk Atlas ➜ goo.gl/eq6ak 

Video ➜ goo.gl/5nZTs \- goo.gl/vlwBZ ― Facts ➜ goo.gl/cB4G4 

The lack of access to Clean Water and sanitation kills Children at a rate equivalent of a jumbo jet crashing every four hours. 

Photos via → goo.gl/YdD09 \- goo.gl/zck8O \- goo.gl/3irdH \- goo.gl/HwdWt ﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SB-zcOVZGIc/UUsSePGvNeI/AAAAAAAAyos/mot-mN4YnUE/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7428-12"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/rainy%20afternoon%20kids%20craft/photos/101130978960587223595/albums/6002623229583796817/6002623229173588290</link><title>Come and celebrate the essence of motherhood with me at Indigo Manulife Centre at Bay &amp; Bloor on Saturday May 3rd at 11:30 am.  Come and have fun with the kids for reading and fun! 

#chaptersindigo   #indigokids   #Toronto #bay&amp;bloor #manulifecentre     #janetaizenstros   #stoneroadmall  #mothersday #events #children #crafts #fun﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7428_12_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-H-ivrIIxAlM/U02aBg9mYUI/AAAAAAAAAS0/kqG_tfj6k7k/w426-h551/chapterstoronto3.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>