<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:20:39" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/103980904609289281346/albums/5845191925311398737/5845191929804079938?authkey=CL-EupmFwJ7CMg</link><title>Via +ElevateD 
                        How should we view the Mali conflict? 
Most people trying to figure out what is happening in Mali are almost entirely dependent on mainstream media outlets. But they all carry the same simplistic narrative. 
The Western media tell us there are ‘good guys’ in the South, who adore the French for intervening. 
They tell us there are ‘bad guys’ in the North. Some are ‘fairly bad guys’ – Tuaregs who were alienated for a long time, who have been manipulated by ‘Islamists’ but who could be part of a long-term solution. 
Others are ‘really bad guys’ – variously described as‘Islamists’, ‘Jihadists’, ‘Rebels’ or ‘Extremists’. We are told they do nothing good and everything bad. 
A Muslim viewing these events can apply certain principles, which avoid simply following the ‘good guys’ versus ‘bad guys’ narrative presented by a politicised and biased media machine in the West. 
How should the Muslim view the recent events? 

1. 
Muslims fighting Muslims is terrible in any circumstance. 
The Prophet (salallahu alaihi wasallam) said: Abusing a Muslim is Fusuq (evil doing) and fighting against him is Kufr (disbelief). [Bukhari &amp; Muslim] 
So, 
whatever the root cause, when it comes to bloodshed on either side, it is a painful and tragic sight, and potentially disastrous for the participants in the akhira (afterlife). 

2 
Western colonial states intervening in Muslim lands is an unwelcome sight and unacceptable. 
Some people may try to justify the invitation of states like France on one side or the other saying the people need the protection of an external force, as a matter of life and death. 
This is dangerous in political terms and unacceptable from a Shari’ah legal perspective. 
From Shari’ah: Allah (swt) says: And never will Allah give the disbelievers a way over the believers (Quran 4:141). 
Politically: This conflict is not the first such intervention by Western colonial powers in Muslim lands – where they maintained a presence of troops or Western installed proxy-rulers in order to secure a way over the politics and wealth of those regions. 
Moreover, we can recall the lies, deceit and abuses committed in Iraq, Afghanistan and elsewhere – as well as the huge death count. 

Allah (swt) says: O Believers, do not take My enemies and your enemies as allies (Quran 60:1). 

France’s history in North Africa includes the systematic killing of hundred of thousands of Muslims and uncountable cases of torture. The French claim the numbers of dead under their policies in Algeria were around 350,000 – but other estimates put the figures as well over 1 million Muslims. It is therefore inconceivable that France’s intervention is purely for humanitarian reasons – and Allah sets a clear limit, so avoiding a Muslim being duped by someone with enmity. 
The Prophet (salallahu alaihi wasallam) is reported to have said: A believer is not bitten from the same hole twice. (Bukhari &amp; Muslim) 

3. 
Keep a healthy scepticism about news reports from a politically biased Western media. 
Allah (swt) says: Believers! If a faasiq (wrongdoer) comes to you with news, verify it, lest you harm people in ignorance, and afterwards you become regretful to what you have done. (Quran 49:6) 

Much of the media carrying the events of Mali to us are not virtuous trustworthy organisations. 

They show images of Malians celebrating as the ‘Jihadists’ are expelled from cities – just as they once showed images of celebrating Afghans when the Taleban were expelled from Kabul, and celebrating Iraqis when Saddam fled Baghdad. 

They present casualties of the conflict just as they present information about deaths from drone attacks in Pakistan – that those killed are without doubt ‘terrorist suspects or insurgents’ – even though there is ample evidence that thousands of innocent civilians are killed. One respected news journalist showed the dead bodies of three teenage Malian boys – and described them as recruits who fought with the Jihadists. How she came to know this with certainty, she did not say – but the information was presented with certainty, and without evidence. 

We are told the rebels are violent, oppressive and barbaric. The most recent crimes laid at their door are the destruction of graves and an ancient library in Timbuktu. But we were once told that Iraqi troops had killed babies in incubators in Kuwait – which was untrue. 

4. 
Beware the negative caricature of the‘Islamic’ behaviour 

The trick of the Western media is to conflate wrong-doing, accusations of wrong-doing and Islamic laws in such a way as to discredit the Islamic laws. 

In Mali, we are told ‘Islamist’rebels enforce strict ‘Shariah’ law and oppressed and abused the people. 

We have no idea if this is true or not. 

If the either side committed wrong-doings or oppressed others, we should view it as wrong and not defend it. 

But we should be wary to come out and condemn it, without being sure if it really did happen – in particular as the aim is to discredit Islamic laws and systems to the audience. 

The same media carry very few criticisms of the criminal Saudi regime’s system or practices because the Saudi regime is a loyal ally of the West. 

A Muslim does not need to defend any wrongdoings of any side (for which we have few reliable verifying sources) in order to oppose the intervention by France and its allies. 

5. 
The problems exist due to the absence of a legitimate unifying power in the Muslim world – the Islamic Khilafah 

Mali is an artificial construct of a colonial era. It was once a great centre of civilisation where the various tribes lived without conflict like that of today. 

The Khilafah is the legitimate political authority – respected and recognised by Muslims – that arbitrated disputes between people. It rises above tribe, race and political faction. 

In 1916, the French along with the British, dismembered the Khilafah in the Sykes-Picot accord – before fatally wounding it after World War I, leading to its demise in 1924. 

The anarchy and chaos that has existed in the Muslim world post-Khilafah can be directly linked to the absence of a legitimate authority in the Muslim world. THe Khilafah is based on their beliefs, consistent with their values and rooted in their history. 

Writing in the Times on 5thMarch 1924, Ameer Ali said of the removal of the Khilafah that “I fear the removal of this ideal [will] drive the peoples included in the vast Sunni following into the ranks of revolution and disorder.” 
(By +taimoor khalid)﻿

Meer lezen (141 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-tUZVaRlf3Tg/UR5LF0vzw0I/AAAAAAAAc8k/vtesQqBQ2-s/w426-h237/mali-troops.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/115399459187056221767/albums/5834553970364770577/5834553977208586562?authkey=CKezme-F7MuCaA</link><title>Conflict in Mali 
French troops advance in Mali to stop rebels﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-45XAHY1rPyg/UPh_7fJcQUI/AAAAAAAAZII/ELu8KEoWeKE/w426-h610/ODlgHintRa6I9Qa91w2s3Q.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/105152337151893753994/albums/5834167766189348417/5834167766716010082?authkey=COXojIqbz8qFuQE</link><title>A Map of the Bewildering Mali Conflict 

Bamako Malian France French Africa African Maghreb 

http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/01/a-map-of-the-bewildering-mali-conflict/267257/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BYp3WM31iyE/UPcgrE8kTmI/AAAAAAAAMJM/82YFYAlyg_M/w426-h635/graphic-mali-conflict-area-615.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/115177451874746263968/albums/5834416565546237793/5834416570766909282?authkey=CKCggebYkLC5OA</link><title>Reluctant Algeria dragged into Mali conflict 

Algeria for a long time insisted on a political solution to the turmoil in Mali, but finally allows overflights by French fighters to support a ground offensive aimed at ousting Islamists in the country's north 
Read more  http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/62724.aspx﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-3_KHIPWAYSI/UPgC9YQ232I/AAAAAAAAdaM/jU2HBAdFqhQ/w426-h255/2013-634940323147734779-773.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/108132698993215237640/albums/5927477171926437857/5927477171460246818</link><title>Conflict in Mali has exacerbated an already worrying food and nutrition situation. Even if conflict has now dissipated, the country’s north remains volatile, half a million Malians continue to be displaced and recent flooding has added to the woes of the population in certain regions. 

See what we're doing to help the situation: http://bit.ly/1b4GNlJ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MAXBdOb6_ZA/UkKhFRMgDSI/AAAAAAAAAh0/h_4-rp6F6Jo/w426-h319/Mali.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/100805478151614737104/albums/5948843877449547729/5948843874640388866</link><title>Education must not be on the frontlines of conflict; it should be on the forefront of building peace. The occupation of parts of northern Mali by armed groups earlier this year had an alarming impact on the region’s education system. Many schools in #WorldHeritage Timbuktu, Gao and Kidal were destroyed. Much of the educational infrastructure was vandalized or pillaged. School furniture was destroyed and used as fuel; electric and digital equipment , books and laboratory material were damaged or burned. http://ow.ly/r494D﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Qx7HhyaB3dg/Uo6J_FQy4wI/AAAAAAAADRI/XOqojlkCjE0/w426-h269/3NxiH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/111113599137714056336/albums/5951359769417521169/5951359772669398002</link><title>Today we've got words from Mali, where two years of conflict have made access to health care difficult for people in the north, in particular for pregnant women and young children. That's why our colleagues on the ground are working hard to provide medical facilities in Gao and Kidal with resources and manpower. Go team! For more info on our activities in Mali, take a look at our website: http://ow.ly/rgOME﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-DAbSU-aozTA/Upd6LnyCS_I/AAAAAAAAFYM/wIE8J3_lYhk/w426-h240/Mali.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/108709341676120188027/albums/5982908117210373873/5982908113889743730</link><title>When conflict broke out in Mali, Hawa and her family fled to Burkina Faso, interrupting her studies. To help refugee children like Hawa access education, Plan’s offering classes in the refugee camp where she lives. Help Plan support children during crises like this: http://bit.ly/HG8ibE ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZvQepxiWvWA/UwePOxQzU3I/AAAAAAAAAt8/dKQi_2jCZJg/w426-h335/I%2Bput%2Bmy%2Bheart%2B%252B%2Bsoul%2Bin%2Bmy%2Bstudies%2B-%2BHawa%2Bin%2BBurkina%2BFaso.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/109561481003775935566/albums/5755768847406230305/5755768848337918066</link><title>Blog Report: AFRICANS ADDRESSING AN AFRICAN CONFLICT: UN TO MANDATE MALI PEACEKEEPING FORCE? By Ambassador Mo 
Mali has been embroiled in coups &amp; rebel fighting complicated by famine that threatens to tear apart the country at its most vulnerable &amp; expose its citizens to further deprivation &amp; killing. As in several other states, relevant regional organizations, The Economic Community of West African States (ECOWAS) &amp; the African Union (AU), are seeking to deploy peacekeepers. &lt;del&gt;-More-&lt;/del&gt; 
http://diplomaticallyincorrect.org/blog_post/africans-addressing-an-african-conflict-un-to-mandate-mali-peacekeeping-force/54400﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-0dcFPkOIa5s/T-CZRa5w2HI/AAAAAAAADIw/SUclAnU8rxU/w426-h639/317576.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7430-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/conflict%20mali/photos/100805478151614737104/albums/5833823062727431937/5833823065545531490?authkey=CMnkvvnC8_7O2wE</link><title>On the current conflict in North Mali: UNESCO urges military forces to protect Malian cultural sites during air raids and ground interventions. The current military intervention must protect people &amp; secure the cultural heritage of Mali. The destruction of World Heritage sites in Mali in 2012, especially the mausoleums in Timbuktu, sparked a wave of indignation across the world, helping to raise awareness of the critical situation facing the Malian people. Mali’s cultural heritage is a jewel whose protection is important for the whole of humanity. This is our common heritage, nothing can justify damaging it. It carries the identity and values of a people. 

* READ THE STORY: http://ow.ly/gQiwN  

* A NEW GUIDE DEDICATED TO THE CULTURAL SITES WE MUST PROTECT: http://ow.ly/gQiAB﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7430_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-poN6ixSMMl4/UPXnK1BSYGI/AAAAAAAAA3k/cGdWYTznyIQ/w426-h365/timbuktu-unesco.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>