<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:24:10" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/116151548242653888082/albums/5796654536883451953/5796654540392383842</link><title>Final! FC Barcelona 2 - 2 Real Madrid. Goals: Ronaldo (31, 61), Messi (23, 63).﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-w8TVOGFFxak/UHHal62-RWI/AAAAAAAA3PY/xbb539YMYL4/w426-h240/iniesta.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/100885584647885880406/albums/5942329909559445889/5942329910974579634</link><title>+Leo Messi  #freekick   #goal  +FC Barcelona vs +Real Madrid C.F. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_02_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DbFPLK_q258/UndlkfnRg7I/AAAAAAAADH8/AR6UV8aeXFk/w426-h240/image.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/100116798924791674530/albums/5994640631628372753/5994640631842418946</link><title>Barcelona's Lionel Messi (L) celebrates a goal next to Real Madrid's Cristiano Ronaldo during La Liga's second 'Clasico' soccer match of the season at Santiago Bernabeu stadium in Madrid March 23, 2014﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-nCPm6AAJ51s/UzE95MkXMQI/AAAAAAAALGw/P8ck38eGjG4/w426-h274/cd783bf0-b363-11e3-9709-5ff5eb96553c_RTR3IAYQ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/103823393581857475140/albums/5994245428146960817/5994245431489427554</link><title>Real Madrid 3-4 Barcelona: Messi hat-trick settles enthralling Clasico clash 

The Argentine became the tie's leading goalscorer after a cool finish and two penalties, while Sergio Ramos was sent off for the home side 

A hat-trick from Lionel Messi - including two penalties - saw Barcelona record a thrilling 4-3 win over Real Madrid at Santiago Bernabeu on Sunday. 

Barcelona's all-time leading scorer struck two second-half spot kicks as the Catalan giants came from behind twice to win a pulsating encounter in the capital. 

The second of those penalties, scored with six minutes left after Xabi Alonso clumsily fouled Andres Iniesta, was hammered into the top-right corner as the defending champions closed to within one point of Real - and city rivals Atletico - in the Liga table. 

Iniesta's early goal was cancelled out by a pair of Karim Benzema strikes, and although Messi levelled before half-time, a controversial Cristiano Ronaldo penalty put Real back in front. 

Sergio Ramos was then sent off for tripping Neymar, though, and Messi's first penalty restored parity. 

And the Argentina star – who became the top scorer in Clasicos with his treble, overtaking Real Madrid legend Alfredo Di Stefano – held his nerve when presented with another penalty as his side notched their first league double over their rivals since the 2009-10 season. 

Much was made of the influence Ronaldo, Gareth Bale and Neymar would have on the contest, but all three were not at their best, leaving Messi to play the starring role in the Spanish capital. 

Neymar had an early strike saved before Iniesta fired Barcelona into the lead to cap a superb team move in the seventh minute. 

Real Madrid supporters were quick to voice their displeasure as the visitors enjoyed a spell of possession, but their whistles turned to silence as Messi's angled ball sent Iniesta through on goal and the midfielder thrashed a powerful left-footed finish past Diego Lopez. 

Benzema, who had already spurned two chances, missed a golden chance to level when he turned over after an Angel Di Maria cut-back, and Messi shot wide when he seemed more likely to double Barcelona's lead. 

Benzema eventually scored for Real, with his powerful header – which came from another cross from the outstanding Di Maria - too hot to handle for Barcelona goalkeeper Victor Valdes, going in off the post to level proceedings in the 20th minute. 

And Benzema doubled his account just four minutes later, as Di Maria, who needed treatment just moments before, again found the forward, who chested down before volleying a classic centre-forward's goal past Valdes. 

Benzema could have had a hat-trick in the first 30 minutes, but saw Gerard Pique clear a curling effort off the line and Messi punished the hosts when he capitalised on a goalmouth scramble to score from close range just before the break. 

Tempers frayed as Pepe and Cesc Fabregas were booked after the goal, but Real settled quickly after the interval, with Valdes doing well to deny Benzema after a great Bale run. 

Real went ahead in controversial circumstances, as referee Alberto Undiano pointed to the penalty spot after Ronaldo was fouled by Dani Alves, although replays showed contact was initially made outside the area. 

Ronaldo dispatched the spot-kick, powering an effort into the bottom left corner for his 26th league goal of the season, and Valdes had to keep out Bale after another Real attack. 

The match swung in Barca's favour when an excellent Messi ball released Neymar, with the 19th red card of Ramos' Real Madrid career giving the Argentinian the chance to score from the penalty spot in the 65th minute. 

And just like Ronaldo before him, Messi made no mistake, forcing Carlo Ancelotti to sacrifice Benzema for defender Raphael Varane. 

A fizzing 20-yard effort from Alves then hit the inside of the left post with Lopez beaten, but Barcelona's numerical advantage was beginning to show. 

Iniesta created the winner with a clever run, as his attempt to get away from Daniel Carvajal was blocked by Alonso, leaving Undiano with no option but to give another penalty. 

And Messi ensured it was his name in the headlines again as he scored a crucial goal that is sure to ease the pressure on coach Gerardo Martino and put Barca firmy back in the title race.﻿

Meer lezen (93 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-aPgdRE0q2Vs/Uy_WdghveGI/AAAAAAAAExQ/td0s9Gz7VQ4/w426-h265/382151hp2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/104756561608847708699/albums/5994181874529024161/5994181879365185058</link><title>+Real Madrid C.F. 3-4 +FC Barcelona: Messi hat-trick settles enthralling Clasico clash 

The Argentine became the tie's leading goalscorer after a cool finish and two penalties, while Sergio Ramos was sent off for the home side. 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1dF9AwR 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1mppe7J 

Match reports: 

Real Betis 0-2 +Atlético de Madrid: Gabi &amp; Costa send Rojiblancos top of the table 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1hd20KK 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1kWeHOp 

+Manchester City FC 5-0 +Fulham Football Club: Toure hat-trick heaps pressure on struggling Cottagers 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1doii86 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1mpoiA9 

+Cardiff City FC 3-6 +Liverpool FC: Suarez hat-trick helps Reds clinch nine-goal thriller 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1doiowB 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1nS1lr8 

+Tottenham Hotspur 3-2 +Southampton FC: Sigurdsson seals dramatic comeback 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1hd1oEX 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1f8kZ8J 

+West Ham United FC 0-2 +Manchester United:  Rooney sets up victory with spectacular long range lob 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/Q5SdQP 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1fSWVX2 

Chievo 0-2 Roma: Destro and Gervinho tighten grip on second spot 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1mpouj3 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/Q5Sx29 

+FC Internazionale 1-2 Atalanta: Nerazzurri stunned by last-gasp Bonaventura 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1kWeuuy 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1gPpwN2 

Napoli 0-1 Fiorentina: Joaquin downs 10-man hosts 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1oRtPOO 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1jkubOR 

Catania 0-1 +Juventus: Tevez tightens champions' grip on the title 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1pqrmt8 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1dojvfC 

Lazio 1-1 +AC Milan: Gonzalez denies Seedorf's men the victory 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1f8lGyW 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1isS5nF 

Mainz 0-2 +FC Bayern München: Bavarians leave it late to edge ever closer to title 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/Q5QhIf 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1gZjuOs 

Hannover 0-3 +Borussia Dortmund:  Klopp's men make Bayern wait for title 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/NI21yw 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1iSpmJV 

#Barca #realmadrid #Betis #Atletico #MCFC #FFC #CardiffCity #LFC #THFC #SFC #WHU #MUFC #Chievo #ASR #Inter #Atalanta #SSNapoli #Fiorentina #Catania #Juventus #Lazio #Milan #LaLiga #EPL #SerieA #Bundesliga +LigaBBVA +Serie A TIM ﻿

Meer lezen (69 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-l__2qbmDUnI/Uy-cqSalLiI/AAAAAAAAGiQ/GuhCB3AZ9Rs/w426-h265/382167hp2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/104756561608847708699/albums/5979692364365620929/5979692369431199858</link><title>From Civil War to Messi's tears - +FC Barcelona &amp; Real Madrid's Copa del Rey finals 

+Real Madrid C.F. 3-3 Barcelona. The Copa del Rey has produced six Clasico finals in its 112-year history and it's all square so far, but a seventh showpiece between Spain's two top teams is now a reality after Barca beat Real Sociedad 3-1 on aggregate to join Madrid in April's big cup clash. 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1fi07eV 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/NDZ7vD 

Bayern to face Kaiserslautern in DFB-Pokal semi-final 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1fi0mqn 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1hdRl8H 

Schweinsteiger relieved to make Bayern return 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1aWr5N1 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1eR93Nt 

+SSCNapoli 'almost perfect' in Coppa Italia comeback, says Benitez 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/MdQvuH 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1eVv1xa 

Falcao enters 'second phase' of recovery 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1hdRJUq 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/NDZR3D﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_inL2Lo78zk/UvwihzoPgHI/AAAAAAAAFCo/lI5BzsVTNn4/w426-h295/129443_heroa.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/104756561608847708699/albums/5943026816880472369/5943026817943894610</link><title>+Cristiano Ronaldo breaks Messi's record for Champions League goals in a calendar year 

Cristiano Ronaldo has broken the record held for Champions League goals scored in a calendar year after his second-half strike for +Real Madrid C.F. at +Juventus on Tuesday - overtaking the mark previously set by  Barcelona's Lionel Messi. 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1fiz8BV 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1dMld6X 

Conte: Juventus are stronger after Real Madrid draw 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1a6Gfvx 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/HIFDSF 

Casillas: I will see out my contract at Real Madrid 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1aDTE0T 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1iLJvhu 

Moyes &amp; Rooney back Van Persie after penalty miss 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1b70Te8 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/HvHHh0 

+Manchester City FC will be feared in Champions League, says Pellegrini 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1eixLWe 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1fizxV3 

Ajax as good as Barcelona &amp;  +AC Milan, says Celtic boss Lennon 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/19B0GRO 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1hhXNLj 

#UCL #RealMadrid #Juventus #MUFC #MCFC #Ajax #Barcelona #ACMIlan #Celtic﻿

Meer lezen (30 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2SAU36221pI/UnnfZ0YqelI/AAAAAAAAAig/kAQXyaK8mCs/w426-h295/337276_heroa.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/116151548242653888082/albums/5850790419019549841/5850790421357197058</link><title>Final. Real Madrid 2 - 1 FC Barcelona. Goals: Benzema and Ramos for Madrid, Leo Messi for FC Barcelona﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-EHGA-HfEuIM/UTIu47BA9wI/AAAAAAAB4_A/t4gNd88Hyas/w426-h240/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/113123434243873298572/albums/5796309806644751153/5796309811743887106</link><title>Barcelona vs. Real Madrid Is About More Than Messi vs. Ronaldo...Isn't It? 

Cristiano Ronaldo is not an easy man to sympathize with. Rich, handsome and fabulously gifted, Ronaldo struts an inexorable course toward greatness and will go down among the very best to have stepped foot on a football field. 
But how would you feel if every time you did something otherworldly at work—like score successive hat tricks—the most likely response was for people to bring up the one person who can it do slightly better? 
That's what happens to Ronaldo, over and over again. Last night he trebled against Ajax, taking his return to 158 in 154 games for Real Madrid and collecting the 17th hat trick of his career. 
Those numbers are beyond stunning. They are the stuff of video-game ridiculousness and heady boyhood fantasy, and they put Ronaldo's goals-per-game ratio for Madrid ahead of those achieved in the careers of Pele, Romario and Ferenc Puskas. 

If Ronaldo's feats were unique to his generation, we'd be putting the Portuguese on a pedestal so high you could barely see the gleam of his hair gel or the glint of those shiny white teeth. He'd be our footballing Elvis, and everything else would be a distant second. 
But for Lionel Messi, that is. But for the fact Messi has scored 167 goals in his last 154 games for Barcelona. And but for the fact that Messi—when you take your C-Ron blinkers off—is just that little bit more talented and drizzled with just that little bit more magic sauce. 
Ronaldo might be Elvis, but he's Elvis in the time of the The Beatles—with Messi playing John and Paul and a team of George and Ringos in Barcelona shirts alongside him. Whatever Ronaldo does and however often he does it, he'll always be compared to the man on the other side of the Clasico rivalry. 

Last night Messi was off-duty. He'd done his work at Benfica on Tuesday—setting up both goals in Barca's 2-0 win—and was likely relaxing at home, watching the evening's Champions League action unfold while juggling peas with both feet and occasionally scissor-kicking one into his mouth 

Over to C-Ron, and he didn't disappoint. A hat trick at Ajax followed the one he'd scored against Deportivo La Coruna in La Liga and took Ronaldo's season tally to 12 goals from 10 games. 
Ronaldo's contribution was clearly more significant than that delivered by Messi the night before, but while the Argentine was once again given the benefit of unqualified adulation, Ronaldo's performance—all too inevitably—seemed to prompt as many mentions of Messi on Twitter as it did his hat trick. 
That's the problem with being Ronaldo. Every time he does something impressive, there are thousands of people who react by screaming he's better than Messi, and there are thousands more screaming back that he's not even close. 
The former is not true; the latter is completely unnecessary. But you can't help feeling the conversation undermines Ronaldo and empowers Messi the louder it gets. 
As a man whose ego has loomed large throughout his career, Ronaldo must long for a day when his name can appear without Messi's beside it. We know he was riled by Danish fans who chanted Messi's name during Euro 2012, and in his reaction, Ronaldo gave us a hint of his underlying frustration with the comparison that stalks his every achievement in football.﻿

Meer lezen (58 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-RQOyseqeKPo/UHChEEkbDwI/AAAAAAAABbg/WnOCfRWVv64/w426-h288/hi-res-107199997_crop_exact.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7441-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/barcelona%20real%20madrid%20goal%20messi/photos/104756561608847708699/albums/5946127500958030641/5946127507176885650</link><title>Messi the first genius of the 21st century, says Valdano 

Former Real Madrid director Jorge Valdano feels that Barcelona star Lionel Messi is "the first genius of the 21st century". Messi has netted 14 goals in 16 official appearances for Barcelona so far in 2013-14. 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/19mKtLT 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1cY0Czq 

Ribery: People in France seem to prefer Messi &amp; Ronaldo for Ballon d'Or 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1cY0QXl 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1gMYHyv 

Ibrahimovic: Ronaldo &amp; Messi favourites for Ballon d'Or 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1cY0WOF 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1cY0Y9d 

'Messi is God, we will always depend on him' - Valdes laments injury to star 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1cY180d 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1cY18NL 

Messi working hard to recover from hamstring injury 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1cY1iF9 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1cY1ioz 

Xavi: Barcelona will miss Messi magic 
Desktop: http://bit.ly/1cY1pAh 
Mobile: http://bit.ly/1cY1rrZ 
#LaLiga   #Barcelona  ﻿

Meer lezen (27 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7441_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-VjwGgpV9By8/UoTjdr51DZI/AAAAAAAABAA/OXDKr7JNfOM/w426-h295/331586_heroa.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>