<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:06:38" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/105356395190203213677/albums/5926600283126398801/5926600287620417570?authkey=CNyXi8XigovXqwE</link><title>Cycling Lookout Mountain: Denver’s Mont Ventoux 
Read More http://footloosecycling.com/2153/cycling-lookout-mountain-denvers-mont-ventoux/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_1hSQEtfNbw/Uj-Dj6VXyCI/AAAAAAAARdU/SdcM7eYWr6M/w426-h240/WP_20130824_004.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5900490190299380881/5900490194398169586?authkey=CPmf2-Dxxum0igE&amp;sqi=114435503478132620253&amp;sqsi=4e002a1c-a288-4ff0-adc6-f740f644400e</link><title>Tour de France: Froome crowned king of Mont Ventoux - Sky inflicts more damage on the Giant of Provence 
http://www.cyclingnews.com/tour-de-france/stage-15/results 

Christopher Froome (Sky) won the showdown on Mont Ventoux, taking the win on the 15th stage of the Tour de France and extending his overall lead. He beat Nairo Quintana (Movistar), the only one remotely able to keep up with him, with Euskaltel's Mikel Nieve taking the spirited battle for third on the stage from Joaquim Rodriguez (Katusha).. 
It was another incredible display of strength by Froome, who one by one dropped all of his rivals until he was alone with teammate Richie Porte and Alberto Contador (Saxo-Tinkoff). With 7.5km to go, Froome jumped and Contador could not respond, and the maillot jaune holder set off in pursuit of Quintana, who had attacked on the lower slopes. 
The other pretenders to the throne had earlier been dropped and could only hope to retain their top rankings. Contador was for a long time in the closest group behind Froome in the finale. But surprisingly he too fell back, losing 1:40 on Froome. 
Quintana looked to be well on his way to a stage victory until Froome joined him. He held on to the Sky rider most of the way up, refusing to pull through as Froome revved the accelerator. The young Movistar rider finally succumbed just outside the one kilometer to go banner. 
With the stage win, Froome once again built up his lead over his challengers. He ended the day 4:14 ahead of Bauke Mollema (Belkin) in second and 4:25 over Contador in third in the general classification. 

How it unfolded 
All 181 remaining riders took to the early start, with much nervousness and tension. The attacks started almost immediately, but no one was able to get away. There were two category 4 climbs within the first 30km, and as expected, they served as the springboard for the day's break group. 
A group of 10 formed around the ever dangerous Peter Sagan (Cannondale) and Sylvain Chavanel (Omega Pharma-QuickStep). The other eight were Wout Poels (Vacansoleil-DCM), Daryl Impey (Orica-GreenEdge), Christophe Riblon (AG2R), Julien El Fares (Sojasun), Alberto Losado (Katusha), Pierrick Fedrigo (FDJ.FR), Markel Irizar (RadioShack-Leopard), and Jeremy Roy (FDJ.FR). 
By 50km, they had built up a lead of 1:50, and it just increased from there, hitting 7 minutes only 25km later. King of the Mountains Pierre Rolland (Europcar) and Marcus Burghardt (BMC) fought hard to catch up, but had trouble making the final connection. Christophe Le Mevel (Cofidis) and Mikel Astarloza (Euskaltel) tried too, but finally had to sit up and wait for the field. 
Burghardt and Rolland had been at one point within 15 seconds of the group, but were unable to close the gap. When it grew to one minute, Rolland realized the futility of his efforts and gave up the chase. Eventually they too were caught by the field. 
After reaching a high of 7 minutes, the gap started to fall by the halfway mark. The break group went through the feed zone with a lead of only 4:35. Europcar led the chase, and it began to look as if the break wouldn't make it to the foot of Mont Ventoux alone. 
The race had gotten off to an exceptionally fast start, over 48km covered in the first hour. The second hour was even faster at 50.5kph, but the third hour settled down to a more reasonable 41.3. 
With 93km to go, Movistar had moved in to lead the chase, with the gap between the 3:30 and 4:00 minute marks. The peloton seemed happy to keep the group at that distance. 
The day's intermediate sprint came 34km before the end, and there was little doubt as to how it will go. No one dared to challenge the green jersey, but Sagan kept a wary eye on the others as he rolled over the line as first. 
As the start of the climb loomed, Euskaltel moved to the front of the field and picked up the pace. With 29km to go the gap had dropped to three minutes. Sky moved back to the front, with the gap now plummeting with every meter. 
That was too much for Chavanel, who attacked the breakaway with visions of Bastille Day glory in mind. With still one kilometer to go before the climb started, the gap was under two minutes. At the other end of the action, riders were falling off the back, including last year's best young rider Tejay van Garderen (BMC). 
Chavanel had built up 28 seconds with 20km to go, and the chase group too started falling apart, with Sagan noticeably lagging back. Surprisingly, Rolland was dropped from the main group, and it seemed unlikely he would be able to play a role in the stage. 
Sagan was one of the first to re-join the field, which he celebrated with a wave and wheelie. Soon Irizar and Riblon were the only chasers, 28 seconds behind Chavanel with 16 km to go, with the field a bit more than a minute behind them. 
Rui Costa (Movistar) and Jan Bakelants (RadioShack-Leopard) were the first to jump from the field. Costa couldn't hang on, but Bakelants soon moved up to Irizar and Riblon. 
Andy Schleck got dropped along the way, and had the further handicap of a “helpful” fan, who no doubt only wanted to give him a push, but nearly shoved him off his bike. 
Irizar sooon fell back, but Bakelants was joined by Mikel Nieve (Euskaltel). Quintana jumped as next, as Nieve passed Chavanel. With 12.4 km the Colombian caught Chavanel, and Sky moved into the lead of the chase, with Froome having two helpers with him. 
Chavanel was soon caught again, and the gap from the field to Nieve was only 39 seconds. Quintana moved up slowly and smoothly in pursuit of the Basque rider. It took a while but he caught Nivel with 10.5 km to go. 
Cadel Evans (BMC), who won the Tour in 2011, had never been top in this year's race, and fell back from the Froome group with a bit more than 10 km to go. Bakelants was caught about the same time, leaving only Quintana and Nieve in the lead by 41 seconds. 
With a little over 9 kilometers to go, Peter Kennaugh dropped out of the lead work, leaving Froome with only Richie Porte to lead him. Contador, right behind, had two helpers. Belkin's Bauke Mollema and Laurens ten Dam were also still in the group. 
The long grinding climb took its expected toll, and the favourites' group became smaller and smaller, with truly only favourites in it. Alejandro Valverde (Movistar) and Jakob Fuglsang were victims, as well. With 8 kilometers to go, there was only a trio: Froome, Porte and Contador. 
Porte put in an incredible performance, pulling the group up the dreaded climb, but he too could finally had to drop back. With 7.5m to go, Nieve could no longer stay with Quintana. 
Shortly thereafter, Froome attacked, quickly passing the fading Nieve. Contador could not or did not respond. The duo fought the motorcycles and crazed fans and Froome easily moved past Quintana, never once getting out of the saddle. The Colombian fought his way back though, and took Froome's rear wheel, eventually taking his turn in the lead. 
As their gap over Contador increased, Quintana moved back into the lead work after a few words with Froome. The Briton tried repeatedly to dump him, and with 1.3 km to go he was finally successful. 
Joaquim Rodriguez jumped from his group as they passed under the flamme rouge, hoping to make up a few seconds. But ahead of him, Froome rolled over the line, with a large smile on his face and still enough energy to celebrate. Quintana came in 29 seconds down. 
The surprise came as the next riders came into view: Nieve and Rodriguez – no Contador to be seen! The Spaniard finished 1:40 down, as sixth, another bitter blow. 

Brief Results 
1 Christopher Froome (GBr) Sky Procycling 5:48:45 
2 Nairo Alexander Quintana Rojas (Col) Movistar Team 0:00:29 
3 Mikel Nieve Ituralde (Spa) Euskaltel-Euskadi 0:01:23 
4 Joaquim Rodriguez Oliver (Spa) Katusha 
5 Roman Kreuziger (Cze) Team Saxo-Tinkoff 0:01:40 
6 Alberto Contador Velasco (Spa) Team Saxo-Tinkoff 
7 Jakob Fuglsang (Den) Astana Pro Team 0:01:43 
8 Bauke Mollema (Ned) Belkin Pro Cycling Team 0:01:46 
9 Laurens Ten Dam (Ned) Belkin Pro Cycling Team 0:01:53 
10 Jean-Christophe Peraud (Fra) AG2R La Mondiale 0:02:08 
11 Bart De Clercq (Bel) Lotto Belisol 0:02:12 
12 Michael Rogers (Aus) Team Saxo-Tinkoff 0:02:26 
13 Alejandro Valverde Belmonte (Spa) Movistar Team 0:02:32 
14 Daniel Martin (Irl) Garmin-Sharp 0:02:36 
15 Richie Porte (Aus) Sky Procycling 0:02:49 
16 Daniel Moreno Fernandez (Spa) Katusha 0:03:06 
17 Robert Gesink (Ned) Belkin Pro Cycling Team 0:03:11 
18 Michal Kwiatkowski (Pol) Omega Pharma-Quick Step 0:03:14 

General classification after stage 15 
1 Christopher Froome (GBr) Sky Procycling 61:11:43 
2 Bauke Mollema (Ned) Belkin Pro Cycling Team 0:04:14 
3 Alberto Contador Velasco (Spa) Team Saxo-Tinkoff 0:04:25 
4 Roman Kreuziger (Cze) Team Saxo-Tinkoff 0:04:28 
5 Laurens Ten Dam (Ned) Belkin Pro Cycling Team 0:04:54 
6 Nairo Alexander Quintana Rojas (Col) Movistar Team 0:05:47 
7 Jakob Fuglsang (Den) Astana Pro Team 0:06:22 
8 Joaquim Rodriguez Oliver (Spa) Katusha 0:07:11 
9 Jean-Christophe Peraud (Fra) AG2R La Mondiale 0:07:47 
10 Daniel Martin (Irl) Garmin-Sharp 0:08:28 

#TDF   #TDF2013   #TDF100   #tourdefrance   #Teamsky   #Froome  ﻿

Meer lezen (161 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-HQryE5BcBMc/UeLAkdXHSfI/AAAAAAAB4Hw/MiKStYgjUf4/w426-h641/ScreenHunter_208%2BJul.%2B15%2B01.22.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/116227443885639403714/albums/5811123732939702273/5811123740953856722</link><title>The Mont Ventoux (1909m) 
Final climb of stage 15 of the +Le Tour De France. 
http://www.cyclingthealps.com/#mont-ventoux-profile﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-KO1ezjZjYq4/UKVCQPVkytI/AAAAAAAAGyg/k-l_grrmTng/w426-h295/mont-ventoux.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/105356395190203213677/albums/5926600846399127601/5926600847042348402?authkey=CISR3NuSpP-fQQ&amp;sqi=106819542950888921347&amp;sqsi=fa66550b-f708-4477-9074-87dc4cf84a4d</link><title>Lookout Mountain is higher than the 1912 meter summit of Mont Ventoux by solid 300 meters (900 feet), but that’s where comparison ends in favor of Lookout Mountain. 
Read More http://footloosecycling.com/2153/cycling-lookout-mountain-denvers-mont-ventoux/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-krGYsgjvrtA/Uj-EEeV9BXI/AAAAAAAARdw/Lyy740Vn9dA/w426-h240/WP_20130824_003.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/110319187537867985956/albums/5834766631850403713/5834766633597029090?authkey=CITfqPXeyIKZEA</link><title>Alpe d'Huez is just as magical, Mont Ventoux is still the "Giant" of Provence, the Passo Stelvio still has 48 switchbacks and the cobblestones of the Arenberg Forest are as sacred as ever. No one person can change any of that. #cycling﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-4UbxA4eaEW0/UPlBVt7aSuI/AAAAAAAABDs/kJbfGG3ihEg/w426-h284/ventoux.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5900418195042680369/5900418200945536450?authkey=CMXonbbZ1_34KQ&amp;sqi=114435503478132620253&amp;sqsi=4e002a1c-a288-4ff0-adc6-f740f644400e</link><title>Tour de France shorts: New Ventoux record? Tweets, Rojas and more 
http://www.cyclingnews.com/news/tour-de-france-shorts-new-ventoux-record 

A new record time on Mont Ventoux? 
The performance of Chris Froome and his overall rivals will be closely scrutinized today with people calculating their VAM, power output and performance. 
Team Sky manager Dave Brailsford and others have dismissed the use of the calculation to suggest or imply if a rider may be doping, but the time the riders take to conquer Mont Ventoux will surely spark debate. 
For the record, Lance Armstrong set the fastest time of 48:33 for the final 15km of Mont Ventoux in 2002. Alberto Contador set the second fastest time of 48:57 in 2009, while Marco Pantani and Armstrong stopped the clock in 48:59. Armstrong was stripped of his seven Tour de France victories and doubts about those fast times remain. 
The final 15km includes 1368m of elevation at an average gradient of 8.7%. The often strong winds are also a major factor in the racing and in the times set on Mont Ventoux. 

Tweeting about Ventoux 
Most of the riders were not really looking forward to today's closing climbs, and tweeted their feelings about it. Especially the sprinters showed a certain lack of enthusiasm. 
Mark Cavendish, Omega Pharma-QuickStep: “Bastille Day means big French motivation. Mont Ventoux means big climber motivation. All these things mean a grim day for sprinters.” 
Gert Steegmans, Omega Pharma-QuickStep: “Maybe we should make a echelon in the crosswinds before the Ventoux :-) could give some good television #tdf #OPQS” 

Greg Henderson, Lotto Belisol: “How do you say "give me a push mate" in French?” 

Peter Kennaugh, Sky: “Big big day tomoro, let's hope the first 2 hrs are a little easier than today but who know it is the tour after all..” 

Simon Geschke (Argos-Shimano): “Big day ahead, 242km + finish on top of Mt.Ventoux. Looking forward to the crowds on one side. Know that my legs will hurt on the other.” 

Rojas has not given up hope 
Movistar's José Joaquín Rojas tried to fight back during stage 14, after the team's bitter blow the day before when Alejandro Valverde dropped out of contention for the overall and the squad lost the lead in the team classification. Rojas was a dangerous addition to the 18-man breakaway which succeeded all the way to Lyon, with the Spaniard eventually finishing fourth for the stage. Teammate Imanol Erviti also made the move and finished 15th. 
"After all, what we wanted today is tell everyone that, despite what happened yesterday, we have not lost all hope in this year's Tour - we're willing, we have the courage to keep fighting and shining," Rojas explained. "It was my turn to contest the win today, but I couldn't take it. The break companions knew I was the fastest guy and, as expected, they forced me to go after several moves in the finale, especially in the last kilometer, when Albasini attacked." 
The Spanish team finished on top for the stage due to the gaps on the road, and moved from fifth to second-place in the team classification, 2:26 behind leaders Saxo-Tinkoff. 

Cavendish shares the joy 
Mark Cavendish (Omega Pharma-Quick-Step) was more than happy for Matteo Trentin to add to the sprinter's two stage victories for this Tour de France with the Italian's win on Sunday. We've seen Cavendish himself get emotional on the podium, but the Manxman was particularly proud of the performance of his teammate on Stage 14. 
"Been lucky to witness some amazing teammates wins in my career, but today was the 1st that brought tears to my eyes," he said via his twitter feed. 

Mollema attempts to do some homework 
Second overall on GC, Bauke Mollema (Belkin) did his best to keep an eye on his rivals ahead of Sunday's key stage up Mont Ventoux while back in the bunch on stage 13. 
"Today was easy, at least the final," said Mollema. "The start was hard, though. It went full gas in the peloton until the escape went. I saw my rivals riding today, but you can't get an idea of how they're feeling. They were always in the front, but since it was an easy day, you can't gauge them. After yesterday, I felt that I recovered well. It was nice to have an easier final today ahead of Mont Ventoux." 
Mollema is 2:28 behind maillot jaune Chris Froome (Sky) with teammate Laurens ten Dam fifth overall at 3:01. Ten Dam reported encouraging signs ahead of Ventoux. 
"It was not easy today with the climbs at the start of the stage and almost every team fighting to make it in the escape," he explained. "Once the escape went, the race settled down for us. My legs are feeling great and I hope to do well tomorrow on Mont Ventoux." 

#TDF   #TDf2013   #TDF100   #Tourdefrance  ﻿

Meer lezen (90 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-J_foLc08VKw/UeJ_F42brcI/AAAAAAAB36o/iQf9pEZ1BHY/w426-h640/ScreenHunter_206%2BJul.%2B14%2B20.41.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/103552890268543091591/albums/5901229925699375185/5901229926720866002?authkey=CLHq9b_NhNTuGw</link><title>Tour de France stage 15: Froome untouchable on Mont ventoux #cycling #tourdefrance 

REPORT: http://www.cyclingweekly.co.uk/news/latest/539428/chris-froome-wins-on-mont-ventoux-to-extend-tour-de-france-lead.html 

GALLERY: http://www.cyclingweekly.co.uk/galleries/photos/35086/1/0/tour-de-france-2013-stage-15.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-pnE08Chf8q4/UeVhWjAaBtI/AAAAAAAADWU/jnDetjv2vy4/w426-h281/Stage%2B15%2BTour%2Bde%2BFrance.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/110319187537867985956/albums/5713890906525627873/5714134751873550930</link><title>Cycling in Provence, France with a view of Mont Ventoux.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-kg-tlspONdw/T0yvSDQjSlI/AAAAAAAAAb4/fOvxwQykMUQ/w426-h320/bike-tour-provence-02.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5792844343155336913/5792844347998360738</link><title>Tour 2013 to climb Ventoux and Alpe d’Huez? 
http://www.cyclingtips.com.au/2012/09/humpday-news-shorts-3/ 
The Tour de France next year will climb the Mont Ventoux and the Alpe d’Huez two times, according to French newspaper Le Dauphiné Libéré. 
The Tour last visited the Ventoux climb in 2009, when Spain’s Juan Manuel Gárate (Rabobank) won. According to the newspaper, the “Giant of Provence” will feature at the beginning of the third week. 
The riders will climb up the Alpe d’Huez twice on July 18, according to the article. The stage will start in Gap, climb the mountain continue to the Col de Sarenne and down the other side. (Crews will need to asphalt the roads.) The stage will then loop back around for another go at the Alpe’s 21 hairpins. 
Two days later, one day before the finish in Paris, the race may visit Semnoz for a time trial. ASO will present the official route on 24 October in Paris. It already announced that the 100th edition will start and stay in Corsica for three days. 
#tourdefrance   #TDF   #TDF2013  ﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_Ls8ze5Q7qs/UGRRPiGSVKI/AAAAAAAA1pA/HA23wTCiLDc/w426-h284/ventoux-11.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7446-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cycling%20on%20the%20mont%20ventoux/photos/103635254282780611303/albums/5900050992325049393/5900050996047726994?authkey=CKyOvKOdyN2D_AE</link><title>Mont Ventoux, the ‘Giant of Provence,’ looms over the 100th Tour de France 
http://velonews.competitor.com/2013/07/tour-de-france/mont-ventoux-the-giant-of-provence-looms-over-the-100th-tour-de-france_294933 

CLERMONT-FERRAND, France (VN) — It rises alone, its greatness unencumbered by company, like an enormous ship at sea. 

Everyone said this Tour de France was over, but Mont Ventoux has yet to speak. 
The “Giant of Provence” appears on Sunday in this 100th Tour de France, at the end of a very long stage of 242 kilometers, from Givors to the mountain’s summit. Over 20.8 kilometers at an average of 7.5 percent in gradient, the peloton will whittle itself down to a mere trickle of dots upon the bleached moonscape of a peak that was once named “white top” in Gallic. 
Now, its name relates to wind, which blows harder than 50 miles an hour across its barren shoulders and peak 240 days a year. 
“The thing with Ventoux is that the wind could play a factor in a way that it doesn’t play in many other climbs. Which means that a guy ahead on his own could suffer, and a guy who’s behind may get a free ride to the line that you wouldn’t normally get on a climb, so that can change things,” said Garmin-Sharp director Charly Wegelius, whose boss, Jonathan Vaughters, once held the record for the fastest ascent of the climb. “It’s extremely fast at the top there if the wind is in the right direction.” 
It’s a climb whose name — Ventoux — is as legendary as the riders who’ve gained fame by riding up it. In cycling, it’s a climb as big as any other. The Tour has ascended the Giant 15 times since 1951. It claimed the life of British champion Tom Simpson, who died upon its slopes from a cocktail of heat exhaustion and amphetamines, in 1967. 
Simpson weaved across the road and crashed, but asked spectators to put him back on his bike, which they did. He nearly crested the Ventoux, but died half a mile from the summit, right on his bike. The last winner here was Juan Manuel Gárate, in 2009. Before that, it was Richard Virenque, in 2002. 
Lance let Pantani win here. Merckx needed oxygen at the top after winning a stage in 1970. Charly Gaul won in 1958, and Poulidor in ’65. It’s holy ground in cycling. And the 100th Tour de France will brush up against its shoulder on Sunday in the first of four immense climbing stages, begging up Ventoux and heading deep into the Alps. 
The climb pitches up gradually over the opening 5km, building in pressure, before it explodes skyward over 3km that average 9.5-percent gradient. From there, the road tilts up no less than 7.5 percent for 9km, with 2km that go at greater than 10 percent. When riders hit the wide-open, lunar-like upper reaches of the climb, near the Chalet Reynard, the steep tarmac gives way to potentially violent winds for 6km. Two final, steep kilometers lead to the summit and the first of three mountaintop finishes in the race’s final week. 
“I think there will be two races,” Wegelius said. “One for the stage, and one for the overall.” 
Chris Froome (Sky) said on Friday, after losing 1:09 to Alberto Contador (Saxo-Tinkoff) and a host of others in the crosswinds, that he thought more time would be lost or gained up Ventoux than in the winds, underscoring Ventoux’s significance, which cannot be overstated. Minutes will be lost and gained. 
“Sunday is the longest stage of the Tour and I think it’s the longest finishing climb also, so I think it’s going to be a tough stage. Also … after all the flat kilometers, to hit a climb like that in the final, it will be a day that some guys will experience that their legs don’t work the way they used to or the way they expect them to, and just the pure fatigue from a long stage will be important too,” said Jakob Fuglsang (Astana) who sits in sixth overall, at 4:39. A bad day on Ventoux will ruin the Tour for an unlucky rider. 
“In the end there’s not so much you can do about it; you can try to be 100 percent and try to recover and try to do as you always do, but if you have bad legs you have bad legs,” Fuglsang said. “There’s not so much to do about it. Normally the long stages suit me well, so I’m pretty optimistic and hoping for the best, including the possibility to do something good there.” 

Fuglsang, and everyone else. 

“Alberto knows it well. He’s climbed it several times in racing and in training. However, it’s the only climb of the day pretty much and no one knows how the bunch will be at the base of Ventoux, it could be like in the Pyrénées,” said Saxo director Philippe Mauduit. “Some leaders will probably lose a lot of time because it will be the first hard time after a full week on the flat. I just hope we’ll see the opposite of what we saw in the first Pyrénées stage. 
Mauduit said the confluence of the wind and the heat make Ventoux an “odd” climb: “It’s really hard up to Chalet Reynard; after Chalet Reynard it’s not that steep. But then you have the wind and the heat. It’s a pretty odd climb, but we just have to make sure he’s in top shape and let his legs talk.” 
A rider who could come to the front is Katusha’s Joaquím Rogriguez, who’s been quiet thus far. He’s 10th on GC, more than five minutes back of Froome after bleeding time in Wednesday’s time trial at Mont Saint Michel. 
“The harder the climbs, the more they suit Joaquím. He likes climbs with gradients above 10 percent. This is clearly a climb that could go well for him. He doesn’t like the long climbs based on rhythm. This is a climb that has steep gradients; I don’t think a team will be able hold the rhythm from the base to the top. There will be attacks, and those attacks suit him. He loves changes in rhythm,” said Katusha director Valerio Piva. “It’s a stage that he’s waiting for. He wants to win it and make a difference on the others. Anyone that has a chance to win the race will have to show themselves on Ventoux.” 

#TDF   #TDF2013   #TDF100   #tourdefrance  ﻿

Meer lezen (100 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7446_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-AInbtzdFJ_4/UeExHwAdSZI/AAAAAAAB3zQ/_PuXbJ72ugo/w426-h284/WATSON_00002054-020.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>