<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:33:59" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/108274246770630435350/albums/6011327736225472849/6011327744313452562</link><title>Yet another stylish W Hotel 
Stairway to heaven? No - stairway at the  W Bangkok: 
http://travelmemo.com/asia/thailand/thailand-trip-bangkok-w-Hotel 

Thanks to Nezasa +Individual travel that works for this great tour! 

#thailand   #Bangkok   #Whotels  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-cfisqvt7igI/U2yGu-xA6BI/AAAAAAAABHo/0jz8cJiyplE/w426-h284/DSC02340.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/106518944031877467881/albums/5828160798119642033/5828160794403942770?authkey=CJH7pfyI0cHM9gE</link><title>The Green Vine Snake (Ahaetula nasuta) occurs in India, Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, Burma, Thailand, Cambodia and Vietnam. Not to be confused with Oxybelis fulgidus, which is found in Central and South America. 
This individual was found in Amboli forest of Northern Western Ghats in the state of Maharashtra, India. In 2013 I plan to travel to Amboli for the monsoons to photograph the Malabar Gliding Frogs and its life-cycle along with some of the spectacular snakes like this one! Happy New Year 2013! Year of the Snake! :D Cheers ~ Abir 
http://www.ifrogs.net﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-iQSEts-TIiY/UOHJXRROMXI/AAAAAAAACh0/4mpFYzla23k/w426-h237/ifrogs%2Byear%2Bof%2Bsnake.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/112958202504391052074/albums/5694742125269471297/5694742124703238818</link><title>Returning to the Reality with Ecotourism 

http://www.easytoindochina.com/travel/returning-to-the-reality-with-ecotourism.html 

People often travel to escape from the reality, however, traveling to become a part of reality and understand more about life of other people from other countries is very interesting. The Gibbon Experience Resort in theNothern of Laos is really wish for many people who love ecotourism and discovering the beauty of nature.In here, guests sleep in the tree houses high in the forest Canopy , and move around the dense jungle by system of large zip wires connected between the tree houses together. “ This is a very unique type of travel. Enjoy the beauty of the jungle and also help protecting wild life in here” said a visitor from Vietnam.With the permission of Lao Government, five years ago, theGibbon Experience Resort operated and preserved the Bokeo Natural Reserve. The proceeds from tourism business was used to pay for 40 employees included the local workers and forest protectors. A part of this proceeds was also to support people of the area in develop agriculture and protect wild animals being in danger of extinction such as Gibbons, Bears, Tigers, Musk –deers, Elephants and buffaloes.Thanks to helping the local people do business while preserving the natural environment, The Gibbon Experience is an ideal example for ecotourism. According to The CEO of Ecotourism Australia, Mr Kym cheatham, this is form of natural tourism to discover, protect the environment and community, “make chance for descendants of visitors today could come back and enjoy, which is called the heritage we leave for our future gernerations”.The market of 89 billion US DollarsThis form of “responsible travelling” includes ecotourism, volunteer tourism, adventure, culture and heritage, green tourism, or sustainable tourism. More and more visitors wish to experience new tourism type.This helps enlarge their knowledge, also contributes to preserve the environment and local people who live in the tourism area. According to the report of adventure tourism market of George Washington University (USA ) in 2010, this trend has been developing into a business field worth 89 billion US Dollars for 2 decades.The Ecotourism was actually established 30 years ago when it was for travellers who only want to travel with nature instead of hotels, resorts, or luxury cruises. However, at that early time, many people had bad action as cutting the forest trees in order to make nice view for visitors. In the 1990s, Australia became the fist nation to establish the program of certifying ecotourism in a guide book of 165 pages and list of more than 200 tourism products certified.Mrs Kristin Lammoureux, Director of Institue for International Tourism Studying of George Washington University, said that: “People have ignored mass tourism in which they themselves feel have no private space”. Therefore, the form of homestay, travelling combines the volunteer work to wild life reserve, rural areas or eco –green accomodations with low cabonic produce has become enjoyable.“Ecotourism has become a main trend and activities for natural environment has become an indispensible part of any tour programes. Visitors can spend one day for personal shopping and join volunteer activities on the next day”. Said Kristin. Asia – Pacifics HighlightAsia Pacific area is nowadays an atractive destination for visitors who love this type of responsible traveling. Ecotourism in Philipines and Indonesia is developing very quickly. Thailand and Laos are trying to catch these two nations. Campuchia where many non – government orgernizations are actives, has a well –developed volunteer tourism. Possessioning a lot of wild and diverse natural spots, Australia is also one of top choice for the nature - love form China, Japan, and Korea. Meanwhile, most of the visitors chosing ecotourism in Southeast Asia are from Western countries, Singapore and North Asia, this means that the tourist potential from Southeast Asia has been unexplored. Vietnam is an example. A girl named Ngoc, who lives in Ho Chi Minh City and is an representative for first visitors of ecotourism discribed her experience to The Gibbon Experience: She and her friend spent 4 hours walking through the jungle to get the tree houses where they would stayed. “I really trembled when initially using the system of zip wires on the trees, however, that fear quickly passed over for feeling of joyfulness. You can hear the sounds of the jungle and welcomed some guests as wild animals here. This type is so unique. Instead of just sightseeing, for this you will feel like you yourself are part of the jungle” Said Ngoc. Protecting, exposing, and taking care of the animal is a main activity of ecotourism. 
In Asia pacific area, visitors have more chance to expose the animals than in Western countries. At the Elephant Village Sanctuaty &amp; Resort located in suburb of Luang Prabang, Laos, visitors could bath the elephants and feed and feed them, or also learn how to train this animal. In china, visitor could work at the Bifengxia Panda Reserve in Sichuan Province, feed them and take - care the little pandas. In Tasmania, Australia, the refuge for unique wild animals, visitors could cuddle the Wombat bears, play with the Koala bears or reach the Kangaroos and feed them.The Borneo Island in Indonesia is also a beautiful destination for ecotourism with the pioneering company named Borneo Eco Tours which was established in 1991. The company has remained the “green policy” so far, contributing to the preserving the rare animal species such as long –nosed monkeys, thick – skinned species such as elephants, rhinoceroses, turtles, and specially the Orang Utan apes – characteristics of the Island. 

Nowadays, the company and Shangri La’s Rasa Ria hotel run a Natural Reserve for program “resettlement” for Orang Utans. At Sukau Rainforest Lodge Resort of Borneo Eco Tours, people built a more than 500 meters path helping the Pymes Elephant ( voi lùn ) easily move on during their migration season. Willie Ki, marketing staff of Borneo Eco Tours said that: “ We do not organize tour program to the zoos, or any other places where the animals are locked in cages. We try to integrate natural preservation educating activities in the tours and through publications”.Helping the visitors raise their awareness of protecting environment and local people community is the goal of most businesses in this responsible tourism field. Bronwen Laopha, the founder of Faa Sai Resort &amp; Spa in Chanthaburi,Thailand, said that: “preserving biodiversity and raise people’s awareness is our mission. Our resort is very beautiful and less human’s action. Beside not causing negative impact to the nature and local people, we also want to bring good things to them”.Eye witnessing some other businesses cut the forest trees to grow rubbers, devastate the ecological environment for their immediate benefit, the Laophas tried to grow plant and grass for medical products and serve cultural activities. They bought devastated land areas and renovated them into mashes or gardens and named them White Water Lake. All constructions were built from hand –made bricks at the local. They could plant rice and vegetables serving the visitors. Bronwen, a member of the Laophas said that they hoped their work would bring positive impact.According to Kym, CEO of Ecotourism Australia, there are aslo many businesses so –called “environmentally friendly” like Bronwen. For example, Mr Rob Pennicottn in the South Coast of Tasmania is the founder of Bruny Island Cruises Company specializing in Whale and seal watching tours. He has used all proceeds of his company with visitor’s fund in order to expel the predator cats from the Tasman Island and protect sea birds in here for three years. The Low Isles Sail Away Resort organizes tours around the Great Barrier Reef ( or Dai Bao Tieu) by rafts. All proceeds is for buying land and growing local plants, creating sustainable forests. These private companies have helped the local government a lot because the government does not have enough budget for such work.Volunteer Tourism in CambodiaThere is no country in Asia developing the voluntary tourism as popularly as in Cambodia. Presence of many NGOs in this country makes Cambodia become a frequent destination for visitors. The American couple Jake – Emily Fisher, for example. On Oct, 2010, they decided to enjoy their honeymoon in Siem Reap as volunteering to help orphans in Svay Savong School. Every morning, the couple took the bus to the school, played and talked to the children about life outside Cambodia. In the afternoon, they spent 3-4 hours teaching them English with topics about tourism and natural conservation.The Fishers are not individual travelers. According to the survey of the center of tourism, hotel and restaurant managing in Virginia Tech University, USA, many visitors are willing to spend 7 – 8 hours per day for voluntary work. After finishing, they spend several days sightseeing and enjoy local food. “Cultural exchange between voluntary visitors and local people could help them understand more about each other” said Nancy McGehee, the professor in charge of that survey.The Fishers completely agree: “America, the small joy of children there becomes our great happiness when we are back to America, this experience really changes our overview on tourism. We often travel to escape from the reality, but to become a part of reality and understand more about life of other people from other countries is very interesting”. Regarding to Ms Ngoc, the nature is so beautiful and needs to be protected. This is a worth preserving property for the future generations.From Jenin St.Lee-John﻿

Meer lezen (149 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_03_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ZkmSSCD_oTs/TwfJylZjyqI/AAAAAAAAAFk/IaNJ8QJOdfI/w426-h259/Vietnam-travel.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/102759493052273217647/albums/5761925025750849601/5761925024512597282</link><title>Will Us Law Hurt Tourism??? 

When the U.S. Supreme Court upheld the country’s health care reform law last week, Costa Rica’s private medical sector paid close attention. 
The Affordable Care Act, known colloquially as “Obamacare,” will extend health insurance to approximately 40 million uninsured U.S. citizens. 
The Supreme Court decision could hamper the growing global medical tourism industry, a key tourist market in Costa Rica. According to the Council for International Promotion of Costa Rica Medicine (PROMED), in 2010, the country counted 36,000 medical tourists, who generated $288 million in revenue. 
Numbers have not yet been announced for 2011. But PROMED estimates 12 percent growth, putting the number at 40,000 tourists. At a medical tourism conference in April, organizers predicated the industry could begin attracting 100,000 medical tourists by 2013. 
Health officials acknowledged those estimates might need to be tempered with U.S. health care reform a reality. Barring a repeal of the law by Republican lawmakers, the full extent of the reforms will go into effect on Jan. 1, 2014. 
The medical tourism industry’s philosophy centers on providing quality care that’s more cost-efficient because it’s received outside the United States. But with more citizens obtaining insurance, health care in the U.S. becomes more affordable. 
However, the law will not cover certain popular medical tourism procedures, including elective surgeries and dental care. Dental treatments represent almost 40 percent of medical tourism, while plastic surgery represents another large percentage. 
At the same time, medical tourism promoters have been researching ways to provide care for procedures often covered by insurance. 
One initiative that is gaining traction is corporate tourism. The program negotiates with health insurance companies working with other private companies to create deals where employees travel abroad for treatment. 
“If we see health care reform possibly reducing the individual market for medical travel, we could have a huge opportunity for corporate buyers for health care,” PROMED Executive Director Massimo Manzi said. 
While “Obamacare” might cause individual tourist numbers to stagnate, businesses still have the potential to bring planeloads of tourists down for treatments. The key to convince companies and their employees to receive treatment in Costa Rica is to provide incentives, said Bob Repke, president of Global Medical Conexions, a corporate medical tourism facilitator. 
Repke has spoken on the law at medical tourism conferences in Costa Rica. The June 28 Supreme Court ruling is fresh, and he and the rest of the industry haven’t had time yet to digest the law, which has more than 2,000 pages. However, he insists medical tourism promoters should see many positives in the outcome. 
“We’ve been seeing an increase in medical travel in the last five years, and we still haven’t penetrated the market fully,” Repke said, adding that opportunities also include markets in the Caribbean and the rest of Latin America. 
Besides corporate tourism, another boost could come from those who are impatient with the new system. In Canada, a country with universal health care, patients can wait up to two years to receive non-life-threatening procedures, such as knee or hip replacements. Patients could choose to receive surgery faster in Costa Rica. 
Repke said those same long lines will form in the U.S., except in larger numbers. Plus, medical tourism’s reputation has strengthened over the years, and Repke believes in the future more foreigners will take interest in the idea. 
Doctors are realistic that certain sectors of medical tourism will see drops in patients due to the reform. 
Dr. Luis Wachong, director of the private medical facility Clínica UNIBE, in northeastern San José, said 90 percent of tourists who come to the hospital are there for cosmetic surgeries. The other 10 percent come for general surgeries, neurological procedures and orthopedics. The latter treatments likely would be covered by health insurance plans under the new law, resulting in a slump in business in that area. 
Cosmetic surgery could face challenges in the future, too. As other medical tourism destinations rush to promote procedures not covered by insurance policies, Costa Rica will need to stay ahead of other Latin American rivals. 
“In plastic surgery, there’s no insurance to cover that, so probably this market will continue to grow,” Wachong said. “And our competition is not in any way ‘Obamacare’; it would be the other countries.” 
But Wachong and other medical officials believe, at the moment, Costa Rica has the edge against its competitors. Costa Rica has long been the go-to destination for medical tourism in the region, unlike emerging markets in Colombia and Panama. Mexico, another medical tourism leader, must keep on combating a negative image brought on by the drug war. 
Furthermore, proximity to the U.S. gives Costa Rica a natural advantage. Few U.S. patients will choose to fly all day to medical tourism hotbeds Thailand and Singapore when most uninsured procedures – such as dental treatment – are short and simple and can be carried out after a quick flight to Central America. 
PROMED’s Manzi also is relieved that in the last few years, medical tourism has received positive attention in the mainstream. More foreigners are aware medical tourism exists, even if less patients might consider the option after the reform. 
He pointed to a recent New Yorker article called “Affordable Health Care in Thailand and Costa Rica.” The item mentioned the possibility of receiving a hip replacement at Costa Rica’s well-regarded CIMA Hospital for a sixth of the cost than what the operation costs in the U.S. 
That same story related an anecdote – and perhaps a warning – about the sudden vanguard of medical tourism: corporate tourism. In addition to logistics and making sure procedures go well, the greatest obstacle appears to be convincing patients they want to travel abroad in the first place. 
 For example, in 2008, U.S. supermarket chain Hannaford set up a program for its workers to receive treatment at a renowned – and cheaper – hospital in Singapore. Hannaford’s employees chose not to try out the enticement, the New Yorker wrote. 
Manzi trusts that it will be easier to sway corporate employees to visit Costa Rica instead of Southeast Asia, but to make the endeavor a success he hopes to receive help from the Costa Rican government. 
PROMED is working to create a centralized database on medical tourism patients by surveying facilities throughout the Central Valley and the northwestern province of Guanacaste. Manzi wants the government to assist in turning the hard data into a medical tourism advertising campaign designed for the U.S. market. 
The Costa Rican government announced at a recent business conference that medical tourism is one of its top priorities. Since the Affordable Care Act passed the U.S. Congress, Costa Rican medical tourism officials have done the legwork. They’ve been talking to insurance companies, working with facilitators and negotiating with major employers. But without a strong tourism campaign, Costa Rica might lose its eminence as perhaps the most favored destinations for U.S. medical tourists. 
“Even if you convince the company, you still always have to convince the patients,” Manzi said. “And that is possibly the missing piece.”﻿

Meer lezen (126 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-G8BjgoXOjoU/T_Z4SCSB3SI/AAAAAAAAAEQ/fOolbA9SXT0/w426-h295/Medical-Tourism-1_newsfull_h.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/113415845792187188340/albums/5979547104044701025/5979547106703173026?sqi=115498623068861010577&amp;sqsi=d36e8fd5-e127-4992-8218-b491cb77bbf1</link><title>#Romantic Holiday: Indulge in a luxury #Thailand holiday directly on the beachfront of the sleepy royal seaside town of #HuaHin with Anantara Hua Hin Resort &amp; Spa. Find complete relaxation and contentment on your Hua Hin holiday, with signature spa treatments and Ayurvedic massage therapy at the Anantara Hua Hin Resort &amp; Spa. Each of the spa’s seven suites is set in its own individual garden courtyard created by award-winning landscape architect Bill Bensley. A choice of flights, transfers and 7 nights accommodation with daily breakfast are available starting from just £ 799 only. Call Brightsun Travel on our dedicated tours line 0208 819 0531 or visit http://bitly.com/1gpMSMl.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-fYR2crEXK08/UvueaZzB5aI/AAAAAAAAEm8/glk_S_7CzWc/w426-h307/1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/108274246770630435350/albums/6010584917725678497/6010584918144818450</link><title>Stellar hideaway on Koh Phangan 
Want to feel like Tarzan &amp; Jane? Visit the amazing +Anantara Rasananda Koh Phangan Villa Resort &amp; Spa 
Here is our report: 
http://travelmemo.com/asia/thailand/thailand-tour-koh-phangan-anantara-Resort 

#kohphangan   #thailand  +Anantara Hotels Resorts &amp; Spas +Individual travel that works ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-RVJ7IO_eqH0/U2njIzpXnRI/AAAAAAAABGw/Dol_yx0Ab2g/w426-h284/DSC02025.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/111512293751292647576/albums/5716366578211983217/5716366583069361858</link><title>Centara Karon Resort is an EarthCheck Star Performer 
Centara Karon Resort Phuket has been awarded Star Performer status by EarthCheck, the international environmental and certification body for the travel and tourism industry. 
The resort when assessed by EarthCheck was found to have a Sustainability Policy in place, and to have eight categories performing at or above Best Practice level. 
The categories are Energy Consumption, Potable Water Consumption, Waste Sent to Landfill, Waste Recycling Rating, Community Contributions Rating, Paper Products Rating, Cleaning Products Rating and Pesticide Products Rating. 
“Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts has environmental management and conservation as one of its highest priorities across our entire range of activities,” says David R Good, vice president for operations. 
“We are delighted that our Karon Resort property has won such a high accolade, as every member of our staff at the resort makes an individual contribution. 
“Their enthusiasm is shared by many of our guests, who take an active part in the environment-related events and promotions that are organised at the resort.” 
Using a science-based approach, EarthCheck helps many of the world's leading travel and tourism companies address risk, deliver bottom line efficiencies, maximise guest experience and minimise their environmental footprints. 
EarthCheck is used in more than 80 countries across the globe and supports its network of members with a team of dedicated relationship managers, online tools, regular regional workshops, and a suite of training packages. 
Centara Karon Resort Phuket is a modern mid-rise resort divided into four resort zones catering to individuals, families, couples, and discerning travelers. All zones have panoramic views of Karon Beach and the lush hinterland of hills behind. 

The resort has earlier successfully achieved the EarthCheck Certification Bronze Status. To gain this, the resort had to report its environmental footprint to independent auditors and adhere to internationally recognised standards of Best Practice. 
Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts is Thailand’s largest operator of hotels, with 38 deluxe and first-class properties covering all the major tourist destinations in the Kingdom. A further 17 resorts in the Maldives, Philippines, Vietnam, Bali Indonesia, Sri Lanka and Mauritius Indian Ocean, brings the present total to 55 properties. Brands and properties within Centara ensure that specific categories such as couples, families, individuals, and meetings and incentives groups will all find a hotel or resort that is appropriate to their needs. Centara operates 25 branches of Spa Cenvaree, one of Thailand’s most luxurious and innovative spa brands, and the company’s Kids’ Club is available at all the family-friendly resorts to ensure that the youngsters and teens are taken care of. Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts also operates two state-of-the-art convention centres in Bangkok, and one in Udon Thani in northeastern Thailand. 
For more information and reservations, please contact tel. +662 101 1234 ext 1 or e-mail to reservations@chr.co.th or visit our website at http://www.centarahotelsresorts.com 
Facebook: www.facebook.com/centarahotelsresorts 
Twitter: www.twitter.com/staycentara 
For high resolution photos, please visit http://www.centarahotelsresorts.com/Photography/ckr.asp﻿

Meer lezen (55 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-cjnJ9FaFE7g/T1SdHuXDRsI/AAAAAAAAATU/7v5pkg3VOGw/w426-h288/Centara%2BKaron%2BResort%2BPhuket.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/111512293751292647576/albums/5717464630489844977/5717464628771896402</link><title>Centara opens Hospitality Centre at Phuket Airport 

Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts has opened Centara Hospitality Centre at Phuket International Airport designed to provide guests and travel representatives with a meet-and-greet point and to provide support and information on the growing number of Centara properties on the island. 

Centara Hospitality Centre opened on 1st March 2012 and is located in the arrivals hall at the airport. 

Coffee, tea, cold drinks and snacks are available, and an airport representative is on full-time duty. 

"We currently have seven properties on Phuket Island, and Centara Hospitality Centre is designed to support the growing number of our guests who are arriving and departing through Phuket International Airport, and the travel representatives who are meeting and greeting individual guests, groups, and corporate and incentives parties,” says Chris Bailey, senior vice president for sales and marketing at Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts. 

"We feel an attractive and comfortable meeting point is an extension of our services and hospitality, and of course Centara Hospitality Centre is also available for those travellers who have no bookings but who wish to find out what we can offer on the island.” 

Centara's seven properties are the Centara Grand Beach Resort Phuket, at Karon Beach; Centara Grand West Sands Resort &amp; Villas Phuket, at Mai Khao Beach; Centara Villas Phuket, at Karon Beach; Centara Karon Resort Phuket, at Karon Beach; Centara Kata Resort Phuket, at Kata Beach; Waterfront Suites Phuket, at Karon Beach; and Centra Ashlee Hotel Patong, at Patong Beach. 

Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts is Thailand’s leading operator of hotels, with 38 deluxe and first-class properties covering all the major tourist destinations in the Kingdom. A further 17 resorts in the Maldives, Philippines, Vietnam, Bali Indonesia, Sri Lanka and Mauritius Indian Ocean, brings the present total to 55 properties. Brands and properties within Centara ensure that specific categories such as couples, families, individuals, and meetings and incentives groups will all find a hotel or resort that is appropriate to their needs. Centara operates 25 branches of Spa Cenvaree, one of Thailand’s most luxurious and innovative spa brands, and the company’s Kids’ Club is available at all the family-friendly resorts to ensure that the youngsters and teens are taken care of. Centara Hotels &amp; Resorts also operates two state-of-the-art convention centres in Bangkok, and one in Udon Thani in northeastern Thailand. 

For more information and reservations, please contact tel. +662 101 1234 ext 1 or e-mail to reservations@chr.co.th or visit our website at www.centarahotelsresorts.com 
Facebook: www.facebook.com/centarahotelsresorts 
Twitter: www.twitter.com/staycentara﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-QDogW0jE_6I/T1iDyZXPPFI/AAAAAAAAAUo/OfVsOSauXq0/w426-h320/Centara%2BGrand%2BWest%2BSands%2BResort%2B%2BVillas%2BPhuket%2BPhuket%2BAirport%2BLounge_01.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7450-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/thailand%20individual%20travel/photos/113739079162408934798/albums/5891463823645720785/5891463826513854370</link><title>Two different shades of "Gray"...Mobile Photography 

While the arrival of Monsoons is mesmerising and spell binding the sub-continent people, it's devastating the thousands others in Uttrakhand state of India. With thousands of people fared dead to Man Made disaster and cost of pseudo development, I was wondering how much we are making our Planet to suffer in the name of development that never is actually?? What defines the maximum and minimum pollution that we venting out?? How many times we have seen the ferocity of Nature as its payback?? America, Japan, China, Indonesia, India, Germany, Thailand, Australia have witnessed Tornados, landslides, floods, tsunamis etc mostly due to changing wether patterns attributed to damage to environment. I wonder who is paying price for that? 

I would eat two meals a day at home rather then spending money leisurely at top restaurants. I will take my family out to zoo and local markets rather then visiting upscale shopping malls. I will travel in Public transport to work, rather then paddling the gas of my car...I will visit my friends n family rather then spending a fortune on holidaying at some exotic location. I will scale down my requirements to save my planet for future generations to see the green is green and clear blue is Blue... 

My heart goes for the families of those killed in Uttrakhand for no fault of theirs. A human life lost is a human life after all, whether its a terror or a nature's attack. While a fortune is being spent of safeguarding people against terror attack, insignificant is done and that too in peice meals by Govts globally to this pollution menace...time to start from us "Individual" ﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7450_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-rRKcJ1uIE_4/UcKvIspr_6I/AAAAAAAARdk/TT53C9xUBuY/w426-h308/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>