<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:20:17" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/100070506056563153536/albums/5709708322559860385/5781361052732762770</link><title>Song Of The Duck At Animal Farm   #oilpaintingoncanvas  by +Monika Blatton 

#BreakfastArtClub by +Breakfast Art Club 
#BreakfastClub by +Breakfast Club 
#PixelWorld by +PixelWorld 

#art #fineart #artists #painters #paintings #oilpaintings  #oiloncanvas #artwork 
You can buy one of my available originals, if you like it: http://ebay.blatton.com﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-PYXO68xGUQw/UDuFPxpqKpI/AAAAAAAAEuc/NsHd79letnw/w426-h527/Piesn%2BKaczki%2BNa%2BFolwarku%2BZwierzecym.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/107567472348039614340/albums/5854195375956551137/5854200355110952114</link><title>Who want give me just 1 usd. Everyday Peoples spent to much money to Internet Games , Erotic Sites, Pokers, or bets. I want to asking  Can you give me a 1 usd. If you give me a 1 usd I will be collect all money and buy first a land for my real farm and then make a green house green energy stations, barracks buy animal etc every they I share my makings with you ? So you like my real live game so Are you ready play this game with me ? I am serious﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Ta92b9oqSzg/UT5MNMJanLI/AAAAAAAAAC8/2M_PelTuBDk/w426-h427/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/105702253354634604817/albums/5943511485398905537/5943511489717386466</link><title>Try grasscutter farming 

Nowadays, a lot of Nigerians go to higher institutions for the sole aim of getting the paper qualification that makes them eligible to get white-collar jobs after graduation. This kind of dream is like one learning to become a well-paid slave forever. Even, the so-called jobs being prepared for are in short supply and many times, not available. The government, which had traditionally provided jobs, can no longer cater for the increasing number of job seekers as it has even on occasions retrenched many without recourse to due process. 

A credible alternative is to start your own animal farming business, produce vital food and be your own boss. We need to produce students, who are not looking for jobs, but who would rather create jobs. Our educational system produces followers. Most people learn to become employees not business owners, this attitude should be revised. Our schools teach students to get jobs and work for someone else; our graduates learn to be good employees. Even parents tell their children, “get a good education so that you can get a good job.” Most parents encourage this without realising that they are handicapping their children’s potential. Why can’t they say, “get good education so that you can own a business or become an employer? Teach a man how to fish and he would be able to catch enough fish than depending on charity or tokenism in the guise of white-collar jobs. Interestingly, no sane man hates education; I have nothing against education, but at times it gives people false confidence. It makes them trust in certificates instead of working hard. 

Grasscutter rearing can make you to be gainfully employed. At Jovana Farms, we specialise in breeding, training, setting-up grasscutter farms and sales. Grasscutter farming is a great money-spinning business that can provide job opportunities for the young and old; the educated or uneducated members of the society. In addition to these facts, it is free from cultural and religious taboos. This makes it to be a universal favourite, breaking all barriers – ethnicity, colour, creed etc. The situation affords the prospective investor the opportunity of raising grasscutters for local and international markets. If you want to be your own boss and you are ready to work hard and get rich, try grasscutter farming. 

If all hands are on deck, over a million jobs can be created in the grasscutter sector alone. But Nigerians’ preference for white-collar jobs has led to the neglect of this lucrative agricultural enterprise. The business does not require millions of naira to execute. It can be started with just one family of grasscutters normally called a colony, which is sold for N45,000 to N50,000, depending on the specie and age. A colony comprises one male and four females. They are reared in cages which can be constructed at a cost of N10,000 by any roadside carpenter. Therefore, with N60,000, you are already in good business. It is advisable to buy them when they are four months old, which is the breeding stock stage. Grasscutter is odourless unlike fowls, rabbits, pigs etc. You do not require an expanse of space to start; the cage can be placed anywhere in the compound or even in the kitchen. In terms of feeding, it is not like fish farming, pig farming or poultry farming, because grasscutters feed on grass. 

In terms of yield, one female grasscutter can give birth to as many as six to 10 babies at a go. I have even witnessed 10 at once in my farm. So, instead of remaining unemployed, even an undergraduate can take a soft loan from a bank, friend or family member and in a few months be able to pay back the loan and still remain in business. For instance, if you start rearing now, in about four months, they will start having babies because they mature for birth at eight months. 

And if you do not have enough space for expansion, you can sell the babies to new farmers; at the end of the day, the four females give you seven babies each, you have 28 litters. Invariably, you only have to be patient for about eight months, and if they carry their babies for about five months, you can start cross-breeding them for stronger breeds and in eight months, you start making profit. Grasscutter meat is also high in demand. It readily comes to mind when people think of ‘bush meat.’﻿

Meer lezen (72 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ws7SMx5QIwk/UnuYNbcOvOI/AAAAAAAAA2I/epNmYeZpuls/w426-h319/e903400e-01ac-4940-b187-7b4b688841d0</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/110867007740944887152/albums/5899393033878978593/5899393035138841234?authkey=CLaFqZHFsNne6QE</link><title>If you can't buy eggs from a CSA (and we hope to someday), this is good to know/look for. 

\- - - - - - - - - - 

Think all “Cage Free” eggs are the same? Think again. 

Cage Free hens without perches (pictured on top) do not have the ability to engage in the natural behavior of perching. Certified Humane® Animal Care Standards require perches for hens, which allow the hens to engage in their natural behavior, as do the Certified Humane® requirements for adequate space, nest boxes and access to dust bathing materials. 

All hens on the Certified Humane® program (pictured on bottom) must have sufficient freedom of movement to be able, without difficulty, to stand normally, turn around, and stretch their wings, enforced by HFAC’s space requirements. Additionally, hens must be supplied with perches, nest boxes, and dust bathing materials. 

Hens need more than freedom from cages. Look for Certified Humane® products if you agree. 

To learn more about what laying hens need on the Certified Humane® program, read our standards: 
http://www.certifiedhumane.org/uploads/pdf/Standards/English/Std09.Layers.2J.pdf 

[Text and image source: Humane Farm Animal Care's Facebook post: http://goo.gl/FmFQZ]﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-InshwbghGQI/Ud7atYndOpI/AAAAAAAAagU/CmYDFDNAlys/s426/Humane%2BFarm%2BAnimal%2BCare%2B-%2B20130711%2BFacebook%2Bpost.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/118203227983345306955/albums/5629223015925387569/5629223015922910002</link><title>How animal welfare signals moral progress 
July 13th, 2011 11:59 AM ET 
http://globalpublicsquare.blogs.cnn.com/2011/07/13/how-animal-welfare-signals-moral-progress/?iref=allsearch Editor's Note: Peter Singer is professor of bioethics at Princeton University and Laureate Professor at the University of Melbourne. His books include Animal Liberation, Practical Ethics, The Ethics of What We Eat, and The Life You Can Save. For more from Singer, visit Project Syndicate's website, or check it out on Facebook and Twitter. 
By Peter Singer 

Mahatma Gandhi acutely observed that “the greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.” To seek to reduce the suffering of those who are completely under one’s domination, and unable to fight back, is truly a mark of a civilized society. 

Charting the progress of animal-welfare legislation around the world is therefore an indication of moral progress more generally. Last month, parallel developments on opposite sides of the world gave us grounds for thinking that the world may, slowly and haltingly, be becoming a little more civilized. 
First, the British House of Commons passed a motion directing the government to impose a ban on the use of wild animals in circuses. The motion followed the release of undercover footage, obtained by Animal Defenders International, of a circus worker repeatedly beating Anne, an elephant. The measure was, at least initially, opposed by the Conservative government, but supported by members of all political parties. In a triumph for parliamentary democracy, the motion passed without dissent. 

More controversially, the lower house of the Dutch parliament passed a law giving the Jewish and Islamic communities a year to provide evidence that animals slaughtered by traditional methods do not experience greater pain than those that are stunned before they are killed. If the evidence cannot be provided, stunning before slaughter will be required in the Netherlands. 

At times, it has seemed that gains for animals in Western countries have been outweighed by increasing animal abuse in China, as growing prosperity there boosts demand for animal products. I found it difficult to watch the videotape of the beating of Anne, but that recording did not compare to videos I have seen of animal cruelty in China. 

The sickening footage available online shows bears kept in cages so small that they cannot stand up, or in some cases move at all, so that bile can be taken from them. Worse still (if one can compare such atrocities) is a video showing fur-bearing animals being skinned alive and thrown onto a pile of other animals, where they are left to die slowly. 
In light – perhaps one should say darkness – of such images, it is sometimes suggested that animal welfare is exclusively a Western concern. But that is implausible, given that Buddhist tradition places more emphasis on concern for animals than Judaism, Christianity, or Islam. Long before Western philosophers included animals in their ethics, Chinese philosophers like Zhuangzi said that love should permeate relations not only between humans, but between all sentient beings. Nowadays, China has its own animal-rights campaigners, and there are signs that their message is beginning to be heard. 

One recent sign again concerns circuses. Chinese zoos have drawn crowds by staging animal spectacles, and by allowing members of the public to buy live chickens, goats, and horses in order to watch them being pulled apart by lions, tigers, and other big cats. Now the Chinese government has forbidden state-owned zoos from taking part in such cruelty. 
Welcome as these initiatives are, the number of animals in circuses and zoos is tiny compared to the tens of billions of animals suffering in factory farms. In this area, Western countries have set a deplorable example. 

Recently, however, the European Union has recognized that the intensive confinement of farm animals has gone too far. It has already outlawed keeping veal calves in individual stalls,and, in six months, it will be illegal in all 27 EU countries, from Portugal to Poland and from Britain to Greece, to keep laying hens in the bare-wire cages that today dominate the egg industry around the world. In January 2013, keeping breeding sows in individual stalls will also be prohibited. 

The United States lags behind Europe in getting rid of the worst forms of abuse of farm animals. The problem does not lie with voters, who, in states like Florida, Arizona, and California, have shown that they want farm animals to have better protection than the animal industries typically provide. The biggest problems are in those states that lack a mechanism for citizens to initiate a referendum on how farm animals should be treated. Unfortunately, this group includes the Midwestern and southern states, where the majority of America’s farmed animals are produced. 
China’s centralized government can, if it so chooses, ensure that animal-welfare laws apply throughout the country. The animal-welfare movement in China should not be satisfied with its small but conspicuous success regarding animal abuse in zoos. It must move on to the far more significant target of better living conditions and more humane deaths for bears and fur-bearing animals, as well as for cows, pigs, laying hens, and chickens. 

There remain many other countries with deplorable animal-welfare standards. In Indonesia, for example, Animals Australia recorded undercover videos showing such brutal treatment of Australian-raised cattle that Australia’s government suspended cattle exports to the country. Now some MPs are calling for a permanent ban. The best hope for further progress, it seems, lies in animal welfare becoming, like human rights, an international issue that affects countries’ reputations. 

At peace with ourselves in the knowledge that we did not cause anguish or pain to our fellow animal brethren, we will have the inner tranquility to pursue our spiritual endeavors wholeheartedly. #SMCH http://veganway2peace.org/﻿

Meer lezen (109 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-JkAnIGQpvDk/Th8EghGJwzI/AAAAAAAAACI/QD4rxzBYDbM/w426-h240/Bear.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/112312612663275547305/albums/5722659461365543441/5722659461084983698</link><title>+Seren Matthews and I went to middle farm to see the animals and buy some meat! Talked to the butcher about making sausages and met this guy. http://goo.gl/uG8y6﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XuGuaimsvVc/T2r4dbx_sZI/AAAAAAAAaVQ/enkJmwHa0Cg/w426-h568/IMG_20120318_135148.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/108855200241623204226/albums/5742496489441380993/5742496490978659458</link><title>Maria and her chickens 
&lt;otherwise titled --a city girl tries going a little country in the name of science&gt; 

For a while now I have been intending to write about my chickens, but keep getting side tracked with other topics. Today, after a weekend in the sun at the beach, my brain is a fried so I can't think of anything to write about except my chickens. After months of clouds and rainy weather, apparently my body has started to mutate into something that can't tolerate too much sunlight. No wonder someone staged a serious of books about vampires living not far from Seattle. Hopefully, I am not morphing into a vampire and will get my sun tolerance back soon. 

Two years ago, my daughter's kindergarten class raised baby chickens as a science project. At the same time my local library had a class about raising chickens, that I decided to take out of interest. My own previous experience with birds was stealing a bunch of duck eggs when I was about 9 and taking care of them till they hatched in my bedroom closet. That is another long story in itself and I will save that for some other time. 

As an adult, I had little experience around animals outside my cat, and the weekly trips I would take to a local farm with my children to help them learn about animals. Sure, I had eaten eggs all my life and seen chickens at a distance as a tourist at various farms, but I had never really been close to or raised any form of live stalk myself. 

The idea of fresh eggs was so mesmerizing since I always purchased eggs at a local supermarket, the local farms had fresh eggs, but there was so much competition to buy them that I had maybe only been lucky once in my life. My eggs came from somewhere, the box said they were free range and organic but the whole process of how they came from a farm to my supermarket was a process I had no experience with. 

In fact I was so naive that I had no idea that chickens do not need to be around a rooster to lay eggs and most eggs are not even fertilized. I think the whole fertilization process was completely beyond me. I knew somehow baby chicks came into the world but the process was as mysterious as human reproduction was when I was 9 years old. So I decided for my scientific benefit as well as my children we would be raising chickens. In my enthusiasms I ordered 4 books on Amazon, diligently attended the chicken rearing class and then went to the local feed store to buy 6 chicks and about $300.00 worth of startup supplies. 

My first lesson in raising chickens was it was going to be expensive. Sure the chicks cost 5.00 each, but the cheapest chicken coop I eventually found was $600.00 and it turns out that was too small for my chickens so I had to invest another 1100.00 eventually to get a better coop. Still, the chicks were so cute and all the fresh, organic, nutritious eggs we would get would be so worth it. Did I mention we had to buy a heat lamp, a smaller cage for the chicks, food, medicines, scratch and the local feed store is a 45 minute drive from my house? So, slowly it starts to dawn on me that by raising my own chickens I am most certainly not going to save money on eggs, but there is the SCIENCE of it after all. 

What the science taught me was chicks grow really fast. Really, REALLY fast, and those cute little baby chicks get smelly, noisy and hungry in about two weeks time. The smell is so bad that as soon as you can you need to get those once cute little chicks that are slowly growing into &lt;del&gt;monsters&lt;/del&gt; chickens outside so you can breathe. 

At the point when the chicks no longer look cute is the point when your kids will lose interest in them. It will be cool for them to tell their friends they have chicks, but don't assume they will want to do any of the work involved when they are no longer cute and fluffy. But this is SCIENCE after all so I was determined to plow onward. 

My chickens grew up quickly and soon became a neighborhood fixture. They would follow me around when I walked, mostly because they learned that I was the one who fed them. This was the next thing I learned about chickens; they are smarter than you think. They knew who I was and while they weren't friendly to other members of the family they would come to me when I was around, some were even almost tame and would let me hold them. 

The next thing I learned about chickens was they are at the bottom of the food chain. No really, they are at the VERY bottom of the food chain. Also raccoons are incredibly smart. I have never lost a chicken so far except to an animal attack. Dogs will kill chickens so you have to make sure your chickens are kept safe from dogs, and raccoons not only love to eat chickens but are smart enough to figure out how to open any chicken coop that is not pad locked. RIP to a few chickens who had to die in order for me to learn that lesson well. Also rats will eat smaller chickens but when the chickens grow big enough that is no longer a concern. 

Cat's are scared of chickens. A chicken will show a cat who is boss if a cat tries anything and that cat will never forget. Cat's and chickens can also become friends as my cat has become friends with my chickens. 

The next thing I learned was that if you think you have a rooster, then don't doubt yourself it is a rooster. We bought sexed chicks so I assumed they were all hens but one of the hens sure seemed like a rooster. It turns out after she started crowing every morning and mounting the hens ever chance she got we decided she was either a very lesbian chicken or more likely a rooster. I will spare telling you what happened to that rooster, except to say it was before I was a vegan and roosters don't taste very good. 

That leads me to the next thing I learned, that roosters are very horney. My 5 hens were exhausted by the extracurricular activity of the rooster. A rooster also isn't polite, it doesn't matter how much the hen hates him and how exhausted he is, if he wants something he is going to get it. Also I learned how country kids probably don't need to wait till they are 9 to learn about the facts of life. "Mom, what is happening , what is that rooster doing? Is something you will have to be prepared to answer if you accidentally get a rooster in your brood. 

Also it is a lot of work to get eggs from your chickens, you have to feed them twice a day, clean them, protect them, remove lots of poop, drive to the feed store, restore the plants they decide to eat and make sure they always have clean fresh water. It is so much work, every time I see a cart of eggs now it is something I think about. Either that or the chickens are not treated in a humane manner and that is also worth thinking about when you crack that egg open for breakfast. 

So far I have no saved any money on eggs by having chickens, I also became a vegan so I am not really sure why we still have chickens besides that they are likeable pets. The oldest chicken we have is quite smart and very tame and will sit on the children's laps and let herself be petted. 
The chickens are a lot of work, and they poop a lot, so I really don't know why I have them now that I am vegan. I don't think I will get another flock when this one passes on to the other side. Now that dogs and raccoons no longer bother my chickens I am afraid I will have this set for a long time; not to mention that baby chicks are really cute and I was just at the feed store last week. Ahhhmmmm. 

Bellow is a picture my friend shot of my chickens following me around. The brown one is Rosabelle and she is our favorite chicken.﻿

Meer lezen (135 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-PdX10AcmHrE/T7FyIiy1zII/AAAAAAAAMSE/vHCCBmFhDVM/w426-h240/69540_146418535407623_72950_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/114529371273443966439/albums/5971837382249294929/5971837387166884098</link><title>Is Butter Secretly Ruining Your Health? 
BY ADMIN · JANUARY 22, 2014 
Growing up, butter was an absolute staple in my household. We thankfully never got into the margarine craze because my mother believed that butter was good for the brain. Turns out, she was right about that and scientists have now concluded that butter is actually good for you in other areas too. It’s high in a compound call CLA that protects you from tumor growth and cancer, is not inflammatory like man-made oils from corn, canola or soy, and provides a nice dose of Omega 3 fatty acids, if you get it from the right source. But finding the right source can be tricky given all the buzz words and fancy marketing these days. Choosing the wrong type of butter can secretly ruin your health without you even knowing it! Here’s a look at what’s really going on and how to choose the healthiest butter for you and your family. 

Beware of Monsanto Butter 
Slide1 

I call conventional butter “Monsanto Butter,” because it comes from cows fed almost entirely genetically engineered or GMO grains and Monsanto is the largest producer of GMOs. 

Conventionally raised cows are most commonly fed GMO corn and soy, however, some farmers fatten up their feed with additional sugar from GMO sugar beets and cottonseed. Cotton is the most toxic crop because it isn’t treated as a food crop but as a textile (it has less regulation.) And then conventional dairy cow feed is sometimes fortified with additional protein, Omega 3 fatty acids and CLA from GMO rapeseed (canola) because the cows are not getting these nutrients naturally from the grass. GMO alfalfa hay is also commonly fed to cows. So basically, conventionally raised cows are almost entirely getting their food from GMOs – food that was created in a laboratory, that hasn’t been tested long term, but has produced horrific results in several alarming animals studies. 

Over 49% of all GMO corn is fed to animals or livestock. Only 2% of the GMO soybeans grown are actually fed to humans, the other 98% get fed to animals. Those figures are pretty scary once you consider the astronomical amounts of herbicides being sprayed on these GMO crops and what they are doing to the increase cancer rates, harm the environment and ourselves. 

Land O’Lakes = Monsanto Butter 
Land O’ Lakes was a staple in my household growing up. We’d use the whipped butter like it was nobody’s business – my mom would use it on her infamous parathas (Indian stuffed flat bread), in countless desserts and to make homemade ghee. Once I found out what was really happening at Land O’Lakes, my Mom and I had a little chat. I explained to her that Land O’Lakes is owned by a pro-GMO company called Dean Foods. Land O’Lakes co-developed genetically engineered alfalfa, directly contributing to the GMO animal feed supply. I also explained that Land O’Lakes contributed nearly $100,000 to the “No on I-522 Lobby” – the bill to label GMOs in Washington State. This is all on top of the fact that Land O’Lakes is not organic, raises their cows with growth hormones linked to cancer, antibiotics and harmful pesticide ridden GMO feed. I told my Mom she has to stop buying Land O’Lakes if we are going to change this world! 

Knowing all these facts, plus the health risks of consuming GMOs, my Mom finally asked “what butter can I buy?” Well there are many brands out there that are light years ahead of Land O’Lakes. Here’s a Butter Buying Guide that will help you (and my Mama) navigate the butter aisle next time you hit the market: 

ButterChoices 

How to Choose The Most Nutritious Butter 
Organic - First and foremost, look for organic butter. This will ensure there are no growth hormones, antibiotics, harmful pesticides and GMOs being fed to the cows. Growth hormone or rbGH that is used to raise cows conventionally is linked to cancer and often accumulates in highest concentration in animal fat. One organic brand I’m suspicious of however, is Horizon, they are owned by Dean Foods (the same company that owns Land O’Lakes). The Cornucopia Institute has filed complaints for labeling their product organic while maintaining factory farm production methods. I won’t buy Horizon organic for that reason. 

Grass-fed - Grass-fed or pastured raised cows are going to be more nutritious than cows raised with grains. Remember, the highest amounts of the most beneficial CLA and Omega 3 fatty acids naturally come from grass-fed cows. Also grass-fed cows produce butter with 50 percent more vitamin A and E and 400 percent more beta carotene (which gives the grass-fed butter a deeper yellow color). 

Ghee - Ghee is clarified butter where all the proteins, milk solids and lactose is removed. This makes the butter more digestible, concentrated with nutrients and really great for immunity building. Ghee does not need to be refrigerated, it can stay on the counter for a few months without going bad. People with dairy allergies or sensitives often do ok consuming this type of butter. Pure Indian Foods, Purity Farms  and Ancient Organics have the best offerings in that they are both high quality, organic and grass-fed. 

In an ideal world, you would be able to find butter that is both organic, grass-fed and no additives like Organic Valley (in the green foil wrapper) , but sometimes that’s just not the case. In that circumstance, I would go for either an organic butter or grass-fed butter like Kerrygold (please note – Kerrygold uses some grains that could be GMOs a couple of months out of the year because grass doesn’t grow year round in Ireland – they admit that 3% of their feed could contain GMOs). Choosing regular organic butter will lessen your exposure to pesticides but will also provide less nutrition since the cows will mostly be fed organic grains vs. grass. Regardless, these choices are superior choices over conventional butter and both options (in light green on the chart above) will lessen your exposure to GMOs. 

Beware of butter mixes with labels like “with olive oil” – 9 times out of 10, these butters will have one or more GMO ingredients like soybean, corn or canola oil. These mixes may have questionable additives in them too – check the ingredient list just to be sure! 

Don’t Eat Butter? Here are some Vegan Substitutes - If you are vegan, skip all the “butter like” or fake butter spreads like Smart Balance that contain GMO oils, artificial ingredients made from petroleum and unnecessary preservatives. Instead, choose 100% coconut oil, olive oil, red palm oil (that is sustainably harvested from Ecuador and does not hurt the rainforest) or hemp oil instead. Also coconut manna, or butter works well too, when slightly heated it spreads just like butter. (These are also much healthier than organic spreads like Earth Balance that are usually a combo of inflammation causing oils). 

Slide3 

Sharing the truth is the first step in changing the food system. If you know someone who is buying Monsanto butter, please share this information with them. Our choices can really change the marketplace, make us healthier  and change companies decisions to use these unhealthy ingredients. 

\- See more at: http://asheepnomore.net/2014/01/22/butter-secretly-ruining-health/#sthash.RCfHbBvH.dpuf﻿

Meer lezen (138 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-BAFdM_8heSw/UuA6dqZ6oQI/AAAAAAABl5Y/yAOMPAVgkqo/w426-h320/Slide1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/117048832399386093907/albums/5755506723466080705/5755506723168636050</link><title>Buy selected Freedom Food labelled products in +Sainsbury's this Farm Animal Week (18 – 24 June) and they will donate 5p for every pack sold to the +RSPCA Official  to support its farm animal work. 

Also! The pic below﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BXSmmpOAiYQ/T9-q3ujWzJI/AAAAAAAAAxk/U1HPN90IK7Q/w426-h602/600960137.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7451-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/buy%20animal%20farm/photos/115576161671583167893/albums/5864875381306481057/5864875382206193778?authkey=CJfq1NjLz4L-PQ</link><title>#SMCH: As a so-called food, meat is simply one of the most unhealthy, poisonous, unhygienic items that could ever be ingested by humans. We should never eat meat at all if we love and cherish our health and our life. We will live longer without meat, healthier, wiser without meat. 
http://crisis2peace.org/book.php?wr_id=28 
\-- 

The Proper Way to Eat a Pig 

On a recent morning in Portland, Ore., Camas Davis was teaching nine high-school kids how to butcher a pig. A 17-year-old named Mady called dibs on the front trotter, slicing through the skin near the pig’s ankle, then using a hand saw to cut through the bone. Nathan, 15, moved up the leg and worked through the hock, while Karina, 16, eyed the shoulder. Pushing up the sleeves of her red cardigan, she placed her blade between the fifth and sixth ribs, scored the flesh, then gave the knife a long pull, separating the shoulder from the carcass, but leaving intact the coppa — a muscle around the pig’s neck — in case anyone wanted to roast it. 
The Best Cuts 

Graphic 
What Not to Waste 
Readers’ Comments 
Readers shared their thoughts on this article. 
Read All Comments (210) » 
The kids were wearing aprons over their jeans. When it wasn’t their turn to butcher, they gossiped and texted friends photos of the dead pig, which was splayed out on a jigsaw of white cutting boards, its head sitting nearby, gazing on; its eyelids had been sliced off during an inspection for parasites. On a counter, industrial plastic bins were marked: bellies, loin/chops, shoulders/roasts, hams, bones/trotters/hocks. The students took turns removing the pig’s feet and breaking the animal down into four “primals”: shoulder, loin, belly and ham. Then Davis stepped in to show them how to butcher it into the cuts they’d seen at the grocery store and the ones they hadn’t. She picked up a leg, peeling off the skin with her blade, removing the “H-bone,” and then turned it toward her students. “Instead of muscling through this,” she said, “I’m going to use the tip of my knife to feather through the fascia,” the pig’s connective tissue. Davis held the knife in a butcher’s grip and delicately separated the muscle groups to reveal a roast. “Now it’s your turn.” 

Butchery is a new course being offered by the Oregon Episcopal School, an independent preparatory academy that prides itself on “inquiry-based learning.” Each year, the week before spring break, called Winterim, is reserved for experimental education projects. Some students go dog-sledding in Minnesota. Others play Dungeons &amp; Dragons or opt for an intensive course in the art of hat-making. Recently, an English teacher at the school, Kara Tambellini, read an article about the Portland Meat Collective and proposed a course on butchery. 

And so Davis, who has taught butchery to mothers and young professionals, to beer brewers and bike messengers, but never to high schoolers, devised a weeklong curriculum that covered the basics. This included a field trip on a Friday, when she took the students to a local farm to meet and select a pig, whom they named Wilbur and then, realizing she was female, renamed Wilburess. 

The next Monday morning, the class met up with Wilburess again at a local slaughterhouse, along with her 30-year-old owner, Bubba King, who had a thick brown beard and bounced a 5-month-old baby named Ulysses on his hip. When the recession hit, King explained, he borrowed some farmland — though he had no previous farm experience — to raise pigs. He learned how to butcher them on YouTube. Eventually, he got in touch with Davis, who, through the Meat Collective, gave him a formal lesson. Now her students buy his hogs for their butchery courses. King sells them for $3.25 per pound of hanging weight, which is how much an animal weighs after it has been slaughtered, gutted and drained of its blood. Wilburess, at 171 pounds, earned him $536 — he gave the students a discount. 

In this farm-to-table era, community-supported-agriculture shares — in which families purchase farm goods through a weekly subscription — have become increasingly popular. Nowhere is that more true than in Portland, where people take their food ethics, among other things, very seriously. There is a sketch in the first episode of the IFC comedy “Portlandia” in which characters played by Fred Armisen and Carrie Brownstein persistently nudge their waitress for information about the chicken on the menu. After asking if the chicken was raised organically and about the size of its roaming area, they find out that the chicken was named Colin and that it grew up on a farm 30 miles outside Portland; later Armisen is handed the chicken’s citizenship papers. (The line between Portland and “Portlandia” often blurs; for example, Armisen gave the commencement address to Oregon Episcopal’s graduating class.) 

Six months before that episode was broadcast, I moved to Portland, and while I was unpacking boxes in my new house, a neighbor stopped by and asked me if I wanted to buy a cow. I went silent for a moment, then asked the only question that came to mind: “Where would I put it?” My neighbor, standing in my doorway wearing his bike helmet, handed me a brochure. “I found two people already, so you’d get one-fourth of the cow,” he said. He pointed to an address. “You can visit him here.” 

It’s not as easy to get farm-to-table meat, however, as it is rhubarb and pattypan squash. Meat regulations are strict, and they dictate that animals must be slaughtered and processed (gutted, cleaned and butchered) at a U.S.D.A.-approved facility before entering the commercial market. There is an exception: If no one is making a profit, and the animal is going to be used only to feed family and friends, it can be slaughtered and processed at the owner’s discretion. The loophole was probably intended for cattle ranchers, but city folks can use this exception to purchase a live animal (or a share of it) before it is killed. Meat C.S.A.’s are catching on throughout the country, and Portland — where its legal to have three or fewer ducks, chickens or pygmy goats on your property without a permit — is already three steps ahead. What better way to learn about the ethics of your meat than to slaughter and butcher it yourself? 

The Portland Meat Collective — a group of butchers and chefs that offers classes on meat production, butchery, cooking and, yes, slaughter — was founded by Davis, a self-described “meat thinker.” She challenges her students and the larger community to engage with all aspects of meat production, whether that means visiting animals at farms or learning the skills to put them on their plates. The collective gave its first butchery course in 2010 and now holds classes in commercial kitchens, charging $100 to $300 per class. In the last three years, it has educated more than 1,000 students. The collective plans to introduce a Kickstarter campaign to expand the model nationwide. They’re considering Seattle and Hood River, Ore., as test markets. 

As a result of being a nose-to-tail carnivore, Davis has been called everything from a killer to an anti-feminist by animal activists, who might be surprised to learn she once was a vegetarian herself. (When I asked her why she began eating meat again, she replied, “I was hungry.”) The organization that leased Davis a commercial kitchen for Winterim asked that we not mention its name, and when Davis initially visited the space, someone asked how she was going to contain the pig’s blood. “What blood?” she said, and the reply revealed that the owners thought she was going to walk a live pig through the front door and kill it in front of nine teenagers. This ignorance, Davis says, is telling of our relationship to the animals that we eat — most of us don’t know the difference between butchery and slaughter. 

Here’s how Wilburess actually died. At the slaughterhouse, she walked down a chute into a kill room where Latin dance music was playing. A man applied an electrical prong to the back of her head to stun her senseless. He sent another stun to her heart to induce cardiac arrest. Then he checked her eyes for rapid movements and, finding none, pierced her brachial artery. He moved her body into a vat of scalding water to loosen the hair follicles. Then she was placed on a table to be dehaired. A worker hung her body on a hook, eviscerated it, then cut it down the middle. The students watched it all. No one fainted. No one cried. (Though a few kids admitted to their teachers later that they were considerably shaken.) As for Davis, she said that the first time she witnessed a slaughter, she broke into tears, and nearly every time she visits a slaughterhouse, she gets choked up. 

The reasoning underlying the Portland Meat Collective, she says, is that by taking part in the process, we begin to think of how to use the animal differently. “Once you slaughter a pig, you dehair it, you butcher it, you wrap it and you put it in your freezer, it’s so much work you don’t want to waste it,” Davis says. “It’s special.” Two days after Wilburess’s slaughter, Davis cut off the pig’s head and started listing its possible uses. “Once I take the face off, there’s a lot I can do with this. I can make my jowl bacon. I can leave the face intact and make porchetta di testa. I can dry the pig ears and give them to a dog. I can make headcheese.” She pointed to the area just next to the jaw. “The more a muscle works, the tougher it is, the more flavorful it is. Imagine how much these worked — the cheeks!” The students watched in silence. “They’re delicious.” 

The first animal Davis ever slaughtered was a chicken. After that, she killed a rabbit. “I’ve never figured out how to fully articulate what happens,” she said. “I don’t feel guilty, and I don’t feel bad. It is a pure and intense experience, but it is the most complicated experience you can have in terms of living and dying.” 

The way the Portland Meat Collective teaches rabbit slaughter is by having a person sit in a chair with a rabbit at their feet and gently place a broomstick over its neck. When you pull the body, the stick breaks the rabbit’s neck. Sometimes, it goes badly. “This one guy pulled the body so hard, he ripped the head off,” Davis told me. “I came home from that class and curled up on a couch and didn’t move for a day.” In a separate incident last year, activists stole 18 rabbits from a breeder who supplies the Meat Collective. Among the group of stolen rabbits was a nursing mother, and because she’d gone missing, several 10-day-old rabbits died. Davis wrote an essay about the incident that was later adapted for the radio program “This American Life.” (Again the line between Portland and “Portlandia” blurred; it turns out one of the suspected rabbit thieves was an extra on the TV show.) 

As a kid, Davis hunted and fished with her family, and one summer she worked in an “intentional community,” where bakers consulted their astrological charts before baking bread. As an adult, after working at National Geographic Adventure and Saveur, she moved west in 2006 to become the food editor of Portland Monthly. There, Davis experienced — and later wrote an article about — “the tastiest cut of beef you’ve never heard of”: bavette. But when she set out to buy it, she was stymied. No butcher carried it or could even tell her where the cut was located on the cow. The chef at the restaurant where she first ate bavette couldn’t tell her exactly where on the animal it came from; nor could the guys at the meat shop, who mostly wielded their knives not to butcher an animal but to cut open boxes and pull out ready-made cuts. Eventually, she discovered that the bavette was located between the sirloin and the flank. It is known as “flap meat” in the U.S., and typically tossed into the container reserved for grind. 

In 2009, in search of a deeper understanding, Davis went to France to study with an American cooking teacher named Kate Hill and to serve as an apprentice with a family of butchers and farmers named the Chapolards. She doesn’t speak French, and the Chapolards didn’t speak English, so she learned their craft through risk and repetition. She made some costly mistakes, like the time they handed her what she thought was a shoulder primal, and she cubed and skewered it, only to realize it was actually a ham. “I basically just lost them hundreds of dollars,” she recalls. 

The Chapolards would say, “Why would you do this thing that’s not for beautiful, smart women?” It wouldn’t be the last time she ran up against this question, which often carries the implication that, given her relatively short apprenticeship in the world of butchery, she has traded on her looks to gain fame. She’s aware but not concerned about the focus on her unexpected appearance. “I don’t want to capitalize off it,” she says, “and I kind of do.” 

After a summer in the Chapolards’ cutting room, Davis returned to Portland and found a job at a specialty-foods store called Pastaworks, where she tried to bring European butchery to the meat counter. “Let’s not do individual pork chops,” she suggested. “Let’s put the whole loin in the case so it looks beautiful and we can cut individual chops.” But the loin was unrecognizable to her customers. “Is that tuna?” they asked. So later that year, she decided to start a school that would replicate her experience in France by purchasing whole animals from small farms and teaching people how to butcher them by hand. “If we gave people the opportunity to try and come up with an alternative system of meat production,” Davis once wrote in response to an online comment by a vegetarian, “we’d a) eat a lot less meat, and b) really dedicate ourselves to thinking about what it means to kill an animal for food, thereby c) causing us to recalibrate our respect for the animal world.” 

On the last day of butchery class, the students made sausages. They loaded a meat grinder with chunks of pork shoulder, fatback (the layer of hard fat used to make lard) and spices. The grinder returned the pork to the students in ribbons, which they packed into the chamber of a sausage stuffer. Each student fit intestinal casings onto a nozzle and churned a crank with one hand while using the other to coax the cased sausage into a spiral. 

I asked Alex, a 17-year-old wearing a fencing-team jacket, how it felt to make sausage out of a pig he knew by name. 

“I hate the feeling of raw meat,” he said. 

“Then why’d you take this class?” asked Sean, a 17-year-old with a side interest in baking cheesecake. 

“I felt like I had to know,” Alex replied. 

Another student, Sophia, 19, who showed promising knife skills throughout the week, said that in the dorms, her butchery lessons hadn’t been so well received. “Everyday someone asks, ‘What did you kill today?’ ” 

“It’s a slow education,” Davis said of teaching people the origin of their food. She has received requests from all over the country asking her to start meat collectives in other states. “Here, it’s been pretty easy to create an alternate economy,” she says, estimating that about one-third of her students go on to purchase meat directly from farmers. But she also points out that in Portland, they’re lucky to be so close to sources of livestock. “We have the Willamette Valley and eastern Oregon that’s full of great small farmers.” Other cities are not so connected, physically and otherwise, to local agriculture. “I had a woman who wanted to start one in Baltimore, and I was like, ‘How far away is a good farm, whatever that means to you?’ ” The woman took her best guess. “She said, ‘I don’t know, 500 miles or something?’ ” 

Once the sausages were made, the class poached them, then browned them on a flattop griddle, then arranged them around the edge of a ceramic platter piled with green lentils. I wondered if the students would suddenly balk, preoccupied with the knowledge that, after days of butchering, they were about to eat an animal they’d once seen alive. 

When they sat down at the table, they didn’t even wait to pass the platter. They reached over one another, spooning heaping servings onto their plates. They scarfed it down and fought over the last links. 

Marnie Hanel is a journalist based in Portland, Ore. She contributes to The One-Page Magazine. 

http://www.nytimes.com/2013/04/07/magazine/the-proper-way-to-eat-a-pig.html?pagewanted=all&amp;_r=2&amp; ﻿

Meer lezen (296 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7451_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-vEFSPvIgPpc/UWQ5FjBVYHI/AAAAAAAATOE/qr3f8DsHvJE/w426-h461/8.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>