<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:26:51" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/111048209307335934360/albums/5853477304166145937/5853477304905789906?authkey=CLjgw5CB8J7tFA</link><title>Should the Arizona Game and Fish Commission restrict bow-hunting in the McDowell Sonoran Preserve and nearby land? http://bit.ly/ZA9Arl 

1\. Yes — there are risks to hikers, plus impacts on wildlife. 
2\. No — studies show the deer and javelina population to be 'stable.' 
3\. Bow hunting?! I had no idea that was even permitted.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-WN4hjfeyGYk/UTu6mIO4cdI/AAAAAAAAG-0/fEgM8lCFsU0/s426/M11_CIFR8bff3bf11e2fa9562d021b4b40d03e15.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/117655050815225660801/albums/5832308906396424369/5832308906352864402?authkey=CNauos7PqoCjjAE</link><title>A reminder from the AZ Game &amp; Fish Department: always boat sober. http://bit.ly/W6n9Lp﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-qoODQSeZyLY/UPCGDKeCbJI/AAAAAAAAAGg/2WFkU0P0TX0/w426-h240/690b8b8e-218b-4338-9f11-443ce095f7f5</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/113931668540956859528/albums/5996995797449240513/5996995797084220018</link><title>Thanks to Arizona Game and Fish Dept. for hosting the Outdoor Festival this past weekend. This was Trent's first fishing trip and now he's hooked (pun intended). I heard that the northern Arizona lakes are being stocked so I need to get him a pole. #Arizona  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-K3DnMFxH8DE/Uzmb52y3KnI/AAAAAAAABac/DfDUDQ8bHjY/w426-h757/20140329_103646.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/102842636515455637809/albums/5949604431130899377/5949604440671397506</link><title>Today the family and I went to Arizona Game and Fish's Adobe Mountain Wildlife Center for their annual open house. There were some beautiful animals out visiting people and I met this wonderful barn owl. The volunteers of AMWC are doing amazing work rehabilitating and releasing animals. 
#amwc  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-x5HFKcVEVM8/UpE9t2hOJoI/AAAAAAAAD1Q/GOGBLTvcQn4/w426-h284/IMG_4453.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/107863598336667519706/albums/5926922068193113281/5926922072811271282?authkey=CPXY2tC-oO3tIw&amp;sqi=102178950756661517066&amp;sqsi=99218f2b-c022-4cd2-8538-68c4d9c07ef7</link><title>#QRCodes  I plan to use QR codes in my wildlife identification unit. Students will scan the codes and it will take them to a link from the AZ Game and Fish website. Some of the QR codes will take them to text and some will take them to videos.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-flpZISWwS4o/UkCoORlWdHI/AAAAAAAAADo/OyT5CjhTx98/w426-h320/QR+Codes+Assignment.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/118059056694971337419/albums/5817142983123202753/5817142981591570610</link><title>As follow up to my previous post, regarding the bighorn sheep rock art panel, I visited the office of Arizona Game and Fish to inquire about their knowledge of Bighorn Sheep living on the San Francisco Peaks, now or in the past. I was informed, "There is no evidence of the Bighorn living on these mountains." I accepted this and wondered how my indigenous friends of over 1000 years ago knew of them. Then this summer I found this, from a living animal. Now what do I do?  :-)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_06_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-t-NyDfcL4IM/ULqkuKFsGLI/AAAAAAAAArQ/XsV-Tz-M5Vc/w426-h320/G_0017_sheath.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/106950193300444716625/albums/5738054458893886273/5738054457916729794</link><title>You may have a difficult time seeing him but there is a little coyote standing near the opening in the wall (northwest corner of 51st Ave &amp; Baseline in Laveen, behind Blockbuster &amp; Frys) . He shouldn't be out at this time of day (mid afternoon) and he was paying way too much attention to me (I was on my bike). His erratic behavior suggests that he is sick -- and possibly dangerous. I called animal control which transferred me to the Arizona Dept of Game and Fish. When their phone maze didn't work right I called the Phoenix PD non-emergency number. Through them I ended up back at the game and fish number -- got the run around there until I finally got a dispatcher who is going to log the incident for the urban wildlife specialist. I was hoping they might actually send someone out since the poor little guy seems distressed. I'm sure they'd like to if they had the budget.﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-tksjz1ZNoME/T6GqIMH5KcI/AAAAAAAALG8/ugkdx1OqdVQ/w426-h320/2012-05-02%2B14.00.45.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/111059520534674643970/albums/5782713309661926545/5782713312386372194</link><title>This video from the 1970s, was created by the Arizona Game and Fish Department and stars John Wayne. It is about FIREARMS SAFETY and is a must view if you have children you want to introduce to the shooting sports. ENJOY.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-pO7flofTZNM/UEBTHpa2UmI/AAAAAAAAAFQ/8Pk-D8BBi-s/w426-h320/AzFandG-with-John-Wayne.mp4</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/101970734713653835322/albums/5773680662430206833/5773680662678917762</link><title>As promised for teachers: here is a second helpful wolf-related educational resource that may help teachers enhance instruction in a manner that addresses national common core standards. 

Today's recommendation is based on an educational project produced by the Arizona Game and Fish Department and addresses the lobo. 

Students conduct online research about the Arizona-New Mexico wolf re-introd 
uction program. They then write a persuasive essay about their stand on the program and email it to the Game and Fish program director. Students are encouraged to come up with a solutions based on internet research. Students can also to make a presentation, i.e. PowerPoint, to go along with the essay. 

RECOMMENDED RESOURCES: 
Arizona Fish and Game: http://www.azgfd.gov/i_e/ee/lessons/wolves/intro.htm 

Mexican gray wolves -﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-veIAanyLid0/UCA7-PGE0oI/AAAAAAAABLU/9xsN0nKyQp4/w426-h283/405491_419503964752692_727756487_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7452-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/arizona%20game%20and%20fish%20homepage/photos/101151920895232897032/albums/5927654358164023057/5927654361567855330</link><title>We've got some WILD conservation news this Wild Wednesday! 
This week Arizona Game and Fish was on hand at the +Phoenix Zoo to pick up 1,246 Chiricahua leopard frogs and tadpoles as part of the Zoo's head start program. These frogs and tadpoles will be released in designated areas near the Mogollon Rim in Arizona. To date the Phoenix Zoo has raised and released a total of 18,236 head-started leopard frogs into the wild since the program first began in 1995! 

The Chiricahua leopard frog is currently listed as threatened under the Endangered Species Act. By releasing a large number of animals back into the wild we are able to greatly increase the chance that more will survive to adulthood and reproduce as well as preserving valuable genes. To learn more about how the Phoenix Zoo is working to save this important local species and how you can get involved, please visit our new local conservation page: http://phoenixzoo.org/conservation/local-conservation/chiricahua-leopard-frog/﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7452_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-iPmDKR6pmPM/UkNCPFyMAuI/AAAAAAAAEbk/7cmU2zUA1ok/w426-h237/09-25-13-Conservation.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>