<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:39:15" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/113054634252590086817/albums/5976195519830664417/5976195525693566466</link><title>Little kids, little ears, big, BAD lyrics? What's a parent to do? Check out the solution Bennett Cunningham Michael Spann came up with!! 

Raising Gaybies: 
The Music Man 

My husband hates Barney – and all the songs that emanate from that purple dinosaur’s month. If I hear Baby Beluga one more time, I am going to smash the radio. I know kids love music, but at some point, I want my cool music back. I really want to listen to “my” music when the kids are in the car. 
\- See more at: http://www.goodenoughmother.com/2014/02/raising-gaybies-music-man/#sthash.s7WWy5r3.dpuf﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-YHzIRM-PGzk/Uu-2Ktk-bgI/AAAAAAAAC9k/NEhXDqlK2bs/w426-h545/KinkyBoots-800x1024.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/109267076309480704067/albums/5882619546384889473/5882619548165898018?authkey=CNPul4_BrMCe0wE&amp;sqi=110720752772835712476&amp;sqsi=6037d437-a53f-402e-97c6-304d238e67e2</link><title>Hmmm Nice...Jazz cats 
Jazz fusion or Jazz rock has much in common with Prog. If may not have concept based lyrics but it is about the music man. Romantic Warrior by Return to Forever sits on top of the Jazz fusion mountain. 

The line up includes Chick Corea, Stanley Clarke, Lenny White and Al Di Meola. With song titles such as 'Duel of the Jester and the Tyrant (Part 1 and Part 2) - which is as it suggests is a musical battle between the players, the album is filled with really good tunes. 

The photo is of the Jap remaster. A remixed version is available on the Return to forever 2CD anthology. Phil﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ynKjV7XeweA/UaNDT8UyfyI/AAAAAAAABbI/8CzHCR3xr3I/w426-h284/returntoforever.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/115855634443584173769/albums/5769488746698183777/5769488748176611522</link><title>I once wrote lyrics to a medley of songs from South Pacific for my sorority..... only problem was, none of the girls knew the musical or the music!!!! 

South Pacific is a musical with music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II and book by Hammerstein and Joshua Logan. The plot draws from James A. Michener's Pulitzer Prize-winning 1947 book Tales of the South Pacific, combining elements of several of the stories in that book. The musical centers on an American nurse stationed at a U.S. Naval base during World War II who falls in love with an expatriate French plantation owner but struggles to accept his mixed-race children. A second romance concerns a U.S. lieutenant who falls in love with a young Asian woman. The issue of racial prejudice is candidly explored throughout the musical, most pointedly in the song, "You've Got to Be Carefully Taught". 

South Pacific is considered to be one of the greatest Broadway musicals. The musical premiered in 1949 and won the Pulitzer Prize for Drama in 1950. Several of its songs, including "Bali Ha'i", "I'm Gonna Wash That Man Right Outa My Hair", "Some Enchanted Evening", "Happy Talk", "Younger than Springtime" and "I'm in Love with a Wonderful Guy", have become popular standards. The Broadway production won ten Tony Awards, including Best Musical, Best Score and Best Libretto, and it is the only musical production ever to have won all four Tony Awards for acting. The show was a critical and box office hit and has since enjoyed many successful revivals and tours, spawning a 1958 film and other adaptations. The 2008 Broadway revival was a strong success, winning seven Tonys including Best Musical Revival. 

[source: Wikipedia]﻿

Meer lezen (28 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-qgZp2TJO_Bk/UBFXcsquGMI/AAAAAAAABxs/2Pk7AnuIFXo/s426/south-pacific-7.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/105712264910232138424/albums/5739442840480535857/5739442838365557026</link><title>Happy Birthday #bobseger 
"Turn The Page" 

On a long and lonesome highway, east of Omaha 
You can listen to the engine moanin' out it's one note song 
You can think about the woman, or the girl you knew the night before 
But your thoughts will soon be wandering, the way they always do 
When you're riding sixteen hours and there's nothing there to do 
And you don't feel much like riding, you just wish the trip was through 

Here I am, on the road again 
There I am, on the stage 
Here I go, playing star again 
There I go, turn the page 

Well you walk into a restaurant all strung out from the road 
And you feel the eyes upon you as you're shaking off the cold 
You pretend it doesn't bother you, but you just want to explode 

Most times you can't hear 'em talk, other times you can 
All the same old cliche's, is it woman is it man? 
You always seem outnumbered, so you don't dare make a stand 

Here I am, on the road again 
There I am, on the stage 
Here I go, playing star again 
There I go, turn the page 

Out there in the spotlight you're a million miles away 
Every ounce of energy, you try to give away 
As the sweat pours out your body like the music that you play 

Later in the evening as you lie awake in bed 
With the echoes from the amplifiers ringin' in your head 
You smoke the days last cigarette, remembering what she said 

Here I am, on the road again 
There I am, up on the stage 
Here I go, playing star again 
There I go, turn the page 

Here I am, on the road again 
There I am, on the stage yeah 
Here I go, playing star again 
There I go, there I go #lyrics #music﻿

Meer lezen (42 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-3XXpTKdE25w/T6aY2kVwUSI/AAAAAAAAA_E/ZqX7Lu0XaQw/s426/backin72.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/114692719232473978721/albums/5893778961003319105/5893778963730210946?authkey=CLrf682X3tmMtQE</link><title>Huntington Playhouse presents the regional premiere of 
"9 to 5: The Musical" 
Come see me and this fabulous cast! 

July 11 at 7:30pm until August 4 at 6:00pm 
Showtimes: Thurs: 7:30pm; Fri/Sat 8pm; Sun: 2pm 

Music and Lyrics by Dolly Parton 
Book by Patricia Resnick 
Based on the 20th Century Fox Picture 

Director: Tom Meyrose 
Musical Director: Kira Seaton 
Choreographer: Jessica Atwood 

9 TO 5: THE MUSICAL, with music and lyrics by Dolly Parton and book by Patricia Resnick, is based on the 1980 hit movie Nine to Five. 

Pushed to the boiling point by their boss, three female co-workers concoct a plan to get even with the sexist, egotistical, lying, hypocritical bigot they call their boss. They conspire to take control of their company and learn there's nothing they can't do -- even in a man's world. Set in the late 1970s, 9 TO 5: THE MUSICAL is a hilarious story of friendship and revenge in the Rolodex era. Outrageous, thought-provoking, and even a little romantic, 9 TO 5: THE MUSICAL is about teaming up and taking care of business. 
Co-sponsored by Westlake Village Retirement Community 
{Special Box} 

TICKETS ON SALE NOW! 
Box Office: 440-871-8333 
Adults: $20; Seniors: $18; Students: $10﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_05_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-YjfLppuPznE/Ucrova3PIII/AAAAAAAABlo/rZCT41L8ZS4/w426-h237/9%2Bto%2B5.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/105712264910232138424/albums/5738899158211911601/5738899158313503074</link><title>+Beastie Boys 
in memory of #mca 
"Shadrach" 

Riddle me this brother can you handle it 
Your style to my style you can't hold a candle to it 
Equinox symmetry and the balance is right 
Smokin' and drinkin' on a Tuesday night 
It's not how you play the game it's how you win it 
I cheat and steal and sin and I'm a cynic 
For those about to rock we salute you 
The dirty thoughts for dirty minds we contribute to 
I once was lost but now I'm found 
The music washes over and you're one with the sound 
Who shall inherit the earth the meek shall 
I think I'm starting to peak now Al 
And then the man upstairs well I hope that he cares 
If I had a penny for my thoughts I'd be a millionaire 
We're just 3 M.C.'s and we're on the go 
SHADRACH MESACH ABEDNAGO 

Only 24 hours in a day 
Only 12 notes a man can play 
Music for all and not just one people 
And now we're gonna bust with the Putney Swope sequel 
More Adidas sneakers that a plumber got pliers 
Got more suites that Jacoby &amp; Meyers 
If not for my vices my bugged out desires 
My year would be good just like Goodyear's tires 
So I'm out pickin' pockets at the Atlantic Antic 
And nobody wants to hear you cause your rhymes are so frantic 
I mix business with pleasure way too much 
I mean wine and women and song and such 
I don't get blue I gotta mean red streak 
You don't pay the band your friends and that's weak 
Get even like Steven like pulling a Rambo 
SHADRACH MESACH ABEDNAGO 

Steal from the rich and I'm out robbing banks 
Give to the poor and I always give thanks 
Got more stories that J.D. got Salinger 
I hold the title and you are the challenger 
I've got money like Charles Dickens 
Got the girlies in the Coupe like the Colonel's got the chickens 
Always go out dapper like Harry S. Truman 
I'm madder than Mad's Alfred E. Newman 
Never gonna let them say that I don't love you 

My noggin is hoggin all kinds of thoughts 
Adam Yoggin is Yauch and he's rockin of course 
Smoke the holy chalice got my own religion 
Rally round the stage and check the funky dope musicians 
Jerry Lee Swaggert or Jerry Lee Falwell 
You love Mario Andretti cause he always drives his car well 
Vicious circle of reality since the day you were born 
And we love the hot butter on what the popcorn 
Sippin on wine and mackin 
Rockin on the stage with all the hands clappin 
Ride the wave of fate it don't ride me 
Being very proud to be an M.C. 
And the man upstairs I hope that he cares 
If I had a penny for my thoughts I'd be a millionaire 
Amps and crossovers under my rear hood 
The bass is bumpin from the back of my Fleetwood 
They tell us what to do hell no 
SHADRACH MESACH ABEDNAGO 
#lyrics #music #hiphop #ripmca﻿

Meer lezen (63 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-GJOt7tVU7go/T6SqYOUQiWI/AAAAAAAAA-Y/iJc2O78f-A4/s426/paulsboutique.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/101983474019961328651/albums/5683911908431080209/5683911908888473618</link><title>ON THIS DATE (39 YEARS AGO) 
December 8, 1972 – Marvin Gaye: Trouble Man is released. 
# ALL THINGS MUSIC PLUS+ 4/5 
# Allmusic 3.5/5 
# Rolling Stone (see original review below) 

Trouble Man is a soundtrack album by Marvin Gaye, released December 8, 1972 on Motown-subsidiary label Tamla Records. As the soundtrack to the 1972 blaxploitation film of the same name, the Trouble Man soundtrack was a more contemporary move for Gaye, following his landmark politically-charged album What's Going On. 

Fresh off the success of his classic 1971 album, What's Going On, Gaye was intrigued by Hollywood. Gaye had acted in two films, The Ballad of Andy Crocker and Chrome and Hot Leather. The singer moved to Los Angeles in 1972 after he accepted the offer to do a soundtrack album. 

Like Isaac Hayes and Curtis Mayfield, Gaye took to recording a soundtrack for a blaxploitation film. Trouble Man, a thriller based in the ghetto, was made solely for the soundtrack Gaye composed and produced himself. Unlike Super Fly and Shaft, the soundtrack to Trouble Man does not feature love songs; except for a few vocal jabs by Gaye, it is made up entirely of instrumental pieces. 

Critics deemed Trouble Man on par with Hayes and Mayfield's albums. Gaye was soon followed by other contemporaries including James Brown (Black Caesar), Willie Hutch (The Mack; Foxy Brown) and Barry White (The Together Brothers). 

ORIGINAL ROLLING STONE REVIEW 
Even when a movie soundtrack isn't so awful you'd just as soon throw it down the stairs, it very rarely achieves anything beyond a sort of banal, predictable mood music: a little suspense, a little drama, an ooze of romance, maybe a brisk driving-in-the-car-to-possible danger track counterpointed with a lighter, romantic-leads-take-a-walk sequence—all compressed, like a week's worth of garbage, for one tight, bright under-the-credits Main Theme. Altogether, it's about as creative as an hour of elevator muzak and only slightly more bearable. 

The score to Shaft took some steps out of this particular mire, especially with that gorgeously gritty title song, but Isaac Hayes' inclination toward the grossest sort of movie music stopped the whole thing dead. Curtis Mayfield moved even further away from soundtrack conventions with his music for Superfly, a track of songs and music which commented upon rather than merely illustrated the film's action. Mayfield didn't restrict his lyrics to the "theme" or title song and kept his score relatively free of genre cliche, so the music stands quite successfully free of the movie. 

Marvin Gaye's work for Trouble Man (yet another Shaft-style black film, this one dropped from sight soon after its release) falls somewhere between that of Hayes and Mayfield. He lacks the Hayes double-punch but avoids his heavy-handedness. While there's no attempt to make a song-score like that of Superfly—"Trouble Man," the title song, is practically the only cut with lyrics and even these are spare—Gaye, like Mayfield, has created a score strong enough to be completely independent of the film. It's not a lot of fluff wrapped around some slick images and obvious themes; mostly, it's sweet and churning jazz that abstracts the action rather than decorating or interpreting it. 

Gaye's first album since his surprising and innovative What's Goin' On more than a year ago, Trouble Man doesn't take his music a whole lot further and certainly sidesteps the problem of how to follow up a sweeping life statement—aha! Just take this movie assignment and make no personal statement at all. Yet it's no throwaway. Most of the music carries on in a similar vein from What's Goin' On, although here it's a little more hard-edged (heavy drum punctuation, sharp horns and a staccato of hand-clapping or tambourines predominate) and at times self-consciously dramatic. The "Main Theme" is handsome if slightly overdrawn; I wouldn't miss the strings if they were cut from the arrangement, however. "'T' Plays It Cool" is more successful and gripping: hard drumming, a Moog line and energetic sax work intertwining like hot electric wires over a sweet, almost mournful piano and light horns. 

Much of the other material is moody and more reminiscent of Gaye's "Mercy, Mercy Me" or "Save The Children," with Marvin singing a few lines of lyrics or scatting in that strangely ethereal voice of his. "Trouble Man" is the only complete song here, Gaye's vocal gliding gracefully, supercool, or grabbing quickly at lines like a black-gloved fist, embodying the slick, fast mood of Mister "T." Gaye handles it all with ease and Trouble Man is surely one of the most attractive and listenable of the recent picture soundtracks, but it only stalls the question of what Marvin Gaye will do after What's Goin' On. A stylish way of stalling, yes, but it's still your move, Marvin. 
~ VINCE ALETTI, March 1, 1973 

TRACKS: 
All songs written by Marvin Gaye. 
"Main Theme From Trouble Man (2)" – 2:30 
"'T' Plays It Cool" – 4:27 
"Poor Abbey Walsh" – 4:13 
"The Break In (Police Shoot Big)" – 1:57 
"Cleo's Apartment" – 2:10 
"Trouble Man" – 3:49 
"Theme From Trouble Man" – 2:01 
"'T' Stands For Trouble" – 4:48 
"Main Theme From Trouble Man (1)" – 3:52 
"Life is a Gamble" – 2:32 
"Deep in It" – 1:25 
"Don't Mess with Mister 'T'" – 3:04 
"There Goes Mister 'T'" – 1:37﻿

Meer lezen (102 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-JyjIAzDdAYI/TuFPxDfo8BI/AAAAAAAAB4g/RCOx1Ma2DE8/w426-h425/Marvintrouble.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/114464945046720636067/albums/5691079849252914065/5691079847888463890</link><title>anybody watched DON2 yet??? 
what are you waiting for man&gt;&gt;&gt;go and watch it as soon as possible... 
great movie,,superb story,,mind blowing action,,amazing suspense,thrill,and mystery,,brilliant acting by every single character present in the movie,, very good,attractive,and eye catching appearances of SHAHRUKH and HRITHIK(playing a chameo),,and i am sure that you will leave the movie with a 4-1/2 to 5 rating!! 
$oh,i'm damn sure about this!$ 
the most most amazing things about the movie that freezes your eyes upon the screen are:- 
1\. FARHAN AKHTAR's DIRECTION. 
-giving the movie the magic that holds breath of you is done by the direction 
of farhan akhtar....ohh man ,,i mean,,what a damn hot screenplay,background 
music,and the stunts,and blasts,and BOOM aND BAMm!!! so hot!!! 
2\. ATTITUDE OF THE DON. 
-the dialogues,the expressions,the action,the stunts,the planning and the 
romantic scenes given by SRK are fabulous,makes you whistle very loud! 
3\. BETTER DEAL THAN BODYGUARD. 
-whatever bodyguard was having---in my opinion was a bullshit story of 70's,, 
totally impractical stunts,,some time-wasting extras and much more! 
the good thing was that about SALMAN's ACTING!! 
i really appreciate the full dedication of SALLU towards the decent character 
played by him(not the tough one). 
and the other thing was that the music and lyrics and dialogues in the movie. 
those were the things that does all about the movie and leaving it by a rating of 
not more than 3 stars! 
$# but DON2 has it all#$ 
SO.go and watch it my dear friends! 
this is the thing not to miss before 2012 comes! 
[give your opinions too below...and plus1] 
thank you all for your attention towards my article!... 
wish you all a $VERY HAPPY NEW YEAR$﻿

Meer lezen (37 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-o1Cd1JHxXfE/TvrG-BHGqBI/AAAAAAAAAA0/l3ZO0nTpUjo/w426-h631/Don2new.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/105712264910232138424/albums/5739797792953639665/5739797793376618034</link><title>#mumfordandsons 
"Little Lion Man" 

Weep for yourself, my man, 
You'll never be what is in your heart 
Weep, little lion man, 
You're not as brave as you were at the start 
Rate yourself and rake yourself 
Take all the courage you have left 
Wasted on fixing all the problems that you made in your own head 

But it was not your fault but mine 
And it was your heart on the line 
I really fucked it up this time 
Didn't I, my dear? 
Didn't I, my dear? 

Tremble for yourself, my man, 
You know that you have seen this all before 
Tremble, little lion man, 
You'll never settle any of your scores 
Your grace is wasted in your face, 
Your boldness stands alone among the wreck 
Now learn from your mother or else spend your days biting your own neck 

But it was not your fault but mine 
And it was your heart on the line 
I really fucked it up this time 
Didn't I, my dear? 

But it was not your fault but mine 
And it was your heart on the line 
I really fucked it up this time 
Didn't I, my dear? 
Didn't I, my dear? 

[harmonizing] 

But it was not your fault but mine 
And it was your heart on the line 
I really fucked it up this time 
Didn't I, my dear? 

But it was not your fault but mine 
And it was your heart on the line 
I really fucked it up this time 
Didn't I, my dear? 
Didn't I, my dear? 
+Mumford and Sons Fan Page #lyrics #music﻿

Meer lezen (46 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-r2pABRo7f-Q/T6fbrqzIxjI/AAAAAAAABBg/VGTApivMUAo/s426/sighnomore.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7457-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/the%20music%20man%20lyrics/photos/105712264910232138424/albums/5739835331366759313/5739835337071674994</link><title>#thewho 
"Behind Blue Eyes" 

No one knows what it's like 
To be the bad man 
To be the sad man 
Behind blue eyes 

No one knows what it's like 
To be hated 
To be fated 
To telling only lies 

But my dreams 
They aren't as empty 
As my conscience seems to be 

I have hours, only lonely 
My love is vengeance 
That's never free 

No one knows what it's like 
To feel these feelings 
Like I do 
And I blame you 

No one bites back as hard 
On their anger 
None of my pain and woe 
Can show through 

But my dreams 
They aren't as empty 
As my conscience seems to be 

I have hours, only lonely 
My love is vengeance 
That's never free 

When my fist clenches, crack it open 
Before I use it and lose my cool 
When I smile, tell me some bad news 
Before I laugh and act like a fool 

If I swallow anything evil 
Put your finger down my throat 
If I shiver, please give me a blanket 
Keep me warm, let me wear your coat 

No one knows what it's like 
To be the bad man 
To be the sad man 
Behind blue eyes 
#lyrics #music﻿

Meer lezen (50 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7457_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-h5dC4ki5OTY/T6f90_9kRnI/AAAAAAAABCI/UsE-vP8gP4c/s426/whosnext.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>