<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7459">little johnny jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:41:48" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/102223619266508824486/albums/5803245975560618241/5803245974405851282</link><title>Doing the chores #Jokes #Humor 

Little johnny comes down for breakfast, since they live on a farm, his mother asks him if he has done his chores."Not yet," said the little johnny. His mother tells him he can't have any breakfast until he does his chores. 

Well he's p!ssed off, so he goes to feed the chickens and he kicks a chicken. He goes off to feed the cows and he kicks a cow. Then he goes to feed the pigs and he kicks a pig. 

He goes back in for breakfast and his mother gives him a bowl of dry cereal. "How come I don't get any eggs and bacon? Why don't I have any milk on my cereal?" he asks. 

"Well" his mother says "I saw you kick the chicken so you don't get any eggs for a week. I saw you kick the pig so you don't get any bacon for a week either. I also saw you kick the cow, so for a week you aren't getting any milk". 

Just then his father comes down for breakfast and kicks the cat as he is walking into the kitchen. Little johnny looks up at his mother and with a smile says, "Are you going to tell him or should I?" 

:-) ﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_01_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-3emNIW08z4M/UIlFd4CtKJI/AAAAAAAAl6k/lGVi9z6WoYo/w426-h411/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/102223619266508824486/albums/5819323636262779393/5819323634969222114?authkey=CO75ip6t2KGCywE</link><title>WORMS #Jokes #fridayfunposts 

Little Johnny watched the science teacher start the experiment with the worms. Four worms were placed into four separate jars. 

The first worm was put into a jar of alcohol 
The second worm was put into a jar of cigarette smoke. 
The third worm was put into a jar of sperm. 
The fourth worm was put into a jar of soil. 

After one day, these were the results: 
The first worm in alcohol - dead. 
Second worm in cigarette smoke - dead. 
Third worm in sperm - dead. 
Fourth worm in soil - alive. 

So the Science teacher asked the class - "What can you learn from this experiment." 

Little Johnny quickly raised his hand and said - "As long as you drink, smoke and have sex, you won't have worms." 

:-) ﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_02_thumb.gif">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-3ui9fxFj0os/UMJkA49gG-I/AAAAAAAATTo/JYv5OYN8N_U/s426/07-12-12%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/102223619266508824486/albums/5789496741402329057/5789496745529535858</link><title>Confusing #Jokes   #Humor 

Little Johnny came home from school with a note from his teacher saying that Johnny was having trouble telling the difference between boys and girls, and would his mother please sit down and have a talk with Johnny about this. So Johnny's mother takes him quietly by the hand upstairs to her bedroom, and closes the door. 

"First, Johnny, I want you to take off my blouse", she said, so Johnny unbuttons her blouse and takes it off. 

"O.K., now take off my skirt", and he takes off her skirt. "Now take off my bra", which he does. 

"And now, Johnny, please take off my panties". Johnny finishes removing these too. 

His mother then says, "Johnny, please don't wear any of my clothes to school anymore!"﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-LBrhs74ot1Q/UFhsnbGRbXI/AAAAAAAAKas/iUWQExWGUto/w426-h240/Little_Johnny_The_Movie_008-1024x576.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/111139905254421432447/albums/5764931852634541825/5764931855792447730</link><title>Back to School Joke: 

Summer vacation was over and Little Johnny returned back to school. 

Only two days later his teacher phoned his mother to tell her that he was misbehaving. 

"Wait a minute," she said. "I had Johnny with me for three months and I never called you once when he misbehaved!; couldn't you show me the same courtesy?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-kIj_g5rW9J4/UAEm-prXoPI/AAAAAAAAAHw/vwJ0AfF14Xw/w426-h415/246880_10150218678472611_3365066_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/113467079318634670629/albums/5949761651490750225/5961916168539523522?sqi=117250769975254574948&amp;sqsi=e254c946-d8bc-4f58-ae7c-d00d187a940e</link><title>Little Johnny Story — funny jokes short one liners - http://www.myfunjokes.com/funny-sms/little-johnny-story-funny-jokes-short-one-liners/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XxfYXEzK-AM/Urz7Ku50ycI/AAAAAAAAP1o/Lm8SRk8xXLE/w426-h423/Little-Johnny-Story-sms.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/115997114756428816858/albums/5944394712375734161/5944394714525829234</link><title>The BEST Little Johnny joke I have ever heard! 

                            The kids filed into class Monday morning. They were all very excited.. 
                            Their weekend assignment was to sell something, then give a talk on 
                            salesmanship. 
                            Little Sally led off. "I sold Girl Scout cookies and I made $30" she said proudly, 
                            "My sales approach was to appeal to the customer's civil spirit and 
                            I credit that approach for my obvious success." 

                            "Very good", said the teacher. 

                            Little Debbie was next. "I sold magazines" she said, "I made $45 and 
                            I explained to everyone that magazines would keep them up on current events." 
                            "Very good, Debbie", said the teacher. 

                            Eventually, it was Little Johnny's turn. The teacher held her breath. 

                            Little Johnny walked to the front of the classroom and dumped a box 
                            full of cash on the teacher's desk. "$2,467", he said. 

                            ; "$2,467!" cried the teacher, "What in the world were you selling?" 

                            Toothbrushes", said Little Johnny. "Toothbrushes", echoed the teacher, 

                            "How could you possibly sell enough tooth brushes to make that much money?" 

                            "I found the busiest corner in town", said Little Johnny, "I set up 
                            a Dip &amp; Chip stand and I gave everybody who walked by a free sample." 
                            They all said the same thing, "Hey, this tastes like dog poop!" Then I would say, 
                            "It is dog poop. Wanna buy a toothbrush? I used the President Obama method 
                            of giving you some crap, dressing it up so it looks good, telling you it's free and 
                            then making you pay to get the bad taste out of your mouth." 

                            Little Johnny got fi ve stars for his assignment. 
                            Bless his heart.﻿

Meer lezen (48 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-TR7gxS9gPSo/Un67f4QFiHI/AAAAAAAABYA/ycvSvOpvaM8/w426-h240/c56b02f56c804be386b7c7616bd3e750.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/113467079318634670629/albums/5949761651490750225/5961916610730126562?sqi=106994183120156359801&amp;sqsi=f42d5702-157d-4135-b766-92a4909a2f33</link><title>Little Johnny Story — funny jokes short one liners ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_0OtjjuP8H4/Urz7keMR7OI/AAAAAAAAP1o/DKSJloDuSEI/w426-h423/Little-Johnny-Story-sms.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/103568000532288679490/albums/5973762385554737009/5973762388592304690</link><title>A JOKE OF THE DAY 
Little Johnny is in art class. The art teacher asks, “what are you drawing?" Johnny answers, “a cow eating grass," "where's the grass?" "The cow ate it!" "Oh... what about the cow?" "She ran away!" 

 ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-R3aUCaSyYbc/UucRPfiiIjI/AAAAAAAAAco/GgMYqFjG7BE/w426-h285/Npic90.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/108992007110283236440/albums/5841291697196933825/5841291695323740418?authkey=CNrk6v7a0J3T8AE</link><title>Little Johnny is always being teased by the other neighborhood boys for being stupid. Their favorite joke is to offer Johnny his choice between a nickel and a dime -- Little Johnny always takes the nickel. 

One day, after Johnny takes the nickel, a neighbor man takes him aside and says, "Johnny, those boys are making fun of you. Don't you know that a dime is worth more than a nickel, even though the nickel's bigger?" 

Johnny grins and says, "Well, if I took the dime, they'd stop doing it, and so far I've made $20!"﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vZZq-UfEpcs/URBv2TE1-QI/AAAAAAAAcPg/EeLtFIqdbIE/w426-h642/24464_420443204696382_1133835799_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7459-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/little%20johnny%20jokes/photos/102223619266508824486/albums/5884217984570423809/5884217987841192258?authkey=CID6j5zj6v3d2gE</link><title>Pain in The Side   #jokes   #fridayfunposts 

At Sunday School they were teaching how God created everything, including human beings. Little Johnny, a child in the Kindergarten class, seemed especially intent when they told him how Eve was created out of one of Adam's ribs. 

Later in the week his mother noticed him lying down as though he were ill, and asked, "Johnny, what is the matter?" 

Little Johnny groaned and responded , "I have a pain in my side. I think I'm going to have a wife." 

Anyway... #TGIF  folks!﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7459_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-4aF5-CxYYLg/UajxFYI88UI/AAAAAAAAlH8/b3ovndjidd8/w426-h240/Little_Johnny_The_Movie_003-1024x576.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>