<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:47:33" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7466-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/interconnects%20skin%20effect/photos/103821567731080143888/albums/6007050351299331185/6007050353463144658</link><title>Neat graphic tracing the roots of religion 

Awhile ago a bunch of humans made up religions (plural) to explain things which they did not yet understand and allay fears of a crazy world. If you believe in one of these religions, here's a great graphic showing the roots of that belief. 

Also, related: the next time someone asks you "do you believe in god" the correct response is: "which god are you talking about?" So many. As a current atheist, former jew, but always student of sociology my favorite god from a historical perspective is actually Ra the sun god, believed in by the ancient Egyptians. No more or less rational a god than any of the current ones people believe in, but at least you can feel and see the sun. And hey, we didn't exactly have the same understanding of our universe back then, so this one makes the most sense to me: sun provides warmth, grows crops and helps our mood. Cool. Also the ancient Egyptians loved cats, so bonus points. 

[found this one via +reddit]﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7466_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-lJjwPlCtzCo/U11UeEIOMNI/AAAAAAAALjA/ELHZR0yy_yI/w426-h280/d8ecc07e906127bf0fd4623504b7eca8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7466-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/interconnects%20skin%20effect/photos/114401975100913640964/albums/5925363937081141729/5925363937267935714?authkey=CNWBton0h_n-lAE</link><title>Mercedes-AMG is unleashing the new S63 AMG: the most powerful high-performance saloon in the luxury segment sets new standards in terms of driving dynamics, lightweight construction and efficiency. The guarantor of effortlessly superior performance is the AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine delivering 430 kW (585 hp) and 900 newton metres of torque - the most powerful member of the BlueDIRECT engine family. Thanks to systematic lightweight construction based on the "AMG Lightweight Performance" philosophy, the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG tips the scales at up to 100 kilograms less than its predecessor. The combination of an efficient drive system and reduced weight results in an NEDC combined fuel consumption of 10.1 to 10.3 litres per 100 kilometres. The new S63 AMG is also available for the first time with the performance-oriented AMG all-wheel drive system 4MATIC as an option. This not only enhances traction - the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG represents a new dimension in driving dynamics in its segment. The design, equipment and appointments of the S63 AMG meet the highest standards in terms of high-class appeal, quality and perfection. 

Systematic implementation of the AMG Lightweight Performance strategy reduces the weight of the S63 AMG by up to 100 kilograms compared to the predecessor model. This weight saving was achieved largely thanks to the use of a lightweight lithium-ion battery, AMG forged light-alloy wheels, and a weight-optimised AMG high-performance composite braking system. Furthermore, the entire outer skin of the S-Class, including the roof and the front end of the body, is made of aluminium. Installing a spare wheel recess made of carbon-fibre, a material used in Formula 1, reduces the weight by a further four kilograms. 

The Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG also leads the way when it comes to power-to-weight ratio, boasting a figure of 3.37 kg/hp. The result is effortlessly superior performance: Acceleration from 0 to 100 km/h takes 4.0 to 4.4 seconds depending on model variant, and the top speed is 250 km/h (electronically limited). 

In terms of maximum output and fuel consumption, the AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine remains the most efficient series-produced V8 engine of all. With an output of 430 kW (585 hp) and a torque of 900 Nm, the AMG eight-cylinder unit from the BlueDIRECT engine family (in-house designation M 157) outperforms all comparable engines. The fuel consumption of the new S63 AMG is up to 0.4 litres per 100 kilometres lower than that of the preceding model, even though the engine output has been increased by 30 kW (41 hp). The range-topping eight-cylinder model already meets the requirements of the EU6 emissions standard, which is due to come into force in 2015. 

AMG sports exhaust system with exhaust flaps 
The AMG sports exhaust system in the S63 AMG has automatic logic-controlled exhaust flaps in both rear silencers. When the transmission is in "C" (Controlled Efficiency) mode, the flaps remain closed in most situations, in which case the eight-cylinder biturbo engine's sound is more understated - perfect for long trips and a comfortable ride in the rear. In "S" (Sport) and "M" (Manual) modes, the exhaust flaps open earlier and more spontaneously, especially if the driver prefers a dynamic driving style. The result is an even fuller, emotional, hallmark AMG engine sound. 

Engine production in the AMG hand-assembly shop 
Like all AMG V8 and V12 engines, the eight-cylinder biturbo engine for the S63 AMG is assembled by hand in the hand-finishing section at AMG, observing the most stringent quality standards. Highly qualified engine fitters assemble the M 157 in Affalterbach according to the "one man, one engine" philosophy. Apart from serving as an AMG hallmark confirming superlative precision and production quality, the AMG engine plate bearing the engine technician's signature also attests to the peerless DNA of Mercedes-Benz's high-performance brand. 

Lithium-ion battery reduces weight by over 20 kilograms 
Following the SLS AMG Coupé Black Series, the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG is the second AMG high-performance model to replace the conventional starter battery with a lithium-ion battery. The new technology offers numerous advantages over a conventional battery concept: With a capacity of 78 Ah, the lithium-ion battery replaces both the starter battery and the backup battery - resulting in a weight saving of over 20 kilograms. The high-performance battery is relatively insensitive to cold temperatures and has compact dimensions. The S63 AMG is the world's first volume-produced vehicle with this type of battery concept. 

AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission 
Maximum individuality and custom-tailored dynamics are the strengths of the AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission. The three transmission modes - "C" (Controlled Efficiency), "S" (Sport) and "M" (Manual) - provide each driver with a personal transmission setup. In comfort-oriented "C" mode the ECO start/stop function is active and shuts off the eight-cylinder engine when the car is at a standstill. In "C" mode, the driver experiences smooth transmission characteristics with comfort-oriented gearshifts. In "C" mode the car always starts in second gear. 

In the "S" and "M" transmission modes the engine and transmission are significantly more agile and the ECO start/stop function is deactivated. A brief and precisely defined retardation of ignition and injection under open throttle results in even faster and acoustically more emotional gearshifts. 

Performance-oriented AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive 
The optionally available performance-oriented AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drivedistributes the engine torque to send 33 percent to the front axle and 67 percent to the rear axle. The rear-biased power distribution provides the signature AMG high driving dynamics and superlative driving enjoyment as well as boosting acceleration from a standing start. The all-wheel drive also enhances driving safety on wet or wintry road surfaces. Optimum traction is guaranteed by a multi-disc clutch with a locking effect of 50 newton metres, which exploits the frictional connection potential of all four wheels to the full on snow and ice in particular. 

The technical basis for the AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive system is a transfer case for the additional power take-off to the driven front axle. This requires no additional installation space, as it is integrated compactly into the AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission. The torque is transmitted from the power take-off via a propeller shaft to the front axle. Power transmission from the front axle differential to the front-left drive shaft is effected via an intermediate shaft which passes through an encapsulated shaft duct in the engine oil pan. The compact and weight-optimised design results in a comparatively low level of additional weight for the all-wheel drive system of only 70 kilograms, which also helps to reduce fuel consumption and exhaust emissions. 

All variants of the S63 AMG are fitted with ESP® Curve Dynamic Assist as standard. Targeted braking intervention at the inside rear wheel results in defined cornering of the vehicle and ensures greater agility when taking corners at high speed. There is no irritating understeer when turning into corners. 

Two suspension variants: AIRMATIC and MAGIC BODY CONTROL 
The S63 AMG 4MATIC is equipped with the AMG sports suspension. The full air suspension system AIRMATIC is equipped with the Adaptive Damping System ADS PLUS. One new feature is the continuous damping adjustment, which can be controlled independently in the compression stage and rebound stage. It allows better adaptation to the driving and road-surface conditions. "Comfort" and "Sport" suspension modes can be selected at the push of a button. Specific front axle kinematics - including higher camber, a larger anti-roll bar and a stiffer subframe carrier on the rear axle - have been developed exclusively for the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG 4MATIC. These measures optimise the vehicle's agility when driving dynamically. With the redesigned front axle and the special all-wheel drive setup, the S63 AMG 4MATIC represents a new dimension in its segment when it comes to driving dynamics. 

The S63 AMG with rear-wheel drive features AMG sports suspension based on MAGIC BODY CONTROL. The new S-Class is the first car in the world able to recognise road surface undulations in advance. If ROAD SURFACE SCAN detects such undulations with the help of the stereo camera, MAGIC BODY CONTROL adjusts the suspension in advance to suit the situation. Both suspension modes - "Comfort" and "Sport" - are also available here. The AMG-specific elastokinematics ensure more directness when driving dynamically. Both suspension variants available for the S63 AMG offer hallmark Mercedes comfort on long journeys. 

The electromechanical AMG speed-sensitive sports steering with variable steering ratio is the perfect complement: this greatly enhances vehicle handling and agilitywhile maintaining driving safety at high speeds. In "Comfort" suspension mode, the AMG speed-sensitive sports steering enhances comfort by providing more steering assistance. If the "Sport" suspension setting is selected, on the other hand, the driver feels a more sportily stiff level of steering assistance - which tends to result in better road feel. The pre-programmed curves for power assistance enhance feedback and steering precision. 

AMG light-alloy wheels based on systematic lightweight construction 
For the first time, the S63 AMG is available with AMG forged light-alloy wheels as standard. This design reduces weight while increasing strength - the result is lower unsprung masses, giving advantages in terms of handling and spring/damper element response. In the standard specification, the S63 AMG is fitted with AMG multi-spoke forged light-alloy wheels painted in titanium grey with a high-sheen finish - front: 8.5 x 19, rear: 9.5 x 19, tyre sizes 255/45 R 19 and 285/40 R 19. 

Optional extras include AMG forged light-alloy wheels in a 10-spoke design painted in titanium grey and polished, front: 8.5 x 20, rear: 9.5 x 20, tyre sizes 255/40 R 20 and 285/35 R 20. The AMG light-alloy wheels feature a high-quality, screwable and fully integrated wheel bolt cover made of forged aluminium. Its shape is reminiscent of a centre lock as seen in motorsport. The AMG logo is elegantly integrated into one of the ten spokes. As an option, these AMG light-alloy wheels are also available painted in matt black with a high-sheen rim flange. Alternatively, forged wheels of the same sizes in a 5-twin-spoke design painted in titanium grey with a high-sheen finish and a black wheel bolt cover are available. 

AMG ceramic high-performance composite brake system as an option for the first time 
Extremely short stopping distances and rapid deceleration are a given for any AMG high-performance car. And the new S63 AMG is no exception as it is equipped with a weight-optimised, fade-resistant AMG high-performance composite brake system. An AMG ceramic high-performance composite brake system is available as an option for the S-Class for the first time. The more than 20 percent lighter design ensures lower unsprung masses as well as enhancing driving dynamics, agility and ride comfort. In addition to this, the system has a longer service life, is more resistant to corrosion and displays higher thermal stability. The AMG ceramic high-performance composite brake system has front brake discs with a diameter of 420 millimetres and is recognisable by the "AMG Carbon Ceramic" logo on the specially painted brake callipers. 

Design: dynamism and exclusivity fused with sensuous forms 
Powerful and exclusive, dynamic and prestigious - the new Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG also makes an impact in visual terms. The high-performance saloon's design is defined by the impressive blend of hallmark Mercedes sensual forms, classic architecture and a sleek silhouette with classic AMG design features. A large, upright and distinctly three-dimensional radiator grille underlines the special status of the S-Class - with an exciting contrast to this being provided by the front apron with its three large cooling air intakes. The front apron with grilles painted in high-gloss black displays the stylised "A" that is a hallmark of AMG vehicles, and emphasises the exclusivity and power of the S63 AMG. Flics (air deflectors) in high-gloss black on the side air intakes optimise the flow of air to the cooling modules - a design that is a familiar sight in motorsport. The three-dimensional front splitter in silver chrome reduces lift. 

Side sill panels with three-dimensional inserts in silver chrome make the vehicle appear closer to the road and create dynamism along the flanks with the "Dropping Line" that is so typical of the brand. Large light-alloy wheels are another trademark AMG feature: they afford a clear view of the AMG high-performance braking system. "V8 BITURBO" lettering in new, contemporary typography on the front wings identifies the top-of-the-range eight-cylinder model. This new lettering also appears in the "S63 AMG" model designation on the boot lid. The design is drawn to a powerful conclusion by the black diffuser insert with trim in silver chrome and the two chromed twin tailpipes of the AMG sports exhaust system with exhaust flaps. 

Interior: beguiling appointments, design and quality 
Like the exterior design, the S63 AMG interior is a beguiling combination of the sporty and exclusive atmosphere of a true AMG model, with classic Mercedes values such as improved interior dimensions, new control logic, new ergonomic touches, ease of use, safety, appeal and aesthetics. The newly developed AMG sports seats with electrical adjustment, Memory function and seat heating offer the driver and front passenger more lateral support. Fine nappa leather in AMG V8 design with AMG badges in the front seat backrests creates an exquisite and luxurious atmosphere on board. Special touches include the embossed emblem on the armrest of the front centre console and the high-quality analogue clock in an exclusive IWC design, which for the first time features three-dimensional, milled metal hands and metal appliqués on the dial. 

The AMG sports steering wheel with its distinctively contoured rim, perforated leather in the grip area and aluminium shift paddles allows perfect vehicle control. Another feature displaying the hallmark AMG look is the high-resolution TFT colour display as an AMG instrument cluster with two animated round dials: in addition to the AMG-specific lettering and the needles in red/silver, further distinctive design features include the AMG logo in the speedometer with 330 km/h scale (left) and the "V8 BITURBO" lettering in the rev counter (right). 

The AMG main menu has a digital speedometer and a permanent gear display in the upper section. In transmission mode "M" the driver is also prompted to perform an upshift shortly before the rpm limit is reached. Selecting "Warm Up" in the AMG main menu brings up two further dials indicating the engine oil and transmission oil temperatures. The transmission and suspension configurations that can be set using the keys in the centre console, as well as the ESP® mode, are shown at the lower edge of the AMG "Set Up" menu. An animated S63 AMG on the TFT display between the speedo and rev counter gives the driver visual feedback. 

Further standard equipment for all Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG models (selection): 
AMG door sill panels 
AMG floor mats 
AMG sports pedals made from brushed stainless steel with rubber studs 
Ambience lighting 
ATTENTION ASSIST 
COLLISION PREVENTION ASSIST 
COMAND Online 
10 loudspeakers with Frontbass 
Metallic paintwork 
Tyre pressure loss warning system 
LED High Performance headlamps 
Numerous individualisation options are available from the AMG Performance Studio (selection): 

AMG Exterior Carbon-Fibre package 
AMG ceramic high-performance composite braking system (available from 03/2014) 
AMG carbon-fibre engine cover 
AMG Performance steering wheel in nappa leather / DINAMICA microfibre, black 
AMG trim in carbon fibre/black piano lacquer 
Brake callipers, painted red 

Additional optional extras (selection): 
AIR-BALANCE package 
Burmester® Surround Sound System 
Burmester® High-End 3D Surround Sound System 
Business Telephony in the rear 
Chauffeur package 
designo appointments packages 
Executive seat 
Exclusive package 
First-Class rear 
Folding tables in the rear 
LED Intelligent Light System 
Climatised seats for the driver and front passenger, including heating and ventilation 
Seat Comfort package incl. ENERGIZING massage function 
Warmth Comfort package 

Intelligent Drive: new standards in safety 
The S63 AMG likewise sets new standards in active and passive safety: what began with PRE-SAFE® ten years ago and continued with DISTRONIC PLUS is now leading to a new dimension in driving. Comfort and safety have blended into one. Mercedes-Benz calls this "Intelligent Drive". New systems make the new S-Class even more comfortable and safe: 

Driving Assistance package Plus 
Night View Assist Plus 

World premiere and market launch in September 2013 
The market introduction of the S63 AMG begins in September 2013. 
Prices for Germany (incl. 19% VAT): 
S63 AMG (short wheelbase): € 149,880.50 
S63 AMG 4MATIC (long wheelbase): € 152,617.50 

Engine: Dynamism, efficiency and emotion 
Efficiency and emotion, top performance and power delivery - in the second generation of the S63 AMG, the AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine once again asserts its leadership in this competitive segment. This high-performance engine from Mercedes-AMG with the in-house designation M 157 outperforms all comparable engines: no other series-production eight-cylinder engine is able to match its output of 430 kW (585 hp) and maximum torque of 900 newton metres. In terms of maximum output and fuel consumption, the AMG eight-cylinder engine from the BlueDIRECT family of engines remains the most efficient series-production V8 engine of all. Even though the engine output has been increased by 30 kW (41 hp), the fuel consumption of the new Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG is up to 0.4 litres per 100 kilometres lower than that of the preceding model. 

The performance figures show thatdynamism and low fuel consumption can be perfectly combined. The S63 AMG 4MATIC accelerates from standstill to 100 km/h in 4.0 seconds, the rear-wheel drive variant in 4.4 seconds. The top V8 model reaches its top speed of 250 km/h (electronically limited) effortlessly and serenely. The driving experience is characterised by the unrivalled power delivery of the charged eight-cylinder power unit from the AMG engine shop in Affalterbach: 900 newton metres of torque is on tap from 2250 to 3750 rpm - guaranteeing exhilarating pulling power in any speed range. 

AMG sports exhaust system with automatic exhaust flaps 
The engine's sound signature traditionally accounts for a high proportion of the emotional appeal when driving an AMG high-performance car - and the same applies to the S63 AMG, which is equipped with an AMG sports exhaust system with exhaust flaps. In each rear silencer there is an exhaust flap which is operated automatically by characteristic mapping. For the first time the engine sound depends on the selected transmission mode: in mode "C" (Controlled Efficiency) the exhaust flaps remain closed in most driving situations, whereas in "S" (Sport) and "M" (Manual) modes they open earlier and more spontaneously, especially if the driver prefers a dynamic driving style. 

This differentiation resolves the conflict of aims between dynamic performance and hallmark Mercedes long-distance suitability: if the driver selects mode "C", the sound signature of the eight-cylinder biturbo engine remains discreet - the best possible solution for long distances and outstanding comfort in the rear, especially if the S63 AMG is chauffeur-driven. In transmission modes "S" (Sport) and "M" (Manual), the driver hears the power residing in the eight-cylinder biturbo more distinctly: in this case the exhaust flaps open earlier and more immediately, the exhaust note from the two chromed twin tailpipes becomes more pronounced and emotional, in true AMG style. The engine starting sound is identical in all transmission modes, however in ECO start/stop mode the V8 has a more subdued starting sound than when started normally using the vehicle key. 

Compliance with the EU6 emissions standard, which only comes into force in 2015 
From the manifolds to the rear silencers, the uniformly twin-pipe exhaust system has a pipe diameter of 70 millimetres. A transition point between the two exhaust tracts helps to achieve the overall acoustic configuration. The isolating element behind the catalytic converters reduces body resonances and compensates for the elongation of the exhaust system. The layout involving a tandem catalytic converter box on each side is efficient and saves space: near the front firewall, two thin-walled ceramic substrates are grouped together in a housing on each side. This solution dispenses with the need for additional underfloor catalytic converters. The two ceramic substrates are different, in order to achieve rapid and effective treatment of the exhaust gases: the front substrate is coated with palladium, the rear with a bimetal layer of palladium and rhodium. A lambda sensor is located upstream of the catalytic converter box for each cylinder bank, and there is a diagnostic lambda sensor between each pair of thin-walled substrates. 

The engineers at Mercedes-AMG GmbH have made major progress where exhaust emissions are concerned: optimisation of the injection timing with the help of multiple injections and adaptation of the European on-board diagnostic system has made it possible to comply with the particularly stringent EU6 emissions standard, which only comes into force in 2015. The AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine is also ideally equipped to meet the second stage of the EU6 emissions legislation, due to come into force from 2017, which prescribes an even greater reduction in particulate emissions. 

Other technical highlights of the AMG eight-cylinder engine include: 
Direct petrol injection 
Biturbocharging 
All-aluminium crankcase 
Four valves per cylinder with camshaft adjustment 
Air-to-water intercooler 
Alternator management 
ECO start/stop function 

Two exhaust gas turbochargers located next to the cylinder banks supply the eight cylinders with fresh air. At their maximum speed of 185,000 rpm under full load, the two turbochargers force 1750 kg of air per hour into the combustion chambers. Thanks to their special, compact design - the turbine housings are welded to the exhaust manifold - there are not only significant space advantages, but the catalytic converters also heat up more rapidly. 

The V8 dispenses with the blow-off valve that is normally used. This means that the compressor housing could be kept extremely compact in design. To ensure an agile, undelayed response from the engine, all the air ducting in the intake tract is as short as possible. The wastegate valve, which reduces pressure in the exhaust system under negative load changes, is actuated by an electropneumatic converter using vacuum pressure. This allows dethrottling in the partial-load range, which in turn reduces fuel consumption. 

Efficient air-to-water intercooler 
As was already the case in the AMG 6.0-litre V12 biturbo engine, the eight-cylinder direct-injection unit uses particularly efficient air/water intercooling. The low-temperature cooler with its water circuit is neatly accommodated within the V of the cylinder banks. It very effectively cools down the intake air compressed by the turbochargers before it enters the combustion chambers, and maintains a constantly lower intake temperature under full load. The large radiator at the car's front end ensures defined cooling of the water circulating in the low-temperature circuit. Extremely short charge-air ducting makes for optimum responsiveness. The stainless-steel pressure pipes for the fresh and charge air are produced by the hydroforming process, have a wall thickness of only 0.8 millimetres and are designed for very low pressure loss. 

All-aluminium crankcase with Silitec cylinder liners 
The crankcase for the AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine is made completely of diecast aluminium. The low (dry) engine weight of 203 kilograms is the result of the uncompromising lightweight construction strategy AMG Lightweight Performance, and gives the vehicle balanced weight distribution. The bearing cover for the main crankshaft bearings, made of grey cast iron, is bolted to the crankcase for high rigidity. Cast-in Silitec cylinder liners ensure that the eight pistons operate with low friction. 

Drilled ventilation holes in the crankcase lead to a higher output and fuel savings under partial load. Above the bearing blocks are longitudinally drilled holes, which interconnect the crankcase cavities. Normally the upward and downward movement of the pistons causes air to be forced into and extracted from the sump, which leads to increased resistance and thus to a reduction in engine output. The ventilation holes prevent this by ensuring effective pressure compensation between the cavities. 

The forged crankshaft made of high-grade 38MnS6BY steel alloy (a combination of the chemical elements manganese, sulphur, boron and yttrium) rotates in five main bearings, has eight counterweights and has been optimised with respect to torsional rigidity, inertia, low rotating masses and a long operating life. A two-mass viscous damper mounted at the front reliably eliminates vibrations. Each connecting rod journal on the crankshaft carries two forged, cracked connecting rods. In the interests of low mechanical friction and high wear resistance, the eight lightweight pistons have a metallic contact surface. Pressure-controlled oil-spray nozzles in the crankcase ensure that the highly stressed piston crowns are efficiently cooled. 

Four-valve technology with variable camshaft adjustment 
Perfect charging of the combustion chambers is ensured by large intake and exhaust valves, of which there are two per cylinder. The exhaust valves, which are subject to high thermal loads, are sodium-cooled and hollow in order to reduce weight. Four overhead camshafts operate the 32 valves via low-maintenance, low-friction cam followers. The infinitely variable camshaft adjustment within a range of 40 degrees on the intake and exhaust sides depends on the engine load and engine speed, leading to outstanding output and torque values. This also results in consistent idling at a low speed. 

Depending on the engine speed, valve overlap can be varied for the best possible fuel/air supply to the combustion chambers and efficient removal of the exhaust gases. The variable camshaft adjustment is carried out electromagnetically via four pivoting actuators, and is controlled by the engine control unit. The camshafts are driven by three high-performance timing chains, which have considerable advantages with regard to noise comfort compared to cylinder roller chains. 

Innovative oil supply and water cooling 
An efficient oil supply under all load and operating conditions is ensured by the oil pump with an electrically controlled compression stage. The oil pressure can be varied between 2 and 4 bar, which has advantages for friction power and fuel economy. A suction stage integrated into the oil pump for the two turbochargers prevents oil entrainment into the charge air and exhaust gases, which further helps to reduce emissions. The oil capacity is 10.5 litres. 

Another intelligent solution is the combined water/oil cooling system: After cold-starting, the engine oil is initially only cooled by the oil-water heat exchanger. If the cooling performance of the compact cooler is insufficient, an oil thermostat allows the flow to pass through the external engine oil air cooler as well. The advantage of this system is more rapid warming of the engine oil, as the coolant warms up more rapidly in the warm-up phase and the oil is later cooled by the coolant. A selectable coolant thermostat ensures rapid warming of the coolant when starting off and during the warm-up phase. 

The engine coolant is cooled using the particularly efficient cross-flow principle. There is a transverse flow of coolant through both the crankcase and the cylinder heads. Additional cooling slots in the cylinder head allow more efficient cooling of the combustion chamber, which brings advantages during combustion by enabling earlier ignition timings to be chosen without incurring the risk of knocking. 

Large apertures in the front apron of the S63 AMG ensure an effective airflow to the coolant, engine oil, charge air and transmission oil coolers. Behind the large cooling module in the front section is a suction-type fan with an output of 1000 watts - this vents the warm air from the engine compartment as necessary. A separate slot above the front splitter directs fresh air to the AMG-specific engine oil cooler in the front. The additional water cooler mounted on the right wheel arch ensures operating safety even when driving very dynamically. 

Alternator management and lightweight lithium-ion battery 
The ECO start/stop function, which shuts down the eight-cylinder engine whenever the vehicle stops in "Controlled Efficiency" mode, is not the only feature to contribute to fuel efficiency. Efficiency is also aided by the alternator management system: whenever the V8 engine is on the overrun, and during braking, kinetic energy is not converted into heat but used to charge the battery. During steady driving or accelerating, a combination of on-board electrical system and alternator management enables the alternator to be kept at a low voltage level. 

As in the SLS AMG Coupé Black Series, Mercedes-AMG uses a lithium-ion battery in the S63 AMG. This replaces the conventional starter battery and has numerous advantages over a conventional battery concept: With a capacity of 78 Ah, the lithium-ion battery replaces both the starter battery and the backup battery - resulting in a weight saving of over 20 kilograms. The high-performance battery is relatively insensitive to cold temperatures and has compact dimensions. The S63 AMG is the world's first volume produced vehicle with this type of battery concept. 

Highly efficient engine electronics for every function 
All the engine functions are executed and controlled by a particularly efficient control unit. This state-of-the-art engine computer not only controls direct petrol injection, charge pressure, camshaft adjustment and variable oil supply but also communicates with all the other onboard control units, such as that of the AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission. The microprocessor has more than 30,000 different parameters and functions stored in its memory, and is able to perform up to 260 million individual operations per second. To reduce the load on the engine control unit, the eight individual ignition coils have an integral electronic module on each cylinder. This ensures a strong ignition spark at all engine speeds and under all load conditions. The highly precise distribution of fuel by the piezo-electric injectors is handled by eight high-voltage output stages. 

Engine production in the AMG hand-assembly shop 
Like all AMG V8 and V12 engines, the eight-cylinder biturbo engine for the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG is assembled by hand in the AMG engine shop in Affalterbach. Highly qualified engine technicians assemble the M 157 according to the "one man, one engine" philosophy. A matter of course: adherence to the strictest quality standards, confirmed by the AMG engine plate bearing the signature of the engine technician who assembled it. Apart from serving as an AMG hallmark confirming superlative production quality, this plate also attests to the peerless DNA of Mercedes-Benz's high-performance brand. 

Power transmission: Performance brings obligations 
Performance also brings obligations - as an AMG-exclusive feature, the S63 AMG comes with the AMG SPEEDSHIFT 7-speed sports transmission and optionally with performance-oriented AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive. For the top V8 model in the S-Class, the focus of the developers at Mercedes-AMG was once again on dynamic performance. 

The technical basis for the performance-oriented AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive system is a transfer case for the additional power take-off to the driven front axle. Unlike in the standard model, 33 percent of the engine torque is sent to the front axle and 67 percent to the rear axle. This rear-biased power distribution provides for the signature AMG high driving dynamics and superlative driving enjoyment. The transfer case requires no additional installation space, as it is integrated compactly into the AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission. The torque is transmitted from the power take-off via a propeller shaft to the front axle. Power transmission from the front axle differential to the front-left drive shaft is effected via an intermediate shaft which passes through an encapsulated shaft duct in the engine oil pan. This compact design leads to an additional weight of only around 70 kilograms. 

Enhanced driving safety on wet or wintry road surfaces 
The AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive improves road safety and grip on wet or wintry roads. Optimum traction is guaranteed by a multi-disc clutch with a locking effect of 50 Nm, which exploits the frictional connection potential of all four wheels to the full on snow and ice in particular. This basic concept allows high traction levels, because the dynamic axle load transfer to the rear axle that occurs during acceleration is used to apply more drive torque there. 

Intervention by the electronic control systems ESP®, 4ETS or ASR can therefore occur as late as possible and the bulk of the drive torque is converted into tractive power, even on slippery roads. All the control intervention functions are performed virtually unnoticed, though the driver is informed immediately if they approach the critical limits. In this instance a yellow warning symbol flashes in the instrument cluster, clearly signalling that the driving style should be adapted in line with the road conditions. 

Whether with optional all-wheel drive or rear-wheel drive, the S63 AMG features wheel-selective braking intervention by ESP® Curve Dynamic Assist, in the interests of high agility. This prevents irritating understeer when turning into bends. During cornering, targeted braking intervention at the inside rear wheel helps the vehicle to corner with precision. 

Exclusive AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission 
Seven gears, three modes and the ECO start/stop function: The AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission combines huge emotional appeal and maximum driving pleasure with outstanding economy. The sports transmission is exclusive to Mercedes-AMG and combines the sporty, direct and agile responsiveness of a manual transmission with the maximum comfort of an automatic transmission. MCT stands for Multi-Clutch Technology and indicates that only clutch elements are employed to perform gearshifts. A compact wet start-up clutch, which runs in an oil bath, replaces the conventional torque converter. Thanks to its low rotational inertia, the transmission responds instantaneously and dynamically without the losses typical of a torque converter transmission - thereby helping to save fuel. The AMG sports transmission also impresses with its low weight of just 80 kilograms. This is made possible by the use of lightweight magnesium for the transmission housing. Vibrations are effectively eliminated by a new, two-stage torsional damper, with ensuing benefits in perceived passenger comfort. 

ECO start/stop function as standard 
The ECO start/stop function fitted as standard is permanently active in the comfort-oriented "Controlled Efficiency" ("C") driving mode. Once the driver comes to a halt, for example at a red traffic light or in a traffic tailback, the engine is automatically switched off. When the brake pedal is released or the accelerator is depressed, the engine is immediately restarted and the car is able to move off again quickly. Intelligent technology guarantees a comfortable and immediate starting procedure: a crankshaft sensor which recognises the direction of rotation registers the rest position of all eight pistons. For an automatic engine start, the cylinder with the most favourable piston position receives an injection of fuel into its combustion chamber. This is helped by the precise piezo-electric injectors, as they make particularly fast starts possible. 

The engine control unit ensures that the engine is only switched off if certain preconditions are met. The starter battery must have sufficient charge, for example, and the engine must be at the necessary operating temperature for efficient emission control. The same applies to the interior temperature selected by the driver: if this has not yet been reached, the engine is not switched off when the car comes to a stop. The electrical management system ensures that active audio, telephone or video functions are not interrupted by the start/stop function. 

A green "ECO" symbol shows the driver when the start/stop function is active. Should one of the abovecriteria prevent use of the system, this is shown by a yellow "ECO" symbol in the central display. The start/stop function is deactivated in the dynamically oriented transmission modes "S" (Sport) and "M" (Manual). 

Fuel-efficient Controlled Efficiency ("C") transmission mode 
In adapting the MCT sports transmission to the AMG 5.5-litre V8 biturbo engine, the AMG engineers paid special attention to the new driving mode Controlled Efficiency ("C"). The emphasis was on keeping engine speeds as low as possible, in the highest possible gear, in any driving situation. When moving off in "C", the transmission always selects second gear and shifts markedly early to the next-highest gears if the driving style permits. At 60 km/h for instance, sixth gear will already be engaged - improving not only fuel consumption but also noise levels. Thanks to its powerful, readily available torque even at low engine speeds, the AMG V8 biturbo unit is absolutely ideal for this style of driving. Controlled Efficiency also means comfortable gearshifts and a "soft" accelerator response setup for outstandingly smooth power transfer. 

Transmission modes "S" and "M" for added driving pleasure and dynamism 
Apart from Controlled Efficiency ("C") there are two transmission modes available that appeal to the dynamically oriented driver: Sport ("S") and Manual ("M"). In transmission mode "S", both the engine and transmission respond with much more agility. Accelerator movements are more directly translated into drive power, and to this end the downshifts are faster. The gears are used to a higher rpm and, at 150 milliseconds, the gearshifts in "S" are 50 percent faster than in "C". If the "C/S/M" key is pressed again, transmission mode "M" is selected. In this mode the shift times are just 100 milliseconds. 

The engine control unit also partially suppresses cylinders in "S" and "M" modes: precisely interrupting ignition and injection under full load for brief periods leads to even faster gearshifts than before. An appealing side effect of this lightning-fast process is a highly emotional sound in response to every gearshift with wide-open throttle. Another strength of the AMG SPEEDSHIFT MCT 7-speed sports transmission is the way in which it allows fast and spontaneous multiple downshifts. Using kickdown it is for example possible to downshift directly from seventh to fourth gear, or from fifth to second. 

No automatic downshifts in manual "M" mode 
In manual "M" mode the driver also benefits from the high torque of the V8 biturbo engine, as there is no automatic downshift under full load and kickdown; the transmission remains steadfastly in the selected gear. Moreover, the 7-speed sports transmission does not perform an automatic upshift in manual mode when the rev limit is reached. In "M" mode the AMG instrument cluster displays the current gear and provides the driver with a visual warning of the need for an upshift just before the needle reaches the red zone. This means that a particularly sporty driver can use the superior performance potential to its fullest extent. When approaching the lower rev limit, for example when braking the vehicle, there is an automatic downshift to the next lower gear. 

The powerful electronic transmission control unit with integrated 200 MHz clock frequency processor controls spontaneous downshifts - for instance if the driver suddenly needs power for dynamic acceleration. 

Chassis, suspension and braking system: Serene driving pleasure 
Whether for the front or rear suspension - the developers at Mercedes-AMG adopted the basic layout of the standard S-Class for the S63 AMG. Numerous components of the four-link front suspension and the multi-link independent rear suspension were however newly developed with the focus on hallmark AMG performance. There is a choice of two different suspension variants: Customers opting for the S63 AMG 4MATIC with performance-oriented AMG 4MATIC all-wheel drive receive the AMG sports suspension with AIRMATIC. The rear-wheel drive variant has the AMG sports suspension based on MAGIC BODY CONTROL. 

A new dimension of driving dynamics in this segment 
Special kinematics were developed exclusively for the four-link front suspension of the S63 AMG 4MATIC.The larger negative wheel camber, together with the larger rear axle stabiliser and the more rigid suspension subframe carrier at the rear axle, leads to greater agility when the driving style is dynamic. The result is that thanks to more direct feedback, a further improvement in grip and highly neutral behaviour at the physical limits, the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG 4MATIC opens up a new dimension of dynamic driving in its segment. 

The full air suspension system AIRMATIC is equipped with the Adaptive Damping System ADS PLUS. This fully automatic, electronically controlled system adjusts the damping at each wheel to the current requirements. As before, the single-tube dampers have two valves for the rebound and compression stages. Continuously adjustable damping is a new feature: on the basis of numerous data such as acceleration, vehicle level or road speed, it allows better adaptation to the vehicle status and road surface condition to be achieved. 

In the centre console to the left of the COMAND controller is a control key that enables the driver to select a personal suspension setup. As an alternative to the comfort-oriented basic setup "Comfort" with a sensitive response and soft damping characteristics, a more sporty setting is available. In "Sport" mode the shock absorbers have a 40 percent stiffer response on average, resulting in reduced body movements when driving dynamically. The selected mode is shown both by the lights on the key and in the AMG menu: After the lettering "AMG RIDE CONTROL sport" or "AMG RIDE CONTROL comfort", an animated S63 AMG appears with a raised or lowered suspension. 

Depending on the driving situation, speed and load condition, the system also automatically and very rapidly varies the damper characteristics and reduces the body roll angle in "Comfort" mode. For the driver this means continuous adaptation between the greatest possible agility and maximum ride comfort. 

Thanks to continuous adaptation of the vehicle level, the AMG sports suspension based on AIRMATIC allows the suspension travel to be maintained under any load conditions. The suspension level is automatically adjusted depending on the road speed, and lowered by ten millimetres at speeds over 120 km/h in suspension mode "Comfort". Aerodynamic drag is reduced, and handling stability is improved by the car's low centre of gravity. If suspension mode "Sport" is selected manually, the suspension is likewise lowered by ten millimetres - also at speeds below 120 km/h. The driver is also able to select a suspension settting raised by 30 millimetres, for example on poor road surfaces or when negotiating a driveway. When a speed of 80 km/h is exceeded the suspension is automatically lowered after driving for three minutes, and immediately when it reaches 120 km/h. 

MAGIC BODY CONTROL: Comfort and driving dynamics 
The S63 AMG with rear-wheel drive is equipped with the AMG sports suspension based on MAGIC BODY CONTROL as standard, including Active Body Control (ABC) and the innovative new ROAD SURFACE SCAN function. In the interests of improved feedback from the road and greater directness when driving dynamically, the S63 AMG has AMG-specific elastokinematics. 

Available choices: suspension mode "Comfort" or "Sport" 
Like the AIRMATIC air suspension system, the active ABC suspension allows the driver a personal suspension setup. There is a choice between suspension mode "Comfort" and the 40 percent tauter "Sport" mode. Pressing the ABC key to the left of the COMAND controller causes the selected mode to appear in the AMG menu display: "AMG RIDE CONTROL sport" or "AMG RIDE CONTROL comfort" is shown depending on the selection. As additional information, an animated S63 AMG with a raised or lowered suspension appears in the display. 

In the case of the MAGIC BODY CONTROL suspension, the suspension level also remains constant irrespective of the load condition. In "Comfort" mode the suspension is lowered by ten millimetres between 120 and 160 km/h, and in "Sport" mode it is already lowered between 65 km/h and 100 km/h. With MAGIC BODY CONTROL, too, a raised suspension level is available at the touch of a button. 

The world's first car with "eyes", thanks to ROAD SURFACE SCAN 
The new S-Class is the first car in the world able to recognise road surface undulations in advance. The "eyes" for the ROAD SURFACE SCAN function are provided by a stereo camera fitted behind the windscreen, which scans the road up to 15 metres ahead of the vehicle and delivers a precise image of the road contours. Based on the camera pictures and driving status information, the control unit constantly calculates the best control strategy for overcoming unevenness such as prolonged bumps. 

This means that in advance, and for each individual wheel, the vehicle is able to select stiffer or softer damper settings and use the active hydraulics to vary the load at each wheel. The suspension is adapted to the relevant situation within fractions of a second, enabling body movements to be considerably reduced. The result is unprecedented ride comfort. As ROAD SURFACE SCAN is camera-based, it works in the daytime, in good visibility, with suitable surface structures and at speeds up to 130 km/h. 

In the Active Body Control system from Mercedes-Benz, the four spring struts are equipped with hydraulic cylinders (plungers) to adjust the force in each spring strut individually. This means that the system can almost completely compensate for lifting, rolling and pitching movements of the body. The control unit receives information on the current driving situation from various acceleration sensors and then compares these data with those from the pressure sensors in the spring struts and the level sensors on the control arms. The system then computes the control signals for the servo-hydraulic valves at the front and rear axle to ensure precisely metered oil flows. 

Once oil flows into the plunger cylinders, this modifies the tracing point of the steel springs integrated into the spring struts, generating the necessary force to counteract the body movements. Thanks to a constantly available hydraulic pressure of up to 200 bar, ABC is able to stabilise the body within fractions of a second. 

ABC has undergone major modifications for the new S-Class: the wheel damping is now continuously adjustable, the spring strut response has been improved and the pump efficiency has been further enhanced. A digital interface connects the control unit and the sensors, while the fast FlexRay bus connects the control unit and the vehicle electronics. Processing power is more than double that of the previous system. 

Electromechanical AMG speed-sensitive sports steering 
A major part of the serene and sporty driving impression of the S63 AMG is also due to the electromechanical AMG speed-sensitive sports steering. This is a Direct-Steer system, which means that the steering becomes noticeably more direct as a function of the steering angle. This significantly improves vehicle handling and agility. At the same time the dampened response from the centred position ensures the necessary handling safety at high speeds. In addition the AMG speed-sensitive sports steering adapts to the personal driving style and the chosen suspension mode: Drivers who select "Comfort" mode feel a higher level of servo assistance. In "Sport" the servo assistance is reduced, with a more sporty and taut setup. The driver benefits from what tends to be better road feedback. 

In the electromechanical AMG speed-sensitive sports steering system the steering gear and the supporting servo-motor form a single compact unit and are mounted as previously on an extremely rigid and low-weight integral support frame made of high-strength steel which is positioned in front of the wheel's centre line. The high-performance control unit processes the parameters captured by the ESP® control unit - including vehicle speed, steering angle, steering angle speed, lateral acceleration and also understeer/oversteer characteristics - and in a split second calculates the forces which the driver needs to input into the steering in different driving situations - from parking to high-speed motorway driving. Active steering dampers enhance the feeling of safety when driving straight ahead at high speed. 

The steering assistance function is able to help stabilise the vehicle. An assisting steering torque level is determined depending on the vehicle status, then applied by the electric servo assistance. The driver is always able to override the steering assistance function, which only gives an indication of the steering direction that will best stabilise the vehicle. 

If the vehicle is braked on a road surface with different friction (µ-split) on the left and right, this generates a yawing impulse which turns the vehicle in the direction of the high friction. The steering assistance system prompts the driver to turn the steering wheel in the appropriate direction to compensate for the yaw caused by the different friction. 

Weight-optimised AMG light-alloy wheels produced by a forging process 
Reduced weightwith increased strength is one of the attributes of the forged AMG light-alloy wheels that are fitted as standard for all variants of the S63 AMG. The weight advantage over conventional light-alloy wheels ensures a reduction in unsprung masses: this produces advantages in terms of handling and of the responsiveness of the spring/damper elements. In standard specification, the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG is fitted with AMG light-alloy wheels painted in titanium grey with a high-sheen finish - front: 8.5 x 19, rear: 9.5 x 19, tyre sizes 255/45 R 19 and 285/40 R 19. 

Optional extras include AMG forged light-alloy wheels in a 10-spoke design painted in titanium grey and polished, front: 8.5 x 20, rear: 9.5 x 20, tyre sizes 255/40 R 20 and 285/35 R 20. As particularly high-grade details, the wheels have the AMG logo integrated into one of the ten spokes and a high-quality, screwable and fully integrated wheel bolt cover in forged metal. Its shape is reminiscent of the centre lock commonly seen in motorsports. As an option, these AMG light-alloy wheels are also available painted in matt black with a high-sheen rim flange . As an attractive design alternative, AMG 5-twin-spoke light-alloy wheels painted in titanium grey with a high-sheen finish and a black wheel bolt cover are available for the S63 AMG. 

Optional: AMG ceramic high-performance composite braking system 
The braking system of an AMG high-performance car needs to meet extremely high expectations: fast deceleration, a precise actuation point and the shortest possible braking distances are a matter of course, as is fade resistance. 

The weight-optimised AMG high-performance composite braking system developed exclusively for the S63 AMG features perforated and ventilated brake discs in size 390 x 36 millimetres (front) and 360 x 26 millimetres (rear) all-round. One major development focus was on reducing brake-judder: the brake discs have a floating connection with the brake disc bowl by means of cast-in retaining arms, significantly reducing the typical "brake-judder" under extreme stresses and heat. Grey brake callipers with the AMG logo are standard, red-painted brake callipers are available on request. 

Alternatively, and as a first for the S-Class from AMG, an even more efficient AMG high-performance ceramic composite braking system is available - this is recognisable by the specially painted brake callipers with the "AMG Carbon Ceramic" logo. Thanks to the material and production technology used, whereby the discs are produced from carbon-fibre reinforced ceramics in a vacuum at over 1700 degrees Celsius, the ceramic discs exhibit a much higher degree of hardness. This not only increases their operating life by many times compared to cast-iron discs, but also their resistance to extreme stresses and heat. The result is even greater stability even under extreme operating conditions. The even larger ceramic discs - front: 420 x 40 millimetres, rear: 360 x 32 millimetres - are of composite construction all-round, with a radial, free-floating connection to an aluminium bowl. 

The ceramic brake discs are more than 20 percent lighter overall than conventional composite brake discs. The further reduction in unsprung masses not only improves driving dynamics and responsiveness, but also the response characteristics of the steering and the sensitivity of the suspension. The AMG high-performance ceramic composite braking system is available exclusively for the S63 AMG 4MATIC as an optional extra. 

The S63 AMG is equipped with an electric parking brake as standard. A combined floating brake calliper with an electric parking brake function is used at the rear axle. With the ADAPTIVE BRAKE, the S-Class offers a wealth of assistance functions. One example of these is the practical HOLD function: after braking to a standstill, briefly pressing the brake pedal a little further is all that is required to activate this function. The car is then held by the brakes, even if the driver's foot is taken off the brake pedal. The HOLD function is deactivated automatically when the car moves off. 

If the driver's foot moves abruptly from the accelerator to the brake pedal before an emergency stop, the brake system increases the pressure in the brake lines and brings the pads into contact with the brake discs so that maximum braking power is available as soon as the driver hits the brake pedal. This priming of the brakes allows the system to assist the standard-fit Brake Assist system. 

ADAPTIVE BRAKE also brings safety benefits in the wet: the system briefly applies the brakes at regular intervals to wipe the film of water from the brake discs and ensure that the brakes are able to perform at their peak. The finely metered brake pulses are imperceptible to the driver. This automatic brake drying function is always activated when the windscreen wipers have been operating for a certain length of time. Finally, ADAPTIVE BRAKE assists the driver when starting on an uphill slope. When the sensors detect that the car has stopped on an uphill slope, Hill Start Assist is activated automatically, briefly holding the brake pressure at a constant level so as to prevent the car from rolling backwards. 

Design and equipment: Dynamism, exclusivity and sensuous forms 
Status and dynamism, performance and elegance, exclusivity and superiority - the S63 AMG visually confirms it special status within the model portfolio, and also embodies "Driving Performance" with its exterior design. The eight-cylinder top model from Affalterbach unmistakably and instantly announces: here comes an AMG. The overall impression is created by a combination of the sensuous lines that are a hallmark of Mercedes, classic architecture and a flowing silhouette with typical AMG design features. 

The S-Class radiator grille is larger than before, upright and decidedly three-dimensional in design. The four louvres are tapered towards the outside, and do not contact the chrome frame. The front apron of the AMG bodystyling package stands in dramatic contrast to the dignified radiator grille. The large cooling apertures are not only reminiscent of motorsport, but also ensure an efficient airflow to the cooling modules located behind them. The high-gloss black flics (air deflectors) located at the side apertures assist this process, as does the slot above the front splitter: This specifically directs the cooling air towards the separate engine oil cooler. In addition the three-dimensionally formed front splitter in silver chrome reduces lift at the front axle. 

The designers at Mercedes-AMG have supplemented the flowing, arched roofline and the sporty, coupé-like side line with the "Dropping Line" that is a hallmark of the brand with striking side sill panels: Three-dimensionally formed inserts in silver chrome make the car appear closer to the road, and add drama to the flank. Large light-alloy wheels are another typical feature of an AMG high-performance car: whether in the 10-spoke or 5-twin-spoke design, the AMG forged wheels allow a clear view of the large AMG high-performance braking system. Standing almost flush with the wheel arches, the AMG light-alloy wheels further enhance the impression of dynamism. Exclusively reserved for the S63 AMG, the " V8 BITURBO" lettering on the front wings is in a new typography. 

The same typography is found in the Mercedes-Benz SLS S63 AMG model badge on the boot lid. Horizontal lines emphasise the width of the vehicle, as does the high-gloss black diffuser insert with a trim strip in silver chrome. Sheer power is suggested by the two chromed twin tailpipes of the AMG sports exhaust system with exhaust flaps. 

Interior with luxurious ambience and sporty functionality 
A feel-good atmosphere combined with a luxurious ambienceand the sporty functionality of a genuine AMG high-performance model - that is how the interior of the S63 AMG might best be described. A pleasure for all the senses: the lovingly designed interior fascinates with its very high-grade materials, first-class quality and carefully chosen colour schemes. All the occupants benefit from improved interior dimensions, a new control logic and new highlights in terms of ergonomics, operating convenience and safety. 

AMG sports seats developed exclusively for the S63 AMG ensure outstanding long-distance comfort. Electric adjustment, a memory function and seat heating are standard features. Newly contoured seat cushions and backrests improve lateral support when cornering at speed. Fine nappa leather in AMG V8 design with AMG badges in the front seat backrests creates an exquisite and luxurious atmosphere on board. This is perfectly complemented by a high-quality, embossed AMG emblem on the front centre console. There is a choice of four colours for the S63 AMG: black, satin beige/espresso brown, crystal grey/seashell grey and nut brown/black. The standard wood trim can be replaced by two different designo trim variants - myrtle wood in high-gloss sunburst brown or metallised ash wood. Trim in AMG carbon-fibre/black piano lacquer is available from the AMG Performance Studio. 

Another feature reserved for AMG is the high-quality analogue clock in an exclusive IWC design between the air vents: this for the first time features three-dimensional, milled metal hands and metal appliqués on the dial. The AMG sports steering wheel in nappa leather with a heavily contoured rim, an insert with AMG lettering, perforated leather in the grip area and aluminium shift paddles allows perfect vehicle control. 

The AMG instrument cluster is in a decidedly sporty design: the animated dial instruments are dominated by the colours silver and red, while other AMG-specific features include the distinctive typography, the 330 km/h speedometer scale with AMG logo and the "V8 BITURBO" lettering in the rev counter. The attention to detail is also obvious here: the AMG logo and V8 BITURBO lettering change their size and appearance depending on the operating state of the vehicle. The AMG start-up display is in keeping with this: when the driver's door is opened, an animated AMG logo appears in the large TFT display on the right. 

Comprehensive information for the driver is provided by the AMG main menu integrated into the AMG instrument cluster: there is a digital speedometer and a permanent gear display in the upper section. In transmission mode "M" the driver is also prompted to perform an upshift shortly before the rpm limit is reached. Selecting "Warm Up" brings up two further dials indicating the engine oil and transmission oil temperatures. The transmission and suspension configurations that can be set using the keys in the centre console, as well as the ESP® mode, are shown at the lower edge of the AMG "Set Up" menu. An animated S63 AMG in the TFT display between the speedometer and rev counter provides the driver with visual feedback: in transmission mode "C" (Controlled Efficiency), the car is seen standing on a normal country road, in mode "S" (Sport) it is on a winding road and in "M" (Manual) the background is a racetrack with red/white kerbs. The upper section of the display contains a permanent gear indicator and, when manual transmission mode "M" is selected, also an upshift recommendation. The activated transmission programme, current ESP® mode and selected suspension configuration can be seen at the lower edge.﻿

Meer lezen (1142 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7466_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-lIAwVKdfms8/UjsfG2XD6eI/AAAAAAAAlT0/Mli6CpcgEWM/w426-h237/Merc-31.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7466-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/interconnects%20skin%20effect/photos/101416803710397935669/albums/5982195537781401409/5982195537424141202</link><title>50th Utility-scale Renewable Energy Project 
... approved on public lands since 2009 

"Secretary of the Interior Sally Jewell today announced the approval of two solar energy projects located near the Nevada-California border that are expected to supply 550 megawatts of renewable energy, enough to power about 170,000 homes, and support more than 700 jobs through construction and operations." 

There's more: http://www.doi.gov/news/pressreleases/secretary-jewell-announces-two-solar-projects-approved-in-california-nevada.cfm 

#solarpower   #solarenergy   #renewableenergy   #jobs   #climateaction   #climateactionplan  ﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7466_04_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-qZDym56wKps/UwUHJXEXy5I/AAAAAAAACPA/fWcGzxjoeN0/w426-h277/tab1.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>