<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:13:14" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/102668811864861348617/albums/5684915114601330369/5684915116553142162</link><title>Needed to get my radiator fluid changed and I usually do my own car maintenance. I also usually create a Superfund site every time I change my oil, though, and since I have 7 dogs at the house I didn't want doggy carnage everywhere. So I thought I would simply drive to work, watch 2 deer jump the concrete barrier in the middle of 6 lanes of rush hour traffic then turn and play a game of chicken (or deer in this case) with me. 

Took one of them head on and now have $5900 worth of damage - no used parts to buy. Glad I have good insurance. 

Shiny new star to anyone who can guess the make/model of the car.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Fw4PGDjJYx8/TuTgLbRl_5I/AAAAAAAAAuc/0Jj533pOMlc/w426-h393/DeerHit.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/108576518325399972302/albums/5742662633322342561/5742662634910956370</link><title>Tips For Car Maintenance :-- 

How to Maintain a Car in its Top Condition 

It’s not an easy task to maintain a car properly along with keeping its performance up to the mark throughout its life. An owner has to take care of a number of things in order to keep the car fine tuned for a long time. Below are some basic points that a car owner should keep in mind to ensure effective maintenance of the car. 

1)Service Schedule: - Every carmaker offers a recommended service schedule with the car that contains information in tabular form regarding the exact distances or durations after which the car needed to be serviced at the company’s work shop. The servicing of a car includes a thorough checking and repairing and replacement of a number of parts. Thus, it is highly recommended to strictly follow the service schedule. 

2)Oil Change: - The car engine oil remains responsible for the lubrication of engine components that reduces the friction among them and keeps the engine from overheating. But the engine oil tends to loose its lubrication power due the heat and mixing of metal particles over a period of time, thus, it is very important for the performance and longevity of the engine to change the oil strictly as per schedule. 

3)Fluids: - There are a number of fluids that are needed to be maintained to their recommended level in order to keep the car’s performance up to the mark that comprises of Brake fluid, battery fluid, transmission fluid and coolant fluid. The level of all of these fluids should be checked and maintained on a fortnight basis. 

4)Tyres: - Where the low inflated tyres enhance the fuel consumption of a car, the high inflated tyres can cause severe damage to the car’s wheels and suspension system. Thus, the tyre pressure should be maintained on its recommended level. 

Follow these simple tips to maintain a car in its top condition and to receive an optimal performance 

Text courtesy : carmaintenanceguide.typepad.com 
Image courtesy : zigwheels.com﻿

Meer lezen (38 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-OruXo_K8QgM/T7IJPZLGu1I/AAAAAAAABIk/65l1SGlAbVw/w426-h320/181435_10150932107441072_218903956071_12165244_1796963961_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/114026527322506807073/albums/5818506623792310353/5818506622471510674</link><title>Winterizing Your Motorcycle Checklist 

Follow these steps to winterize your motorcycle. 
1\. Fill the Tank and Add Fuel Stabilizer - Fresh fuel is best. Make sure that you use fresh stabilizer as well – a bottle is only good for two years aft 
er you open it. 
2\. Change the Oil Filter - You should change your oil and filter, even if you did it recently. The byproducts of used oil are very corrosive, and you don’t want that sitting all winter. 
3\. Drain the Carburetor - Turn off the main gas valve from the tank. Next, open the petcock and close the valve when it stops flowing. 
4\. Keep the Mice Out - Fill a few sandwich bags with steel wool, and put them into the air intake and tailpipes. Stick a piece of brightly colored tape or caution tape on so you remember to remove them before you begin to ride the motorcycle again. 
5\. Lube the Chain and Pivot Points - Spray chain lube on the chain and all pivot points. It prevents rust from forming. 
6\. Remove the Battery or Install a Maintainer - You can do either. A battery maintainer charges the battery only when it needs it; connect one to your battery, and you’ll be able to start the bike right up when spring arrives. It’s fine to remove the battery entirely as well. 
7\. Check Antifreeze and Coolant – Dip the suction tube of the coolant tester into the radiator. Suck up enough to make the indicator float, and read the protection level. Change the fluids if they’re not up to par. 
8\. Spray the Bike With WD-40 – Do this after you’ve washed and waxed the motorcycle. It helps prevent corrosion. In the spring, take it to a car wash and hose it down – and you’ll be good to go.﻿

Meer lezen (25 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-5glJG6Qt6sQ/UL988gOsGpI/AAAAAAAAAJ8/-3Q17blneCw/w426-h320/winter%2Briding.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/118400417455591622079/albums/5786263379204076273/5786263379549952002</link><title>So on to a fun part four!  Cars!  +Kwangjae Jung will probably get a chuckle out of this section and +Kenneth Zieres knows far too much about this part of my life.  He was riding shotgun through much of it after all. :) 

\------------------ 
Part one: https://plus.google.com/u/0/118400417455591622079/posts/UKyZ93THp8s 

Part Two: https://plus.google.com/u/0/118400417455591622079/posts/QP8XHMFTaaf 

Part Three: https://plus.google.com/u/0/118400417455591622079/posts/FuNfFp3TfVG 

\----------- 
Cars 

    What young, part hillbilly, sixteen year old boy who has his licence doesn’t like cars?  Sure growing up I leaned more toward the nerdy with my music, computers, and games it doesn’t mean I didn’t learn the basics of cars and an appreciation for them.  When I turned sixteen my folks gave me access to my first car, a 1979 Caprice Classic station wagon.  The huge boat of a car gave me a freedom I never had before, and reinforced my old duties to my younger brothers by forcing me to drive them around.   Driving the eight cylinder with a four barrel carburetor led to some interesting “physics experiments” as I found out how far you could jump one, what kind of damage it could take without showing, and how hard it was for one guy to push it out of a sand dune.  Good times. 

    With a handyman father like mine it was impossible to not learn a little bit about working on the beast while growing up. I helped him change the disc and drum brakes (Two very different assemblies), the spark plugs, the brake fluid, the tires, the oil, the plethora of belts, and even a battery or two all things I know think of as “standard maintenance.”  What I didn’t know until later was how many folks don’t know even those basic car tasks.  The knowledge that there are folks driving down the road right now who don’t even know how to change a tire is frightening!  In fact it’s pretty unheard of where I’m from because of how much in the middle of nowhere Needles is.  When you grow up with lots of bumpy, pot-hole filled, broken down desert roads with the nearest help miles away all before cell phones?  Yeah you learned to fix a car. 

    In my senior year of high school I wanted to take a break from all my usual classes so I decided to take auto shop.  Back when I took auto shop it was considered where all the “dumb” kids or the troublemakers went when they weren’t taking “real” classes.  As I’ve aged I realize that auto shop is a class most people should take if for no other reason than to better appreciate their cars! Also there are still plenty of people out there who do better with their hands than with their minds or mouths so why neglect them?  My buddy Travis (technically most of Needles was my buddy but I digress) was on his fourth year in auto shop so he quickly took me under his wing as the noob I was.  (Before we even used the word noob.) 

    I learned how a combustion engine worked,  I learned how to tear one apart and put it back together again, and I learned about parts of mine and other cars I never even knew about!  The teacher pulled a bit of a prank on the class one day when he pulled in the class dirt track race car (what good auto shop doesn’t have a race car?) and popped the hood.  We were talking about the coolant system and he wanted us to find the fan clutch on the car.  Now the car enthusiasts will correct me if I’m wrong but on older cars they had the fans directly connected to the motor unlike newer fans which tend to be electric.  These fans would be damaged if they were being forcibly spun through the high speed air of a car at speed so the fan clutch was invented to disengage the fan when the car was moving at speed and then reengage to draw air across the radiator when the car was sitting still.  Like many mechanical solutions it was simple yet elegant in concept and application. 

    So I’m sitting there in the back of the class picturing where the fan clutch had to be between the shaft and the fan head itself.  Something simple and easy to point out.  The teacher then proceeds to call on member after member of the class to find the fan clutch and no one can find it!  I’m starting suspect a trick when it finally comes down to me and Travis and the teacher picks him.  Travis helped build this car in the first place I’m sure he must know the answer but nope!  The teacher says he’s wrong to. So I sit there thinking as he asks me and I just lean back and say, “There isn’t one.” 

    I mean seriously if all the kids who know more about cars than me can’t find it, it doesn’t exist right? 

    Turns out I am correct and we all end up getting into a discussion about the strange speed based shape changing fan the car has in it.  I have to admit I really liked learned about what makes cars work from fuel/air ratios and spark plug gaps and everything else, it was a whole new world to discover and it had the advantage of going fast!  Racing down alleys and back roads against my buddies in my station wagon was fun, but it would have been better in my own hotrod! 

    Unfortunately all of this never entered my mind when it came time to talk about “what’s next.”   If I had thought about it or if someone had mentioned it I might have realized that engineers make cars so I could have actually gone to study such things.  Maybe I could have gotten into the car scene because growing up in Southern California there was no shortage of good old cars to build.  Was it too dirty and hot for me to work on cars?  Did I think it was too basic to me?  Why did I not have a greater appreciation for the mechanical precision of a car?  How could I make the mistake of not even knowing what a mechanical engineer was or did? 

    Years later while living in Barstow I ended up buying a Volkswagen Beetle.  Even at the time the idea of big old me getting into a little Beetle was funny but I figured I could just Hightower the thing and toss out the front seat if things went bad.  Unlike my previous vehicles the Beetle was my first car that was MINE.  I bought it straight up and was hence fully responsible for it’s maintenance and any possible upgrades I wanted to do.  As a college drop out and now assistant manager at a movie theater the idea of souping up the bug into a sand rail was nice dream but it would take forever at my income level. It didn’t stop me from looking into it, nor did it piss me off when the head cracked on the POS old thing and started shooting oil all over the road. 
    I swear I wanted to shoot that car after all the work I put into it for no good end. 

    After that I swore off car repairs and stuff again for a few years until Geoff and I became buds at Goldstone.  See Geoff is a HUGE Dodge man.  He can tell you pretty much everything about every Dodge every made and he knows quite a bit about older engines of all kinds.   As a single guy making darn good money I had a lot of money to throw around that the married Geoff didn’t.  This lead to the partnership I like to think of as “you go first.”  See, Geoff wanted to get a Dodge Stealth as it was a newer car with turbos in it that seemed to do well on the track and such.  At the time he knew I liked the World Rally Championship and how much I wanted a Subaru WRX.  Devious Geoffrey had a plan. 

    It was a simple plan really, I would buy a 1991 Dodge Stealth and he would help me soup it up like I wanted.  We shopped for parts, figured out what laws I could bend, and planned it all out.  Later he would buy his own Stealth and we could be a racing “team.”  Getting car was the first part and it was pretty easy to find, but one at a good cost and that wasn’t torn up was a bit harder.  We were being very picky about what one we went for, it had to be a Twin Turbo, and as I was a Bean Bandit fan it had to have the all wheel steering of the early models.  This lead us to the ‘91 and my trip into the expensive world of car modification. 

    The first problem with the car was getting it past smog.  California has some of the dumbest and most idiotic smog laws in the nation that actually made me down tune my engine to get it to pass smog.  Luckily I had a legal loophole to fight back against the tyranny from Sacramento in the form of being born in Needles.  See California’s clean air laws prevent you from doing all sorts of fun things to your car, most notably they prevent you from removing the catalytic converters on your car to improve air flow.  Lucky for me there are two towns in the entirety of the state that got special exemption from the clean air laws because Nevada had power plants right on the other side of the border from them.  One of those towns was Needles. 

    So after squeaking past smog I tore the car apart.  We drilled out the pre-cats and put a straight pipe out to the fast flow mufflers.  We added a new instrument cluster for boost pressure, oil temperature and the like as well as buying a blow off valve and a simple boost controller for the turbos.  A high flow air intake was of course put in and we had so many plans beyond that point to make it into a truly bad ass car. 

    Now anyone who works with cars knows things never seem to go to plan with them as something always seems to go wrong.  Found out the blow off valve was killing my engine as it was an open air blow off and not an into the system blow off.  Then the fiberglass mount for my new gages was broken.  Those pre-cats we didn’t even know what to do with which is why we just drilled them out.  The list goes on and on and I was quickling thinking I was in the money pit movie.  At the end of the day though I had me a fast car that I liked.  It was fun to drive and it could do pretty darn good job on the quarter mile. 

    Then one day one of those parts I never knew existed broke.  In fact Geoff didn’t really know anything about it either because the engine on the Stealth is sideways mounted and he’s always dealt with cars with a straight mount.  This little thing called a transaxle  broke in a major way when it leaked it’s oil and seized up.  Now all the car guys out there are just shaking their heads because they know how bad this is, but the end result was my wonderful fun fast car was not a very heavy paperweight.  Luckily I had a buddy who was a tow truck driver so I was able to get it to Geoff’s no worries but it would end up sitting there for a year or so before finally being fixed a bit and sold. 

    I made a lot of mistakes when it came to cars, especially the Stealth.  What some maybe saying right now is that my first mistake was buying a Stealth, let alone a first model year one.  In retrospect I agree especially since I liked the tail end of the 3000GT more (which is what the Stealth is a rebranding of), but I was young, dumb, and I had a Dodge guy whispering in my ear.  Another problem we both had is that we hadn’t found the 3000GT/Stealth community and gotten properly informed before we dove in. Geoff and I basically made every mistake we could that new wannabes made with those cars.  Luckily for Geoff is we made all those mistakes with MY car and not his.  So his “you go first” plan worked out well for him. 

    In the end I have a deeper appreciation of cars due to these mistakes and for those who fix and maintain them.  Cars are wonderful machines that I do wish I had realized were actually engineering marvels that were worthy of study.  Who knows what other versions of me are out there making cars or working on car design?  Heck even a mechanic is a worthy profession that many seem to turn their nose up against that I could have done but didn’t even consider.  Is it a mistake to think that ignoring that path and my enjoyment of it at that early time was going to lead me to a better future?  ﻿

Meer lezen (210 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-hqIlwstKZOQ/UEzv4wLtGAI/AAAAAAAABSw/nlGPeX8R2dQ/w426-h320/%2524%252528KGrHqJHJE8E-vUdME76BP3OW0blm%2521%257E%257E60_3%255B1%255D.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/114401975100913640964/albums/5821427945343278865/5821427947517971922?authkey=CNmBkraTn8GGTw</link><title>The flagship Maserati Quattroporte is larger, lighter, more luxurious and more practical than the globally acclaimed car it replaces. With a 307 km/h top speed, it's also as fast as most two-door supercars. 

The sixth-generation Maserati Quattroporte delivers a leap forward that not only sets the high-technology tone for Maserati's upcoming new-model onslaught, but also remains faithful to Maserati's long history in luxury sports saloons. 

The powerful engine and the large cabin at the core of the Maserati Quattroporte's design, dominated by a long, powerful nose and a concave Trident grille, provide a clear link to both the outgoing Quattroporte and the GranTurismo. 

Even with all of its new technology, the new Quattroporte remains true to Maserati's roots. Its V8 twin turbo makes it not only the fastest four-door Maserati ever built, but also the most powerful and the most fuel efficient. 

The direct-injection engine family will boast a 3.8-litre V8 and a 3.0-litre V6, both of which are all new, twin turbo charged, designed by Maserati Powertrain and assembled by Ferrari at Maranello. 

The 3.8-litre V8 engine provides Maserati's new performance benchmark, reaching 100 km/h in just 4.7 seconds and achieving a 307 km/h top speed. It is 20 km/h faster than the Maserati Quattroporte Sport GT S and delivers up to 200Nm more torque as well. The V6 twin turbo doesn't lack in performance, either, reaching 285 km/h. 

With an eight-speed automatic transmission and both rear-wheel drive and all-wheel drive configurations (V6 only, AWD not available in RHD markets), it is also the most secure all-weather performance car in Maserati's history. 

To offset its scintillating performance, the V8 Maserati Quattroporte has lowered both its fuel consumption and emissions by 20% over the outgoing Quattroporte. 

The all-new architecture retains the Maserati Quattroporte's traditionally exquisite handling thanks to its 50:50 weight distributions, a double-wishbone front suspension and a state-of-the-art five-link rear suspension. It can now deliver the added security and all-weather assurance of all-wheel drive as well. 

It also delivers new standards in quality in every area from design, development, fabrication and process controls. It is produced in a new plant that combines Maserati's traditions of craftsmanship with cutting-edge technologies that are able to guarantee outstanding quality by controlling even the tiniest details. 

Traditional hand crafted detailing continues in the Quattroporte's cabin, now more spacious and featuring both four and five-seat layouts. 

Cabin luxury leaps forward technically too, with features like the Maserati Touch Control screen, adjustable pedals (left hand drive only), reversing camera and the optional 15-speaker Bowers &amp; Wilkins audio system, as well as WLAN-based WiFi and compatibility with most modern mobile phone systems. 

With the original Quattroporte in 1963, Maserati invented the concept of the luxury sports saloon and the new Quattroporte continues to be the benchmark for high quality engineering, supercar performance and comfort. 

EXTERIOR DESIGN 
Maserati has been considered a master of sports saloon design from the day the original 1963 Quattroporte became the first automobile to blend speed and luxury with four doors. 

A powerful engine and a large cabin are at the core of the Maserati Quattroporte's design, dominated by a long, impressive nose with its short overhang. 

"The design of the Quattroporte is inspired by Maserati's core stylistic principles: harmony of proportions, dynamic lines and Italian elegance," Head of Maserati Centro Stile, Marco Tencone explains. 

"Every new model is a step into the future, but for a brand with the strong heritage of Maserati it is fundamental to bring on the most distinctive features as a signature: the contour of the air intake in the front, the three small outlets on the front wings and the strong triangular C pillar bearing the logo". 

"The design has been kept simple and clear - continues Tencone - with a character line flowing on the side to define the strong volume of the rear wing and create a very muscular look. The cabin is sleek, with a three window treatment and frameless doors". 

"The Quattroporte is a high performance sports saloon featuring a light, sensual design that embodies all the most famous stylistic touches of Maserati in a contemporary language". 

But the Maserati Quattroporte body design isn't just about looks; it has delivered a 12% improvement in drag (Cx), down to 0.31, and an enormous 24% reduction in lift. These figures reduce fuel consumption and increase high-speed stability. 

A large part of the Quattroporte's aerodynamic work is out of sight, beneath the car. It has a flat floor that contains several aerodynamic features with the scope of optimizing performance by lowering drag coefficient and keeping the proper cooling of all systems (engines, brakes, and transmission) at speeds over 300 km/h. 

ENGINES 
At the heart of the new Quattroporte is an entirely new engine grid, which follows recent Maserati tradition as it is designed in-house by Maserati Powertrain and manufactured under contract by Ferrari at Maranello. 

V8 TWIN TURBO ENGINE AND PERFORMANCE 
The flagship 3.8-litre V8 engine is a perfect representation of Maserati's performance tradition combined with a 20% reduction in emissions. 

It is almost a liter smaller in capacity than the 4.7-litre V8 in the Quattroporte Sport GT S, yet this is more than countered through twin turbo charging and directs fuel injection to deliver 18% more power and 39% more torque. 

The engine produces 390kW (530 hp) of power at 6800rpm and accompanies this with 650Nm of torque from 2000rpm to 4000rpm. 

This maximum normal torque figure can be over boosted to 710 Nm from 2250rpm to 3500rpm. 

These figures represent the highest specific power output in the class, with 139hp/l, and the best specific torque as well, with 171Nm per liter. 

It also has a considerably more powerful engine than the finely balanced 4.7-litre engine in the Maserati Quattroporte Sport GT S, with a full 59kW (80hp) more power and an astonishing 200Nm more torque (on the overboosted output). The torque peak also arrives at less than half the engine speed of the Sport GT S's V8, too, peaking at 2000rpm versus 4750rpm. 

In addition, its combination of a lighter body design and a stronger engine give the Quattroporte the best power-to-weight ratio in class, with just 3.6kg for each horsepower. 

These engine figures help the Quattroporte reach 100 km/h in just 4.7 seconds, which is 0.3 seconds faster than the previous Sport GT S, making the new Quattroporte the fastest accelerating four-door car in Maserati's history. This also makes it 0.6 seconds faster to 100 km/h than the outgoing Maserati Quattroporte S and almost a second faster than the 4.2-litre Quattroporte. 

Another ground-breaking figure is the Quattroporte's top speed, comfortably breaking through the 300km/h barrier to reach 307km/h. Again, this makes it the fastest four-door Maserati in history and second amongst all Maserati production cars behind the mighty V12-powered MC12. 

However, the new engine is not just about big performance numbers or high torque. Maserati engines have always been known for their incredible throttle response and that unique Maserati sound - and this engine is no different. 

The new engine generation's smaller capacity does help with the Quattroporte's handling too, but Maserati's engineers concentrated mainly on delivering the brand's traditional crisp pickup and low rotational inertia. 

The most technically advanced engine ever fitted to a Maserati, the 3799cc V8, uses a pair of low-inertia, twin-scroll parallel turbos to increase its output. 

Its architecture retains the over-square, free-revving nature of the outgoing V8, with a bore of 86.5mm and a stroke length of 80.8mm, and it has a slightly lower compression ratio of 9.5:1. 

It has been specifically designed to deliver exceptional performance at all engine speeds, combined with lower consumption and emissions. The engine diagrams show that the V8 engine's torque is very high, even at speeds as low as 1500 rpm. 

It uses high-tumble cylinder heads with four cam phasers, (doubling the number of the naturally aspirated V8), in a concept refined by Maserati Powertrain for optimal combustion control to deliver high performance and low consumption. 

With hydraulically adjusted roller finger followers and two continuous cam phasers for each cylinder head, it can advance or retard the inlet and exhaust valve timing independently in real time and it also reduces friction losses compared to old valvetrain systems. 

Another characteristic feature of the new Maserati engine family is the 200 bar direct fuel-injection system. This very high pressure, coupled with seven holes laser drilled oriented holes injectors and multiple injection, helps atomizing the fuel directly in the combustion chamber, thus improving the fuel-air mixture and the combustion process at any engine speed. 

The new V8 engine is boosted by two small parallel twin-scroll turbines, (one for each bank of four cylinders), which provide the high performance expected of a Maserati engine while reducing inertia. Maserati Powertrain focused on integrating the turbine housing into the exhaust manifold for a compact, light-weight solution. 

Each turbocharger is fed by its own air-to-air intercooler. The Quattroporte has two intercoolers, each mounted low and wide of the main radiators to catch a constant supply of fresh, cool air. 

The engine also uses a state-of-the-art ECU, with integral high-speed processors, which handle an array of shifting functions in real time. 

Maserati Powertrain has also switched to on-demand ancillaries, with a variable displacement oil pump that works under electrical control for improved consumption and performance. 

It also uses an innovative, computer-controlled alternator, which monitors the vehicle's electricity consumption and manages the alternator's workload to suit. 

The engine also operates in both Normal and Sport modes, along with Manual versions of either mode, operated by elongated shift paddles fixed to the steering column. 

The new Quattroporte also introduces the I.C.E. (Increased Control and Efficiency) strategy, a function aimed at reducing consumption, emissions and noise. 

It is a user-select strategy and delivers a softer throttle pedal response for smooth driving, cancels the turbocharger's overboost function and keeps the exhaust's Sport flaps closed until 5000rpm. It also adjusts the gearshifts to make them softer and slower and reduces torque at each gear's take-up point. 

Besides delivering the Maserati Quattroporte's peak fuel efficiency figure, the I.C.E. mode is also very useful for driving on low-grip surfaces. 

V6 TWIN TURBO ENGINE AND PERFORMANCE 
The Quattroporte's all-new V6 twin turbo engine is a close relation of the V8, sharing most of its core components. 

With 301kW (410hp) of power at 5500rpm, it still provides a tremendously powerful driving experience, especially with 550Nm of flat torque between 1500rpm and 5000rpm. In Normal mode the torque is smoothed at 500Nm in the lower rpm range, reaching the 550Nm threshold at 5000rpm to guarantee the 301KW of maximum power. 

The engine shares the V8's bore and combustion chamber design, the same valves control technology (i.e. roller finger followers and four cam phasers), the same twin turbocharging approach and direct injection-ignition system. The engine auxiliaries are identical (alternator, starter motor and power steering pump) or very similar (variable displacement oil pump). 

Nonetheless it has a character of its own, revving to a lower 6500rpm maximum speed and delivering its torque level of 500rpm sooner than the V8. 

While its specific power output is slightly lower than that of the V8, at 137hp per liter, its specific torque is actually higher than the larger-engine car's standard specific torque, at 183Nm per liter. 

It is also a lighter car, with 1860kg in its rear-wheel drive configuration (+70kg in all-wheel drive). 

In rear-wheel drive mode, it accelerates to 100 km/h in 5.1 seconds, while the all-wheel drive V6 twin turbo manages the sprint in 4.9 seconds. 

Both cars are still as fast as people would expect from the Maserati brand, with the rear-wheel drive's 285km/h top speed matching the outgoing Sport GT S and the all-wheel drive V6 twin turbo reaching 284km/h. 

The rear and all-wheel drive models are also very similar in their fuel consumption, with both cars posting 10.5 l/100km on the combined cycle, with the rear-wheel drive car claiming 244 grams of CO2/km and the all-wheel drive 246 grams. 

EXHAUST SYSTEM 
In the best Maserati tradition, the sound and performance of the Quattroporte's exhaust system is controlled by pneumatic valves in the pipes of each bank in order to maintain the classic and rich sound characteristic of the brand. 

In the default Normal mode, the bypass valves are closed up to 4,200 rpm to give a comfortable and discreet engine sound. 

In Sport mode, not only does the car adjust a variety of handling parameters, but the exhaust valves are opened, giving the shortest possible high-energy route for the exhaust gases. This gives the Quattroporte its maximum engine performance and the unique Maserati engine sound. 

Beneath the rear bumper, the V8 version finishes its exhaust system with trapezoidal tips with two double pipes in polished steel. 

DRIVETRAIN 
All versions of the new Maserati Quattroporte are fitted with the ZF AT8-HP70 eight-speed automatic transmission. 

Pre-engineered for both rear and all-wheel drive configurations, the transmission delivers increased comfort, faster gear shifting, reduced fuel consumption and reduced NVH (Noise, Vibration and Harshness) values compared to the six-speed automatic in the outgoing Quattroporte. 

By delivering two over-driven gears, the transmission alone delivers relevant fuel economy benefit and also weighs 4kg less than the outgoing six-speed transmission. 

Befitting Maserati tradition, it features five dedicated shift modes: Auto Normal, Auto Sport, Manual Normal, Manual Sport and the I.C.E. mode (Increased Control Efficiency). 

Auto Normal is the Quattroporte's default setting and performs its gear changes with fluid shifts at low engine speeds to emphasize the car's comfort and minimize fuel consumption. 

The Auto Sport mode sees the transmission switch character to change gears with greater alacrity at higher engine speeds and deliver a distinct gear engagement to enhance the powertrain's sporting feel. 

In both of these modes, the car recognizes a variety of conditions, such as whether the car is travelling up or down hill or is braking hard or driving through a corner, and selects the best gear and the best gear-shift style accordingly. 

The transmission can also be controlled manually by selecting the M button on the transmission tunnel. 
In Manual Normal mode, the driver can change gear with either the elongated gearshift paddles attached to the steering column or by using the transmission lever. The driver is in charge of the gear selection, though the system will intervene and change to a lower gear if the engine revs drop too low, or change to a higher gear if the engine revs climb too high. 

In Manual Sport mode, however, the gearshifts are at their fastest and crispest, giving the driver full control of the powertrain. The system will not intervene, even if the driver strikes the engine's rev limiter. It will only intervene if the engine's revs drop too low to be effective in a given gear. 

The I.C.E. (Increased Control Efficiency) mode is designed for remarkable fuel economy, relaxed driving and extremely low grip conditions. The transmission changes gear as softly as possible, both going up through the gears and returning back down. 

All gearshift modes can be selected via buttons on the left of the gear knob. 

The Maserati Quattroporte also utilizes a mechanical limited-slip differential. The asymmetric locking feature offers 35 % lock-up under power and 45 % under release. 

The rear differential is driven via a two-piece, 80mm diameter steel propshaft (hollowed for weight saving) with two constant velocity joints and one head rubber coupling, for comfort improvement. The propshaft runs through a cross member-mounted rubber bearing for higher comfort in respect to vibrations and harshness levels. 

The completely brand new AWD transmission is compact, efficient and light weight. The all-wheel drive system is capable of switching the powertrain torque from full rear, to split axles, rear and front, almost instantly (150ms). The smart logic of the system provides the vehicle with the optimum torque split, thus guaranteeing maximum stability in all driving conditions. 

From the Quattroporte AWD you can expect maximum performance and enjoy maximum traction torque and safety: the system is able to work in team with the ESP for maximum safety even on the most slippery of surfaces, but at the same time is able to operate independently, preserving driving efficacy and sportiness within limits of safety. 

The sensors in the car's body and the AWD CPUs will monitor all vehicle functioning parameters, reacting to each event specifically. The driver can monitor these functions by looking at the display where the front-rear torque split is visible. When the vehicle is running at sustained high speed, the CPU sets all the torque to the rear axle for maximum efficiency and transmission longevity, but then it is always ready to react to ensure optimum safety. 

In addition, the AWD system is mechanically designed to deliver the lowest level of operating noise, and maximum performance. 

CHASSIS 
The chassis of the new Quattroporte has been designed to meet the performance and comfort demands of Maserati buyers, as well as all foreseeable safety regulations. 

With the longest wheelbase in its class, the Quattroporte's architecture lends itself both to extreme interior comfort and an exciting handling platform. 

Based around a rigid and extremely secure steel safety cell, it uses an array of different steel and aluminum alloys, each designed to maximize strength, minimize weight and retain the sports saloon's perfect weight distribution. 

The front of the chassis is based around an aluminum sub frame and a reinforced cross-strut to deliver outstanding rigidity. 

The choice of aluminum for the bulk of the Maserati Quattroporte's body panels guarantees the maximum occupant safety with the lowest possible weight. Accordingly, all four doors, the bonnet, the front wings and the boot lid are all made from aluminum. 

Along with the freedom it allowed Maserati's designers, the choice of aluminum has also had a positive impact on reducing the Quattroporte's weight, thus lowering its fuel consumption and emissions. 

Other diverse materials are also used in the Quattroporte's body, including ultra-light weight magnesium, which is used in the dashboards cross strut. 

AERODYNAMICS 
The modifications to the Quattroporte body design aren't just about looks, but have also allowed for a 12% improvement in drag (Cx), now down to 0.31, and an enormous 24% reduction in lift. These figures reduce fuel consumption and increase high-speed stability. 

The Quattroporte has gone through extensive aerodynamic work, most of which is out of sight, beneath the car. It has a flat floor that contains several aerodynamic features, including a NACA duct to help cool the differential without increasing drag and flaps on the rear suspension arms to channel airflows. 

SUSPENSION 
Double wishbone suspension layouts are a race-bred tradition at Maserati and the new Maserati Quattroporte continues with this heritage, also incorporating some new technology for greater driving precision. 

The front suspension uses high-mounted, all-aluminum double wishbones to guarantee light and precise handling characteristics. 

Aluminum is the dominant metal of the front suspension system with the shock towers, the upper and lower control arms and uprights all made from forged aluminum, while the springs are made of steel. All of these match up to constantly adaptive Skyhook dampers and an anti-roll bar. 

The quadrilateral architecture of the system has enabled Maserati's handling team to deliver steering that is precise, communicative and comfortable. 

The rear suspension employs a five-bar multi-link system, with four aluminum suspension arms, and has been developed to achieve the apparently conflicting goals of exceptional comfort and extreme sports performance. 

The suspension package also uses anti-roll bars and steel springs damped by a faster and more accurate development of the Skyhook adaptive damping system. All four Skyhook dampers can be electronically controlled independently of one another. 

One of the standout features of the new Quattroporte, the default Skyhook mode prioritizes comfort and then becomes more sporting and athletic if the driver presses the suspension button. This extra stiffness transforms the Quattroporte's handling and was developed in both extreme test scenarios and on the race track. Essentially, it drastically reduces both lateral and longitudinal load transfers and minimizes body roll to bring out the sportiest side of the Quattroporte's character. 

The computer system in charge of the Skyhook dampers monitors an enormous array of parameters, including speeds and lateral and longitudinal acceleration, individual wheel movements, body movement and damper dynamics. 

Adjusting also to suit the suspension mode chosen by the driver, the system delivers the perfect damping mode for each wheel almost instantly. 

WHEELS AND TYRES 
Featuring 20-inch rims as standard equipment, the new Quattroporte is also available with either smaller 19-inch rims or larger 21-inch rims. 

The 19" and 20" alloys are crafted from flow-forming technology which reduces the core thickness of the wheels and optimizes light weight, without sacrificing stiffness and strength. 

The 21" rim is a forged alloy wheel, which also emphasizes light weight and weighs no more than the 20" rim. 

All the Maserati Quattroporte's rims have been designed and engineered to enhance the visual design of the body and to lower the unsprung masses to improve grip and handling. 

The 19" wheels, with 245/45 front tires and 275/40 rear tires, are geared towards reduced fuel consumption combined with low road noise and long, comfortable journeys. 

The 20" wheels, with 245/40 front tires and 285/35 rear tires, are the perfect compromise between sportiness and comfort, while the 21" wheels, with a 245/35 front and 285/30 rear tire combination, are focused on sports handling. 

All three wheel sizes are available with Pirelli, Dunlop and Continental tires. The 19" and 20" wheels can also be fitted with winter tires. 

Additionally, the Quattroporte continuously monitors its tyre pressure with a sensor mounted inside the rim, as part of the valve. The pressure can be read off the display on the dashboard. If a tire punctures or its pressure changes, the system notifies the driver with visual and acoustic warnings. 

DIMENSIONS 
The new Quattroporte has grown to set size benchmarks in its class in almost every dimension. It is bigger in every significant dimension than its predecessor including delivering 105mm more rear legroom and 80 liters more luggage capacity than the outgoing Maserati Quattroporte. 

Most importantly, these increases have not created a similar rise in mass, with the Quattroporte weighing almost 100 kg less than the flagship predecessor, (1900kg in V8 form). 

Another vital factor is weight distribution and consequently the Quattroporte retains perfect balance with 50:50 front-to-rear weight. This is despite the forward repositioning of the fuel tank to create greater luggage space and the addition of all-wheel drive, bigger radiators and two intercoolers beneath the bonnet. 

BRAKES 
Maserati has continued its long lasting partnership with Brembo on the new Maserati Quattroporte and all models feature fixed-caliper braking technology. 

The V8-powered models feature 380mm x 34mm ventilated and cross-drilled brake discs inside the front wheels. These brake discs continue to use the technology pioneered by Maserati, which allows the weight of the cast-iron braking surface area to be offset with an alloy hat to minimize unsprung mass. As with the V6 models, the V8's front discs are slowed by six-piston fixed alloy Brembo calipers. 

The rear end of the Quattroporte V8 uses 350mm x 28mm ventilated and cross-drilled brake discs, with four-piston fixed alloy Brembo calipers. 

These brakes, with an enlarged swept area and highly efficient cooling, are designed for consistent performance in sports driving situations. They are also bigger in order to respond to the demands created by the extremely high performance potential of the new Quattroporte. 

The brakes on the V6 twin turbo Quattroporte models are only marginally smaller than the V8 twin turbo's brakes - 360mm x 32mm ventilated and cross-drilled brake discs, with six-piston fixed alloy Brembo calipers on the front axle and carrying over the V8 twin turbo's rear braking hardware. 

However, high-performance stopping power is only one measure of overall braking performance. The collaboration with Brembo has also concentrated on evolving the acoustic comfort of the Maserati Quattroporte's braking systems. 

The Quattroporte also uses an electronic parking brake, which operates on all four wheels. The ergonomically placed button on the gear lever bezel activates the brake when the car is at rest. 

It can also act as a safety device when driving. In this case the system communicates with the stability control ECU and decelerates the car at 0.5g in full safety until released. 

The brakes also operate as part of the Quattroporte's automatic hill starting system. The on-board sensors detect the vehicle's tilt when parked facing uphill, then lock the brakes for a few seconds; this gives the driver's foot time to move from the brake to the accelerator pedal without the vehicle rolling back. 

BRAKE CALIPERS 
Besides their strength and effectiveness, Maserati brake calipers have also always added a significant stylistic effect. 

This continues with the new Quattroporte, with the front and rear brake calipers available in the standard classic black with the Maserati name in white. 

These are also available in red, blue, silver and polished aluminum. 

STEERING 
The Maserati Quattroporte uses an all-new aluminum steering box, developed specifically for the new front-suspension geometry. 

This has allowed Maserati's suspension engineers to deliver ultimate precision combined with the steering sensitivity needed for turning into corners at speed. 

Its reduced steering ratio delivers an agility that is rare for this class of luxury saloon and while it is comfortable in all situations, the steering feel is geared towards driving enjoyment. 

Avoiding electro-hydraulic steering systems, the Quattroporte employs a servo-powered hydraulic system that prevents artificial assistance when the driver turns the wheel quickly. The power assistance has also been reduced compared to the previous Maserati Quattroporte; the intention being to deliver more feedback to the driver for consistency at high speed, yet maintaining easy maneuvering at low speed. 

MASERATI STABILITY PROGRAMME 
Maserati drivers have long known the benefits of the Maserati Stability Programme (MSP) and the system has evolved and improved in the new Quattroporte. 

Developed in the most extreme of test circumstances, the MSP uses a wide array of sensors to detect any need to intervene on the driver's behalf. 

MSP adds a layer of security on top of the new Quattroporte's inherent chassis stability which helps drivers enjoy anxiety-free handling under all driving conditions. 

MSP constantly measures the Quattroporte's handling and grip and combines a host of safety and performance systems to maintain the car's ideal handling stance. 

The MSP most common areas of intervention are the engine and the brakes. If skidding is detected, the MSP reduces the engine's torque output and can actuate the brakes with minute, finely varied inputs to restore the car's stability within milliseconds. 

The other key systems that make up the MSP include: 
ABS - stops the wheels locking up under brakes, thereby maintaining steering control at all times. 
EBD (Electronic Brake Force Distribution) - distributes braking force between the front and rear axles to prevent rear-wheel lock up. 
ASR (Anti-Slip Regulation) - stops the driven wheels from spinning in low-grip situations. 
MSR - prevents the driven wheels from locking up when down-shifting on low-grip surfaces. It does this by measuring the speed of the driven wheels against the speed of the free wheels and accelerating the driven wheels slightly if needed. 
BAS (Brake Apply Sensor) - uses a variety of sensors to recognize panic or emergency braking situations and increases the pressure in the braking circuit. 
Hill Holder - automatically connects to the braking system to prevent roll back when the car moves away from rest on hills. 
SAFETY 
The new Maserati Quattroporte's passive safety equipment has been given a tightly focused overhaul to successfully improve its crash safety, without compromising its weight or fuel consumption. 

Maserati has balanced these conflicting demands by using hot-formed steels in critical areas of the passenger compartment for added occupant safety, while using aluminum in other areas to save weight. 

For example, the front of the passenger compartment (the pillars and under-door mouldings) features hot-moulded steel components, with a magnesium dashboard struts to save weight, while the rear is stiffened with high strength steel. 

The crash bars at the front and rear of the car are made of extruded aluminum, while the doors, engine compartment, mudguards and luggage compartment are in aluminum. 

AIRBAGS 
The New Quattroporte is equipped with a six-airbag system to provide maximum occupant safety. 

At the front, two-stage airbags are concealed from the occupants inside the steering wheel and dashboard to protect the head in case of a frontal impact. 

The chest and hips of the front occupants are further protected by the side airbags located in the seats. 

The sides of the occupants' heads are protected by two "curtain" airbags mounted in the roof of the car, next to the B-pillar. The "curtain" airbag protects the heads of the front and rear occupants against lateral impact. 

SEATBELT FEATURES 
The front seats feature excellent integrated safety equipment designed to reduce trauma to the occupants' cervical vertebrae. 

If the car is involved in a rear-end accident, its active headrests automatically reduce the distance between their surface and the occupants' heads. 

The front and rear three-point seatbelts are equipped with load-limiting pyrotechnic pre-tensioners, which trip in a collision to hold the passengers securely and prevent or minimize injury. 

The front seatbelts are fitted with height adjusters; properly adjusting the height of the seatbelts to the occupant's height, which is not only more comfortable but also improves the safety function of the device. 

REAR VIEW CAMERA 
The rear-view parking camera, standard on the new Maserati Quattroporte, makes manoeuvring and reversing safer and more comfortable. 

Installed next to the luggage compartment's release button, it views the area behind the car and shows the resulting color image on the 8.4" MTC display. The system works together with the standard parking sensors and an acoustic warning can be heard as it approaches obstacles behind the car. 

LIGHTING 
The Quattroporte's exterior design is so distinctive partly due to its Bi-xenon headlights and LED daytime running lights. 

The LED tail light assembly is also highly innovative, providing excellent visibility as well as the style and safety essential to this class of car. 

HEADLIGHTS 
The standard headlights contain an Automatic Frontlighting System (AFS), which actively adjusts the headlight depth to combine an outstanding view of the road with very low glare for oncoming traffic. 

The bi-xenon headlights combine technology and style, while all of its secondary functions are provided entirely by LED. 

Each headlight includes LED daytime running lights, with a light shape that provides instant recognisability in both day and night running. Each light also contains a high-pressure lens washer nozzle, direction indicators, LED side position lights and a side reflector. 

With a video camera mounted in front of the rear-view mirror, the lighting system offers a beam control specifically for motorway driving. This increases the depth of the light beam, without the need for manual high beam activation. 

Sensors monitor the driving style and speed and, if the road is clear, the beam depth offers the maximum depth and width combined with the directional rotation of the headlights themselves. 

In addition, there are four different automatic lighting setups: for city driving, motorway conditions, low visibility and for driving on the opposite side of the road in applicable countries. Each of these modes automatically activates a strategy to best illuminate the road surface. 

The town beam turns on below 45km/h and sets the beam wider and shallower, giving a better view for turning and for peripheral danger zones, whilst causing minimum disturbance for fellow road users. 

There is also a rain beam, which comes on when the windscreen wipers operate for a continuous period. The individual beams are set to different levels to minimize reflections, while the outer beams are set wider and higher to make the Maserati Quattroporte more visible to other road users. 

Note: In the USA and Canada, cars are not equipped with the AFS function. They retain the automatic depth and rotation control functions. The beam rotation function and the four AFS functions may be deactivated via the menu in the European Union, whilst in the USA only the beam rotation function may be deactivated in this way. 

TAIL LIGHTS 
The Quattroporte's tail lights have been designed to offer maximum visibility and to have a recognizable style. These full LED lights integrate the position light function in an illuminated ring running right around the tail light itself. Inside this ring are the brake lights, the direction indicators, reversing lights and fog lights. The outside reflector and LED side position lights round off the unit. 

INTERIOR 
The interior of the new Quattroporte combines refined, timeless design with high technology and a functional sporting character. 

The increases in the size of the Maserati Quattroporte have brought a huge evolution in roominess for the front and especially the rear passengers. Its increased wheelbase has allowed Maserati to add more rear legroom, more shoulder room for all passengers and more luggage capacity. 

"The interior achieves elegant simplicity, with clean lines and a user-friendly interface" Mr Tencone said, " assuming that less is more when carefully designed". 

"The functional features are downplayed to focus the attention on the top class natural materials - wood, leather, metal - and the refined craftsmanship with which they have been worked". 

"The combination of classy and elegant colors makes the interior an exclusive lounge for the occupants that can become unique with a tailored approach for each customer". 

Confirming Mr Tencone's views, the Quattroporte's interior shows streamlined, wraparound forms, which give the dashboard and tunnel an unprecedented feeling of lightness 

Like all Maseratis, the Quattroporte features a driver interface that is intuitive and simple to use. The instrument cluster has a large speedometer and a large tachometer that flank a 7" TFT display used for many of the car's operational features. 

The leather-finished steering wheel is electrically adjustable for both reach and height, while the pedals are also adjustable (LHD cars only), moving towards the driver at the touch of a button mounted at the front of the driver's seat. 

Many of the vehicle's settings are oriented towards the driver and are controlled with the buttons alongside the gear shifter, while other on-board settings can be set by the driver via the Maserati Touch Control (MTC) at the centre of the dashboard. 

The Quattroporte standard equipment includes leather, heated front seats with 12-way electrical adjustment, dual-zone climate controlled air conditioning and active cruise control, while the upper and lower dashboard and the interior upholstery are wrapped in Poltrona Frau Leather. 

MASERATI TOUCH CONTROL (MTC) 
By utilizing the MTC's 8.4" Touch Screen display, the user can control almost all of the Maserati Quattroporte's on-board equipment simply and intuitively. 

The system includes radio, satellite navigation and DVD player. It also has Bluetooth connection to connect to external sources like mobile phones and Apple devices. 

Using its Aux-in, USB sockets or the SD card reader, the user can play music, watch films or even view images. 

Its menus have options to configure the car's main settings and the system's various menus are always available from the icons displayed at the bottom of the screen. 

The MTC also controls the front seat heating and ventilation, the steering wheel heating and the operation of the rear window shade, as well as providing the screen for the reversing camera. 

CRUISE CONTROL 
An active cruise control system is standard on the new Quattroporte. The controls for this system are mounted on the steering wheel and the speed is shown on the instrument panel display. 

WI-FI HOTSPOT 
The new Quattroporte contains optional WLAN technology that effectively turns it into a rolling Wi-Fi HotSpot. 

A SIM card can be placed into its WLAN router to receive Internet signals, which can be resent around the car as a wireless Internet signal. 

Up to three devices, such as laptops, mobile phones or tablets can be connected simultaneously. The system supports HSDPA, UMTS, EDGE and GSM. 

AUDIO 
The optional Bowers &amp; Wilkins Premium Surround System is as good as it gets in production car hi-fi systems. The choice of components, the layout of the 15 speakers and the perfect configuration of HARMAN's QuantumLogic™ Surround Sound processing and system integration is the result of a long and very demanding process of experimentation and countless hours of listening by the best ears in the audio business. 

Bowers &amp; Wilkins has close to 50 years' experience in the development of drive units and their materials. Materials like Kevlar - introduced in speaker cones by Bowers &amp; Wilkins in the 1970s - are the result of decades of commitment to acoustic research and development. For the tweeter aluminum offers a combination of lightness and rigidity that's ideal, as the sound extends to the very limits of human hearing, unlike lesser fabric domes. For speed, stiffness and unshakable bass, Rohacell, which is normally used for aircrafts, rockets and performance cars' bodies, is the perfect cone material. 

The result is an audio system that perfectly reproduces every nuance of the recording; with crisp, pristine treble, amazing natural dynamics, and impressive bass. The system's natural, realistic performance delivers a completely new level of musical enjoyment on the road. 

The Bowers &amp; Wilkins premium surround system features: 
15 speakers 
5 x 25mm aluminum dome tweeters 
5 x 100mm Kevlar midrange drivers 
2 x 165mm Kevlar bass/midrange drivers 
2 x 165mm Rohacell bass drivers 
1x 350x200mm racetrack subwoofer 
16 channel Class D amplifier, with a combined output 1,280W 
QuantumLogic™ Surround Sound processing 
CLEVER KEY 
Incorporating Keyless Go technology, the body of the new Quattroporte's key is made from polished aluminum and looks and feels heavy, elegant and technically advanced. 

When the car is locked, it is enough to keep the key in a pocket or a handbag and simply open the car by pulling on the door handle or luggage compartment button. This way, there is no need to always find the key to push a button to open the car. 

SPACE 
One objective was clear right from the start: to maximize the space available to the occupants. Special attention has been paid to the rear passengers, and the legroom available to them is the highest in the standard wheelbase class. 

Two individual rear seats have also been developed as an option, to deliver outstanding comfort and prestige, and they offer unbeatable relaxation by featuring ventilation and electrical movement, in addition to standard heating. 

Furthermore, the interior features two front cup holders, four 12V power sockets, (one in the luggage compartment), a rear USB charging port and a number of large compartments: two at the bottom of the dashboard (a climate controlled, illuminated passenger glove compartment, and another for the driver), and a large front armrest. 

The rear seats are also modular in a 40/60 pattern: the smallest part can be folded down, thus allowing long objects to be stored in the back and inside the 530-litre luggage compartment. 

SEATING 
The luxurious leather seats offer the highest levels of comfort and support. The three-seats in the rear are designed to provide exceptional comfort along with abundant legroom. 

To highlight the attention paid to outstanding comfort and prestige, two individual seats have also been developed as an option, featuring ventilation and electrical movement, to offer unbeatable relaxation during long working trips. They can also be fitted with individual entertainment screens. 

The three rear seats are heated and the door panels feature electrical sun blinds, along with the rear window sun blind. 

The rear armrest has a USB socket for charging mobile devices and two foldaway cup holders. Finally, the seats are equipped with ISOFIX fittings, the universal child seat mounting system. 

The interior of the new Maserati Quattroporte not only features unique styling and valuable materials, but also uses light to further enhance its lines and to improve the quality of the occupants' experience when driving in the dark. 

The system uses an optical fiber running along the dashboard and the doors, and even in the door handle cavities and door pockets, to give the interior a modern, sophisticated look. 

The front and rear ceiling lights mount a diffused lighting lamp and two separate reading lights; along with these, two LEDs concealed in the ceiling light give constant soft light for the area beneath them; even the foot area is illuminated. The brightness of the light can be adjusted with a dimmer. 

REAR SEAT ENTERTAINMENT 
With the option of the rear-seat entertainment unit, the Quattroporte will feature two tilting 10.2" LCD displays. Rear-seat occupants can either view the same content simultaneously, individually or watch completely different content. 

The system allows users to reproduce audio, video or photographs from external sources and it can deliver them in formats ranging from MPEG, WMV, Xvid, MP3, MP4, WMA and AAC. 

It also has an A/V-IN connection for devices like video game consoles, cameras, video cameras and laptops. In addition, it can be equipped with a television tuner in Europe and China. 

Each monitor comes with individual battery-powered remote and wireless headphones. 

WINDOWS 
The new Maserati Quattroporte is intended not only to be safe and technically superb, but also comfortable. 

The windscreen and the rear window are both made from double laminated acoustic glass. As 51% of a car's external noise enters the cabin through the windscreen, the use of acoustic glass means Maserati could make the cabin more comfortable and focus on delivering just the type of noise Maserati owners prefer. 

The side windows employ similar technology with single-layer lamination and acoustic damping, thus reducing external noise and stabilizing internal temperature, and at the same time, increasing the occupants' comfort and safety. 

In addition, all three rear windows can be fitted with darkened glass for greater privacy. 

CLIMATE CONTROL SYSTEM 
The automatic climate control operates on a dual-zone system and delivers huge amounts of air through 13 ventilation ports: a demister on the windscreen, four outlets on the dashboard, two on the joint between the front pillars and upper door surround, two at the feet of the front occupants, two central ports on the rear unit and two more at the feet of the rear occupants. 

The four rear ventilation ports balance their output via a sunlight sensor. This provides outstanding levels of comfort and seamless maintenance of the chosen temperature. 

There are separate temperature adjustment functions for the driver and the passenger, which can be controlled through the MTC or via a physical control panel under the screen. 

Delivering 455 cubic meters of air an hour, the system performs much better than its predecessor, cooling or heating the air far faster than ever before. 

This power is driven by a variable-displacement compressor that is electronically controlled to ensure that its operation matches perfectly to the exact demands of the car's occupants. 

A wide array of sensors help the system maintains its internal environment, including a humidity sensor that governs the flow from the defrosting and demisting ports. Additionally, there is a sunlight sensor that regulates the temperature of the air from the ports to nullify the effects of the sunlight and outside temperature. 

A four-zone climate control system, which increases comfort for the rear passengers, is optional. It contains a dedicated nebuliser and two additional ports on the B-pillars to increase airflow to the rear of the car. It also delivers a separate temperature control unit for the rear passengers.﻿

Meer lezen (1032 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-rSysX8nSys8/UMnd4AFXDdI/AAAAAAAARTY/poWRCySe4V4/w426-h309/Maserati-11.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/116655151902977944784/albums/5776920403804575137/5776920401529991922</link><title>Remember to check all the fluids of your vehicle. The temperature of the vehicle not only affects the fluid levels but could cause injury if you come in contact with the hot engine parts. 

Oil Change:While it is a good idea to follow the recommendation of your vehicle’s manufacturer, we recommend that you give your vehicle an oil change every 5,000 miles. Oil changes go hand in hand with replacing your filter. An oil change is only good when you replace the old filters as well. Think of making fresh coffee with the old filter, it’s never as good as when the filter is brand new. 

The oil levels should be checked at regular intervals or before trips. Changing and checking your vehicle’s oil is an inexpensive task that will ensure that it operates trouble free, extending the life of your engine and preventing costly repairs. When you add oil to the vehicle be sure not to add too much as excessive oil can cause serious engine problems. If disposing of the oil and keeping clean is not for you, Car Crafters can give you an oil change with all the accessories (filters and tire rotation) for only 30 minutes of your time. Without promotional discounts oil changes are approx. $32! 

Coolant: Remember, in order to avoid injury, never check the coolant when the vehicle is hot. Most new cars have a “coolant reservoir” that allows you to check the levels without opening the radiator cap; it should be closer to the Low mark when cold and closer to the High mark when hot. If the level is low and fluid needs to be added, use the correct coolant concentration as recommended by the manufacturer. In order to maintain the correct PH balance of the coolant, the entire coolant should be changed out a minimum of once every two years. Doing this will ensure the integrity of the gasket materials and prevent the premature failure of many components. 

Windshield Washer Fluid: Make sure and only use windshield washer fluid as it contains anti-freeze and anti-corrosion ingredients. If you use water, your reservoir will freeze and possibly crack during the winter season. 
Brake Fluid: It is a good practice to bleed brakes at least once a year as moisture tends to get trapped in the brake caliper and will eventually lead to caliper replacement. 

My brakes are making a funny noise. A chirping noise or continuous squeals and grinding noises almost always mean that your brakes are in need of a mechanic’s attention immediately. Brakes are designed to give you a warning when it is time for new brake pads; if the brake pads or shoes are replaced immediately when the chirping noise begins you can avoid expensive brake rotor replacement costs that will be incurred after the indicators are worn.﻿

Meer lezen (44 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-W67e0Md8L20/UCu-f2zm8vI/AAAAAAAAAyA/g-RJHc7uuEU/s426/lube.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/116655151902977944784/albums/5729806318470547761/5729806323028623842</link><title>Preventative maintenance 
\- Oil Changes 
\- Transmission fluid service 
\- Radiator coolant flush 
\- Belts 
\- Tire Rotation Brake Systems 
Alignments 
Diagnostics 
Tune-ups 
Factory recommended services 
Pre-purchase and pre-trip inspections﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-fyjupUPdVF4/T4RcfjPogeI/AAAAAAAAAhg/QEbE2CWlNUU/w426-h319/Estimators.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/106143130461432755257/albums/5751766145637900641/5751766146628394994</link><title>5 Tips for Summer Car Maintenance 

Winter driving can be tough on cars, with its icy roads and salt buildup. But summer has its hazards, too. The heat stresses the engine, wears down the tires and makes the car work harder to keep everything cool. 
Here are five steps to help your car make it through the summer. 

1\. Be kind to your engine. 

Your engine gets hot very quickly in the summer. You can save a lot of trouble — and expense — by doing some routine checks to make sure it stays lubricated and cooled. Check the oil level and make sure the oil looks clean. If it doesn't, get an oil change. Sears will change it for less than $20. Also look for cracks in the hoses, which pump coolant from the radiator to the engine block. 

2\. Replace your fluids. 

Many drivers don't think about fluids beyond their motor oil. But your car also has coolant for the engine in the radiator, and fluids for the transmission and brakes. 

They're critical for keeping parts lubricated and preventing your engine from overheating. Over time, all of them lose their effectiveness and get dirty, with little metal parts floating in the liquid. 

"Coolant starts to eat everything. It becomes like an acid," says Hisham Ebrahim, a mechanic at Fawzi's Westgate Auto Repair in Ann Arbor, Mich. Both low fluid levels and old fluid can damage the parts in your car. 

If you follow your car's maintenance schedule, you shouldn't have to worry about fluid levels, which are often checked and replaced around 60,000 miles. 

Ebrahim says it costs about $200 to $300 to flush out and replace all the fluids. That can be far less expensive than the alternative: An overheated engine or blown transmission. 

3\. Replace your windshield wipers. 

Don't wait until you're caught in a summer downpour to find out your wipers aren't working well. Winter can take a toll on wipers, and it's a $25 fix to replace them. You can also get wiper refills — which just replace the worn rubber — for half the cost of new blades. 

4\. Switch out your tires and check the tread. 

If you have winter tires, change them. The compounds used in winter tires are softer, which helps them grip better in ice and snow. But they also wear down more quickly in summer heat. You need plenty of tread in the summer, when sudden showers create slippery roads. 

The Rubber Manufacturers Association suggests several ways to check the tread. Tires have built-in "wear bars," or narrow strips of rubber across the tires that appear when the tread is worn down to one-sixteenth of an inch. If you can see wear bars, your tires need to be replaced. 

You can also use the old penny trick: Stick a penny in the tread. If you can see all of Lincoln's head, it's time to replace the tire. 

Consider a tire rotation in the summer to make sure all your tires are getting equal wear. Tires should be rotated every 5,000 to 10,000 miles, according to vehicle information site Edmunds.com. That can cost around $50, but prices vary widely. 

5\. Check your tire pressure. 

Overinflated tires have less traction on rainy streets, while underinflated tires can bulge out, putting pressure on the sidewalls and making the tires more vulnerable to blowouts on hot roads. Check your tire pressure before you start driving, and make sure you're meeting the manufacturer's recommended level. You can buy a tire gauge for $5 or less, or a digital tire pressure gauge for $25, and keep it in the glove compartment. 

-Courtesy of MainStreet.com﻿

Meer lezen (77 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-c9rLUmXkO7E/T9Jg1hDnH_I/AAAAAAAAB_U/y4VXorA869U/w426-h377/car2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/105854092670688607102/albums/5930521385027047617/5930521387752935266</link><title>Did you know that October is fall #CarCareMonth? Check out some of our new #deals to help you celebrate: 
$9.99 fall car care package (including tire rotation, tire inspection + 4 other services) 
*Buy 1, Get 1 50% on select maintenance services, including coolant fluid service, brake fluid exchange, bulb replacement &amp; wiper blade replacement 
$21.99 standard oil change - includes a FREE battery check 
Print coupons:  http://ow.ly/psuP6 ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_e51ObHgjcE/Uk1xx-nez2I/AAAAAAAAAr0/wE6cFPw0Fmg/w426-h237/FirestoneCompleteAutoCare_Whatever_You_Drive_Drive_a_Firestone.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7468-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/car%20change%20radiator%20fluid/photos/101655845735588056287/albums/5973512311813813345/5973512311425698370</link><title>Cracked Engine Block Symptoms 

We go through some symptoms to help diagnose whether you have a cracked engine block or blown head gasket. Follow these steps to help point you in the right direction 

Antifreeze In Oil 
Coolant in Oil 
 Just like a cracked engine block allowing engine oil to mix with the antifreeze the opposite can also happen. Antifreeze can mix with circulating engine oil this only happens when an engine block has a deep enough crack, allowing the antifreeze to pass into the engine oils passageways. Usually when antifreeze is contaminated with oil an odour will be produces with a visible smoke exiting the exhaust, or a cloudy milky-coloured oil that can be spotted on the engines dipstick. 

Oil In Antifreeze 
Oil in Coolant 
 A major sign of a cracked engine block or blown head gasket is when you can see the engines antifreeze has mixed with the oil. A cracked block or blown head gasket can let the circulating engine antifreeze to mix with passing engine oil. The engine block has small channels where oil and coolant pass through and circulate a vehicle's engine. If an engine block crack happens close enough to these channels, passing engine oil can mix with and pollute circulating antifreeze. Fortunately checking this is easily done by removing the radiator cap and inspecting. 

Low Engine Compression 
compression test 

Engine compression is the result of engine combustion; the combustion is housed within the engine cylinders which are located within the engine block. A crack in the engine block can be the cause of low compression. This will cause engine combustion pressure to be disrupted lowering the engine compression causing poor engine performance. 

Engine Smoke 
engine smoke 
Engine smoke is a major sign of a cracked engine block. Smoke from an engine is normally caused by a severely cracked engine block. This is often a sign of a severe engine block crack or fracture, normally coinciding with severe engine performance issues in addition to visible smoke. 

Visual Crack in Block 
crack in engine block A routine visual vehicle inspection can sometimes be enough to fine a cracked engine block. If your engine is clean and free from excess dirt or grime a visual inspection could be enough to spot a problem these should be noticed when a service or possibly M.O.T is taking place. More often than not large engine block cracks cause obvious symptoms, but in some situations where there is no mechanical symptoms but you suspect a problem ask for it to be checked during routine maintenance or servicing. 

Engine Overheating 
Engine Overheating 
Engine overheating will occur when a cracked engine block is severe enough to allow engine antifreeze to leak, this will cause the engine temperature to rise and in turn cause the engine to overheat. Engine antifreeze travels within an engine block around the combustion chambers. Only severe engine block cracks or cracks that are deep inside the engine expose the passageways where the antifreeze circulates would cause the engine to overheat. 

Checklist For A Blown Engine Block: 
• Check your oil and antifreeze. If you think there is any discolouration or changes to either have then tested. 
• Check if your engine is leaking oil or coolant. This will cause your engine to overheat quickly. 
• Check for codes flashing on the dashboard. This is often happens with reduced performance or a noticeable change in the way the car feels while driving. 
• Check the level of fluid in the radiator. If your car suddenly loses coolant or the level is very low this can be a sign of a cracked block. 
• React quickly if you notice excessive smoke coming out of the exhaust. 
• Check the radiator’s mixture of coolant, antifreeze and water to see if it has frozen. 
• Check to see if the engine has overheated. Overheating can be caused by another engine problem, usually the head gasket but the overheating can be a cracked block.﻿

Meer lezen (99 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7468_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-pi7ZVq-8oEI/UuYtzFfzikI/AAAAAAAAANM/D9lDBEsp6kg/w426-h320/cracked_engine_block.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>