<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:48:41" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/109780686446922422512/albums/5986738431445142417/5986738430208357442</link><title>Tutorial: Raspberry Pi GPIO Pins and Python 

The GPIO pins on a Raspberry Pi are a great way to interface physical devices like buttons and LEDs with the little Linux processor. If you’re a Python developer, there’s a sweet library called RPi.GPIO that handles interfacing with the pins. In just three lines of code, you can get an LED blinking on one of the GPIO pins. 

http://makezine.com/projects/tutorial-raspberry-pi-gpio-pins-and-python﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QXnOpbFYrts/UxUq4he_tEI/AAAAAAAAmR8/FoVOkAPSEwg/w426-h263/fb_fig0701.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/114040550910618745631/albums/5974339057352925809/5974339064648977618</link><title>I recently finished working on the first version of a "smart" wall clock based on a Raspberry Pi Model B. Since this kind of setup allows you to create endless solutions while being extremely simple to develop, I think sharing the basics about how I did it could be interesting. 

THE BASICS 
The smart clock shows the current time and weather, a weather forecast for the next 18 hours and waiting time at the bus stops closer to my house. As you'll read, configuring the kind of data displayed is really easy, and it only requires a little knowledge of Linux systems (in my case, the Raspbian distribution) and PHP (even if you can also use Python, NodeJS or any other language). 

SHOPPING LIST 
First of all, you'll need a Raspberry Pi computer. I chose the "Model B" because it is a little bit more powerful than the original one. You can buy one from one of the Raspberry official resellers (a list is available here: http://www.raspberrypi.org/ ). If you live in Italy, you'll find that buying it on Amazon.it is easier than ordering it from the official sellers. I bought mine at this link http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B008PT4GGC/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B008PT4GGC&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21. 

The second step is to buy an SD card. Check the list of compatible SD Cards on the Raspberry Pi site. I am using this one bought (once again) on Amazon: http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B000OF2F36/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B000OF2F36&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21 

Your next step is finding a way to provide power to the Raspberry. You have two choices: if you plan to use a modern TV as a monitor for your clock, then you can just plug the Raspberry into one of the TV's USB ports; the other solution is to use any micro-USB adaptor (yes, the one that comes with your Android or Windows Phone mobile will work perfectly). Should you need to buy one, Amazon is still a good place where you can find a cheap power adaptor ( http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B003XRQE3E/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B003XRQE3E&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21 ). Every Raspberry Pi official seller has its own adaptor. 
Also, I noticed that sites like Adafruit ( http://www.adafruit.com/ ) sell a "Raspberry Starter Kit" that already contains the Raspberry itself, the power adaptor and the SD card. You might consider buying one of them. 

Another thing you'll need is a monitor. My specific need was to have something extremely small, so I chose to buy a 4.3'' LCD monitor. This kind of monitors are the one that you are using as rearview monitors on your car, they're very cheap (mine cost me around 26 EUR) but not too accurate in displaying fancy graphics (consider this if your design contains a lot of pictures and low-contrast graphics). My idea is to fit everything, Raspberry + Monitor in some sort of box and hang it to the wall next to my apartment's entrance door. If your requirements are different, maybe you'll find a different solution. Anyway, the monitor that I am using is like this one, again, from Amazon: http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B009VYKGLO/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B009VYKGLO&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21. 

You will probably need to find a way to supply power to the monitor: This kind of device is designed to work on cars, so you'll need to buy a power adaptor to make it work in your house. Amazon is full of cheap devices that will do this job, just like this one: http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B002TPY1VS/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B002TPY1VS&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21 

Another thing that you have to consider is the internet connection: the Raspberry comes with an Ethernet port, if you plan to use WI-FI you have to buy a USB adaptor; again, check the Raspberry Pi site for a list of compatible devices, the one that I am using is this one: http://www.amazon.it/gp/product/B002VGQQAE/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=3370&amp;creative=23322&amp;creativeASIN=B002VGQQAE&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=simonlippo06-21 

Raspberry Pi: 38.90 EUR 
SD Card: 6.08 EUR 
Power adaptor for the Raspberry: 16.99 EUR 
Monitor: 29.55 EUR 
Power adaptor for the monitor: 14.14 EUR 
Wi-fi USB adaptor: 12.08 EUR 
\-------------------------------------------------------------------- 
Total: 117.74 

INITIAL SETUP 
First thing you'll need to do is setting up your Raspberry properly. Follow the instructions that you can find on the Raspberry website ( http://www.raspberrypi.org/downloads ) on how to install the latest Raspbian version on your SD card. The process won't take more than 30 minutes; once it's completed, just insert your SD card into the Raspberry, plug the power in, and start some advanced configuration. During this process, my advice is to connect the Raspberry to a real monitor, just to be able to read what appears on the screen. 

Now you have to setup your network connection: if you plugged an ethernet cable in, then you don't need to do anything. If you are using the USB wi-fi adaptor, follow this tutorial to configure it: http://www.raspberryshake.com/raspberry-pi-wireless-network-setup/ 

The next phase consists of updating your system (type sudo apt-get update) and installing the server-side software you'll need. I wrote my bots with PHP, so I installed Apache and Php5 with mod_curl. Follow this tutorial: http://www.dingleberrypi.com/2012/09/tutorial-install-apache-php-and-mysql-on-raspberry-pi/ for step-by-step instructions. 

Now your Raspberry is ready to be transformed into a Kiosk or, since the monitor you bought is smaller than the one on your iphone, a wall clock. Follow this tutorial to install chromium and configure your Raspberry to boot with a full-screen chromium instance: http://blogs.wcode.org/2013/09/howto-boot-your-raspberry-pi-into-a-fullscreen-browser-kiosk/ If you plan to use a small analog monitor as a display, you can skip any editing at the /boot/config.txt file. 

Once it's done, you're almost set. Shut the Raspberry off, disconnect it from the "real" monitor and connect it to your small monitor. Turn the power on and see what happens. 

Well, actually I know what will happen. The Raspberry will start, and you'll see a lot of unreadable lines on your monitor. Since the screen that you are using is analog, the Raspberry is unable to read its resolutions and properties, so you'll have to manually configure them. Just use another computer to SSH into your Raspberry Pi, and follow this tutorial on how to setup the screen resolution: http://learn.adafruit.com/using-a-mini-pal-ntsc-display-with-a-raspberry-pi/overview you'll probably need to play a lot with the overscan settings: my monitor was sold as a 480x272px but I was forced to add more than 50px at the top and as overscan... This is the most boring part, because every time you'll edit a parameter you'll need to reboot to see the changes. But once it's one, you're all set! 
In the next post I'll spend a couple of words on how the interface was created, and on how to create some simple bots written in PHP.﻿

Meer lezen (132 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-N-Zl-ed1Vo0/UukdudQkTNI/AAAAAAAAJvY/O00cCZMFBDs/w426-h320/unnamed.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/114424163811716070551/albums/5701287279516143745/5701287277453833650</link><title>Over 200 Free Online Educational Resources (v.2.3) 

Warning: Very long post. Please open in a new browser tab. 

Here is decades' worth of knowledge freely available online for those who love to learn. Links that fit under multiple categories are listed only once. 

What are your favorite sites to learn from? What sites would you add to this list? 

(View the original post for any future updates: http://goo.gl/8HLFw) 

CONTENTS: 

I. Top Picks 
II. Universities and Higher Education (updated to v.2.0 on 1/27/12) 
III. General Collections (updated to v.2.3 on 2/10/12) 
IV. How-to &amp; DIY 
V. Studying with Peers 
VI. Online Books, eBooks, &amp; Journals 
VII. Computers, Software, &amp; Programming (updated to v.2.2 on 2/6/12) 
VIII. Science &amp; Math (updated to v.2.3 on 2/10/12) 
IX. Logic, Words, &amp; Memory 
X. Languages 
XI. Music (updated to v.1.2 on 1/26/12) 
XII. History 
XIII. Business, Economics, Finance, &amp; Investing (updated to v.1.2 on 1/26/12) 
XIV. Food, Nutrition, &amp; Cooking 
XV. Survival Tips 
XVI. Documentaries &amp; Film Studies (updated to v.2.3 on 2/10/12) 
XVII. Other 

=========== 

I. TOP PICKS 

Khan Academy 
http://www.khanacademy.org/ 

Academic Earth - Online courses from the world's top scholars 
http://academicearth.org/ 

TED - Technology, Entertainment, &amp; Design 
http://www.ted.com/ 

MIT Open CourseWare 
http://ocw.mit.edu/courses/ 

Stanford Engineering Everywhere 
http://see.stanford.edu/see/courses.aspx 

Open Yale Courses 
http://oyc.yale.edu/ 

About U. - Collection of free online courses from About.com 
http://u.about.com/ 

Wikiversity 
http://en.wikiversity.org/wiki/Wikiversity:Main_Page 

YouTube EDU 
http://www.youtube.com/education?b=400 

The Open University - Study at the OU 
http://www3.open.ac.uk/study/ 
http://openlearn.open.ac.uk/ 

University of the People 
www.uopeople.org 

University of Reddit 
http://ureddit.com/ 

Open Culture - The best free cultural &amp; educational media on the web 
http://openculture.com/ 

VideoLectures - Exchange ideas &amp; share knowledge 
http://videolectures.net/ 

CosmoLearning - Free educational website with thousands of courses &amp; documentaries 
http://www.cosmolearning.com/ 

================================ 

II. UNIVERSITIES &amp; HIGHER EDUCATION 

Lecture Fox - Free university lectures 
http://lecturefox.com/ 

Faculty Project - The best professors from the world's leading Universities 
http://facultyproject.com/ 

Google in Education 
http://www.google.com/edu/index.html 

More Open Courses: 

OCW Search - Find free university courses online 
http://www.ocwsearch.com/ 

Open Courseware Consortium 
http://www.ocwconsortium.org/ 

Harvard Extension School - Computer Science &amp; Technology 
http://computerscience1.tv/2010/spring/ 

Johns Hopkins University 
http://ocw.jhsph.edu/ 

Kaplan University 
http://ocw.kaplan.edu/ 

Notre Dame 
http://ocw.nd.edu/ 

Princeton's Institute for Advanced Study 
http://video.ias.edu/all 

Tufts 
http://ocw.tufts.edu/ 

Utah State 
http://ocw.usu.edu/ 

ArsDigita University - Computer science and math lectures 
http://aduni.org/courses/ 

UC Berkeley Webcast - Central service for online video &amp; audio for learners around the globe 
http://webcast.berkeley.edu/ 

UC Berkeley Video Courses - Free education online 
http://education.jimmyr.com/ 

Capilano University 
http://ocw.capilanou.ca/ 

Carnegie Mellon Open Learning Initiative 
http://oli.web.cmu.edu/openlearning/ 

Delft University of Technology 
http://ocw.tudelft.nl/courses/ 

Rice University Connexions - A place to view and share educational modules 
http://cnx.org/ 

Stanford on iTunes U - Stanford-related digital audio content 
http://itunes.stanford.edu/content/overview.html 

UC Irvine 
http://ocw.uci.edu/ 

UC San Diego Podcasts 
http://podcast.ucsd.edu/ 

University of Chicago's Mind Online - Thought-provoking samples of critical thinking &amp; debate 
http://news.uchicago.edu/multimedia 

University of Colorado, Colorado Springs 
http://www.uccs.edu/~math/vidarchive.html 

University of Massachusetts 
http://ocw.umb.edu/ 

University of Michigan 
http://open.umich.edu/education 

University of Southern Queensland 
http://ocw.usq.edu.au/ 

University of Sydney - Podcast episodes 
http://sydney.edu.au/podcasts/2011.php 

University of Virginia - Podcasts &amp; webcasts 
http://www.virginia.edu/uvapodcast/ 

University of Washington - Computer Science &amp; Engineering 
http://www.cs.washington.edu/education/course-webs.html 

Utah Valley University - Online courses &amp; open educational resources 
http://open.uvu.edu/ 

YouTube Channels: 

Stanford 
http://www.youtube.com/stanford 

Stanford Class Central - YouTube summaries of Stanford's online courses 
http://www.class-central.com/ 

UC Berkeley 
http://www.youtube.com/user/UCBerkeley 

University of New South Wales 
http://www.youtube.com/user/UNSWelearning 

Yale 
http://www.youtube.com/yalecourses 

India's NPTEL 
http://www.youtube.com/user/nptelhrd 

====================== 

III. GENERAL COLLECTIONS 

Udemy - Take and build online courses on any subject 
http://www.udemy.com/ 

Free Video Lectures - 800+ Online Courses and 19,000+ Videos from Top 30+ Universities on 35+ Categories 
http://freevideolectures.com/ 

100 Intro Open Courses on Everything You've Ever Wanted to Learn 
http://www.bestcollegesonline.com/blog/2010/05/12/100-intro-open-courses-on-everything-youve-ever-wanted-to-learn/ 

Annotum (formerly Google's Knol) 
http://annotum.org/ 

InfoCoBuild's Free Education - Audio/video lectures for academic courses 
http://www.infocobuild.com/education/education.html 

IncrediCampus - Lectures and preparation/admission advice for college &amp; graduate schoolshttp://www.incredicampus.com/ 

Learners TV - Thousands of downloadable video lectures on liberal arts, science, engineering, and more 
http://www.learnerstv.com/ 

Online Education Database - 200 free online classes to learn anything 
http://oedb.org/library/beginning-online-learning/200-free-online-classes-to-learn-anything 

Infoplease - All the knowledge you need 
http://www.infoplease.com/ 

MERLOT - Multimedia educational resource for learning and online teaching 
http://www.merlot.org/merlot/index.htm 

Internet Archive 
http://www.archive.org/ 

101 Online Self-improvement Resources 
http://www.pickthebrain.com/blog/101-self-improvement-resources/ 

Alison - 300 free online courses at certificate or diploma level (sign-up required) 
http://alison.com/ 

Teaching Resources: 

The Orange Grove Digital Repository - Online library of openly available instructional resources for Florida's educators 
http://www.theorangegrove.org/ 

Learner.org - Browse teacher resources 
http://www.learner.org/resources/browse.html 

Google in Education - Teacher Resources 
http://www.google.com/edu/teachers/educator-resources.html 

============== 

IV. HOW-TO &amp; DIY 

WikiHow - The how-to manual that you can edit 
http://www.wikihow.com/ 

How Stuff Works 
http://www.howstuffworks.com/ 

Wonder How To 
http://www.wonderhowto.com/categories/ 

Instructables 
http://www.instructables.com/ 

Make Magazine 
http://www.makezine.com/ 

How-to Help &amp; Videos for Dummies 
http://www.dummies.com/ 

VideoJug - Get good at life 
http://www.videojug.com/ 

How to Create a Book in Wikipedia 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Help:Books 

Let's Make Robots 
http://letsmakerobots.com/ 

==================== 

V. STUDYING with PEERS 

Open Study - Study together 
http://openstudy.com/ 

P2P University - Learn anything with your peers 
http://p2pu.org/en/ 

Study Blue - Your digital backpack 
http://www.studyblue.com/ 

================================== 

VI. ONLINE BOOKS, eBOOKS, &amp; JOURNALS 

Google Books 
http://books.google.com/ 

WikiBooks - Open-content textbooks collection that anyone can edit 
http://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Main_Page 

Project Gutenberg 
http://www.gutenberg.org/wiki/Main_Page 

Planet eBook - Home of free classic literature 
http://www.planetebook.com/about.asp 

Open Book Project 
http://openbookproject.net/ 

The Free Library 
http://www.thefreelibrary.com/ 

Many Books - Ad-free eBooks 
http://www.manybooks.net/ 

WorldCat - Collections &amp; services of more than 10,000 libraries worldwide 
http://www.worldcat.org/ 

iBiblio - The public's library and digital archive 
http://www.ibiblio.org/ 

LibriVox - Free public domain audiobooks 
http://librivox.org/ 

The Assayer - Web's largest catalog of books whose authors have made them available for free 
http://theassayer.org/ 

Amazon.com Free eBook Collection 
http://www.amazon.com/b/ref=amb_link_85650291_15?ie=UTF8&amp;node=2245146011 

Scribd - Reading and publishing evolved 
http://www.scribd.com/ 

Textbook Revolution - Student-run site dedicated to increasing the use of free educational materials 
http://www.textbookrevolution.org/index.php/Main_Page 

Directory of Open Access Journals 
http://www.doaj.org/ 

eReaderIQ - Recent non-public domain freebies &amp; price-drop alerts 
http://www.ereaderiq.com/ 

Longform - New and classic non-fiction articles curated across the web 
http://longform.org/ 

Flatworld Knowledge - The first and largest publisher of free &amp; open textbooks 
http://www.flatworldknowledge.com/ 

======================================= 

VII. COMPUTERS, SOFTWARE, &amp; PROGRAMMING 

Google Code University 
http://code.google.com/edu/ 

The New Boston - Step-by-step tutorials for multiple coding languages 
http://thenewboston.org/ 

UDacity - CS 101 
http://www.udacity.com/ 

PHP Academy 
http://www.youtube.com/user/phpacademy 

Better PHP 
http://www.youtube.com/betterphp 

Programming eBooks 
http://appsapps.com/ebooks/ 

W3Schools - The world's largest web development site 
http://www.w3schools.com/ 
http://w3fools.com/#what-should-be-done 

Wired How-to Wiki - Teach a kid to program 
http://howto.wired.com/wiki/Teach_a_Kid_to_Program 

NetTuts+ - A large collection of coding tutorials 
http://nettuts.com/ 

Tutorial Guide - The site for all your tutorial needs 
http://www.tutorialguide.net/ 

Codecademy - Fun &amp; interactive way to learn how to code 
http://www.codecademy.com/ 

Free Technology Academy - High quality educational material based on free software &amp; open standards 
http://ftacademy.org/ 

Higher Computing for Everyone - Writing basic programs 
http://www.highercomputingforeveryone.com/ 

HTML 5 Please 
http://html5please.us/ 

Rails for Zombies 
http://railsforzombies.org/ 

Ruby Warrior - Open source game to teach Ruby language 
http://www.trybloc.com/courses/ruby-warrior/chapters/beginner#/1 

Got API - Documentation search engine 
http://start.gotapi.com/ 

Coding Bat - Online code practice in Java &amp; Python 
http://codingbat.com/ 

PySchools - Python programming language tutorial 
http://www.pyschools.com/ 

Python Learn - Provides materials to learn Python on your own 
http://www.py4inf.com/ 

appendTo - Learn jQuery and Javascript for free 
http://learn.appendto.com/ 

Professor Messer - Free CompTIA A+ Certification Training Course 
http://www.professormesser.com/ 

Lynda - Online software training videos 
http://www.lynda.com/ 

Intro to Linux 
http://www.reddit.com/r/Ubuntu/comments/bbnkp/ive_tinkered_in_ubuntu_before_but_its_the_primary/c0lzpwk 

Stack Overflow - Q&amp;A for professional and enthusiast programmers 
http://stackoverflow.com/ 

DZone - Fresh links for developers 
http://www.dzone.com/links/index.html 

Project Euler - A series of challenging mathematical &amp; computer programming problems 
http://projecteuler.net/ 

Photoshop &amp; Graphics: 

Tutorial Hero - Photoshop &amp; Flash tutorials 
http://www.tutorialhero.com/ 

PSD Tuts+ 
http://psd.tutsplus.com/ 

Photoshop Tutorials 
http://photoshoptutorials.ws/ 

Graphic Tutorials 
http://www.graphictutorials.net/ 

Photoshop Pack Graphic Design Resources 
http://www.photoshop-pack.com/ 

PSD FanExtra Tutorials 
http://psd.fanextra.com/category/tutorials/ 

Vandelay Design - Photoshop Tutorial Hall of Fame 
http://vandelaydesign.com/blog/design/photoshop-tutorial-tutorials/ 

Grokking the GIMP 
http://gimp-savvy.com/BOOK/index.html 

Video CoPilot - Tutorials for VFx &amp; motion graphics 
http://www.videocopilot.net/tutorials/ 

================== 

VIII. SCIENCE &amp; MATH 

Google Scholar - Stand on the shoulder of giants 
http://scholar.google.com/ 

Scirus - The most comprehensive scientific research tool on the web 
http://www.scirus.com/ 

Cite Seer X - Access scientific and scholarly knowledge 
http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/ 

getCited - Academic database, directory, &amp; discussion forum 
http://www.getcited.org/ 

Academia.edu - A place to share and follow research 
http://academia.edu/ 

National Science Digital Library - Explore, share, create 
http://nsdl.org/ 

Science Magazine Podcasts 
http://www.sciencemag.org/multimedia/podcast/ 

National Programme on Technology Enhanced Learning - Science, Engineering, &amp; Technology 
http://www.nptel.iitm.ac.in/ 

KQED's Quest - Explore science, nature, and environment stories from Northern California and beyond 
http://science.kqed.org/quest/ 

Freelance Teacher - Videos on physics, chemistry, math, &amp; biology 
http://www.freelance-teacher.com/videos.htm 

FHSST - Free high school science texts in physical sciences &amp; math 
http://fhsst.org/ 

Free Science Lectures - Free Science Videos &amp; Lectures 
http://www.freesciencelectures.com/ 

Minute Physics on YouTube 
http://www.youtube.com/user/minutephysics/featured 

Physicist TV - Collection of science &amp; documentary videos 
http://www.physicisttv.com/ 

Educated Earth - Videos on astronomy, biology, chemistry, earth sciences, math, physics, and more 
http://www.educatedearth.net/ 

The Science Network - Videos about science meetings and general science discussions 
http://thesciencenetwork.org/ 

cK-12 Flexbooks 
http://www.ck12.org/flexbook/ 

Paul's Online Math Notes 
http://tutorial.math.lamar.edu/ 

Reddit's List of Useful Online Math Resources 
http://www.reddit.com/r/math/comments/bqbex/lets_list_all_the_useful_free_online_math/ 

Math, Better Explained 
http://betterexplained.com/ 

Astronomy &amp; Outerspace: 

Space Engine - Free space simulation software 
http://en.spaceengine.org/ 

Google Sky 
http://www.google.com/sky/ 

NASA for Students 
http://www.nasa.gov/audience/forstudents/index.html 

Scale of the Universe - Interactive Flash Animation 
http://www.scaleoftheuniverse.com/ 

Statistics: 

Vassar Stats - Concepts and applications of inferential statistics 
http://faculty.vassar.edu/lowry/webtext.html 

StatSoft Electronic Statistics Textbook 
http://www.statsoft.com/textbook/stathome.html 

Connexions Collaborative Statistics 
http://cnx.org/content/col10522/latest/ 

Handbook of Biological Statistics 
http://udel.edu/~mcdonald/statintro.html 

========================= 

IX. LOGIC, WORDS, &amp; MEMORY 

Mind Tools - Memory improvement techniques 
http://www.mindtools.com/memory.html 

The Nizkor Project - List of logical fallacies 
http://www.nizkor.org/features/fallacies/index.html 

Wikipedia's List of Logical Fallacies 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_fallacies 

Wikipedia's List of Figures of Speech 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Figure_of_speech 

Tool Kit for Rhetorical Analysis 
http://grammar.about.com/od/rhetorictoolkit/Tool_Kit_for_Rhetorical_Analysis.htm 

KnoWord - Expand your vocabulary 
http://knoword.org/ 

Vocabulary.com - Learn new words &amp; explore language 
http://www.vocabulary.com/ 

Brain Workshop - A Dual N-Back Game 
http://brainworkshop.sourceforge.net/ 

Argument Mapping Tutorials 
http://austhink.com/reason/tutorials/ 

Philosophy Bites - Podcasts of top philsophers 
http://www.philosophybites.com/ 

============= 

X. LANGUAGES 

Basic Composition - Reading &amp; Writing 
http://www.basiccomposition.com/ 

BBC Languages - Beginner courses in multiple languages 
http://www.bbc.co.uk/languages/ 

Foreign Service Institute Language Courses 
http://fsi-language-courses.org/Content.php 

Language Guide - Foreign language vocabulary, grammar, &amp; readings 
http://www.languageguide.org/ 

eLanguage School - Free foreign language lessons online 
http://www.elanguageschool.net/ 

Free Online Language Courses via About.com 
http://distancelearn.about.com/od/onlinecourses/a/freelanguage.htm 

DuoLingo - Learn a language for free &amp; simultaneously translate the web 
http://duolingo.com/ 

Babel Nation - Learning languages online for free 
http://www.babelnation.com/ 

Transparent Language - Language learning software &amp; resources in over 100 languages 
http://www.transparent.com/language-resources/languages.html 

Survival Phrases - Learn essential travel phrases, tips, and insights 
http://survivalphrases.com/ 

Talk to Me in Korean 
http://talktomeinkorean.com/ 

Chinese Toolbox - Software for learning Chinese through reading 
http://www.chinesetoolbox.com/ 

LiveMocha - World's largest language learning community 
http://www.livemocha.com/ 

American Sign Language (ASL) University 
http://www.lifeprint.com/asl101/lessons/lesson01.htm 

Handspeak - Sign language 
http://www.handspeak.com/ 

Signing Savvy - Your sign language resource 
http://www.signingsavvy.com/index.php 

======== 

XI. MUSIC 

Berklee Shares - Free music lessons from Berklee College of Music 
http://www.berkleeshares.com/ 

Music Theory - Lessons, exercises, &amp; tools 
http://www.musictheory.net/ 

Ear Training &amp; Music Theory Software 
http://www.trainear.com/ 

Basic Music Theory 
http://www.howmusicworks.org/ 

About.com Music Education - Music theory 
http://musiced.about.com/od/musictheory/u/musiced_musictheory.htm 

Teoria - Music Theory Web 
http://teoria.com/ 

Ultimate Guitar - Lessons, techniques, &amp; styles 
http://www.ultimate-guitar.com/lessons/ 

Justin Guitar - The best guitar instruction on the web 
http://www.justinguitar.com/ 

Chorder - Chord fingering and guitar resources 
http://www.chorder.com/guitar-chords/ 

Funk University - Assembly of Music's Finest 
http://www.thefunkuniversity.com/ 

Play Bass Now - Lessons, licks, and low notes 
http://playbassnow.com/ 

How to Play Piano 
http://www.howtoplaypiano.ca/ 

=========== 

XII. HISTORY 

Teacher Resources - Western Civilization (52 half-hour video programs) 
http://www.learner.org/resources/series58.html 

Metropolitan Museum of Art - Timeline of Art History 
http://www.metmuseum.org/toah/ 

========================================= 

XIII. BUSINESS, ECONOMICS, FINANCE, &amp; INVESTING 

Investopedia 
http://www.investopedia.com/ 

Google Advisor 
https://www.google.com/advisor/home 

Google Finance 
http://www.google.com/finance 

MarketWatch by WSJ 
http://www.marketwatch.com/ 

Main Street - Business &amp; financial headlines &amp; advice 
http://www.mainstreet.com/ 

Stanford University's Entrepreneurship Corner 
http://ecorner.stanford.edu/ 

Value Based Management - Methods, models, and theories 
http://www.valuebasedmanagement.net/ 

Ludwig von Mises Institute - Austrian economics and praxeology 
http://mises.org/ 

Foundation for Economic Education 
http://www.fee.org/ 

Library of Economics and Liberty 
http://www.econlib.org/ 

============================ 

XIV. FOOD, NUTRITION, &amp; COOKING 

Good Eats Fan Page 
http://www.goodeatsfanpage.com/GEFP/index.htm 

Jamie's Home Cooking Skills 
http://www.jamieshomecookingskills.com/ 

Chef Todd Mohr's Web Cooking Classes (YouTube) 
http://www.youtube.com/user/ChefToddMohr 

Nutrition Data - Self nutrition data; know what you eat 
http://www.nutritiondata.com/ 

Nutrition.gov - Smart nutrition &amp; practical tips 
http://www.nutrition.gov/ 

Choose My Plate via USDA 
http://www.choosemyplate.gov/ 

The World's Healthiest Foods 
http://whfoods.org/foodstoc.php 

Calorie King 
http://www.calorieking.com/ 

Start Making Choices - Simple ideas for living healthier on a budget 
http://www.startmakingchoices.com/index.jsp 

Eat Right Nutrition Tips 
http://www.eatright.org/Public/content.aspx?id=206 

================ 

XV. SURVIVAL TIPS 

Off Grid Survival - Wilderness and urban survival skills 
http://offgridsurvival.com/ 

Backwoods Magazine - Self reliance and self sufficiency 
http://www.backwoodshome.com/index.html 

Survival Topics - Your online survival kit 
http://www.survivaltopics.com/ 

Wilderness Survival - Free info covering all aspects of survival 
http://www.wilderness-survival.net/ 

Discovery's Worst-Case Scenario Video Clips 
http://dsc.discovery.com/videos/worst-case-scenario/ 

=============================== 

XVI. DOCUMENTARIES &amp; FILM STUDIES 

Documentary Wire 
http://www.documentarywire.com/ 

Factual TV - The documentary film video store 
http://www.factualtv.com/ 

Documentary Heaven - Food for your brain 
http://documentaryheaven.com/ 

Surf the Channel 
http://www.surfthechannel.com/cat/61482.html 

DocuWatch - Free streaming documentaries on Art, History, Science, and more 
http://www.docuwat.ch/watch-documentaries/ 

Documentary Tube - Watch full-length documentaries online for free 
http://www.documentarytube.com/ 

Documentary Log - Watch hundreds of the most interesting, popular, and full-length documentaries 
http://www.documentary-log.com/ 

Documentary Stream 
http://www.documentarystream.com/ 

Documentary Storm - Free streaming documentaries 
http://documentarystorm.com/ 

Top Documentary Films - Watch free documentaries online 
http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/ 

Movies Found Online - Free movies &amp; documentaries 
http://www.moviesfoundonline.com/documentaries.php 

Quick Silver Screen - Movies &amp; documentaries 
http://www.quicksilverscreen.ch/videos?g=5&amp;mt=1 

MVGroup Forums - An education in P2P (sign-up required) 
http://forums.mvgroup.org/ 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MVGroup 

InfoCoBuild's Books and Films - Science and Technology 
http://www.infocobuild.com/books-and-films/science.html 

Film Studies: 

Film Studies for Free - Web archive of notable film studies resources 
http://filmstudiesforfree.blogspot.com/p/open-access-film-e-books-list.html 

Online Film and Movie Image Studies, PhD and MPhil Theses 
http://filmstudiesforfree.blogspot.com/p/online-film-and-moving-studies-phd.html 

Online Film and Media Studies Journals 
http://filmstudiesforfree.blogspot.com/p/fsff-online-film-media-studies-journals.html 

========== 
XVII. OTHER 

Advanced Yoga Practices - Directory for Main Lessons 
http://www.aypsite.com/MainDirectory.html 

Creative Live - A live, worldwide creative classroom 
http://www.creativelive.com/﻿

Meer lezen (919 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_04_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-LVrNt-Qu7wk/Tx8KkncW9bI/AAAAAAAADDc/N_ProGORzs4/w426-h373/Online%2BLearning.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/107770072576338242009/albums/5874488124032979441/5874488132214957058?authkey=COTz_bDDrvqzFA&amp;sqi=113390432655174294208&amp;sqsi=bd2cf842-b503-4d09-aaca-3af67a4a7e14</link><title>Recommendations for touch screens to use with Raspberry Pi? 

Someday I'd like to teach my kids a little programming and I'm thinking about getting a Raspberry Pi. They like my touch screen laptop a lot (where they draw with a stylus in Tux Paint), their Learn and Go Tablet*, and they're quite comfortable with our Nexus 7 tablet. So I'm thinking if I'm going to buy a Raspberry Pi and need to buy a monitor and keyboard anyway, maybe I should buy a touchscreen. Also, I figured I'd start with Python, if that matters. Any thoughts on this or recommendations? 

I'm trying to reconcile what +Eben Upton says at http://creativecodingpodcast.com/34-raspberry-pi-with-eben-upton/ about the Raspberry Pi being a cheap computer for kids to hack on, one that they don't need to worry about breaking, versus the cost of a touch screen, which I assume will be considerably higher than a regular monitor.I do want my kids to feel free to hack away on something. :) 

* http://www.vtechkids.com/product/detail/2073/Learn_and_Go_Tablet﻿

Meer lezen (17 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_06_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-hoSSSR-ZD0Q/UYZf1PXrpAI/AAAAAAAABWg/e8gMITfVwGY/w426-h331/Raspberry_Pi_Tou_5103de6c28f0f.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/112526208786662512291/albums/5919494425198917009/5919494431458527954?authkey=CL_B7O_vpcGbAQ</link><title>Tutorial: Introducing TRINKET 
http://learn.adafruit.com/introducing-trinket/ 

rinket may be small, but do not be fooled by its size! It’s a tiny microcontroller board, built around the Atmel ATtiny85, a little chip with a lot of power. We wanted to design a microcontroller board that was small enough to fit into any project, and low cost enough to use without hesitation. Perfect for when you don’t want to give up your expensive dev-board and you aren’t willing to take apart the project you worked so hard to design. It’s our lowest-cost arduino-IDE programmable board! 

The Attiny85 is a fun processor because despite being so small, it has 8K of flash, and 5 I/O pins, including analog inputs and PWM ‘analog’ outputs. We designed a USB bootloader so you can plug it into any computer and reprogram it over a USB port just like an Arduino. In fact we even made some simple modifications to the Arduino IDE so that it works like a mini-Arduino board. You can’t stack a big shield on it but for many small &amp; simple projects the Trinket will be your go-to platform. 

There are two versions of the Trinket. One is 3V and one is 5V. Both work the same, but have different operating logic voltages. Use the 3V one to interface with sensors and devices that need 3V logic, or when you want to power it off of a LiPo battery. The 3V version should only run at 8 MHz. Use the 5V one for sensors and components that can use or require 5V logic. The 5V version can run at 8 MHz or at 16MHz by setting the software-set clock frequency. 

Learn more at our GIANT learning guide for this TINY little board! 
http://learn.adafruit.com/introducing-trinket/ 

#trinket  ﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-x_Q5qhcmXb8/UiZE0pT9CtI/AAAAAAAAaqU/dnc6D6jpx4E/w426-h328/adafruit_products_trinket_clear_products_1500_ORIG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/102032172002540958643/albums/5967029238198762305/5967029242782510578?sqi=113390432655174294208&amp;sqsi=44f03421-6cfa-48f9-bf50-91932724c322&amp;sqi=113390432655174294208&amp;sqsi=44f03421-6cfa-48f9-bf50-91932724c322</link><title>my last #raspberrypi  project. temperatur tracking. 
i used a DS18B20, python, postgres and cron. Costs me 2h and 3€.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_08_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-i-TeaUAGyIc/Us8le0xrbfI/AAAAAAAAahU/uXWRJ_fDhZg/w426-h237/nerd.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/105059362788808645801/albums/5835786282413991985/5835786282655408338?authkey=CPrzkPT5o_XP-AE</link><title>Just a shot in the dark here: Does anybody know if there's an easy way to generate the running maximum, minimum and average time series of multiple irregularly sampled time series in Python and Scipy? 

I'm attaching a simple example of what I mean. Three series, in shades of light blue and green. The sample points are irregular and do not in general overlap. 

The resulting average series uses data values and interpolated values from the three series as needed, and is marked with a dotted orange curve. 

The maximum and the minimum over all series are marked as red dotted curves. Note that these series have data points at the cross-over points of the original data series in order to generate a tight maximum or minimum over them. 

As you can see I can obviously calculate this by myself. But it would take a fair bit of time two write something that is reliable and handles all odd corner cases that come up. I much prefer using a well-tested existing solution, so if there is a neat way to do this already, using Scipy and Numpy, perhaps, then I would very much like to know about it. 

#python #numpy #scipy #statistics  ﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_09_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-qp-XcxcVBRQ/UPzgtGrF4NI/AAAAAAAACBk/ojQpn9fN8tY/w426-h282/ts.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/105279625231358353479/albums/5990680194653145121/5990680199641830290</link><title>The US Supreme Court said corporations are people. 

Clearly not. See graph. Come on Corporations, be people! (And I don't mean in just an unlimited political spend way?) 

Related unrelated note: If you are an analyst, here's a tutorial on how to make this graph (in a head to head match between r and python): http://goo.gl/YPyf5R﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_10_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-rjtyShDuJfY/UyMr5s6eE5I/AAAAAAAAbOg/cnAfG24Ie7M/w426-h341/graphPredictR.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/113639078034208008248/albums/5952727867630230049/5952727868739029266?sqi=109728488971985783565&amp;sqsi=2623473f-51a8-4e47-920c-2fadb37b88f1</link><title>Do you know in which languages most popular websites built? 

All the programmers must need to know this... 

Let us know if anything is missing...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-NFkNntIHmTY/UpxWdSzCCRI/AAAAAAAABlg/YSbl7MjA1k0/w426-h346/languages.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7472-12"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/python%20re%20tutorial/photos/112526208786662512291/albums/5776601385692198273/5776601384531328082</link><title>Tutorial: Using the BMP085 with +Raspberry Pi  – +Adafruit Industries  Learning System 

http://learn.adafruit.com/using-the-bmp085-with-raspberry-pi/ 

The Raspberry Pi includes support for Python, which makes it easy to get access to a lot of low-level hardware and software stacks — USB, TCP/IP, multiple file systems etc.  This is a good thing since it means you don’t need to wrap your head around all the obscure details that go along with these complex stacks or the implementation details of various serial buses: you can focus on getting your data off your sensor and into your project as quickly as possible.  Hurray for abstraction! 

Most sensors tend to communicate with other devices based on one of three well-defined mechanisms: I2C, SPI or good old analog output.  There are dozens of other serial buses and communication protocols out there (CAN, 1-Wire, etc.), and they all have their strengths and weaknesses, but I2C, SPI and analog cover the overwhelming majority of sensors you’re likely to hook up to the Pi… 

Comes with our python BMP085 library and example code, you’ll be up &amp; running in 15 minutes! Learn more… (http://learn.adafruit.com/using-the-bmp085-with-raspberry-pi/) 

By +Kevin Townsend 

#raspberrypi  ﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7472_12_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-cRiMNtzEnYg/UCqcWn4E_FI/AAAAAAAAFpY/dfXmyUH3PgM/w426-h302/using-the-bmp085-with-raspberry-pi.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>