<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7474">php convert special symbols to html</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:31:46" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/110884604033336753419/albums/6005873174305237153/6005873224448094322</link><title>Liquid Spacetime: Superfluid vacuum theory gains some momentum : Superfluid vacuum theory (SVT) is an approach in theoretical physics and quantum mechanics where physical vacuum is viewed as a superfluid. The goal of SVT is to unify quantum mechanics with gravity, as an extension of the Standard Model. It has been suggested that spacetime itself should be treated as a superfluid. Fascinating indeed! Do look at all the links, it will help to get a grasp of what the physicists are talking about :) 

Article Extract: What if spacetime were a kind of fluid? This is the question tackled by theoretical physicists working on quantum gravity by creating models attempting to reconcile gravity and quantum mechanics. Some of these models predict that spacetime at the Planck scale is no longer continuous but discrete in nature. Just like the solids or fluids we come into contact with every day, which can be seen as made up of atoms and molecules when observed at sufficient resolution. 

In this theoretical framework, it has been suggested that spacetime should be treated as a fluid. In this sense, general relativity would be the analogue to fluid hydrodynamics, which describes the behaviour of fluids at a macroscopic level but tells us nothing about the atoms/molecules that compose them. 

Quantum mechanics is able to effectively explain three of the four fundamental forces of the Universe (electromagnetism, weak interaction and strong interaction). But it does not explain gravity, which is currently only accounted for by general relativity, a theory developed in the realm of classical physics. Identifying a plausible model of quantum gravity (that is, a description of gravity within a quantum physics framework) is therefore one of the major challenges physics is facing today. However, despite the many models proposed to date, none has proved satisfactory or, more importantly, amenable to empirical investigation. Studies like the one carried out by Liberati and Maccione provide new instruments for assessing the value of possible scenarios for quantum gravity. 

Liberati and Maccione showed that viscosity tends to rapidly dissipate photons and other particles along their path, "And yet we can see photons travelling from astrophysical objects located millions of light years away!" he continues. "If spacetime is a fluid, then according to our calculations it must necessarily be a superfluid. This means that its viscosity value is extremely low, close to zero". 

Article Link: http://phys.org/news/2014-04-liquid-spacetime-slippery-superfluid.html 

Research Paper: http://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevLett.112.151301 

Related Paper: http://link.springer.com/article/10.1140%2Fepjc%2Fs10052-013-2491-x 

Properties of Superfluids: http://ffden-2.phys.uaf.edu/212_fall2003.web.dir/Rodney_Guritz%20Folder/properties.htm 

Superfluidity: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superfluidity 

Superfluid Vacuum Theory: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superfluid_vacuum_theory 

Pics courtesy: R.G. Cloves http://www.uclan.ac.uk/staff_profiles/roger_clowes.php via Holographic Universe.﻿

Meer lezen (60 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_01_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-5B4GdZRQc_A/U1kl4I1CMHI/AAAAAAAAcLI/1M_wfZ3hp8I/w426-h320/A_Flight_through_the_Universe___Fly_through_the_Millennium_Simulation_hd720.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/109188140938851476797/albums/5870153717237078433/5870153723165876338?authkey=CN7isYimxYnNHg&amp;sqi=114501790911330126436&amp;sqsi=c25428e6-cbb0-4bf1-8cf3-ce1fa8b7cd8d</link><title>Beauty Without Cruelty Full Volume Natural Mascara Review 
by Jenny of RedHead Beauty Diaries 

Beauty Without Cruelty is a British brand that has been around for 30 years and were one of the first companies to really promote not testing cosmetics on animals. I have used some of their cosmetics before -  when I was a teenager so around 23 years ago ~ oh dear that is a long time! 

For those of you reading my blog for the first time my 'natural make up mission' is a challenge I have set myself this year to see if I can find suitable natural alternatives to my current everyday conventional make up, without compromising on quality or performance. I was particularly looking for a mascara to 'replace' my Clinque High Impact Mascara which I have used for years, and the Beauty Without Cruelty Full Volume Mascara caught my attention. 

Firstly, I have to say how lovely the packaging is, it comes presented in a nice card box that has the same very pretty swans head heart design that is BWC logo, as is on the mascara tube. 
 I think BWC have really gone out of their way to make the mascara tube, which they could have easily left plain,  into something that is a joy to pull out of your make up bag in the morning! 

The mascara is of course not tested on animals and bears the 'leaping bunny' symbol, 100% suitable for vegans &amp; vegetarians, only uses natural ingredients, is paraben free, PEG free, and fragrance free. 

The mascara claims it's 'double depth' brush maximizes extension &amp; thickness for extra volume. I have to agree the brush is fabulous it has a lot of bristles and is quite wide. This does have a negative side though, because of the abundance of bristles it picks up too much mascara, far more than you need to coat your lashes. If you were to go straight from the tube to your lashes there would be clumps galore! 

However, this is easily rectified by wiping the brush first to remove the excess - not ideal as it's wasting the product,  but once the brush has the right quantity of mascara on it, it works amazing well and is clump free! It did a great job of really gripping my lashes from their base and separating them out giving good definition and was a good deep shade of black. It didn't take any extra amount of time to dry either. It stayed put all day long,  there was no flaking and it didn't leave any black grubby marks under my eyes at the end of the day, like some mascaras can 

Beauty Without Cruelty Mascaras: 
http://www.beautywithoutcruelty.com/scat.php?link=BEAUTYWITHOUTBEAUTY&amp;subcat=0471&amp;vendor_id=11150 

Read the entire review at RedHead Beauty Diaries: 
http://www.redheadbeautydiaries.co.uk/2013/03/beauty-without-cruelty-full-volume.html﻿

Meer lezen (52 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-mBRADp-ADc0/UXb5tbY9IHI/AAAAAAAAA8E/Lp_ulh_0a7U/w426-h273/redhead-beauty-diaries.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/113414575058701971173/albums/5914936296714067345/5914936300603687714?authkey=CKym1__wpJ-q0wE</link><title>Share this picture on your wall or make it your profile picture to show solidarity with the Muslims of the world and of Egypt. 
That's what I see. 
But will it stop? Will it ever stop? The slaughter of  innocents and all the injustice? The least we can do is stand united. But can this be enough? What can we do to make things better? 

United we stand, Divided we fall. 

Raaba / Rabia or R4BIA means four in Arabic and it's the symbol of the incident of Egypt Massacre. More than 181 people were killed last Friday in mass rallies staged by Morsi supporters in several Egyptian cities to protest Wednesday's violent dispersal of their two main protest sites Cairo's Rabaa al-Adawiya and Giza's Nahda squares on Wednesday. 

The Health Ministry said that at least 638 people had been killed in nationwide violence since Wednesday, including 288 in Rabaa and 87 in Nahda. 

Erdogan (Primeminister of Turkey) showed solidarity with Muslim brotherhood by showing 4 fingers. Muslims from all over the word embraced this symbol for the protest of killings of Muslims in the world. 

The information provided to me was the courtesy of +Islamic Republic of Pakistan 

I, as a human being, Muslim and a Pakistani citizen condemn such acts but it baffles me and saddens me when I come to think about what I can really do to stop it. 
Praying for Allah to show us the right way and give us strength. 
Assalamualaikum﻿

Meer lezen (30 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-IhomYJvT81Q/UhYTOgqLwyI/AAAAAAAARPs/IDoV8RpLAd4/w426-h431/BR6IlADCEAAtuvI.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/118011560178264222649/albums/5735518548379408225/5735518548668278370</link><title>The Visual Web: Killing the Discussion 
The introduction to the new Google+ reminds you to "Liven up your post" with a photo or a video, cuz, you know, words are soooo dead. 

With the recent successes of Instagram and Pinterest, analysts are hailing a revival of an old trend in communication (with its roots in stone age cave paintings). Pictures! "Andrew Lipsman, the vice president for industry analysis at the research firm comScore, called [Pinterest's] popularity among brands one more example of “the rise of the visual Web,” along with Instagram (which was recently acquired by Facebook) and Facebook’s timeline feature, which is heavily driven by images instead of text ." 

Mobile versus the Desktop: Tool Limitations on Text 
As we consume more and more of our content over mobile devices, we are losing our tools both for consuming and creating text. On a mobile device, even responsive, voluble readers can hardly be expected to do much more than tap out an acknowledging +1 with our thumbs or, if we are really motivated, a "LOL". The marketers worry about the lack of audience engagement. Would they also expect us to clap without hands? Give us a keyboard where we can touch type. 

Opposable thumbs gave us an evolutionary advantage but thanks to our mobiles we're now all thumbs. I saw one poor man at SXSWi pawing at his iPad screen like a puppy, as if his fingers had fused. 

I know some of you are wonderfully adapted to typing with your thumbs. And limitations often result in new art forms as the creative among us test the boundaries. In Japan, the mobile phone beget the thumb novel, keitai shosetsu fiction serialized for text messaging. 

In 2009, Barry Yourgrau wrote, "...the keitai shosetsu phenomenon hasn’t so far headed west...mobiles play a different role in Japan. They, not computers, are the principal portal to the internet. "The majority of my students (19-22-year-olds) don't have a PC," notes Yuki Watanabe, a PhD candidate in Tokyo. "They're of the keypad, not keyboard, generation. The lingo of texting is normal language to them." 

In 2012, we seem to have caught up. In the introduction of the Google+ redesign, Vic Gundotra touts "Conversations you'll really care about". Unfortunately, the limitations of reading and typing over our mobiles hamper in-depth discussion and influences the design of our tools. It's hard to "cherish the conversations that unfold" when we have to open every long comment separately -- even when viewing on the desktop. (Maybe that's what unfold refers to.) This is time-consuming, and annoying. Being constantly required to fiddle with the tool distracts our attention from the content of the discussion. 

&lt;del&gt;Opening a comment also causes the left text margin to jump. Our eyes strain trying to find the beginning of the next line.&lt;/del&gt; (I can no longer find an example of this so maybe it's been fixed.) As with using any kind of tool, the user should be focused on job, not the tool. 

So what tools does Google+ provide for conversation? Per Vic: 
• Full bleed photos and videos that'll make you really proud to post 
• A stream of conversation "cards" that make it easier to scan and join discussions 
• An activity drawer that highlights the community around your content 

Look at a screenful of conversation cards. How many lines of actual content text do you see per screen? 

Driven by Images 
Kelly Mooney. "[People] love scrolling for minutes or even hours looking through photos by friends, celebs and brands or on topics they’re passionate about. With Instagram, there’s no need to share any sentiment or craft the perfect post. Words aren’t the magic here; pictures are." (Emphasis mine.) 

Vic Gundotra. "Simply put, we're hoping to make sharing more awesome by making it more evocative. You know that feeling you get when a piece of art takes your breath away, or when a friend stops by with unexpected gifts? We want sharing to feel like that, every single time." (Emphasis mine.) 

So the visual web is like TV channel-surfing on steroids. We j-key through the conversations cards, passively staring at images which reduce us to our primal, emotional state. Awesome! Do we stop there with what Wordsworth called "the spontaneous overflow of powerful feelings" and call it a success? Or do we press forward and meditate, mull, analyze, synthesize, and create something of our own? Do we have a real conversation? 

I can't settle for appeals to emotion; I want thought-provoking ideas. 

A Picture's Worth 
I enjoy seeing beautiful, startling, evocative photographs and paintings on Google+. But I get tired of that old saw, "A picture's worth a thousand words." 

Show me the picture that expresses, for example, all that +Peter Strempel does with his words. 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/110695872689494369839/posts/6ufQzefD6se 

Despite the setbacks, we lovers of words don't give up. No. We keep trying to make it better. You can find some of us in +Dieter Mueller 's Homo digitalis circle. 
https://plus.google.com/u/0/110168665701189567035/posts/YBFJinfnREb 

\------------- 
Sources 
The Visual Web 
http://www.nytimes.com/2012/04/18/business/media/marketers-find-a-friend-in-pinterest.html 

Kelly Mooney: The Rise of the Visual Web 
http://www.resource.com/wethink/the-rise-of-the-visual-web 

Vic Gundotra: Toward a Simpler, More Beautiful Google 
http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2012/04/toward-simpler-more-beautiful-google.html 

Barry Yourgrau: Thumb Novels -- Keitai Shousetsu 携帯小説http://www.keitai-shosetsu.com/ 
\--------------- 
#newgoogleplus﻿

Meer lezen (120 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-VRYdp6oRF0c/T5inu2AJZmI/AAAAAAAAB9M/lWpsSTK-EM4/w426-h237/background2048x1266</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/105479712798762608629/albums/5969293961206672497/5969293963660951970</link><title>Let's dance.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-El4iLyJBfVw/UtcxO7flAaI/AAAAAAABr60/sO0xyT2nYu4/w426-h284/1.15.14%2BLets%2BDance.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/113848500993836596528/albums/5973232572638432113/5973232572665191298?sqi=101996609942925099701&amp;sqsi=9b30e14a-ca6e-48c5-9376-f108acf5e411</link><title>Many scientific investigations have proved that modern humans or the homo sapiens evolved in Africa. They migrated towards north; in due course of time they settled near Mediterranean Sea. When the ice age ended, the humans migrated in different directions from that area. One branch went to the western Asia , then to the Indian peninsula and finally towards Australia. From the Indian peninsula , branch migrated towards China and subsequently to North America. From North America, humans migrated to South America. From the Mediterranean sea , the second branch migrated towards Europe; where they are believed to replace the Neanderthals. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-IdG0u0jmHpI/UuUvYJaAW4I/AAAAAAAAAjU/xf8lmofg-UE/w426-h304/2014%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/114963786071989905755/albums/5752107733525826913/5752107729613394066</link><title>Taking Candy From A Baby – A ZERO SUM GAME (Backgammon) 

The conscious and intelligent manipulation of the organized habits and opinions of the masses is an important element in democratic society. 
~Edward Bernays 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edward_Bernays 

In the seventh grade; our homeroom teacher who also served as our English teacher, always threaten to assign a 1,000 Word Essay on Life Inside a White Ping Pong Ball. 

As a means of gaining controlling his class. 

My senior year at Penn State University provide an opportunity to share a finance class with a White Africa from the former Rhodesia. His only conversation with me during the semester was: “Why Do Africans Like to Play Games?”. 

He provided No opportunity for a question or follow-up 

As a Wall Street executive. 
I was introduced to the phrase: “It’s like taking candy from a baby”. 

Reflection on these experiences; among many others, reveals life is not without interferences. 

In fact our lives are monitored on a regular basis with one single objective in mind; influencing our actions, to accomplish the goals and objectives of others. 

Living and unexamined life; most of this passes without observation. 

Start to think, reflect, and act in your own interest, and you begin to see the trail of the “Invisible Hand” 

As described by Adam Smith in “Wealth of Nations”. 

We have gamed ourselves to an unsustainable point; where little can be said for the quality of our lives, job security, sustainability of communities, and the sustainability of our planet. 

Reality has been so distorted that “Fear, Distrust, and Hate” has replaced “Civility, Respect, and Community” as the foundation of personal, organizational and governmental relationships. 

The tragedy is that “Billions” have been spent on studying the human mind, culture, and relationships over the past sixty years. In the end, we have more rather than less manic depressive people and dysfunctional relationships. 

Governments consistently fail in carrying out the simple task of providing for the safety and well being of their citizens. 

“Marketing Campaigns” promote a constant state of despair, fear, inferiority, and incompetence as a means for facilitating even more consumption of things we don’t need. 

How much of this is an accident or calculated? 

I don’t know. 

Given the amount of money and time spent researching and analyzing human behavior, why has our quality of life decreased? 

With more educated professionals and technocrats, why have governance of organizations and institutions been a failure? 

There are “Games” being played, but they are nothing like Backgammon, Pinochle, Poke Her, or the simulated video War Games you have become accustomed to. 

NO, we are all unwitting players in a game based on a principle called “GAME THEORY”. 

“Game Theory” attempts to mathematically capture behavior in strategic situations, or games in which an individual’s success in making choices depends on the choices of others (Myerson, 1991). Base on this definition, one can manipulate the success of the individual by influencing those on whom his choices depends. 

How Else Can a Individual or a Group Of People Consistently Act Against Their Own Interest? 

These “Game Masters” are better capitalized, have more information, and the ability to act in real time, anywhere they please. 

Where as groups without capital or other resources needed to accomplish their goals and objectives seek cooperation; 

“Game Masters”, understand there is more to be had by getting the benefits from cooperation without returning it. 

“Game masters” do as little as possible; it means deception, in order to secure your trust and cooperation in exchange for nothing. 

They have a “Winner Takes All” mentality. 

Men have always set their sights on power, fame, and fortune through warfare, tricks, magic, sabotage, and slavery. “Game Theory” is simply another tool in their arsenal. 

“I felt guilty throughout the whole time, but I was seduced. 
The power of these drugs, sex, power, and money, was extremely strong for me.” ~John Perkins 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Confessions_of_an_Economic_Hit_Man 

In our modern world, it is unfashionable to be overtly racists. In fact many overt acts are outlawed. Take look at housing, financing, education, healthcare, and employment statistic and it becomes clear that something is still going on. The same can be said for imperialism in its reincarnated form; “Cultural Imperialism”: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cultural_imperialism. 

Relying on Applied Mathematics, Economics, Evolutionary Biology, Ecology, Engineering, Political Science, International Relations, Computer Science, Social Psychology, and Philosophy: “Game Theory” is for the Contemporary Soldier of Fortune, Pirate, Robber Barron, and Empire Builder what the Castillian Sword (El Cid), the horse, and riding skills were for Rodrigo Diaz de Vivar http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/El_Cid; Hernando Cortes http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hern%C3%A1n_Cort%C3%A9s; and Francisco Pizarro http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Francisco_Pizarro. 

It is within this paradigm that we try to accomplish things like the Millennium Development Goals; communities seek to find solutions for job losses and deterioration; individuals seek to make friends, develop business connections, and find new opportunities using social networking sites. 

In this paradigm, treaties are signed knowing they may never be implemented, or scenarios are created to prevent them from even being considered. Financial commitments are made with no desire of ever fulfilling them. Rules are created with sufficient loopholes to ensure they are circumvented. 

“It is the world of ME, MYSELF, and I”. 

A world where the “Common Good” is “Incidental” or “Accidental”. 

Links for further reading: 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sustainable_development 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_theory#History 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Theory_of_Games_and_Economic_Behavior 

http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/game-theory/ 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zero-sum 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Games_People_Play_%28book%29 

Free Game Theory Video lecture with Professor Ben Polak 

http://oyc.yale.edu/economics/game-theory/ 

http://levine.sscnet.ucla.edu/general/whatis.htm 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transactional_Analysis 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/I%27m_OK,_You%27re_OK 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_games﻿

Meer lezen (164 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-TQ0Xwo3I5wQ/T9OXgQ1ikJI/AAAAAAAAAYI/S0Rj1QElzzk/w426-h320/BellForms.wmv</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/103232769074537012489/albums/5306220156854637665/5315332427767784210</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-S_pAHkxclTM/ScParmQ2oxI/AAAAAAAAASE/2vyU0T9ueho/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/116279565780834821134/albums/5947841732313894129/5947841734145991298</link><title>Experience #Jquery #mobile and #Jqtouch #application.....!! 
Jqtouch offers native animations, immediate route and themes that help you construct applications that support touch occasions. These requisitions can run in full-screen mode, incorporating tweaked symbols and startup screens. 
-Touch-Based Events 
-Orientation 
-Advanced Web Applications 
-Distinctive Themes 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
. 
http://www.htmlpanda.com/jqtouch-development.php﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-lerJXp0zrdY/Uor6i1AD4oI/AAAAAAAAAXo/kH4fLtEH3VQ/w426-h298/jqtouch%2Bapp.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7474-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/php%20convert%20special%20symbols%20to%20html/photos/115476431375193466884/albums/5745022229370990481/5745022234159845570</link><title>Let's Compare Che Ulisses Results to the Average of All Quiz-Takers... 

Political Ideology Definitions - http://www.balancedpolitics.org/ideology.htm 

Liberal... 
\- http://www.thefreedictionary.com/liberal 
\- http://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/liberal%5B2%5D 
\- http://oxforddictionaries.com/definition/liberal 
\- http://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/liberal 

Liberalism - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liberalism 

What is "Neo-liberalism" (A Brief Definition) - http://www.globalexchange.org/resources/econ101/neoliberalismdefined 

Why Do You “Attack” Putin? - http://mybook.amizadevirtual.com.br/2012/why-do-you-attack-putin/ 

The Motherland Calls: Russia's symbol of victory (RT documentary) - http://youtu.be/RLPM5VnOjHY 

The Paradox of President Putin - http://youtu.be/Vyzw-yuUgqU 

Too many liberals in new government – Communists - https://rt.com/politics/liberals-new-government-communists-779/ 

Russia's "Jurassic Capitalism" - http://youtu.be/BegBHxCDYuA 

CrossTalk: Banking Mafia - http://youtu.be/RQBNq4vIo74 

Anatomy of casino capitalism - http://youtu.be/PNbgvyb0o-I 

Part 1 The History of America's Secret Casinos DOCUMENTARY - http://youtu.be/2xd-ze-uHeY 

TED talk you weren't supposed to see - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=73727 

Las Vegas Documentary Part 1 - http://youtu.be/FIYUiOU5tuk 

Finance - Highway Robbers to Drunken Drivers - http://youtu.be/ACQh1DreCm0 

Part 2 The History of America's Secret Casinos DOCUMENTARY - http://youtu.be/1gJ4v1lgZ6A 

Michael Moore: What We're Seeing is the End of Capitalism - Michael Moore: What We're Seeing is the End of Capitalism 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt.2 - http://youtu.be/X5aU8LbcPGI 

Las Vegas Documentary Part 2 - http://youtu.be/W9RNg6R-tOo 

The Best Governments Money Can Buy - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=73731 

Read More about Mafia in the United States - http://www.history.com/topics/mafia-in-the-united-states 

Europe: USA colony - http://english.pravda.ru/world/europe/04-05-2012/121018-Europe_us_colony-0/ 

TalkingStickTV - George Galloway - Speaking in Seattle - 09/20/05 - http://youtu.be/NpXn1SfGp6M 

DEBTOCRACY: Causes of Greece's debt crisis and solutions, hidden by the government and the dominant media [full length documentary] - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=71170 

Zhmurki For Those Who Survived The 90s [click &lt;del&gt;cc&lt;/del&gt; for English subtitles] - http://youtu.be/P13k6NCDAVI 

Group of Two and the New World Disorder - http://english.pravda.ru/world/europe/21-05-2012/121181-new_world_disorder-0/ 

Money As Debt 1 - The Rothschild Mafia (Paul Grignon) - http://youtu.be/YS88F7Bw2AQ 

TalkingStickTV - Naomi Wolf - The End of America - http://youtu.be/RjALf12PAWc 

Food Inc exposes the truth behind what Americans eat - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=71691 

Money as Debt 3 - The Rothschild mafia (Paul Grignon) - http://youtu.be/f6uuAupT4AQ 

The Mafia: American Conspiracy Theories Confirmed True... 
\- http://youtu.be/ASAl4UrfQAY 
\- http://youtu.be/4Ag3mHuIHxk 

Capitalism: A Love Story - http://www.blatantworld.com/comedy/michael_moore_capitalism_a_love_story.html 

The Mafia, the CIA and Bush Sr - http://youtu.be/i1SrZfxbLOU 
\- http://archive.org/details/AV_483_484-THE_MAFIA_THE_CIA_AND_GEORGE_BUSH 
\- http://youtu.be/lUiAbeDs5Sk 

Modern Mafia, Greenspan, Bernake, Geitner $15 Trillion Fraud Exposed In UK House Of Lords - http://youtu.be/l5PsXZVDYCo 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt.3 - http://youtu.be/Dr11ErG5ivQ 

Thieves by Law - Vory V Zakone 2010 Document FullHD HD english subtitles - http://youtu.be/1w8zME-uDtw 

Economic Inequality Explained in 3 Minutes - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=73167 

Who really owns America's wealth? - http://youtu.be/O67XNBl-Xog 

Former Soviet state wants to set Ukraine against Russia - http://english.pravda.ru/world/ussr/17-05-2012/121150-lithuania_russia_ukraine-0/ 

USA Befriends Kazakhstan Dictator, Now World's Largest Producer of Uranium - http://youtu.be/v62b46Q6smw 

Anatomy of casino capitalism - Power of the Fed Pt.4 - http://youtu.be/P92oOYTUpW8 

Krugman: Jamie Dimon Must Resign Over JPMorgan's $3B Lost &amp; Campaign Against Financial Regs - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=73716 

Hitler's Generals and American Politicians - http://english.pravda.ru/opinion/columnists/22-05-2012/121200-hitler_generals_american_politicians-0/ 

The ELITE blew it , REVEALED their plans to start WORLD WAR 3 - http://youtu.be/ZnY_yXVrWiU 

Richard Wilkinson: How economic inequality harms societies - http://youtu.be/cZ7LzE3u7Bw 

TalkingStickTV - John Perkins - Confessions of an Economic Hit Men 
\- http://youtu.be/yTbdnNgqfs8 
\- http://youtu.be/29GhXsx7-Rs 
\- http://youtu.be/n7Fzm1hEiDQ 

George Galloway at "Oxford Union" on IRAN 
\- http://youtu.be/AfRRpDwsNhE 
\- http://youtu.be/jXG-UJ9LTEo 

J.P. Morgan Funds Senate Finance Chair, Even Bigger Problem in the Wings - http://youtu.be/Y2elH4Vy5CU 

Le taux mondial du chômage des jeunes est de plus en plus élevé - http://www.humanite.fr/social-eco/le-taux-mondial-du-chomage-des-jeunes-est-de-plus-en-plus-eleve-497066 

Why You Should Care: GMOs on your plate (E6) - http://youtu.be/sU1koyocWeI 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt.5 - http://youtu.be/jx2OdJWq6P4 

La OTAN habla de estabilidad, pero genera caos en Chicago - http://youtu.be/vCA4-Pn-4ls 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt6 - democratize or replace The Fed - http://youtu.be/nuV2ilZ_I9o 

The Las Vegas Mafia (The Chicago Outfit) - Full Documentary - http://youtu.be/x7ZR8oyCJPg 

The American Dream? - FULL LENGTH - http://youtu.be/OaHSWjbMvQ0 

Keiser Report: Scatological Finance (E291) - http://youtu.be/-dfCLVcagxo 

CENSORED HISTORY OF THE MAFIA [historical documentary] - http://youtu.be/59Qn0Q5R4Uo 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt.7 - http://youtu.be/Cac-m8NDUWg 

The Money Masters - Full - http://youtu.be/JXt1cayx0hs 

Anatomy of casino capitalism Pt.8 - http://youtu.be/jW5cPhFVtww 

Has the Revolution started...on the Bankters? - http://youtu.be/ADETNiH0D64 

Russia's "Jurassic Capitalism" Pt.2 - http://youtu.be/8pTkbdeu9QI 

California as broke as Greece? - http://youtu.be/RKMF21VFMyg 

Paul Krugman: Public Spending Not Deficit Hysteria - http://therealnews.com/t2/component/hwdvideoshare/?task=viewvideo&amp;video_id=73717 

'Serbs had enough of Tadic oligarchy that kept them in poverty' - http://youtu.be/7IH2nCKRu74 

The Godfather trilogy - http://youtu.be/_q1dszEFfUk 

TalkingStickTV - Michael Parenti - The U.S. War on Yugoslavia - http://youtu.be/GEzOgpMWnVs 

Super Rich The Greed Game - http://youtu.be/suZb9Z0b05I 

TalkingStickTV - Michael Parenti - Lies, War, and Empire 
\- http://youtu.be/CZTrY3TQpzw 
\- http://youtu.be/oaTPDFsDdIk 

"...I prefer Russia/China. It's corrupt as America (USA &amp; NATO &amp; European Union), but there's less bullshit."One of my favorite movie lines. Probably because I know it's true.Thanks for uploading this scene. 

The Russia House (1990) - Sean Connery Questioning... 
\- http://movieclips.com/VSrc-the-russia-house-movie-anarchist-tendencies/ 
\- http://movieclips.com/ZvQ6F-the-russia-house-movie-a-picasso-metaphor/ 

“Internet a very large-scale spying machine” – info leaking site co-founder - https://rt.com/news/cryptome-classified-secret-wikileaks/ 

Corporate Media and the Austerity Campaign - http://youtu.be/mnPAII2yTeU 

Hardwired - http://youtu.be/bdImGZA-2SM 

ONU cuestiona medidas de austeridad en España por “desproporcionadas” - http://www.cubadebate.cu/noticias/2012/05/21/onu-cuestiona-medidas-de-austeridad-en-espana-por-desproporcionadas/ 

American Spring: The Documentary - http://youtu.be/b5F9nTlCpTc 

World's oldest democracy turns into dictatorship - http://english.pravda.ru/world/americas/22-05-2012/121204-democracy_dictatorship-0/ 

The Top 1% Vs YOU - http://youtu.be/IyJIGlInJnk 

Austerity, the Euro Crisis and the US - http://youtu.be/na7PRGUgLwI 

History Channel, Russian Mafia 1 - http://youtu.be/U1u2PrPqdUc 

INSIDE JOB - http://youtu.be/FzrBurlJUNk 
\- http://vimeo.com/23086688 

Hardwired (2009) - http://www.videodetective.com/movies/hardwired/81550#.T7uzorcSi-0 

Top 1% Tax Cut Bigger Than 99% Income - http://youtu.be/twVinyvOQjk 

'Vicious spiral of decline: Germany leads Europe into a worse crisis' - http://youtu.be/HEs1kQYqLyk 

JP Morgan Debacle Shows Deep Systemic Risk Unchanged - http://youtu.be/yyifLaiTM98 
\- http://youtu.be/8aufSeGRZz0 

Assange Episode 6: Coups &amp; Corruption - http://youtu.be/yZXs-iYs95g 

Joint statement issued by communist parties from across the European Union (updated) - http://www.pcp.pt/en/joint-statement-issued-communist-parties-across-european-union 

Eurocrat mandarins want more cash amid economic turmoil - http://youtu.be/CE1DN_1LG2U 

The third crisis of capitalism - http://english.pravda.ru/business/finance/08-05-2012/121052-The_third_crisis_of_capitalism-0/ 

History Channel, Russian Mafia 2 - http://youtu.be/S4daDrmvbh4 

Chekist - http://youtu.be/6WmZ8ncEXds 

History Channel, Russian Mafia 3 - http://youtu.be/QJaC-n1nsmc 

A Different Loyalty - http://youtu.be/yCdi7DLGvgM 

Historical Song (Песня о мечте Свой среди чужих,чужой среди своих) - http://youtu.be/4VkLH5WbrG8 

"Struggle is the path" - http://www.pcp.pt/en/struggle-path 

Soviet Music - Bravely We Will Fight (english subtitles).mp4 - http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

Julian Assange Show: Rafael Correa (E6) - http://youtu.be/ZvUwC5JTAJY 

Sun Tzu - Art of War [with subtitles in English] - http://youtu.be/YPevcesvz8w 

“The path towards peace and its enemies” - http://www.pcp.pt/en/%E2%80%9C-path-towards-peace-and-its-enemies%E2%80%9D 

David Harvey on Class and Class Struggle - http://youtu.be/UhqD3az9cZ4 

Humans destroy a third of Earth's biological resources in 40 years - http://english.pravda.ru/news/science/15-05-2012/121122-humans_earth-0/ 

David Harvey at BBC Hardtalk 1/3 - http://youtu.be/F_XqTXsGBL8 
David Harvey at BBC Hardtalk 2/3 - http://youtu.be/LEoaxSDVsSA 
David Harvey at BBC Hardtalk 3/3 - http://youtu.be/lHBcEz3cYM8 

'US next Greece if debt is not dealt with' - http://youtu.be/h8TiFx56pxU 

CAPITALISM IS THE CRISIS: Radical Politics in the Age of Austerity examines the ideological roots of the "austerity" agenda and proposes revolutionary paths out of the current crisis - http://www.capitalismisthecrisis.net/watchthefilm.html 
\- http://youtu.be/fYFw3O--2R0 

A Deeper Crisis is Coming, WE MUST CONTROL THE BANKS/FINANCE SYSTEMS - http://youtu.be/6WlmsqvKZvI 

Richard Wolff: Question capitalism - http://youtu.be/h8CO3t9bEwI 

Thoroughly modern Karl Marx... 
\- http://youtu.be/FV3emNd9zwA 

Thoroughly modern Karl Marx... 
\- http://youtu.be/oWudLEwveGE 

Thoroughly modern Karl Marx... 
\- http://youtu.be/d-MaV6uZrgM 

America Beyond Capitalism - http://youtu.be/RKaCyB41yCQ 

"The European Union, a threat to democracy" - http://www.pcp.pt/en/european-union-threat-democracy 

The Master and Margarita (English subtitles). Part 3 (5/5) - http://youtu.be/XMo0M6Xs11w 

The Master and Margarita (English subtitles). Part 4 (1/5) - http://youtu.be/CAo3XbyUpzk 

The Master and Margarita (English subtitles). Part 4 (2/5) - http://youtu.be/qyaqRBrN_0c 

The Master and Margarita (English subtitles). Part 4 (3/5) - http://youtu.be/lI2m1O1jfxA 

Capitalism brings immense suffering to the world and needs to be overthrown that is according to political economist and author Raymond Lotta from New York. He told RT he thinks a revolution is coming - http://youtu.be/tg3hYLzfWYQ 

Marx on Capitalism - http://youtu.be/TrWEfAxnRp0 

What Have The Soviet Unions ☭ ☆ Ever Done For Us? 
\- http://youtu.be/184NTV2CE_c 
\- http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1irg4_l-appel-des-resistants_news 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

I See You [Theme from Avatar] - http://youtu.be/3YDz-ftqr1g 

Obama uses nuclear summit to issue new threats against North Korea and Iran - https://www.wsws.org/articles/2012/mar2012/obam-m27.shtml 

"COLLAPSE OF SOVIET UNION A HUGE MISTAKE" ... treason !- http://youtu.be/Ee1MM6prcik 
\- http://youtu.be/IatoF2H-pnQ 

Combat Neoliberalism/Capitalism - http://youtu.be/yhfZaJXDV8Q 

First Squads &amp; many other compatible ☭☆☭☆ Countries... The Moment Of Truth (STOP NATO &amp; USA &amp; EU) 
\- http://youtu.be/V6ZsV4-EmHk 
\- http://youtu.be/Tp_z1wEDxeE 
\- http://youtu.be/x2ZMGPnLrok 

A Nuclear Winter wonderland? - http://english.pravda.ru/society/stories/07-12-2011/119879-A_Nuclear_Winter_wonderland-0/ \- http://english.pravda.ru/opinion/columnists/05-12-2011/119846-Nuclear_war_on_the_horizon-0/ 

Desastres naturales, ¿obra de armas climáticas? - http://actualidad.rt.com/actualidad/internacional/issue_37389.html 

S.M.E.R.S.H. Protect yourself... BRIC + SCO + CSTO &amp; or any other compatible ☭☆☭☆ Countries/Nations (places outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER/E.U. IV REICH &amp; Weirmarch NATO) BROTHERS ☭ ☆ UNITE &amp; STICK ALWAYS TO ALL YOUR GUNS (FAIR ECONOMIC TRADE, MILITARY, TECHNOLOGIC &amp; OTHERS SECTORS)... 

Lenin's speech: Consumers' and Producers' Co-Operative Societies ☭ ☆ 
\- http://youtu.be/GE9JXScBK3g 

(...) COMMUNISM, which in modern times has been based mainly on the writings of Karl Marx, Friedrich Engels, and Vladimir Lenin, is an economic system where the means of production are publicly owned collectively by the people of a state, and where people work co-operatively toward a common good.(...) 

Soviet Education - http://youtu.be/ymUytfnBhD8 

CHINA + RUSSIA + CUBA + INDIA + VIETNAM + LIBYA + SOUTH AFRICA + VENEZUELA + ANGOLA + NICARAGUA + NORTH KOREA + BRIC + SCO &amp; many other compatible ☭☆☭☆ Countries/Continents/Nations (places outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER/E.U. IV REICH &amp; Weirmarch NATO )… ARE &amp; SHOULD BE BROTHERS FOREVER ! 
\- http://youtu.be/KUx6FZtKi8A 
\- http://www.spike.com/video/sasha-dith-russian/2754505 
\- http://youtu.be/lYFmnnElNXU 

On the brink of Third World War - 2012... 
\- http://english.pravda.ru/world/americas/26-03-2012/120891-third_world_war-0/ 
\- http://english.pravda.ru/world/americas/26-03-2012/120891-third_world_war-1/ 

Soviet Music - Bravely We Will Fight (english subtitles)... 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

\- Communism... http://youtu.be/ise7lyGP1dM 

Order 22 - NOT ONE STEP BACK!... I HOPE TO BE INVITED SOON WITH WORK CONTRACT, ALL DOCUMENTS TO LIVE &amp; WORK IN EURASIA (China &amp; Russia &amp; or any other compatible ☭ ☆ Countries /Nations/places outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER) and NATO (the new Wehrmacht) &amp; this Secret Rulers of the World IV REICH... 

We from the future 2 - http://www.latestrussianfilms.com/video-online-We_from_the_future_2_Russian_Movie.php 

Anti-Soviet Propaganda in Enemy at The Gates - http://youtu.be/hlFePQbWX-k 

Russia's "Jurassic Capitalism" - http://youtu.be/BegBHxCDYuA 

Highway Robbers to Drunken Drivers - http://youtu.be/ACQh1DreCm0 

Strategic Planning Lessons from Enemy At The Gates- http://vimeo.com/40647618 

Russia's "Jurassic Capitalism" Pt.2 - http://youtu.be/8pTkbdeu9QI 

Enemy at the Gates - NO MERCY FOR COWARDS - http://youtu.be/EbToIVXo8C4 

We from the future promo video - http://youtu.be/jxs6qiLqAkY 

«In my opinion, Western countries have repeatedly invaded Russia (&amp; china) because of these two factors: 

First, a miscalculation that their combined force will be enough to 
overcome Russian force of resistance. 

Then, after first failed attempt in 1812-1813 Russia did not avenge 
and thus the invaders have understood that even in case of their 
failure they don't lose much and the enemy gets weakened anyway. So, why not try again? As long as he gets away with impunity, offender will certainly repeat the crime. 

In my humble opinion, the reason why western nations are so carefree when attacking other nations, including Russia, is because they 
practically never got punished for it.» V 

First World War, Civil War, Foreign Interventions (WWII)... All those have been won, with high price, that many payed dearly with their lives or the lives of the ones they cared. So many sacrifices, so many lives lost. Back to square one... - http://youtu.be/6WmZ8ncEXds 

Enemy At The Gates - Commissar Danilov's Final Stand - http://youtu.be/uJRhtf-dT4k 

Inside Kremlin: What's hidden from public eye? (RT documentary) - http://youtu.be/JdHO3q9oRPk 

Enemy At The Gates - Deleted Scene - http://youtu.be/mb16RB0aygM 

Perestroika deception/treason/betrayal created mistrust of present day - http://youtu.be/ybxXrp3jR8Y 
\- http://youtu.be/ZaeICQbRht8 

BROTHERS ☭ ☆ ... S.M.E.R.S.H. Protect yourself! - MANY Millions GRU/Vympel/ Osnaz/Spetsnaz &amp; оперативная тройка - судебная тройка - чрезвычайная тройка - специальная тройка &amp; MANY thousands of new improved RA-115s &amp; RA-115-01s &amp; many others &amp; many others... 
\- http://youtu.be/ghg1msJpeas 
\- http://youtu.be/KUx6FZtKi8A 
\- http://youtu.be/ghg1msJpeas 
\- http://youtu.be/S6oH7CY-8Fg 
\- http://youtu.be/Eeo2LuqtLj0 
\- http://youtu.be/kq24oayfpm0 
\- http://youtu.be/ookHhYDzlxo 
\- http://youtu.be/mEabVfmQ9N8 
\- http://youtu.be/Kfi-llNlU0g 
\- http://youtu.be/P5DY90S56dc 
\- http://youtu.be/CW4nR6kgg8I 

Communism - http://youtu.be/aZm3vIgt9aY 

(...) COMMUNISM, which in modern times has been based mainly on the writings of Karl Marx, Friedrich Engels, and Vladimir Lenin, is an economic system where the means of production are publicly owned collectively by the people of a state, and where people work co-operatively toward a common good.(...) 

Thoroughly modern Marx - http://youtu.be/FV3emNd9zwA 
\- http://youtu.be/oWudLEwveGE 
\- http://youtu.be/d-MaV6uZrgM 

SAYING NO (bu shi &amp; нет) &amp; NO &amp; NO... TO NATO USA UN EU &amp; Capitalism/Neoliberalism/Imperialism/Neocolonialism (THIS NEW EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG IV REICH EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER &amp; Weirmarch NATO)!- http://youtu.be/zFGtEHJLok0 

Capitalism brings immense suffering to the world and needs to be overthrown that is according to political economist and author Raymond Lotta from New York. He told RT he thinks a revolution is coming - http://youtu.be/tg3hYLzfWYQ 

Marx on Capitalism - http://youtu.be/TrWEfAxnRp0 

What Have The Soviet Unions ☭ ☆ Ever Done For Us? 
\- http://youtu.be/184NTV2CE_c 
\- http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1irg4_l-appel-des-resistants_news 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

"Everything You've Been Told about Communism Is Wrong, Capitalism Is a Failure, Revolution (MARXISM-LENINISM ☭☆ COMMUNISM) Is the Solution" - http://youtu.be/Ms99-3Nj81I 

PROLETARIANS ☭☆☭☆ OF ALL COUNTRIES UNITE (Proletarian ☭☆ internationalism &amp; International ☭☆ Brigades) AGAINST COUNTER-REVOLUTIONARIES TERRORIST (Bank$ters, hooligans,profiteers, speculators, bandits) SPONSORED BY THIS EUROATLANTIC (U.S.A. &amp; E.U.) THIS EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/CORRUPT KLEPTOCRACY, MODERN DAY SLAVERY, WAGE DEBT SLAVES/NEW ORDER/NATO (the new Wehrmacht) &amp; this Secret Rulers of the World IV REICH &amp; THE ENDGAME = Blueprint for Global Enslavement - Combat Liberalism 
\- The American Dream By The Provocateur Network 
\- http://youtu.be/n7Fzm1hEiDQ 
\- http://youtu.be/Bb3gB-qY2bQ 
\- http://youtu.be/IDJMjuKt-gc 

Capitalism brings immense suffering to the world and needs to be overthrown that is according to political economist and author Raymond Lotta from New York. He told RT he thinks a revolution is coming - http://youtu.be/tg3hYLzfWYQ 

Marx on Capitalism - http://youtu.be/TrWEfAxnRp0 

What Have The Soviet Unions ☭ ☆ Ever Done For Us? 
\- http://youtu.be/184NTV2CE_c 
\- http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1irg4_l-appel-des-resistants_news 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

"Everything You've Been Told about Communism Is Wrong, Capitalism Is a Failure, Revolution (MARXISM-LENINISM ☭☆ COMMUNISM) Is the Solution" - http://youtu.be/Ms99-3Nj81I 

The voice of allegiance/loyalty... 
Please NO “MISUNDERSTANDINGS” OR “MISINTERPRETATIONS... 

I was... I am... &amp; I always will be a far-left (MARXIST-LENINIST ☭☆ COMMUNIST) social moderate (Laic, Humanist, Secular, Atheist ), non- interventionist, internationalist and cultural liberal and... «I'm not Scared, and Do It Anyway» &amp; "I will always stick to my guns" ... I WILL WORK FOR RUSSIA &amp; CHINA &amp; or any other compatible ☭☆ Countries/Nations (outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG IV REICH) IF &amp; WHEN I RECEIVE A FORMAL LETTER OF INVITATION, JOB OFFER, SIGN A WORK CONTRACT, GET ALL LEGAL DOCUMENTS AND AUTHORISATIONS... 

Valete - Anti Heroi (legendado)... 
\- http://youtu.be/QeHd3em2gWA 

L’appel des résistants... 
\- http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1irg4_lappel-des-resistants 

Latinoamérica... 
\- http://youtu.be/IMiPSf2QNZ8 

\- Combat Neoliberalism/Capitalism - http://youtu.be/yhfZaJXDV8Q 

Raymond Lotta Takes on Lies about Mao's Great Leap Forward - http://youtu.be/Jw8VEwHUlJs 

Bob Avakian, "A better world is possible," clip from Revolution, a film of a talk - http://youtu.be/SGVKkHPQBjc 

(...) The post-Soviet Russia has neither the ideology - global soft power appeal of the USA (...) nor has it the vibrant, world-leading and highly lucrative High-Tech and IT sector (... ) 
21.02.2012 - Geopolitics of Technology and the Hydrocarbon Status Quo - Pravda 

BUT IT HAS ALL CONDITIONS TO REBUILT WHAT WAS DESTROYED (soft power and hard power) BY THE HUGE MISTAKE (TREASON by drunken turncoats &amp; traitors &amp; political deserters &amp; corrupt Apparatchiks) THAT REPRESENTED THE COLLAPSE OF SOVIET UNION... 

Putin and the tall wall against western mischief - http://english.pravda.ru/business/finance/28-02-2012/120637-Putin_and_the_tall_wall-0/ 

What Have The Soviet Unions ☭ ☆ Ever Done For Us? 
\- http://youtu.be/IatoF2H-pnQ 
\- http://youtu.be/184NTV2CE_c 
\- http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1irg4_l-appel-des-resistants_news 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

Society » Real life stories - World's most powerful rocket performed only two flights - http://english.pravda.ru/society/stories/15-05-2012/121118-energia_rocket-0/ 

Ideals of social justice... Combat Neo-Liberalism, Imperialism, Fascism, all Theocracies, Capitalism, Neocolonialism, Proto-nazism THIS EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/CORRUPT KLEPTOCRACY, MODERN DAY SLAVERY, WAGE DEBT SLAVES/NEW ORDER,NATO (the new Wehrmacht) &amp; this Secret Rulers of the World IV REICH &amp; THE ENDGAME = Blueprint for Global Enslavement... 
\- Combat Neoliberalism/Capitalism - http://youtu.be/yhfZaJXDV8Q 
\- The American Dream By The Provocateur Network - http://youtu.be/ZPWH5TlbloU 
Total Collapse - The Build up to World War III - http://youtu.be/X_KAj8O8qes 
\- http://youtu.be/n7Fzm1hEiDQ 
\- http://youtu.be/Bb3gB-qY2bQ 
\- http://youtu.be/IDJMjuKt-gc 
\- http://english.pravda.ru/society/stories/20-09-2011/119095-wost_enemy-0/ 
\- http://vimeo.com/29701339 
\- http://youtu.be/QeHd3em2gWA 
\- http://youtu.be/yhfZaJXDV8Q 

\- Combat Neoliberalism/Capitalism - http://youtu.be/yhfZaJXDV8Q 

Hu Jintao/CPC: No tolerance to corruption &amp; turncoats &amp; traitors &amp; political deserters &amp; corrupt Apparatchiks &amp; DEBT SLAVES OLIGARCHIES - http://english.cpc.people.com.cn/66097/66188/4480819.html 
\- http://english.cpc.people.com.cn/66097/66188/4485875.html 
\- http://english.cpcnews.cn/92275/6287709.html 
\- http://english.cpc.people.com.cn/66097/66185/4473075.html 
\- http://english.cpc.people.com.cn/65547/65572/4481151.html 
\- http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/90002/92169/92187/6283181.html 

\- Communism... http://youtu.be/ise7lyGP1dM 

Soviet Music - Bravely We Will Fight (english subtitles)... 
\- http://youtu.be/DSMPqSV2KTU 

USA Military NATO and CIA Interventions since World War II - http://www.globalresearch.ca/index.php?context=viewArticle&amp;code=BLU20120220&amp;articleId=29410 

I WILL CONTINUE TO MAKE MY CASE FOR reinforcing SCO &amp; CIS &amp; CSTO &amp; Proletarian ☭☆ ☭☆ internationalism &amp; rebuilt International ☭☆ ☭☆ Brigades &amp; MANY Millions GRU☭☆ ☭☆ /Vympel ☭☆ ☭☆ / Osnaz☭☆ ☭☆ /Spetsnaz ☭☆ ☭☆ &amp; ☭☆ ☭☆ TROIKAS ☭☆ ☭☆ (оперативная тройка ☭☆ ☭☆ Proletarian ☭☆ ☭☆ NGOs ☭☆ ☭☆ International ☭☆ ☭☆ Carbonari ☭☆ air/land/sea ☭☆ Brigades (better trained equipped than capitalist imperialist XE Blackwater) - судебная тройка ☭☆ ☭☆ - чрезвычайная тройка ☭☆ ☭☆ - специальная тройка ☭☆ ☭☆ &amp; BRICS &amp; LIBYA AND THE GREEN REVOLUTION/GADAFI (and all previous/future victims of this ignoble proto-nazi capitalist warmongering strategies) AND AGAINST CAPITALISM, NATO,NEOCOLONIALIST/IMPERIALIST OPERATIONS BARBAROSSA, BILDERBERG, KLEPTOCRATIC PLUTOCRACIA/OLIGARCHIES, BOHEMIAN GROVE, IMF, HUMANITARIAN HYPOCRISY, LIES, E.U., DOUBLE STANDARDS, REGIME CHANGE, U.S.A.,USING HUMAN RIGHTS TO SELL ECONOMIC HITMEN WARS, OPPORTUNISM, CORPORATOCRACY,NEOCOLONIALISM &amp; THE REAL “END GAMES” WITHOUT CONSPIRACY THEORIES BUT TRUE HISTORICAL FACTS/EVENTS AND LOGICAL, UNCOMPROMISED, UNBIASED ANALYSIS! 

CHINA + RUSSIA (BRICS &amp; SCO &amp; ALBA) BROTHERS FOREVER! - http://youtu.be/KUx6FZtKi8A 

CHINA + RUSSIA (BRICS &amp; SCO &amp; ALBA are a Superpower again - http://youtu.be/qo2tXjcAHCU 

BROTHERS ☭ ☆ ... S.M.E.R.S.H. Protect yourself! - MANY Millions GRU/Vympel/ Osnaz/Spetsnaz &amp; TROIKAS (оперативная тройка - судебная тройка - чрезвычайная тройка - специальная тройка) &amp; MANY thousands of new improved RA-115s &amp; RA-115-01s &amp; many others &amp; many others... 
\- http://youtu.be/8KQGXf5b7dU 
\- http://youtu.be/ZbHLc2kP8V4 
\- http://youtu.be/XZJrB62Qv8o 
\- http://youtu.be/KOS0_WEuYUU 
\- http://youtu.be/4MNMNJ7oWI8 
\- http://youtu.be/y6fN6wUAbjU 
\- http://youtu.be/9RaQzcB8i_A 

SCO Tribute - http://youtu.be/v_yjgwk-_e8 \- http://youtu.be/qOjvc-DOyAw 

Discurso Che Guevara - Abaixo ao imperialismo (Capitalism &amp; Neocolonialism)! 
\- http://youtu.be/h0DnbRAdYCc 
\- http://youtu.be/0jy2sHwakLY 
\- http://youtu.be/OCDBCeRRk9Q 

PUSH Clip - "Telekinetic Gun Fight" 
\- http://youtu.be/nPAoy3UMh_Y 
\- http://youtu.be/EgB70STcqSw 
\- http://youtu.be/TNsOqVBzrYo 
\- http://youtu.be/afT1fAwSr-Q 
\- http://youtu.be/oow0d-lLY8E 

Crisis: The stupidity of the western approach - http://english.pravda.ru/opinion/columnists/29-11-2011/119777-stupidity_crisis-0/ 

One of the reasons why I NEVER WORKED AND I WILL NEVER WORK FOR ANY OF THESE 1%+19 % (of abetters/acolytes/capitalist economic hitmen/henchmen/accomplices &amp; Plutocratic Bilderberg Bohemian Club &amp; THIS IS WHY I DO NOT WANT America (USA NATO E.U.) to stay a superpower (Corporatocracy, Corporatism, Fascism) &amp; Gladio odeSSa operations nazi Bilderberg Bohemian Club IV reich economic Dictatures)... Controlled Worldwide Economic Collapse Planned Around Arrival of 2nd Sun Brown Dwarf Star - http://youtu.be/ZnpACqHJXPo 

Ten myths about capitalism - http://english.pravda.ru/business/companies/15-02-2012/120518-ten_myths_capitalism-0/ 

CPC ☭☆ ☭☆ discipline &amp; cadre ☭☆ ☭☆ watchdog vows zero tolerance to Corruption, Stagnation, Economic Sabotage, Corrupt Capitalist Kleptocracies/Plutocracies &amp; Neoliberal Burocracies &amp; Hooligans Profiteers &amp; Speculators &amp; Corporocracys &amp; Officials &amp; Burocrats &amp; Turncoat &amp; Trojan and global treasons/proto-nazi capitalist warmongering strategies... 
\- http://english.cpc.people.com.cn/66102/7293682.html 

World ☭☆ ☭☆ Revolution is coming - http://youtu.be/y-SxRGB36D8 

Capitalism brings immense suffering to the world and needs to be overthrown that is according to political economist and author Raymond Lotta from New York. He told RT he thinks a revolution is coming - http://youtu.be/tg3hYLzfWYQ 

Marx on Capitalism - http://youtu.be/TrWEfAxnRp0 

"Everything You've Been Told about Communism Is Wrong, Capitalism Is a Failure, Revolution (MARXISM-LENINISM ☭☆ COMMUNISM) Is the Solution" - http://youtu.be/Ms99-3Nj81I 

Respect. 

COMRADES ☭☆☭☆ &amp; FRIENDS ☆☆☆☆ FROM CHINA &amp; RUSSIA &amp; or any other ☭☆ compatible Countries/Nations (places outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER &amp; this Secret Rulers of the World IV REICH)... 

Lou Reed - perfect day (animated) - http://youtu.be/IcFwFXlSwRk 

I HOPE TO BE INVITED SOON TO LIVE &amp; WORK IN EURASIA (China &amp; Russia &amp; or any other compatible ☭☆ Countries/Nations/places outside this EUROATLANTIC BILDERBERG EMPIRE/MATRIX/NEW ORDER/IV REICH)! WHERE ARE THE JOB/EMPLOYMENT OFFERS SENT BY POSTAL MAIL OR EMAIL OR BY PHONE CONTACT OR A DIRECTLY AND PERSONALLY CONTACT ?!? 

Boss AC - Sexta-feira (Emprego Bom Já) with subtitles in English - http://youtu.be/sFH0-u9L_9I 

IT IS TIME TO PUT WORDS &amp; INTENTIONS INTO ACTIONS AND SEND ME THE FORMAL INVITATIONS/DOCUMENTS/WORK CONTRACT/ALL LEGAL AUTHORIZATIONS. 

Maroon 5 - Payphone (Lyric Video) ft. Wiz Khalifa - http://youtu.be/5FlQSQuv_mg﻿

Meer lezen (813 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7474_10_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Emayz1unV6k/T7prSJXRkMI/AAAAAAAAQl0/E5LK-btSTJg/w426-h311/snapshot26.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>