<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:51:38" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/107234826207633309420/albums/5793684916839960385/5793684923343852338</link><title>Do you work as an IT consultant from your home? If so, which tools do you rely on to help you get the job done for your customers and clients? 

http://www.lockergnome.com/it/2012/09/29/independent-it-consultant-tips/ 

Have you taken a look at what GoToAssist can do for your business?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-fU61_YYmuwo/UGdNvdRyUzI/AAAAAAABzSk/wXo0XDQsGzA/w426-h319/Phone-250x187.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/115918496651393562489/albums/5937320953538400817/5937320959899078338</link><title>Work with exciting external clients and an internal team of intelligent and committed team members! 

Hello STAR Collaborative Network! 

We are actively seeking interested candidates for the following opportunity! If you are interested in the position, and if you feel you are qualified, please follow this link to read more and apply online: 
www.STARcollaborative.com/opportunities. 

Opportunity Details: 
STAR # 3633 
Project Manager - Road Warrior / 75% Travel - Minnesota - Direct Hire 
Location: Minneapolis, MN 
Date Due to STAR: 11/1/2013 4:12 AM 
Start Date: 10/7/2013 

We are on the hunt for a Project Manager with 5+ yrs of hands on project management experience. Your career history must be primarily full-time employment with most of your tenure in software businesses, as an employee, not as a consultant. Responsible for the overall management of our client’s implementation projects and is responsible for the direction, coordination, implementation, execution, control of all resources (people, product, process and infrastructure) needed to successfully complete a project in a manner consistent with company strategy, commitments and goals. 

If you possess a strong employment history and tenure, with references from past employers, peers and direct reports who can attest to your strong delivery outcomes, we want to talk with you immediately. Our client has very specific requirements on this role to ensure a strong match to their very unique and evolving culture and scope of this role. The environment is collaborative and you will work with senior leaders in the organization and enjoy their goal of creating a strong employee experience while ensuring superior client service. 

Travel is anticipated to occur so that you can work Monday through Thursday nationwide at client sites, and fly home for the weekend. Not every week will include this level, but candidates must have the ability, desire and ambition to be that true "road warrior". 

Essential Job Responsibilities: 
&gt; Lead the planning and implementation of the company software suite for a specified customer 
&gt; Generate the requisite service contracts (Statement of Work or Change Requests) and maintain ongoing governance 
&gt; Facilitate the definition of project scope, goals and deliverables 
&gt; Define project tasks and resource requirements 
&gt; Develop full scale project plans 
&gt; Assemble and coordinate project staff 
&gt; Manage project budget and resource allocation 
&gt; Plan and schedule project timelines 
&gt; Track project deliverables using appropriate tools 
&gt; Provide direction and support to project team 
&gt; Monitor and report on progress of the project to all stakeholders 
&gt; Present reports defining project progress, problems and solutions 
&gt; Implement and manage project changes and interventions to achieve project outputs 
&gt; Up to 75% travel within US 

Experience/Skills Required: 
&gt; 5+years retail experience at either a retailer or a firm concentrating on retail as a Business or Technical team member or consultant 
&gt; 5-7 years Project Management and has managed projects with teams of 5-10 people 
&gt; Project Management of ERP level retail software implementation (demand planning, forecasting, assortment planning, replenishment, procurement, space management preferred) 
&gt; Experienced with MS Project, MS Office Suite and MS Vision-preferred 

Education: 
&gt; BA/BS Required 
&gt; PMI certification preferred 

Read more/apply online at www.STARcollaborative.com/opportunities 

Some clients require background checks and drug screening as a condition for engagement or employment. This means you could be asked to submit to any or all of the following: criminal background check, credit check or drug screen. 

Candidates must be eligible to work in the United States without sponsorship. In addition, we are seeking local candidates only as this role is not eligible for travel and relocation reimbursement. 

Attention Recruiters: We thank you for your interest, but we prefer to work directly with individuals and our own Collaborative Network on this posting. We will not review resumes/return calls from unsolicited recruiters. 

If you are interested in learning more about STAR Collaborative and the clients we serve, send an e-mail to opportunities@STARcollaborative.com. 

If this isn't a match for you, please forward on to anyone you might think interested and qualified! Pay it forward! 

Thanks from the Team at STAR Collaborative! 
Partner of Choice for the Collaborative Network (R) 

#MNjobs #STARcollaborative  ﻿

Meer lezen (101 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-hU84x8Hg5Ac/UmWZ9KxEDsI/AAAAAAAACP0/sAqaAjDu3AE/w426-h284/shutterstock_145291327.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/111372176993021916262/albums/5997421315169172641/5997421317492113202</link><title>Meet Dorothy Graham :: Software Testing Consultant 

In software testing for forty years, Dorothy Graham is coauthor of four books—Software Inspection, Software Test Automation, Foundations of Software Testing and Experiences of Test Automation—and is currently working with Seretta Gamba on a new book on test automation patterns. 

Dorothy will be leading two half-day tutorials at #STAREAST , learn more here: http://vlt.me/dgg 

#testautomation   #management  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_03_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-d4rdhnCdi3k/Uzse6Z14_zI/AAAAAAAAAas/o_X7t2v4tZI/w426-h237/Dorothy_stareast.png.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/103106034875884987429/albums/6014554462653088129/6014554463267376898</link><title>Professional Income Tax Resolution and much more! 
www.oc-services.net 
www.ictaxpros4u.com 
www.oc-services.net 

Always Professional... 

________________________________________________________________ 

&lt;meta name="description" content="My name is Irene Christensen, my team and I would like to make OC Financial your number one source for financial solutions and services dealing with personal income tax, notary public services, real e" /&gt; 
&lt;meta name="keywords" content="Christensen, business tax, real estate tax, taxes, tax law, tax questions, Orange County tax, , tax questions, income tax questions, Los Angeles tax, Los Angeles tax questions, small business taxes, small business tax questions, tax debt, IRS taxes, IRS tax debt, California taxes, Franchise Tax Board, Franchise Tax board debt, California tax questions, difficult taxes, Internal Revenue Service, IRS notice, IRS extension, 4868, Form 4868, back taxes, innocent spouse, offer in compromise, tax negotiation, Schedule A, Schedule C, Schedule D, itemized deductions, student loan deduction, IRA deduction, Schedule E, Schedule C, Schedule C-EZ, self-employed taxes, 1099, 1099C, 1040, 1040A, 540, 540A, 8812, 8917, earned income credit, dependent, 8888, cancelled debt, net operating loss, NOL, bad debt, foreclosure debt, Mortgage debt relief, Mortgage debt relief Act, taxable income, tax installments, installment agreement, form 9465, 9465, tax penalties, tax penalty, tax help, business write offs, tax information, taxes due date, taxes 2012, taxes 2011, taxes 2010, taxes 2009, taxes 2008, amended taxes, amended income tax return, publication 17, filing status, filing information, personal exemptions, exemptions, tax withholding, estimated tax, estimated taxes, interest income, dividend distribution, corporate distribution, rental income, rental expenses, home buyer tax credit, California home buyer tax credit, tax solution, tax solutions, tax solutions Fullerton CA, income taxes Brea CA, payoff tax debt, Franchise Tax Board problems, Franchise Tax Board debt, remove wage garnishment, remove bank levy, free tax consultation, free tax advice, types of tax deductions, tax deductions, tax credits, tax preparation, tax consultant, backed up taxes, US Treasury, federal income taxes, FICA, tax brackets, AGI, adjusted gross income, head of household, Anaheim Hills, Anaheim, Brea, Chino Hills, Yorba Linda, Placentia, Buena Park, Orange, Orange Hills, Villa Park, Irvine, Costa Mesa, Tustin, Newport Beach, Newport Coast, income tax collections, 2330 W. Valencia Dr. Fullerton, CA. 92833, inexpensive tax help, income tax deadline, ITIN, individual tax payer identification number, service en Español, taxes de negocio. We offer professional tax preparation services for both individuals and small businesses. If filing your taxes online is not what you are looking for and prefer to have us prepare your taxes, please call us for a tax interview appointment at 714-626-0558.We are located at 2330 W. Valencia Dr. Fullerton, Ca 92833.We are Tax Preparers with access to CPAs specializing in individual income tax and small business tax preparation and tax planning, serving Orange County and North Orange County, including Anaheim, Brea, Buena Park, Fullerton, Placentia and Yorba Linda. Accountant, accounting, cpa, Fullerton, Brea, Buena park, Yorba Linda, Placentia, individual income tax, small business accounting, tax experts, bookkeeping, payroll, tax preparation. We have professionals ready to help you with your Tax Returns. Quick turnaround, satisfaction guarantee, contacts us. Tax preparation in Fullerton, California, file taxes in Fullerton, California, and prepare taxes in Fullerton, California, Fullerton, California tax filing, Fullerton, California tax professional, tax preparers in Fullerton, California, professional tax filing Fullerton, California, professional tax preparers Fullerton, California. Accounting, accountant, accountants, business services, tax irs, bookkeeping, tax preparation, bookkeeper, business tax, business consulting, tax accounting, tax deduction, tax accounting software, tax deductions, tax services, accounting accountant, accounting bookkeeping, accounting firms, certified public accountants, payroll services, payroll tax, tax accountant, small business accounting, tax planning, tax preparation service, accounting firm, accounting services, certified accountant, payroll accounting, tax preparer, accounting service, book keeping, certified public accountant, certified public accounting, tax audit, audit accounting, business taxes, cpa accounting, cpa firm, cpa firms, small business consulting, small business tax, cpa accountant, cpa tax, auditing accounting, bookkeeping services, small business payroll, accounting help, tax preparation services, tax preparers, tax self employed, bookkeepers, tax consultant, accounting consulting, bookkeeping service, mileage tax, online tax preparation, payroll accounting software, tax accountants, tax consulting, accounting tax services, business accountant, income tax preparation services, small business taxes, income tax service in Fullerton. 
" /&gt; 
&lt;meta name="author" content="metatags generator"&gt; 
&lt;meta name="robots" content="index, follow"&gt; 
&lt;meta name="revisit-after" content="3 month"&gt; 
&lt;title&gt;income tax service&lt;/title&gt; 
&lt;!-- --&gt;﻿

Meer lezen (90 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-tt5NzW3uLx8/U3f9avlKzwI/AAAAAAAA90A/A2fkDMd4sis/w426-h289/energyquote.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/110275992142500804031/albums/6007743298151904193/6007743303916550098</link><title>#Detroit / #Livonia Career Expo on April 30. YES! tomorrow 
Hiring Companies Include The Following: 
Hired in Detroit Job Fair - April 30. YES! Tomorrow 
Look Who Hiring: 
Quicken Loans – Hiring Mortgage Bankers, Mortgage Sales and more positions see website - http://bit.ly/1ha7Tb6 

Roush Industries – Hiring Auto Technicians/Mechanics, Engine Design and Development Engineer, Peoplesoft Programmer, Engineering Lab Tech, Warehouse Supervisor, Plant Manager, Engineers, Technology, Mold Makers, Business Management, Technical, Quality Engineers, Vehicle Test Drivers, Plastic Injection, Entry-Level Mechanics, Chassis Engineer, Engine Calibration Engineer, Welding Inspectors, NVH Test Engineer, Product Engineer, Metal Fabrication, Mechanic Automotive, CNC Machinist, Powertrain Engineer and more positions see website http://bit.ly/1f3eYus 

The Harvard Drug Group – Hiring Inside Sales Representatives, Sales and more positions see website - http://bit.ly/1ha806L 

Verizon Wireless – Several Positions available see website at http://vz.to/1mk7mc6 

Mahindra Engineering Services – Hiring Electrical Engineer, Automotive Seat Engineer, Design Engineer and more positions see website http://bit.ly/1ler5gn 

Job Seekers Meet The Experts - Morgan Stanley Advisors – Contact Sammy Amine at http://bit.ly/QtrugN 

HiredinMichigan.com – Hiring Inside Business Development Representative $ 12.00-15.00 hourly plus commission, Experienced Business Telemarketer $ 12.00-15.00 hourly plus commission, Telemarketers$ 12.00-15.00 hourly plus commission, Account Managers with experience in specialty food industry $ 75,000 yearly. Submit Resume to oaksales@hiredinmichigan.com 

Global Information Technology – Hiring Entry Level and Advance It Professionals / Attend Free IT Training Seminar – review website at http://bit.ly/1les00f 

C* Mac Transportation - Hiring Truck Drivers, Dispatchers and more positions at http://bit.ly/1gH6eKY 

Budco / Novo 1 – Hiring Non-Licensed Insurance Agents $ 12.00 – 14.00 hourly plus commission, Experienced Insurance Sales, Customer Engagement Advocate $11.00 – 13.00 hourly plus commission, Social Media Advocate $13.50 hourly, Tuition Management Customer Service $9.75 -10.50 hourly, Blood Donation Specialist $9-10 hourly, Bilingual Spanish/English Customer Service Advocate $10-12 hourly – see more positions at http://bit.ly/1hUaMCX 

United Lawnscape - Several Positions Available Now – Landscaping Crew, Supervisors, Truck Drivers, Landscaping Forman, Fertilizer Tech and more see website http://bit.ly/1hTSZLt 

First Financial Insurance Group – Hiring Insurance Agents (earn hourly plus commission) – see website http://bit.ly/1eQWHpN 

Jewish Senior Life - Hiring Nursing, Healthcare, Rehabilitation and Therapist – see website http://bit.ly/1kJe3EE 

Trinity Transportation - Hiring Mechanics, Bus Drivers, School Bus Driver, Diesel Mechanic, Mechanic Helpers, School Bus Attendant, Motor Coach Driver and more positions see website - http://bit.ly/1nfW5fL 

New York Life Insurance - Hiring Insurance Agent ( Experienced Licensed or Entry-Level Non-Licensed) – review website http://bit.ly/1awgx0i 

New Horizons Computer Learning Center – Account Executive, Sales review website at http://bit.ly/1lexQyA 

H &amp; H Wholesale Distributors –Several Positions 

Waddell &amp; Reed Financial Advisors – Financial Advisors review website at http://bit.ly/1lgSwSa 

Precision Door Detroit – Sales, Service Tech, Garage Door Installation and Maintenance – review website at http://bit.ly/QttmWE 

Titan Solutions – Several Positions 

Rxtra Solutions – Several Positions 

Walden University (Student Recruitment Only) – Meet Recruiter at Job Fair 

Minacs (Onstar, Netflix Hiring) - Hiring Netflix Customer Service Representative $ 11.50 hourly, Wireless Customer Service &amp; Sales Agent $ 11.00 houly and more positions see website at http://bit.ly/1jR7UW5 

Uncle Ed's Oil Shoppe - Hiring Store Managers, Assistant Managers, Service Associates $7.40/hr - $40,000+/yr review website for details at http://bit.ly/1habDcT 

Wayne County Health Authority - Nursing Positions – review website at http://bit.ly/1me07VG 

Dialog Direct / Dialogue Marketing - Hiring Non-Licensed Insurance Agents $ 12.00 – 14.00 hourly plus commission, Experienced Insurance Sales, Customer Engagement Advocate $11.00 – 13.00 hourly plus commission, Social Media Advocate $13.50 hourly, Tuition Management Customer Service $9.75 -10.50 hourly, Blood Donation Specialist $9-10 hourly, Bilingual Spanish/English Customer Service Advocate $10-12 hourly – see more positions at http://bit.ly/1hUaMCX 

Mainstreet Computers – Business 2 Business Sales, Web Developer, Technology, IT, Analyst, Developers, Programmers and more review website at http://bit.ly/1tixKap 

F. LAX Construction – Hiring Construction Project Manager, Construction Supervisor, Construction Estimator, Construction, Carpenters, Painters, Skilled Trades and more review website at http://bit.ly/1jR8CCN 

Colonial Life Insurance – Hiring Insurance Agents review website at http://bit.ly/1kJh0oX 

Inspire Home Care – Hiring Caregivers, CNA’s, HHA’s and more Healthcare/Nursing Jobs and many more positions at http://bit.ly/1kJh73S 

Brightstar Care of Novi - Medical Staffing/Medical Jobs and many more position at http://bit.ly/1tiygFr 

Sandler &amp; Travis Trade Advisory Services – Hiring Event Marketing, Webinar Coordinator, Analyst, Billing Analyst, Data Entry, Clerical, Trade Management Specialist, Compliance Analyst, Customs Specialist, Director European Operations, Technical Advisor, Human Resource, Sales Manager and more see website at http://bit.ly/1mk3VCc 

HTC Global Services – Hiring Programmers and Analysts, Technical and Software Architects, Project/Program Managers, Software Engineers, Database Administrators, Technical Analysts, Test Analysts/Managers, Business Analysts, System Administrators, Network Engineers, Security Analysts, ERP Analysts and more review website at http://bit.ly/QtuZE1 

Impact – Quality Engineers, Sales, Account Managers, Recruiters, Manufacturing Engineers, Several Positions Review Website at http://bit.ly/1eIjaVD 

Workforce Software – Hiring Integration Consultant, Product Manager, Senior System Administrator, Software Implementation Consultant, Technical Support Engineer, Human Resource Director, Information Security Engineer, Integration Consultant, Linux System Administrator, Senior System Administrator, Site Reliability Engineer, Staff Counsel, Windows Administrator, Director of Support Services, IT Services Desk Intern, Product Manager, Project Manager, QA Team Leader, Sales Engineer, Senior Software Engineer, Software Development Manager Technology Positions review positions at http://bit.ly/PcE1UX 

Primerica - Hiring Representatives review details at http://bit.ly/1f3qshy 

Elite Merchant Services – Hiring Telemarketers Merchant Sales, Technical and many more positions details at http://bit.ly/1lgXLRZ 

H.E. Lennon / Swagelok – Hiring engineering, finance, human resources, customer service, information services, marketing, communications, machinists, assemblers, welders, technicians and other manufacturing associates and sales review website for all positions at http://bit.ly/1mdSBu0 

Broder and Sachse Real Estate Services – Hiring leasing consultant, maintenance, property maintenance, construction, site manager accounting, insurance, real estate services and more review website at http://bit.ly/1hTZu0w 

Burger King - Hiring Restaurant Managers and more positions at http://bit.ly/1qVlb2C 

Sachse Construction Services - Hiring property maintenance, construction, accounting, insurance, real estate services and more review website at http://bit.ly/1hTZu0w 

A - Line Staffing – Hiring Application Developer, Engagement Center Specialist, Application Developer, Business Analyst, Several Positions Available review website at http://bit.ly/1gHdo1I 

Molex – Hiring Electrical Engineers, Test Manager, Metrology Specialist, Product Specialist and more review website at http://bit.ly/1kJlKuM 

MSC Industrial Supply – Hiring Account Representative, Branch Sales and more review website at http://bit.ly/1f3ueaH 

Mojo Host – Hiring Linux System Administrator, Technology Positions review website at http://bit.ly/1i2GvMy 

Courtyard Manor of Wixom - Healthcare/Nursing Positions review website at http://bit.ly/1kJmEau 

Halo Burger - Hiring Restaurant Managers review website at http://bit.ly/QtwxxJ 

Subway - Hiring Restaurant Managers review website at http://bit.ly/QtwxxJ 

Speedway - Hiring Manager &amp; Team Leaders review website at http://bit.ly/1nfZ3AG 

KC Transportation - Hiring CDL Drivers / Haulers review website at http://bit.ly/1qVoWoV 

Fraza Forklifts - Hiring Forklift Mechanics review website at http://bit.ly/1f3vfiR 

Nurse Family Partnership – Hiring Nurses-Home Visitor, Nurse-Family Partnership, Nurses with Experience review website at http://bit.ly/1me07VG 

MaryCrest Manor / Trinity Health – Hiring Assistant Director of Nursing, CNA, Clinic Care Coordinator, Clinic Life Coordinator, LPN, LPN Manager, RN, RN Manager, Staffing and more see website at http://bit.ly/1qVqgYJ 

Midwest Memorial Group – Hiring Advance Planning Counselors, Many terrific career opportunities are available with Midwest Memorial Group, with openings in Sales, Operations and Administration at our different locations in Michigan at any given time. Review website at http://bit.ly/1hU3cHu 

HealthMarket / Insphere Insurance Solutions – Insurance Sales Agents review website at http://bit.ly/PcJUBm 

Randall Data System – Hiring Customer Support, Training, Sales, Account Management, Marketing, Technology, Programming and more see website at http://bit.ly/RvsC4H 

LaJoy Group – Several Positions Available review website at http://bit.ly/1eIpg8v 

And many other companies....... 

Mark Your Calendar: Wednesday April 30, 2014 - Marriott Hotel- 17100 Laurel Park Drive North, Livonia, MI from 9am-3pm. 

Details at http://www.JobFairGiant.com/﻿

Meer lezen (244 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-LcPA9RH5c6U/U1_KtFutd9I/AAAAAAAAFAE/YVQgtxSewFI/s426/FRI4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/107130247487186913773/albums/5702396273635213377/5702396271040737106</link><title>BIOGRAPHY Google Search - Nelio Guerson Music Download 
google search | nelioguersonmusicdownload 

Google Search 
The Google homepage 
http://www.google.com (Original) 
https://www.google.com (Secure Version) 
Commercial? Yes 
Type of site Search engine 
IPv6 support Yes, by arrangement or ipv6.google.com 
Registration Optional 
Available language(s) Multilingual (124) 
Owner Google 
Created by Sergey Brin and Larry Page 
Launched September 15, 1997 (1997-09-15) 
Alexa rank 1 (July 2011) 
Revenue From AdWords 
Current status Active 

Google Search or Google Web Search is a web search engine owned by Google Inc. and is the most-used search engine on the Web. Google receives several hundred million queries each day through its various services. The main purpose of Google Search is to hunt for text in webpages, as opposed to other data, such as with Google Image Search. Google Search was originally developed by Larry Page and Sergey Brin in 1997. 

Google Search provides at least 22 special features beyond the original word-search capability. These include synonyms, weather forecasts, time zones, stock quotes, maps, earthquake data, movie showtimes, airports, home listings, and sports scores. (See below: Special features). There are special features for numbers, including ranges (70..73), prices, temperatures, money/unit conversions ("10.5 cm in inches"), calculations ("3*4+sqrt(6)&lt;del&gt;pi/2"), package tracking, patents, area codes, and language translation of displayed pages.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;The order of search results (ghits for Google hits) on Google's search-results pages is based, in part, on a priority rank called a "PageRank". Google Search provides many options for customized search (see below: Search options), using Boolean operators such as: exclusion ("-xx"), inclusion ("+xx"), alternatives ("xx OR yy"), and wildcard ("x * x").&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;The frequency of use of many search terms have reached a volume that they may indicate broader economic, social and health trends. Data about the frequency of use of search terms on Google (available through Google Adwords, Google Trends, and Google Insights for Search) have been shown to correlated with flu outbreaks and unemployment levels and provide the information faster than traditional reporting methods and government surveys.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In June 2011, Google has introduced "Voice Search " and "Search by Image" features for allowing the users to search words by speaking and by giving images.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Contents &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1 Search engine &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.1 PageRank&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.2 Search results&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.3 Non-indexable data&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;1.4 Google optimization&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2 Functionality &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.1 Search syntax&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.2 Query expansion&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.3 "I'm Feeling Lucky"&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.4 Rich Snippets&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.5 Special features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.6 Search options&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.7 Error messages &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.7.1 January 2009 malware bug&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.8 Doodle for Google&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.9 Google Caffeine&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;2.10 Encrypted Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3 Instant Search &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3.1 Negative reception&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;3.2 Censorship&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;4 Features &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;4.1 June 2011 redesign&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;5 Google +1&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6 Adding the +1 button &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.1 Interface features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.2 Media features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.3 Navigation bar design&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.4 Google logo size reduction&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;6.5 Move of links&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7 International &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7.1 Languages&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;7.2 Domain names&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;8 Search products&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;9 Energy consumption&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt; &lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search engine PageRank&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's rise to success was in large part due to a patented algorithm called PageRank that helps rank web pages that match a given search string. When Google was a Stanford research project, it was nicknamed BackRub because the technology checks backlinks to determine a site's importance. Previous keyword-based methods of ranking search results, used by many search engines that were once more popular than Google, would rank pages by how often the search terms occurred in the page, or how strongly associated the search terms were within each resulting page. The PageRank algorithm instead analyzes human-generated links assuming that web pages linked from many important pages are themselves likely to be important. The algorithm computes a recursive score for pages, based on the weighted sum of the PageRanks of the pages linking to them. PageRank is thought to correlate well with human concepts of importance. In addition to PageRank, Google, over the years, has added many other secret criteria for determining the ranking of pages on result lists, reported to be over 200 different indicators. The specifics of which are kept secret to keep spammers at bay and facilitate Google maintain an edge over its competitors globally.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search results&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The exact percentage of the total of web pages that Google indexes is not known, as it is very difficult to accurately calculate. Google not only indexes and caches web pages, but also takes "snapshots" of other file types, which include PDF, Word documents, Excel spreadsheets, Flash SWF, plain text files, and so on. Except in the case of text and SWF files, the cached version is a conversion to (X)HTML, allowing those without the corresponding viewer application to read the file.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Users can customize the search engine, by setting a default language, using the "SafeSearch" filtering technology and set the number of results shown on each page. Google has been criticized for placing long-term cookies on users' machines to store these preferences, a tactic which also enables them to track a user's search terms and retain the data for more than a year. For any query, up to the first 1000 results can be shown with a maximum of 100 displayed per page. The ability to specify the number of results is available only if "Instant Search" is not enabled. If "Instant Search" is enabled, only 10 results are displayed, regardless of this setting.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Non-indexable data&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Despite its immense index, there is also a considerable amount of data available in online databases which are accessible by means of queries but not by links. This so-called invisible or deep Web is minimally covered by Google and other search engines. The deep Web contains library catalogs, official legislative documents of governments, phone books, and other content which is dynamically prepared to respond to a query.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google optimization&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Since Google is the most popular search engine, many webmasters have become eager to influence their website's Google rankings. An industry of consultants has arisen to help websites increase their rankings on Google and on other search engines. This field, called search engine optimization, attempts to discern patterns in search engine listings, and then develop a methodology for improving rankings to draw more searchers to their client's sites.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search engine optimization encompasses both "on page" factors (like body copy, title elements, H1 heading elements and image alt attribute values) and Off Page Optimization factors (like anchor text and PageRank). The general idea is to affect Google's relevance algorithm by incorporating the keywords being targeted in various places "on page", in particular the title element and the body copy (note: the higher up in the page, presumably the better its keyword prominence and thus the ranking). Too many occurrences of the keyword, however, cause the page to look suspect to Google's spam checking algorithms.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google has published guidelines for website owners who would like to raise their rankings when using legitimate optimization consultants.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;It has been hypothesized, and, allegedly, is the opinion of the owner of one business about which there has been numerous complaints, that negative publicity, for example, numerous consumer complaints, may serve as well to elevate page rank on Google Search as favorable comments. The particular problem addressed in The New York Times article, which involved DecorMyEyes, was addressed shortly thereafter by an undisclosed fix in the Google algorithm. According to Google, it was not the frequently published consumer complaints about DecorMyEyes which resulted in the high ranking but mentions on news websites of events which affected the firm such as legal actions against it. There has also been a Google toolbar for use on many internet browsers.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Functionality &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Image of definition link provided for many search terms.Google search consists of a series of localized websites. The largest of those, the &lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt; site, is the top most-visited website in the world. Some of its features include a definition link for most searches including dictionary words, the number of results you got on your search, links to other searches (e.g. for words that Google believes to be misspelled, it provides a link to the search results using its proposed spelling), and many more.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Search syntax&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's search engine normally accepts queries as a simple text, and breaks up the user's text into a sequence of search terms, which will usually be words that are to occur in the results, but one can also use Boolean operators, such as: quotations marks (") for a phrase, a prefix such as "+", "&lt;/del&gt;" for qualified terms, or one of several advanced operators, such as "site:". The webpages of "Google Search Basics" describe each of these additional queries and options (see below: Search options). Google's Advanced Search web form gives several additional fields which may be used to qualify searches by such criteria as date of first retrieval. All advanced queries transform to regular queries, usually with additional qualified term. 

Query expansion 
Google applies query expansion to the submitted search query, transforming it into the query that will actually be used to retrieve results. As with page ranking, the exact details of the algorithm Google uses are deliberately obscure, but certainly the following transformations are among those that occur: 

Term reordering: in information retrieval this is a standard technique to reduce the work involved in retrieving results. This transformation is invisible to the user, since the results ordering uses the original query order to determine relevance. 
Stemming is used to increase search quality by keeping small syntactic variants of search terms. 
There is a limited facility to fix possible misspellings in queries. 
"I'm Feeling Lucky"Google's homepage includes a button labelled "I'm Feeling Lucky". When a user types in a search and clicks on the button the user will be taken directly to the first search result, bypassing the search engine results page. The thought is that if a user is "feeling lucky", the search engine will return the perfect match the first time without having to page through the search results. However, with the introduction of Google Instant, it is not possible to use the button properly unless the Google Instant function is switched off. According to a study by Tom Chavez of "Rapt", this feature costs Google $110 million a year as 1% of all searches use this feature and bypass all advertising. 

On October 30, 2009, for some users, the "I'm Feeling Lucky" button was removed from Google's main page, along with the regular search button. Both buttons were replaced with a field that reads, "This space intentionally left blank." This text faded out when the mouse was moved on the page, and normal search functionality is achieved by filling in the search field with the desired terms and pressing enter. A Google spokesperson explains, "This is just a test, and a way for us to gauge whether our users will like an even simpler search interface." Personalized Google homepages retained both buttons and their normal functions. 

On May 21, 2010, the 30th anniversary of Pac-Man, the "I'm Feeling Lucky" button was replaced with a button reading the words "Insert Coin". After pressing the button, the user would begin a Google-themed game of Pac-Man in the area where the Google logo would normally be. Pressing the button a second time would begin a two-player version of the same game that includes Ms. Pacman for player 2. This version can be accessed at google.com as a permanent link to the page. 

Rich Snippets 
On 12 May 2009, Google announced that they would be parsing the hCard, hReview, and hProduct microformats and using them to populate search result pages with what they called "Rich Snippets". 

Special features 
Besides the main search-engine feature of searching for text, Google Search has more than 22 "special features" (activated by entering any of dozens of trigger words) when searching: 

weather – The weather conditions, temperature, wind, humidity, and forecast, for many cities, can be viewed by typing "weather" along with a city for larger cities or city and state, U.S. zip code, or city and country for smaller cities (such as: weather Lawrence, Kansas; weather Paris; weather Bremen, Germany). 
stock quotes – The market data for a specific company or fund can be viewed, by typing the ticker symbol (or include "stock"), such as: CSCO; MSFT; IBM stock; F stock (lists Ford Motor Co.); or AIVSX (fund). Results show inter-day changes, or 5-year graph, etc. This does not work for stock names which are one letter long, such as Citigroup (C) or Macy's (M) (Ford being an exception), or are common words, such as Diamond Offshore (DO) or Majesco (COOL). 
time – The current time in many cities (worldwide), can be viewed by typing "time" and the name of the city (such as: time Cairo; time Pratt, KS). 
sports scores – The scores and schedules, for sports teams, can be displayed by typing the team name or league name into the search box. 
unit conversion – Measurements can be converted, by entering each phrase, such as: 10.5 cm in inches; or 90 km in miles 
currency conversion – A money or currency converter can be selected, by typing the names or currency codes (listed by ISO 4217): 6789 Euro in USD; 150 GBP in USD; 5000 Yen in USD; 5000 Yuan in lira (the U.S. dollar can be USD or "US$" or "$", while Canadian is CAD, etc.). 
calculator – Calculation results can be determined, as calculated live, by entering a formula in numbers or words, such as: 6*77 +pi +sqrt(e^3)/888 plus 0.45. The user is given the option to search for the formula, after calculation. The calculator also uses the unit and currency conversion functions to allow unit-aware calculations. For example, "(3 EUR/liter) / (40 miles/gallon) in USD / mile" calculates the dollar cost per mile for a 40 mpg car with gas costing 3 euros a liter. The caret "^" raises a number to an exponent power, and percentages are allowed ("40% of 300"). There is also some debate as to Google's calculation of 0^0. Many mathematicians believe that 0^0 is undefined but Google's calculator shows the result as 1. 
numeric ranges – A set of numbers can be matched by using a double-dot between range numbers (70..73 or 90..100) to match any positive number in the range, inclusive. Negative numbers are treated as using exclusion-dash to not match the number. 
dictionary lookup – A definition for a word or phrase can be found, by entering "define" followed by a colon and the word(s) to lookup (such as, "define:philosophy") 
maps – Some related maps can be displayed, by typing in the name or U.S. ZIP code of a location and the word "map" (such as: New York map; Kansas map; or Paris map). 
movie showtimes – Reviews or film showtimes can be listed for any movies playing nearby, by typing "movies" or the name of any current film into the search box. If a specific location was saved on a previous search, the top search result will display showtimes for nearby theaters for that movie. 
public data – Trends for population (or unemployment rates) can be found for U.S. states &amp; counties, by typing "population" or "unemployment rate" followed by a state or county name. 
real estate and housing – Home listings in a given area can be displayed, using the trigger words "housing", "home", or "real estate" followed by the name of a city or U.S. zip code. 
travel data/airports – The flight status for arriving or departing U.S. flights can be displayed, by typing in the name of the airline and the flight number into the search box (such as: American airlines 18). Delays at a specific airport can also be viewed (by typing the name of the city or three-letter airport code plus word "airport"). 
package tracking – Package mail can be tracked by typing the tracking number of a Royal Mail, UPS, FedEx or USPS package directly into the search box. Results will include quick links to track the status of each shipment. 
patent numbers – U.S. patents can be searched by entering the word "patent" followed by the patent number into the search box (such as: Patent 5123123). 
area code – The geographical location (for any U.S. telephone area code) can be displayed by typing a 3-digit area code (such as: 650). 
synonym search – A search can match words similar to those specified, by placing the tilde sign (~) immediately in front of a search term, such as: ~fast food. 

Search options 
The webpages maintained by the Google Help Center have text describing more than 15 various search options. The Google operators: 

OR – Search for either one, such as "price high OR low" searches for "price" with "high" or "low". 
"-" – Search while excluding a word, such as "apple &lt;del&gt;tree" searches where word "tree" is not used.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;"+" – Force inclusion of a word, such as "Name +of +the Game" to require the words "of" &amp; "the" to appear on a matching page.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;"*" – Wildcard operator to match any words between other specific words.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Some of the query options are as follows:&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;define: – The query prefix "define:" will provide a definition of the words listed after it.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;stocks: – After "stocks:" the query terms are treated as stock ticker symbols for lookup.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;site: – Restrict the results to those websites in the given domain, such as, site:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.acmeacme.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;. The option "site:com" will search all domain URLs named with ".com" (no space after "site:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;allintitle: – Only the page titles are searched (not the remaining text on each webpage).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;intitle: – Prefix to search in a webpage title, such as "intitle:google search" will list pages with word "google" in title, and word "search" anywhere (no space after "intitle:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;allinurl: – Only the page URL address lines are searched (not the text inside each webpage).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;inurl: – Prefix for each word to be found in the URL; others words are matched anywhere, such as "inurl:acme search" matches "acme" in a URL, but matches "search" anywhere (no space after "inurl:").&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The page-display options (or query types) are:&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;cache: – Highlights the search-words within the cached document, such as "cache:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt; xxx" shows cached content with word "xxx" highlighted.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;link: – The prefix "link:" will list webpages that have links to the specified webpage, such as "link:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;" lists webpages linking to the Google homepage.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;related: – The prefix "related:" will list webpages that are "similar" to a specified web page.&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;info: – The prefix "info:" will display some background information about one specified webpage, such as, info:&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;www.google.com&lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;. Typically, the info is the first text (160 bytes, about 23 words) contained in the page, displayed in the style of a results entry (for just the 1 page as matching the search).&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;filetype: – results will only show files of the desired type (ex filetype:pdf will return pdf files)&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Note that Google searches the HTML coding inside a webpage, not the screen appearance: the words displayed on a screen might not be listed in the same order in the HTML coding.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Error messages&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Some searches will give a 403 Forbidden error with the text&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;"We're sorry... ... but your query looks similar to automated requests from a computer virus or spyware application. To protect our users, we can't process your request right now. We'll restore your access as quickly as possible, so try again soon. In the meantime, if you suspect that your computer or network has been infected, you might want to run a virus checker or spyware remover to make sure that your systems are free of viruses and other spurious software. We apologize for the inconvenience, and hope we'll see you again on Google."&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;sometimes followed by a CAPTCHA prompt.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt; &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google's Server Error pageThe screen was first reported in 2005, and was a response to the heavy use of Google by search engine optimization companies to check on ranks of sites they were optimizing. The message is triggered by high volumes of requests from a single IP address. Google apparently uses the Google cookie as part of its determination of refusing service.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In June 2009, after the death of pop superstar Michael Jackson, this message appeared to many internet users who were searching Google for news stories related to the singer, and was assumed by Google to be a DDoS attack, although many queries were submitted by legitimate searchers.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;January 2009 malware bug &lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;A screen-shot of the error of January 31, 2009.Google flags search results with the message "This site may harm your computer" if the site is known to install malicious software in the background or otherwise surreptitiously. Google does this to protect users against visiting sites that could harm their computers. For approximately 40 minutes on January 31, 2009, all search results were mistakenly classified as malware and could therefore not be clicked; instead a warning message was displayed and the user was required to enter the requested URL manually. The bug was caused by human error. The URL of "/" (which expands to all URLs) was mistakenly added to the malware patterns file.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Doodle for Google&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Main article: Google logo&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;On certain occasions, the logo on Google's webpage will change to a special version, known as a "Google Doodle". Clicking on the Doodle links to a string of Google search results about the topic. The first was a reference to the Burning Man Festival in 1998, and others have been produced for the birthdays of notable people like Albert Einstein, historical events like the interlocking Lego block's 50th anniversary and holidays like Valentine's Day.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google Caffeine&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;In August 2009, Google announced the rollout of a new search architecture, codenamed "Caffeine". The new architecture was designed to return results faster and to better deal with rapidly updated information from services including Facebook and Twitter. Google developers noted that most users would notice little immediate change, but invited developers to test the new search in its sandbox. Differences noted for their impact upon search engine optimization included heavier keyword weighting and the importance of the domain's age. The move was interpreted in some quarters as a response to Microsoft's recent release of an upgraded version of its own search service, renamed Bing. Google announced completion of Caffeine on 8 June 2010, claiming 50% fresher results due to continuous updating of its index. With Caffeine, Google moved its back-end indexing system away from MapReduce and onto BigTable, the company's distributed database platform. Caffeine is also based on Colossus, or GFS2, an overhaul of the GFS distributed file system.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Encrypted Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;In May 2010 Google rolled out SSL-encrypted web search. The encrypted search can be accessed at &lt;/del&gt;&lt;del&gt;encrypted.google.com&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Instant Search&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Google Instant, an enhancement that displays suggested results while the user types, was introduced on September 8 2010. One concern is that people will select one of the suggested results instead of finishing their request, and that such a practice could cause bias toward familiar businesses or other search terms. Pornographic or otherwise offensive search terms are excluded from the suggested results. The instant feature appears only on the basic Google site and not specialized iGoogle pages. Google expects Google Instant to save users 2 to 5 seconds in every search, which they say will be collectively 11 million seconds per hour. Search engine marketing pundits speculate that Google Instant will have a great impact on local and paid search.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;In concert with the Google Instant launch, Google disabled the ability of users to choose to see more than 10 search results per page. Instant Search can be disabled via Google's "preferences" menu, but autocomplete-style search suggestions now cannot be disabled. A Google representative stated, "It's in keeping with our vision of a unified Google search experience to make popular, useful features part of the default experience, rather than maintain different versions of Google. As Autocomplete quality has improved, we felt it was appropriate to have it always on for all of our users."&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Negative reception&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;Many users have reported being unable to save the Instant Search "off" setting in their Google preferences.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Censorship&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;The publication 2600: The Hacker Quarterly has compiled a list of words that are restricted by Google Instant. These are terms the web giant's new instant search feature will not search. Most terms are often vulgar and derogatory in nature, but some apparently irrelevant searches including "Myleak" are removed.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Features&lt;/del&gt; 
&lt;del&gt;June 2011 redesignIn late June of 2011, Google introduced a new look to the Google home page in order to boost the use of the Google+ social tools.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Google +1+1 helps people discover relevant content aimed to increase Google search result status offering a status to show people know and trust the content. When a signed-in Google user is searching, Google search result snippet will show an annotation with the names of the user's connections who've +1'd your page.&lt;/del&gt; 

&lt;del&gt;Adding the +1 buttonA small script is added before the closing header tag containing the Google Plus One Java Script and then on the website page position the button is added with &lt;g:plusone&gt;&lt;/g:plusone&gt;. Additional to this there is button sizes which are small (15px), medium (20px), standard (24px) and large (60px). A reference to a website URL can also be for example:&lt;/del&gt; &lt;g:plusone size="medium" href="WEBSITE URL"&gt;&lt;/g:plusone&gt;. 

Interface features 
Simple white background with time-to-time changes in the title, “Google” with a special historic day or to celebrate a certain day. 
Top bar has web, image, videos, maps, news, shopping, Gmail, and more. 
Voice search on Google Chrome like how you can use voice search on your phone. 
When you sign onto your Google account, you have a history of all the searches that you have done with that specific account. (only when your logged in) 
Google Instance, which instantly brings up what you are typing for example, if you are looking for “Google”. As soon as you type G and O the word Google will come up so it saves you time like a short cut. 

Media features 
Share your own picture to the world. You can upload your own picture. 
Image search with optional settings such as size, color, type, and sorting. 
Video search that is connected to YouTube. Also with optional setting such as duration, time, quality, also other sources that is related to the topic that you are searching. 

Navigation bar design 
One of the major changes was replacing the classic navigation bar with a black one. Google's digital creative director Chris Wiggins explains: "We're working on a project to bring you a new and improved Google experience, and over the next few months, you'll continue to see more updates to our look and feel." The new navigation bar has been negatively received by a vocal majority. 

Google logo size reduction 
The new design also has a reduced size logo. 

Move of links 
Links for advertising, business partners and company information pushed to the bottom edges of the browser. 

International 
Google is available in many languages and has been localized completely or partly for many countries. 

Languages 
Afrikaans 
Akan 
Albanian 
Amharic 
Arabic 
Armenian 
Azerbaijani 
Basque 
Belarusian 
Bemba 
Bengali 
Bihari 
Bosnian 
Breton 
Bulgarian 
Cambodian (Khmer) 
Catalan 
Cherokee 
Chichewa 
Chinese (Simplified) 
Chinese (Traditional) 
Corsican 
Croatian 
Czech 
Danish 
Dutch 
English (United Kingdom) 
English (United States) 
Esperanto 
Estonian 
Faroese 
Filipino 
Finnish 
French 
Frisian (West) 
Galician 
Georgian 
German 
Greek 
Guarani 
Gujarati 
Hausa 
Haitian Creole 
Hawaiian 
Hebrew 
Hindi 
Hungarian 
Icelandic 
Igbo 
Indonesian 
Interlingua 
Irish 
Italian 
Japanese 
Javanese 
Kannada 
Kazakh 
Kinyarwanda 
Kirundi 
Korean 
Kurdish 
Kyrgyz 
Laotian 
Latin 
Latvian 
Lingala 
Lithuanian 
Luganda 
Luo 
Macedonian 
Malagasy 
Malay 
Malayalam 
Maltese 
Maori 
Marathi 
Mauritian Creole 
Moldavian (Romanian) 
Mongolian 
Montenegrin 
Nepali 
Norwegian 
Norwegian (Nynorsk) 
Occitan 
Oriya 
Oromo 
Pashto 
Persian 
Polish 
Portuguese (Brazil) 
Portuguese (Portugal) 
Punjabi 
Quechua 
Romanian 
Romansh 
Runyakitara 
Russian 
Scots Gaelic 
Serbian 
Serbo-Croatian 
Sesotho 
Setswana 
Shona 
Sindhi 
Sinhalese 
Slovak 
Slovene 
Somali 
Spanish 
Sundanese 
Swahili 
Swedish 
Tajik 
Tamil 
Tatar 
Telugu 
Thai 
Tigrinya 
Tonga 
Tshiluba 
Turkish 
Turkmen 
Twi 
Uighur 
Ukrainian 
Urdu 
Uzbek 
Vietnamese 
Welsh 
Xhosa 
Yiddish 
Yoruba 
Zulu 

The interface has also been made available in some languages for humorous purpose: 

Bork, bork, bork! 
Elmer Fudd 
Hacker 
Klingon 
Pig Latin 
Pirate 

Domain names 
Main article: List of Google domains 
In addition to the main URL Google.com, Google Inc. owns 160 domain names for each of the countries/regions in which it has been localized. 

Search products 
Main article: List of Google products 
In addition to its tool for searching webpages, Google also provides services for searching images, Usenet newsgroups, news websites, videos, searching by locality, maps, and items for sale online. In 2006, Google has indexed over 25 billion web pages, 400 million queries per day, 1.3 billion images, and over one billion Usenet messages. It also caches much of the content that it indexes. Google operates other tools and services including Google News, Google Suggest, Google Product Search, Google Maps, Google Co-op, Google Earth, Google Docs, Picasa, Panoramio, YouTube, Google Translate, Google Blog Search and Google Desktop Search. 

There are also products available from Google that are not directly search-related. Gmail, for example, is a webmail application, but still includes search features; Google Browser Sync does not offer any search facilities, although it aims to organize your browsing time. 

Also Google starts many new beta products, like Google Social Search or Google Image Swirl. 

Energy consumption 
Google claims that a search query requires altogether about 1 kJ or 0.0003 kW·h.﻿

Meer lezen (737 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-H9ZYpSI-Dp0/TyL7MiflL1I/AAAAAAAAFS4/F81C747tRjA/w426-h237/Google-Music-Player-Logo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/103548154156907458340/albums/5966911291980625057/5966911293118517314</link><title>I got an Idea about how to plan my finances ------ Joyti Kutwad (Self employed) 
It was just an excellant session ----- Aziz Talwari (Software professional) 
Today i came to know difference between what is investment and what is not. ----- Vikas Patole (Self employed consultant) 
Today I came to know why not to prepay the home loan and disadvantage of same ----- Rajendra lande (Software professional) 
key learning for me : How to plan budget and save more ------ Yogesh Acharya (Self employed consultant) 
3 key earnings for me : How to plan personal finance,How to save and invest in proper way &amp; How to set financial goals ------- Namrata Shah (Self employed) 
How to set priorities in financial life and how to plan for it ------ Manisha Mahajan 
(Salaried in Auto) 
Managing my finances keeping in mind my present and future financial situations ------- Sandeep Desai.(Employee) 
Understood better about the savings ------ Usha Gangadhar (Employee) 

Some of the testimonials given to "Design your financial life".﻿

Meer lezen (18 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-i7QYoTC_DOY/Us66NQCYkEI/AAAAAAAABAc/TOrsR5Po4s0/w426-h320/Adv.10.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/112364936061478201829/albums/6008661385291080129/6008661386755084130</link><title>Immigration Update! 

Last April 26, 2014 the Canadian Embassy has released the New TOP 50 CAtegories under Federal Skilled Work Program - Immigrant Visa. 

Follow this link: http://news.gc.ca/web/article-en.do?nid=841339 

Limited to 1000 Applicants for each Category 
Apply Now! 

• Senior managers – financial, communications and other business services 
• Senior managers - trade, broadcasting and other services, n.e.c. 
• Financial managers 
• Human resources managers 
• Purchasing managers 
• Insurance, real estate and financial brokerage managers 
• Managers in health care 
• Construction managers 
• Home building and renovation managers 
• Managers in natural resources production and fishing 
• Manufacturing managers 
• Financial auditors and accountants 
• Financial and investment analysts 
• Securities agents, investment dealers and brokers 
• Other financial officers 
• Professional occupations in advertising, marketing and public relations 
• Supervisors, finance and insurance office workers 
• Property administrators 
• Geoscientists and oceanographers 
• Civil engineers 
• Mechanical engineers 
• Electrical and electronics engineers 
• Petroleum engineers 
• Information systems analysts and consultants 
• Database analysts and data administrators 
• Software engineers and designers (2173) 
• Computer programmers and interactive media developers 
• Mechanical engineering technologists and technicians 
• Construction estimators (2234) 
• Electrical and electronics engineering technologists and technicians 
• Industrial instrument technicians and mechanics 
• Inspectors in public and environmental health and occupational health and safety 
• Computer network technicians 
• Nursing co-ordinators and supervisors 
• Registered nurses and registered psychiatric nurses 
• Specialist physicians 
• General practitioners and family physicians 
• Dietitians and nutritionists 
• Audiologists and speech-language pathologists 
• Physiotherapists 
• Occupational therapists 
• Respiratory therapists, clinical perfusionists and cardiopulmonary technologists 
• Medical radiation technologists 
• Medical sonographers 
• Licensed practical nurses 
• Paramedical occupations 
• University professors and lecturers 
• Psychologists 
• Early childhood educators and assistants 
• Translators, terminologists and interpreters 

For seat reservation you may apply online at: http://pinoycarevisa.com/apply-online/ 
Email us: online@pinoycarevisa.com Call or Text: 09157128610 or 09984253647 
Visit us: www.pinoycarevisa.com﻿

Meer lezen (66 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-gWyxj7y8o28/U2MNsi0kj2I/AAAAAAAAAP4/KuJ166-ww6I/w426-h314/zzzzzz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/103474446216149411814/albums/5882939185200009713/5882939186289290114?authkey=CKG9jNeCmaKlXg&amp;sqi=116055609795749223156&amp;sqsi=837b7761-24a9-4890-a672-4fb537dc256f</link><title>Work from Home. 
Essential information for your concern.. 

Ads like this are everywhere — from the telephone pole on the corner to your newspaper, email and favorite websites. The jobs might be different, but the message is the same — start earning a great living today working from home, even in your spare time. 

When money’s tight, work-at-home opportunities can sound like just the thing to make ends meet. Some even promise a refund if you don’t succeed. But the reality is many of these jobs are scams. The con artists peddling them may get you to pay for starter kits or certifications that are useless, and may even charge your credit card without permission. 

Others just don’t deliver on their promises. The ads don’t tell you that you may have to work a lot of hours without pay, or they don’t disclose all the costs you might incur — say, for placing newspaper ads, making photocopies, or buying the envelopes, paper, stamps and other supplies you need to do the job. People tricked by these ads have lost thousands of dollars, not to mention time and energy. 

Here are some examples of work-at-home schemes to avoid: 
Envelope Stuffing 
For a “small” fee, the ad says, you’ll learn how to earn lots of money stuffing envelopes at home. But once you pay, you find out the promoter never had any work to offer. Instead, after you send in your money, you get a letter telling you to get other people, even your friends and relatives, to buy the same envelope-stuffing “opportunity” or some other product. The only way you can earn any money is if people respond the same way you did. 

Assembly or Craft Work 
According to the ad, you can make money assembling crafts or other products at home. You may have to invest hundreds of dollars for equipment or supplies — for example, a sewing or sign-making machine from the company, or materials to make items like aprons, baby shoes or plastic signs — or spend lots of hours producing goods for a company that has promised to buy them. 

But after you’ve paid money and done the work, the company doesn’t pay you — supposedly because your work isn’t “up to standard.” Unfortunately, no work ever is, and you’re left with equipment and supplies — but without any income to show for it. 

Rebate Processing 
The ad in your email says you can earn money by helping to process rebates. And the fee for training, certification or registration is nothing compared to what you’ll earn processing rebates from home, according to the promises in the ad. It says the #1 certified work-at-home consultant behind the program will show you how to succeed like she did. 

What you get are poorly written and useless training materials. There are no rebates to process, and few people ever see a refund. 

Online Searches 
The ad on the website piques your curiosity — earn $500 to $1000 a week, or even $7,000 a month, running Internet searches on prominent search engines and filling out forms. Even better, you can be your own boss and do the work right from home. What have you got to lose, except a small shipping and handling fee? 

Unfortunately, you have a lot to lose. The company isn’t really connected with a well-known search engine — scammers are just lying to trick you into handing over your credit or debit card information. If you pay them even a tiny fee online, they can use your financial information to charge you recurring fees. 

Medical Billing 
The ads lure you with promises of a substantial income for full- or part-time work processing medical claims electronically — no experience needed. When you call the toll-free number, a sales rep tells you doctors are eager for help, and in exchange for your investment of hundreds — or thousands — of dollars, you’ll get everything you need to launch your own medical billing business, including the software to process the claims, a list of potential clients and technical support. 

But companies rarely provide experienced sales staff or contacts in the medical community. The lists they give you often are out-of-date and include doctors who haven’t asked for billing services. The software they send may not even work. Competition in the medical billing market is fierce, and not many people who purchase these “opportunities” are able to find clients, start a business or generate revenue — let alone get back their investment and earn any income. Many doctors’ offices process their own medical claims, and doctors who contract out their billing function often use large, well-established firms, rather than someone working from home. 

To avoid a medical-billing scam, ask for a sizable list of previous purchasers so you can pick and choose whom to contact for references. If the promoter gives only one or two names, consider that they may be “shills” hired to say good things. Try to interview people in person where the business operates. Talk to organizations for medical claims processors or medical billing businesses and to doctors in your community about the field. Finally, consult an attorney, accountant or other business advisor before you sign an agreement or make any payments up front. 

When it comes to business opportunities, there are no sure bets. Promises of a big income for work from home, especially when the “opportunity” involves an up-front fee or divulging your credit card information, should make you very suspicious. It doesn’t matter if the ad shows up in a trusted newspaper or website — or if the people you talk to on the phone sound legitimate. The situation demands both research and skepticism. 

Ask Questions 
If you’re thinking about following up on a work-at-home offer, do your homework. Here are some questions to ask: 

What tasks will I have to perform? (Ask the program sponsor to list every step of the job.) 
Will I be paid a salary or will I be paid on commission? 
What is the basis for your claims about my likely earnings? Do you survey everyone who purchased the program? What documents can you show me to prove your claims are true before I give you any money? 
Who will pay me? 
When will I get my first paycheck? 
What is the total cost of this work-at-home program, including supplies, equipment and membership fees? What will I get for my money? 
The answers to these questions may help you determine whether a work-at-home program is legitimate, and if so, whether it’s a good fit for you. 

You’ll also want to check out the company with your local consumer protection agency, state Attorney General and the Better Business Bureau, not only where the company is located, but also where you live. These organizations can tell you whether they’ve gotten complaints about a particular work-at-home program. But be wary: just because there aren’t complaints doesn’t mean the company is legitimate. Unscrupulous companies may settle complaints, change their names or move to avoid detection. 

In addition, consider other people’s experience by entering the company or promoter’s name with the word complaints into a search engine. Read what others have to say. After all, you are making a decision that involves spending your money. 

Where to Complain 
If you have spent money and time on a work-at-home program and now believe the program may not be legitimate, contact the company and ask for a refund. Let company representatives know that you plan to notify law enforcement officials about your experience. If you can’t resolve the dispute with the company, file a complaint with these organizations: 

The Federal Trade Commission at ftc.gov/complaint or 1-877-FTC-HELP (1-877-382-4357). 
The Attorney General’s office in your state or the state where the company is located. Visit naag.org; the office will be able to tell you whether you’re protected by any state law that may regulate work-at-home programs. 
Your local consumer protection offices. 
Your local Better Business Bureau at bbb.org. 
Your local postmaster. The U.S. Postal Service investigates fraudulent mail practices. Visit postalinspectors.uspis.gov. 
The advertising manager of the publication that ran the ad. The manager may be interested to learn about the problems you’ve had with the company. 
This article was previously available as Work At Home Schemes.﻿

Meer lezen (161 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Pn1OJ2bijU4/UaRmBVH_q4I/AAAAAAAAAkk/zGVVDxoF67k/w426-h337/Working-from-Home-and-Living-the-Life.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7475-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/software%20consultant%20work%20at%20home/photos/117487668359646793321/albums/5911979952162252241/5911979951467361794?authkey=COuwrcuSq92D5AE</link><title>Mike Stern is a Senior Advisor in Software Engineering here at Flexion. As a Java technology consultant for Flexion, Mike brings experience, patience and a passion for delivery to clients. He also enjoys working with teams of developers who share a passion for software development within an agile based methodology. 
When he isn’t leading agile projects for our clients, Mike enjoys building home theater PC’s (homemade DVR’s). To learn more about our exceptional employees, visit: http://flexion.us/about/item/about-us-our-people/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7475_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-tUYkiDHmy-s/UguScV5xdgI/AAAAAAAAAOY/psyuz7Y2MXk/s426/flexionProfile.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>