<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 19:54:08" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/104967270984482672377/albums/5833381345220663185/5833381350466196210?authkey=COn4vbmKjarjdw</link><title>Dunbar Number, From Guru of #Social Media http://buswk.co/WXi9t7﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-rDUPbEp6_oE/UPRVboHtEvI/AAAAAAAALSc/_6eyRRUAVVo/w426-h237/ext%2B%252825%2529.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/109028905526370179147/albums/5870937940839170833/5870937943717877634?authkey=CMfgmc2snr6WjQE</link><title>Social Dunbar 

Dunbar's number is a suggested cognitive limit to the number of people with whom one can maintain stable social relationships. These are relationships in which an individual knows who each person is, and how each person relates to every other person. Proponents assert that numbers larger than this generally require more restrictive rules, laws, and enforced norms to maintain a stable, cohesive group. It has been proposed to lie between 100 and 230, with a commonly used value of 150. 

Dunbar's number states the number of people one knows and keeps social contact with, and it does not include the number of people known personally with a ceased social relationship, nor people just generally known with a lack of persistent social relationship, a number which might be much higher and likely depends on long-term memory size. 

Look at your social media followers, and understand that most of them are non-entities to you and thus socially expendable. The ones that matter will make it a point to stay in the loop, and the rest you should never have a problem eliminating from that social circle if they go from neutral to negative. Look at your contacts list and understand that unless you're in that proactive and positive social circle, then you are expendable as well. 

Whether Dunbar's number is right or not... there is a limit on how many people you can remember and remain socially close to and stable. So save your sanity (and aggravation) and strive for a quality social media :)﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-NmeKy-FM-a4/UXnC9Emql4I/AAAAAAAAOm4/Lh2LJRQ7ytU/w426-h268/blur-large.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/106687590803153376067/albums/5675007190789363873/5675007194879002914</link><title>Is there a new Dunbar number? 

That number is around 150, the maximum number of people with whom we can retain stable social relationships. 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunbar's_number 

It's a concept I think a lot about on Google+, especially now that I follow around a thousand people. I often see a mini thumbnail in my 8-tile boxes on my profile page, and think, hey, I haven't seen him around in a while! Then I go to their profile and see that they've been busy posting, but I've been missing it. 

So is the number somewhat accurate? Has this, or any other social network changed that number to presumably something higher? 

I know that I don't like missing my friends' posts, that's for sure.﻿

Meer lezen (13 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ZWrkN8uMoBY/TsGs-eyMiSI/AAAAAAAAD5c/ispaYPMUV7Q/w426-h432/n527665805_1968003_6161387.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/115717892107037523817/albums/5748868369266115937/5748868367480886642</link><title>★ how i organise my circles ... ★ 
i finally found the circle management system that achieved just what i wanted, chiefly getting more interaction out of G+ ... 

there are plenty of #guides and #tutorials around, that teach you, how to organise your circles ... most are pretty helpful and i've taken loads of good ideas out of them, but none really fitted my needs ... regognise yourself in this? ... everybody seems to have the perfect circle system, but nobody seems to have the perfect system for you ... i know somebody who does! ... you! ... as with everything here on G+, there is no one-for-all recipe ... i had to figure out myself, what kind of circle management fitted me best ... i've had a few goes at it ... i even wrote a post not so long ago (i won't link to it, since this one outdates the previous one), but i changed my approach the very same day i wrote it ... that was, because through a comment on that post i met +Bud Hoffman and he explained his intercation ladder to me ... i never looked back! ... 

of course i had to adjust his system to my needs and combine it with that part of my existing system that worked ... this is how i did it ... 

☛ how i increased interaction through my new circles management ... 
the post will be divided into sections as follows: 
the normal way is not for me | first steps | interaction ladder | targeted circles ... 

➢ the normal way is not for me ... 
i think by now we've all found out, that the way #google advertises to use circles is not exactly working ... what does google say about how to use #circles ? ... 

"Create circles for every group of people in your life from family to music buddies or alumni. Then you can share relevant content with the right people and find the content you're interested in." [1] ... 

i don't know about you, but, though i was initially really excited about the idea, i hardly ever share anything limited, meaning to a certain group nowadays ... i might use my outgoing circles to notify certain groups of certain articles, but even those are usually public ...at the beginning i thought, that i might us limited posts to send stuff only to my real life friends or my family, but those buggers just won't follow me over from the other large social network so i gave up on it ... here i want to make new friends, with the same interests, so i need to post public, so everybody can see, what my interests are ... 

same with incoming circles ... yes, it was a nice idea to get interesting content by circling the right people ... in theory! ... reality looks rather different though! ... it is true, that my friend john q. public posts about finswimming (my great passion), but only about 20% of the time ... 80% is all kinds of other stuff ... he could post that limited, but he's made the same experience as me ... outgoing circles don't work ... so, just like me, he posts everything public and i have to sift through it ... and through the stuff of the 250 other people i used to have in my V.I.P. circle (the one i check every day) ... it took me hours and i didn't have time anymore to write my own wisdom down or to interact with the posts of others ... i needed to do something ... 

➢ first steps ... 
▸ reducing the incoming stream ... there were far too many people in my V.I.P. circle to follow ... according to dunbar's number one can maintain stable social relationships with between 100 and 230 individuals, with a commonly used value of 150 [2] ... so, i reduced the members of my V.I.P. circle to under 100 (currently 69) and put everybody else in a probation circle ... the slider for the V.I.P. circle i set to show everything while the one for the probation circle i set to show fewer things ... suddenly my stream became manageable ... positive side effect; i now had more time to interact with my stream and to write my own posts (read more at how i found my place G+ ... [3]) ... 

▸ changing who i put in my V.I.P. circle ... since i realised that curating my incoming content via circles didn't work, i decided to use my circles just like i do in real life ... the ones in the V.I.P. circle should be the ones i most care about ... out went all those that i originally circled because they post interesting suff from time to time and in went those, that are important to me ... the ones that i like to follow, not because their content is always witty and intelligent, but because i care about them and i want to know, what is going on in their lifes ... i also kept a few in there who really post about one thing only and always have something interesting for me to say like +Denis Labelle +Rahul Roy or +Shamil Weerakoon ... 

▸ where do i get my content from now? ... #savedsearches ! [4] ... i saved some of the most interesting searches and come back to them, whenever i want to read interesting stuff ... now this is really content orientated, rather than person orientated ... nice side effect; i continuously find more peeps who write about things that interest me ... 

➢ targeted circles ... 
the fact, that i didn't want to read all the ballast in between interesting posts of the people i follow, made it obvious to me, that my followers probably wouldn't want to read my babbling in between the posts that interested them either ... i post about several subjects regularly and i can't expect my peeps to be interested in all of them ... that is when i came up with the targeted circles system ... i've been wanting to do that for ages and a post by +Rahul Roy reminded me of it again ... i thought, if i turn around my #circlemanagement , i might as well do it right ... 

i wrote a post about this already [5], so i won't get too much into it, but in short it works like this ... for every subject i usually post about, i have a circle which i notify, if there is a new post for that subject ... you can request to be added to the circle that interests you ... if you like you can then stick me in a circle you never read and wait for me to notify you of the posts that do interest you ... no ballast, and you can rest assured, that you'll never miss an important post ... read my targeted circles post [5] to find out more about it and, if you'd like to be added to one or more of the circles, +1 the appropriate comment underneath the post ... 

➢ interaction ladder ... 
when i wrote a post about how i organise my circles, i got an interesting comment which directed me to a post about the interaction ladder system by +Bud Hoffman [6] ... the thing i care about here most at #googleplus is interaction ... i just love to interact with you, my followers, and i love it, when you guys interact with me ... follower counts are hollow, empty numbers, but intelligent, interesting interaction is the key to a satisfying experience here at G+ ... i went the first step to improve that with my targeted circles but when i heard of bud's system, i knew that this is the cherry on top ... 

again you can read the post mentioned above [6], if you want the full explanation, but in short it works like this ... every time you interact with me, you get added to a certain circle ... the sliders of those circles are set at different levels, meaning the higher you get on the ladder, the more of your posts will show up in my stream ... these are the circles of my interaction ladder (slider settings in brackets) ... 

▸ interacted with my comment ... if you either +1ed or +mentioned me in a comment on either one of my posts or somebody else's you go in this circle ... (show fewer things) ... 
▸ +1ed my post ... if you +1ed one of my posts you get stuck in here ... (show fewer things) ... 
▸ commented on my post ... if you commented on one of my posts, this is your next station ... (show fewer things) ... 
▸ shared my post ... this is the circle you go if you shared any of my posts ... (show fewer things) ... 
▸ interactors ... if you have completed all of the steps above, you get upgraded to this circle ... (show most things) ... 
▸ regular interactors ... this is the aristocracy of interactors ... here you'll find those of you who perform all (or most of) the steps above on a regular basis ... this circle fluctuates, because people are taking out of it or are added to it all the time ... (show everything) ... 

what i like best about bud's system is that it enables me to reciprocate for the #interaction i receive from you guys ... the more you interact, the more the system let's me see your own posts and gives me the opportunity to interact with them ... i love it! ... 

☛ summary ... 
as you can see, my circle system is targeted on interaction, because that is what is most important to me here at #google \+ ... you might have entirely different priorities, and this system might not be for you at all, but that is up to you to decide ... maybe you can take just some ideas from it and tailor it to your own needs ... i like staying in touch with my mates here via my V.I.P. circle, but apart from that my stream is determined by my interaction ladder ... my targeted circles allow me to keep my followers streams free from ballast and provide everybody with just the posts they like to read ... this is the perfect circle system for me! ... 

thank you ever so much for reading through this rather lengthy post ... i hope you enjoyed it ... please, +1, comment and (most importantly) share! ... sharing to me is the biggest compliment you can pay my posts ... it means that you didn't only like it yourself, but see value in it for your followers too ... after all you might've found your perfect circle system already, but there are certain to be some amongst your followers who haven't and they will miss this, if you don't share ... +Sharing is Caring on G+ ... 

greez, 
+Jens Graikowski ... 

********************************************************************* 
permalink to this post: http://bit.ly/LjPnPf ... 
#jggplus #jgguides #pleasesharethispost #sharingiscaring #jghowi #Plushelp 

☛ resources ... 
[1] google+ help: about circles \- http://bit.ly/M0nGxb ... 
[2] wikipedia: dunbar's number \- http://bit.ly/J41BIZ ... 
[3] how i found my place at G+ \- http://bit.ly/JzcYfP ... 
[4] google+ help: save your google+search \- http://bit.ly/JUnIV8 ... 
[5] targeted circles \- http://bit.ly/JPJxor ... 
[6] bud hoffman's interaction ladder \- http://bit.ly/KhnHKT ... 

******************************************************************** 
if you'd like to be notified about these kinds of posts, please read http://bit.ly/JPJxor ... if, on the other hand you are already receiving these notifications and would rather not anymore, please let me know in a PM (no questions asked) ...﻿

Meer lezen (195 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_04_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-xgIhbLuLi18/T8gVUkgtlXI/AAAAAAAAD1k/zPYcScMIcrY/w426-h273/circles_confused.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/117828903900236363024/albums/5788206087659484945/5788206084869946498</link><title>On Identity, Community, and Systems Management 

&gt; Louie C.K. says "I've been having trouble sleeping at night, as we all should." There are easier things in this world that convincing a white middle class ivy-educated heterosexual male that there might be identity problems he wouldn't understand, but that's the task before me. 

// snip 

&gt; Dunbar suggests that a self-organized network near Dunbar's number will be spending about 40% of its time on social grooming behavior. If the goal of social grooming behavior is to get groomed, you might think there are optimal ways to groom a community, and you might see the time and energy wasted on more passive social grooming techniques as suboptimal. "If we want to brush everyone's hair", you shout, "We should send them through a bank of hair-brushing machines in parallel! We'd be done in 20 minutes instead of four hours! And we wouldn't waste all that time on mindless gossip and chatter!" But this is obviously a mistake. The goal of social grooming is precisely to spend that time gossiping and chattering. If you try to optimize it for just hair-brushing, you miss out on the whole point of the process; although the system now has brushed hair it is yet completely ungroomed, and whatever social benefits accrue from the grooming process will be almost entirely lost. Social grooming takes a lot of time and resources, and as such has allowed gossip and chatter to develop as functional parts of group dynamics; if you get rid of the chatter, you effectively get rid of the group. With the kids on the corner, your attempt to eliminate their colloquial protocols and replace them with your proprietary standards is likewise a way of eliminating the target culture. Remove the linguistic ticks that helps the group self-identify and you eliminate the group, in want alternative methods for self-identification. 

&gt; In other words, by saying that she is "unclear and obscure", you are effectively saying "she is part of a sub-community that I don't identify with and (hence?) I don't think should exist". You are saying that she shouldn't talk like that, even when talking like that is partly what sustains the communities she identifies with. In the racial cases, this is something close to the suggestion that black parents should not give their children distinctively black names. Yes, such names might objectively weaken their opportunities in the surrounding communities, but those aren't the communities that are informing the choice of a name, and they aren't trying to optimize for them. 

&gt; Okay, you might grant the analogy and still think that there are some reasons for eliminating some linguistic communities and promoting others. Hate speech communities are a pretty easy example, perhaps obscure post-structuralist philosophy is another. But before we start putting linguistic communities on the chopping block, what should be our global standards for which communities live or die? You've cited clarity and productivity as constraints, but clarity and productivity by what standards? By whose standards? This kind of top-down engineering has me suspicious, even assuming you can give universal standards for clarity and productivity (you probably can't). Before we shoulder the task of literally deciding which communities live or die, perhaps we should be looking for more natural footholds into the dynamics of language and community. 

More: http://digitalinterface.blogspot.com/2012/09/on-identity-community-and-systems.html 

Attn: +Jon Lawhead +Rebecca Spizzirri +kyle broom ﻿

Meer lezen (62 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-7gZFRP1vmeI/UFPWxFdtfII/AAAAAAAACF0/i6hmpDmAS_0/w426-h320/Butler_Title.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/115717892107037523817/albums/5734501580485144177/5734501587530336514</link><title>★ how i found my place at G+ ... ★ 
and how i get exactly what i want out of the platform ... 

» ϟ#@!!%, it doesn't work ... 
i bet there are many of you out there right now who think that #googleplus is a #ghosttown ... most of the time that is, because you don't seem to get anything (or very little) out of the platform ... you write posts, re-share those of others, find funny pictures on the internet, engage and do all the other things you read in various #guides and how-to-be-successful-on-google+ #tutorials you can find all over the internet and G+ itself ... still, you might as well write a diary that you only read yourself, for all the response you get from the community for your efforts ... you don't understand it and envy those who seem to effortlessly collect tens of thousand of followers and get 100 comments and 200 +1s per post ... you might be at a point where you feel like quitting G+ for good and heading back to the other large social network ... don't give up just as yet! ... 

» you are not alone ... 
i was at the same point you are now ... my +CircleCount stats used to look like this ... 

0 comments per posting 
0 reshares per posting 
1 +1's per posting 
(those numbers are from before february) 

now they look like this ... 

11 comments per posting 
1 reshares per posting 
6 +1's per posting 
(those numbers are from the 18/04/2012) 

i've learned how to get exactly what i want out of G+ and i'm sure that you can do that too ... but please don't expect a tutorial that will guide you through all the steps ... i don't have one ... the articles and posts i have collected under the unique hashtag #jgguides might be of some help, but in the end there is only one way that'll work for you ... your way! ... 

i've been wanting to write this post for a long time and never had the balls to do so ... why now? ... 

» everybody is an expert for what is best for him ... 
i just read a post by +Visnja Zeljeznjak explaining that many people feel they don't have the expertise to write about something and therefore choose not to (http://bit.ly/HRHBQ0) ... even people who are generally considered experts in their field sometimes feel like that, as this article by +Scott Hanselman (former professor, now speaker, consultant and microsoft employee) shows (http://bit.ly/HRHxzP) ... i'm one of those too ... not one of the experts ... one of those who feel inadequate ... 

i'm no #expert for G+, but i am an expert in how to make G+ work for me ... nobody knows that better than i do, because i'm the only one who knows exactly what i want to get out of the network ... i won't tell you, what you have to do to make G+ work for you, but maybe you will benefit from me telling my story and that is why i decided to write this post now ... 

» this is my story ... 
the post will be divided into sections as follows: 
how it all started | i needed a break | what i was doing then | what i'm doing now ... 

— how it all started ... 
obviously, when i first came to G+ i didn't know at all what to expect ... it was invite-only then and i got my invitation from an old friend of mine by the name of +Lars Mueller with whom i stay in contact via facebook ... he couldn't tell me anything about the then brand-new platform either, because he is a busy man and hadn't had the time yet to get into it ... i was then becoming increasingly annoyed with facebook and decided to give G+ a try ... 

i read everything i could find about how to start and wasn't afraid to ask for help either ... i quickly got the hang of #hangouts (no pun intended) and found incredibly helpful people there ... i gained more followers in the first 2-3 months on G+, than i collected on facebook in two years! ... i was quite happy for some time, but then i fell into the ghost town hole ... 

— i needed a break ... 
for all i posted on G+, the response was rather poor ... nobody seemed to be interested in what i was writing ... it seemed to me, like i was the only one who was reading my posts ... i fell into a G+ crisis ... my fall was made all the more terrible by the fact that i had been so enthusiastic about the platform before ... i had to do something or i'd quit G+ for good ... 

i took a leave of absence ... i wanted to find out first, if i'd miss it and i really needed to reorder my thoughts, rethink my approach ... i was obviously doing something wrong ... the posts of others were read and interacted with here, so there was no reason, why mine shouldn't be ... i'm not one of those who start whining huuaah ... G+ is a ghost town because i don't get interaction ... if others are successful it means that i am doing something wrong! ... even if of the more than 100.000.000 G+ members there'd be only one person who got response to his posts, that would be enough for me ... that would mean, that the other 99.999.999 (incl. me) were doing it wrong ... 

— what i was doing then ... 
so, first i analysed, what i was currently doing ... 

▶ posting: i realised, that i was all over the place with my posts ... you see, i tried to please as many people as possible with my ramblings ... i wanted (no, i needed) to be accepted by the #community ... i spend hours on the internet, searching for articles, that i thought might interest the people here ... i posted 4-5 (or even more) times a day, every posts about another subject and usually all together ... i took the advise of some successful peeps here and always added my own take on the story, but that didn't seem to make any difference either ... so, i read through my own stream and tried to figure out, what it would look like to somebody else and if that person would find it worth reading ... 

and it wasn't! ... i put myself in somebody else's shoes and realised, that because of me writing about so many subjects, there was too much noise ... sure, if somebody was interested in G+ related subjects, he'd get at least one post a day on that from me, but he'd also get at least 3-4 posts that wouldn't interest him ... also most subjects i wrote about were not what i was interested in or knowledgeable about ... they were what i thought the community would be interested in ... i added my own opinions to the article, but they were not usually based on any expertise ... 

i realised that i added a lot of needless noise to the streams of my followers, further "improved" by my senseless babbling ... i'm surprised some stuck with me as long as the did! ... 

▶ interaction: all this posting had a negative side effect too ... i didn't have time anymore to read through my own stream, which meant i rarely interacted with the posts of others and my own enjoyment of G+ was greatly diminished ... 

▶ circling: i had a V.I.P. circle (the one i read daily) of more than 250 peeps ... who is supposed to follow that many? ... dunbar's number suggests that it's viable to maintain between 100 and 230 stable social relationships, with a commonly used value of 150 [sourse: wikipedia http://bit.ly/J41BIZ] ... i also had other subject based circles i would've liked to follow,but there was no time for that ... i could hardly keep up with my important one ... 

— what i'm doing now ... 
i did a 180° turn ... 

▶ circling: first i did some spring cleaning in my circles ... i sacked quite a few people completely (and lost some good ones accidentally), but the most important step was, to reduce my V.I.P. circle ... i now maintain it constantly under 100 ... with the sliders of some other circles set to minimum i still get the posts of about 150 peeps in my daily stream ... 

second i decided to care less about my "success" and more about what i wanted to get out of the network ... i decided to make G+ more enjoyable for me rather than try and make it enjoyable for my followers ... as bill cosby said ... 

i don't know the recipe for success, but the recipe for failure is trying to please everybody ... 

▶ posting: so, i reduced the number of my daily posts by at least half ... i decided to write about what i am interested in and only that ... i still write some posts about G+ (because i still love it), but generally i leave that to much more knowledgeable peeps like +Denis Labelle +Rahul Roy +Shamil Weerakoon and others ... i now write mainly about #formula1 , a subject that is a passion of mine, but which i completely neglected before ... i like cooking, sci-fi and fantasy movies and book, gadgets and future technology so i add the occasional posts about those subjects too, but all in small measures ... my followers now find far less noise in my stream ... they now know, what to expect from me ... also, because i'm now writing what interests me most and what i'm reasonably knowledgeable about, i increasingly enjoy joining in discussions about my posts and i can make informed comments ... 

▶ interaction: because of my reduced posting i suddenly found myself with some spare time on my hands ... i'm using that now to read through my own stream ... due to the fact, that the size of that is reduced significantly too, i can spend more attention on each post and i have time to write some comments and even get into lengthier discussions if i feel so inclined ... the effect was, that i began to enjoy G+ much more again and with that interaction i suddenly seemed to catch the attention of my peers and people started to interact more with me too ... i noticed a surge in my follower count too ... i found myself in some well curated shared circles and collected followers who are really interested in what i have to say and interact with me ... 

» summary ... 
i found my place at G+ ... sometimes less is more ... less posting, less following, that was the recipe for me ... quality over quantity ... i'm now having interesting discussions about what i post with my fellow plussers ... one of my posts reached more than 100 comments the other day and all of them meaningful and inspiring ... even if you just go by stats and numbers people interact far more with me now ... regarding my followers i now attract more people who are interested in what i have to say ... less in total maybe, granted, but more relevant ones ... 

as you can see, just like bill cosby i don't have the recipe for success either, but what i do now works for me ... you will have to find your own way, but maybe this post helped you a bit ... thank you for reading it! ... please fell free to let me know your take on it and of course share it on! ... my ramblings might be of benefit for some of your followers, who would otherwise miss it ... 

greez, 
+Jens Graikowski ... 

**************************************** 
permalink to this post: http://bit.ly/JzcYfP ... 
#jggplus #jgguides   #jghowi  #Plushelp 

if you'd like to be notified about these kinds of posts, please read http://bit.ly/JPJxor ... if, on the other hand you are already receiving these notifications and would rather not anymore, please let me know in a PM (no questions asked) ...﻿

Meer lezen (217 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_06_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Kk9lPwOuWK0/T5UKz6ioyQI/AAAAAAAADCM/DmTk2DtNUbM/w426-h397/interaction.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/109544171595380130352/albums/5976719811595395073/5976719810958017202</link><title>[Facebook: 10 years to redefine 10 words] 

Facebook is 10. Every publisher on the internet is covering it because it’s important to all of us, even those that have drifted away from the platform recognise its astounding reach. 

At 1.2bn users (more than the global population of 1850) its audience dwarfs that of other social networks and its recent financial results bear that out with $2.59bn in revenue. 

I wanted to look quickly at Facebook’s history but from a different angle than other blogs. Wordwise, I’m struck by how social media has enabled a seemingly constant and varied arpeggio of coinage. 

The word of the year and new additions to the OED are spread faster than they ever were, via networks like Facebook and Twitter. 

So, I’m looking at 10 words that have been redefined by Twitter over 10 years. And to add some relevant content, I’ll include some trivia, too. 

Like 
Verb and noun, both are words now shadowed by Facebook. The most liked retailers on Facebook to date are Starbucks and Walmart with 36m and 34m Likes/fans respectively. Walmart uses the Like facility to sign up customers for rollback alerts on various products. 

The Like and Share buttons are viewed over 22bn times daily across more than 7.5m websites. 

Profile 

Above is a Facebook profile in 2005. By the way, Facebook guy in the top left is actually Al Pacino. 

Though we’re familiar with profiles on many social networks now, Facebook was the pioneer. 

Ok, there was MySpace, but generally you’d ask someone to check out your MySpace page, not your ‘profile’. 

News 
As in News Feed. As Facebook and later Twitter started to change how people found out about news items on the web, so did the definition of ‘news’ change. 

News was suddenly what our friends were up to and what they were sharing. 

Facebook coined the term ‘News Feed’ in 2006 but it was continually tinkered with. In 2011 options were added to allow filtering of who would appear in it, everyone or just recent interactions. 

This year the feed was changed again, making organic reach harder to gain for brands. 

Privacy 
Ok, the web as a whole has redefined privacy , but Facebook has played a big part. 

First there were many backlashes against Facebook when users felt the network was less than clear about who it would share photos with. New privacy settings in 2010 helped to clear this up, but the confusion is evident when you look at the editorial coverage at the time. 

More recently, Facebook was one of the internet giants affected by Edward Snowden’s NSA revelations. Only yesterday, it released data about National Security requests over the past year. 

Facebook 
Facebook itself is obviously now a proper noun, but also a verb, to describing browsing the site (that’s fallen out of usage a little over the past few years) or more often connecting with someone (“I’ll Facebook you!”). 

Heck, the word Facebook has been the most searched for on search engines for the past three years. 

Follow 
Or following. It’s no longer sinister to literally and not figuratively follow your friends (in the Facebook sense). 

Paper 
Will this be the next word we think we knew? Check out Matt Owen’s post on the new Facebook publishing app called Paper, which will change how we access new content. 

Post 
Post is now more of an online, non-physical verb and noun than anything in the ‘real’ world. It’s not specific to Facebook, indeed the network likes ‘update’ but ‘post’ is also in common use. 

More than 250bn photos have been posted on Facebook, with over 350m now posted daily. 

Friend 
Around 150bn friend connections have been made on Facebook. In the real world, the average number of social connections one person can handle is known as the Dunbar’s Number and is about 150. 

This means, and I’m aware this maths isn’t exactly sound, friend connections in the real world could number 7bn multiplied by 150 (and then halved, as the connection is two way), which amounts to 525bn. 

It’s fairly astounding to think that Facebook friend connections could be 30% the number of real-life connections after only 10 years of the platform.﻿

Meer lezen (106 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_07_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-5_jp4fTlHvM/UvGTAIYxQrI/AAAAAAAAA3Q/Fz7A7VL0VHA/w426-h237/facebook_edgerank2.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/115717892107037523817/albums/5819368016686334209/5819368020257703202?authkey=CK7bqe6JndXASQ</link><title>★ How I found my place at G+ ... ★ 
And how I get exactly what I want out of the platform (Updated Version). 

☛ ϟ#@!!%, it doesn't work ... 
I bet there are many of you out there right now who think that #GooglePlus is a #GhostTown . Most of you will be under that impression, because you don't seem to get anything (or very little) out of the platform. You write posts, re-share those of others, find funny pictures on the internet, engage and do all the other things you read in various #Guides and how-to-be-successful-on-google+-in-10-steps tutorials you can find all over the internet and G+ itself. Still, you might as well write a diary that you only read yourself, for all the response you get from the community for your efforts. You don't understand it and envy those who seem to effortlessly collect tens of thousand of followers and get 100 comments and 200 +1s per post. You might be at a point where you feel like quitting G+ for good and heading back to the other large social network. Don't give up just yet! 

☛ You are not alone ... 
Been there, seen it, got a t-shirt. My +CircleCount stats used to look like this: 

0 Comments per posting 
0 Reshares per posting 
1 +1's per posting 
(Those numbers are from before February 2012) 

Now they look like this: 

10 Comments per posting 
11 Reshares per posting 
37 +1's per posting 
(Those numbers are from the 5th of December 2012) 

I've learned how to get exactly what I want out of G+ and if I can do it, so can you. But please don't expect a tutorial that will guide you through all the steps. I don't have one. You might find some helpful tips in this post of mine (http://bit.ly/Z0Bqys), but in the end there is only one way that'll work for you. Your way! 

I wrote the first version of this post in July and it took me a considerable effort to do so. I'm not much of a writer and I'm most certainly no expert on G+, but a good friend encouraged me to put this to paper (erm, screen) anyway. This was the first of my "How I ..." posts which became quite popular later on in the year. I fact they became my most popular posts and I rewrote them all from back to front and put them in a more updated format. This is the last one to go through that treatment. 

☛ Everybody is an expert for what is best for him ... 
I read a post by +Visnja Zeljeznjak explaining that many people feel they don't have the expertise to write about something and therefore choose not to (http://bit.ly/HRHBQ0). I'm one of those. Even people who are generally considered experts in their field sometimes feel like that, as this article by +Scott Hanselman (former professor, now speaker, consultant and Microsoft employee) shows (http://bit.ly/HRHxzP). I'm one of those too. Not one of the experts. One of those who feel inadequate. 

I'm no #Expert for G+, but I am an expert in how to make G+ work for me. Nobody knows that better than me, because I'm the only one who knows exactly what I want to get out of the network. I won't tell you, what you have to do to make G+ work for you, but maybe you will benefit from me telling my story and that is why I decided to write this post. 

☛ This is my story ... 
The post will be divided into sections as follows: 
How it all started | I needed a break | What I was doing then | What I'm doing now 

➢ How it all started ... 
Obviously, when I first came to G+ I didn't know at all what to expect. It was invite-only then and I got my invitation from an old friend of mine by the name of +Lars Mueller with whom I stay in contact via Facebook. He couldn't tell me anything about the then brand-new platform either, because he is a busy man and hadn't had the time yet to get into it. I was then becoming increasingly annoyed with Facebook and decided to give G+ a try. 

I read everything I could find about how to start and wasn't afraid to ask for help either. I quickly got the hang of #Hangouts (no pun intended) and found incredibly helpful people there. I gained more followers in the first 2-3 months on G+, than I collected on Facebook in two years! I was quite happy for some time, but then I fell into the #GhostTown  hole. 

➢ I needed a break ... 
For all I posted on G+, the response was rather poor. Nobody seemed to be interested in what I was writing. It seemed to me, like I was the only one who was reading my posts. I fell into a G+ crisis. My fall was made all the more terrible by the fact that I had been so enthusiastic about the platform before. I had to do something or I'd quit G+ for good. 

I took a leave of absence. I wanted to find out first, if I'd miss it and I really needed to reorder my thoughts, rethink my approach. I was obviously doing something wrong. The posts of others were read and interacted with here, so there was no reason, why mine shouldn't be. I'm not one of those who start whining huuaah ... G+ is a ghost town because I don't get interaction. If others are successful it means that I am doing something wrong! Even if of the more than 500.000.000 G+ members there'd be only one person who got response to his posts, that would be enough for me. That would mean, that the other 499.999.999 (incl. me) were doing it wrong. 

➢ What I was doing then ... 
So, first I analysed, what I was currently doing. 

▸ Posting: I realised, that I was all over the place with my posts. You see, I tried to please as many people as possible with my ramblings. I wanted (no, I needed) to be accepted by the #Community . I spent hours on the internet, searching for articles that I thought might interest the people here. I posted 4-5 (or even more) times a day, every posts about another subject and usually all together. I took the advise of some successful peeps here and always added my own take on the story, but that didn't seem to make any difference either. So, I read through my own stream and tried to figure out, what it would look like to somebody else and if that person would find it worth reading. 

And it wasn't! I put myself in somebody else's shoes and realised, that because of me writing about so many subjects, there was too much noise. Sure, if somebody was interested in G+ related subjects, he'd get at least one post a day on that from me, but he'd also get at least 3-4 posts that wouldn't interest him. Also most subjects I wrote about were not what I was interested in or knowledgeable about. They were what I thought the community would be interested in. I added my own opinions to the article, but they were not usually based on any expertise. 

I realised that I added a lot of needless noise to the streams of my followers, further "improved" by my senseless babbling. I'm surprised some stuck with me as long as they did! 

▸ Interaction: All this posting had a negative side effect too. I didn't have time any more to read through my own stream, which meant I rarely interacted with the posts of others and my own enjoyment of G+ was greatly diminished. 

▸ Circling: I had a V.I.P. circle (the one I read daily) of more than 250 peeps. Who is supposed to follow that many? Dunbar's number suggests that it's viable to maintain between 100 and 230 stable social relationships, with a commonly used value of 150 [Source: Wikipedia - http://bit.ly/J41BIZ]. I also had other subject based circles I would've liked to follow,but there was no time for that. I could hardly keep up with my important one. 

➢ What I'm doing now ... 
I did a 180° turn. 

▸ Circling: First i did some spring cleaning in my circles. I sacked quite a few people completely (and lost some good ones accidentally), but the most important step was, to reduce my V.I.P. circle. I now maintain it constantly under 100. I realised that the way #Google  advertises circle doesn't suit me. They are useless for incoming traffic, because very few people post about one subject only. If I continued to follow people for their content I'd have too much ballast in my stream. So I changed my incoming stream to my #InteractionLadder (http://bit.ly/VfSrjs). I know get almost all my incoming traffic via Saved Searches, which has the positive side effect, that I meet new people with my interests all the time. 

I also noticed, that circles didn't serve me for outgoing traffic, since I mostly posted to Public anyway. So I changed my outgoing circle management to my #TargetedCircles system (http://bit.ly/XSXBoR). 

Second, I decided to care less about my "success" and more about what I wanted to get out of the network. I decided to make G+ more enjoyable for me rather than try and make it enjoyable for my followers. As Bill Cosby said: 

I don't know the recipe for success, but the recipe for failure is trying to please everybody. 

▸ Posting: So, I reduced the number of my daily posts by at least half. I decided to write about what I am interested in and only that. I still write a lot about G+ (because I still love it), but I add the occasional post about the Formula 1, cooking, Sci-Fi and Fantasy movies and books. I also like to re-share posts about good causes. There can never be too much of that. My followers now find far less noise in my stream. They now know, what to expect from me. Also, because I'm now writing what interests me most and what I'm reasonably knowledgeable about, I increasingly enjoy joining in discussions about my posts and I can make informed comments. 

▸ Interaction: Because of my reduced posting I suddenly found myself with some spare time on my hands. I'm using that now to read through my own stream. Due to the fact, that the size of that is reduced significantly too, I can spend more attention on each post and I have time to write some comments and even get into lengthier discussions if I feel so inclined. The effect was, that I began to enjoy G+ much more again and with that interaction I suddenly seemed to catch the attention of my peers and people started to interact more with me too. I noticed a surge in my follower count too. I found myself in some well curated #SharedCircles and collected followers who are really interested in what I have to say and interact with me. 

☛ Summary ... 
I found my place at G+. Sometimes less is more. Less posting, less following, that was the recipe for me. Quality over quantity. I'm now having interesting discussions about what I post with my fellow plussers. Some of my posts reach more than 100 comments and all of them meaningful and inspiring. Even if you just go by stats and numbers people interact far more with me now. Regarding my followers I now attract more people who are interested in what I have to say. Less in total maybe, granted, but more relevant ones. 

As you can see, just like Bill Cosby I don't have the recipe for success either, but what I do now works for me. You will have to find your own way, but maybe this post helped you a bit. Thank you for reading it! Please fell free to let me know your take on it in a comment and of course share it on! My ramblings might be of benefit for some of your followers, who would otherwise miss it. 

Greez, 
+Jens Graikowski 

**************************************** 
Permalink to this post: http://bit.ly/SMrQgu 
#jggplus #jgguides #gplustips #googleplustips #tutorial #guide #tipsandtricks #tipsfornewbies #pleasesharethispost #sharingiscaring #sharethis +Reshare 

The following of my "Targeted Circles" have been notified of this post: 

▸ Google 
▸ Cream of the Crop 
▸ How I ... 
▸ Find your G+spot 

If you'd like to be notified about these kind of posts too, please let me know in a comment! Also read http://bit.ly/XSXBoR . If, on the other hand, you are already receiving these notifications and would rather not any more, please let me know in a PM (no questions asked). ﻿

Meer lezen (239 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_08_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-WQBogu7fKrs/UMKMYdC6hSI/AAAAAAAAJCk/lEhDv-Q_tzQ/w426-h397/interaction.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/106702324621449002266/albums/5775177452943363425/5775177452729413362</link><title>Serious Question: Here's a Diagram 

Dunbar's # is a complicated social concept, where the humane brain can't really handle more than a hundred "network" connections at the same time. 

This has a large impact on social networking... where if you flip reddit, you get to tidder and that means to use with tenderness and care... more what you would do with a small tribe than with any anonymous person on the net. 

How do you think the Internet will resolve this dilemma in the future?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-odWehEYufL0/UCWNS4jILvI/AAAAAAAASFw/lI6B66JtTyo/w426-h266/Does_Twitter_have_a_dunbar.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7479-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/dunbar%20number%20social%20networks/photos/101010252943098026073/albums/5974283667945687489/5974283672539565186</link><title>Intangibles, part 8: Trust   http://goo.gl/1HL38r 

"Conversations slightly outside our shared interest graphs scaffolds serendipity." 
\-- John Kellden 

Trust, transactions and win-win-win 
"...the product of each successful transaction in trust platforms is the exponential increase in trust. This in turn increases the utility for all." 
\-- +Robert Paterson 

Conversation below from   http://goo.gl/ztxjmh 

+David Amerland : 
Thanks for the share John Kellden this is a great find. Robert Paterson says the Highland Park contract is broken and he is right. It has been broken for some time. Social media's ability to create transparency only makes this more obvious which then begs the question, what are you prepared to do about it? 

The self-organising network of largely self-sufficient (in terms of how they get work and then make purchases) individuals does indeed lead to a new model of the network. To quantify a little of what Robert has said, the network organises itself along a community model with gatekeepers (influencers) and connectors. Connectors may not necessarily be gatekeepers, gatekeepers could be connectors. Essentially for anything to spread through a network you require three things: 

A. Relatively low network density (online you could argue we may never get high network density) 

B. Gatekeepers who can be approached 

C. Connectors who can then take the 'message' from one cluster of the network to another or one network to another. 

Trust and Authority (not always synonymous) are important not least because Google algorithmically calculates them for every person in G+ and every website outside it. As units of measurement they are here to stay. ﻿ 

+Robert Paterson : 
Thank you all - The person who could do the measurement would be 
+Valdis Krebs   http://goo.gl/wNZ8Jd 

+John Kellden : 
Great addition Robert - Valdis Krebs is also insightful about influence, cf cc +John Tropea  http://goo.gl/NFxJ6A 

+John Kellden : 

"The cycle of serendipity (or not) came to me while having coffee yesterday with Valdis Krebs: “what you know depends a lot on who you know which depends a lot on what you know which depends a lot on who you know” …iteratively.  If you stay within those confines, your network remains fairly constant and self-selected.  Your chances of learning something new, of encountering ‘happy accidents’ is reduced, perhaps not zero, but not high.  It’s when you venture outside of that circle that your network, and knowledge, starts to expand – you ‘know’ more people so you ‘learn’ more which leads to knowing more people and on and on." 
\-- +Deborah Mills-Scofield    http://goo.gl/1aBpwr 

+John Kellden : 
Social Capital coevolves with Networks of Trust. Valdis Krebs on Social Capital:  http://goo.gl/R4goWF 
via +Dave Gray 

+John Kellden : 
Not wanting to go too much into complex reasoning and synthesis, but to me it seems like the emergent vector out of the twin spiral of social capital and networks of trust, could be thrivability. 

Catalyzing Creativity:      http://goo.gl/K1z1kw 
\-- +jean russell 

+David Amerland : 
+John Kellden I have a question. How is Thrivability different to sustainability?﻿ 

+John Kellden : 
As +jean russell puts it  "The language of sustainability is about neutralizing. Thrivability is about succeeding." 
There's more here, a great conversation between +Jon Lebkowsky  and +jean russell :    http://goo.gl/BvE9tI 

I would probably agree with most of what Jean says - one thing is important, when it comes to Networks of Trust, Social Capital, P2P-processes and Appreciative Inquiry: a difference in Approach and Aspiration. 
I would add there are differences in Intention and Strategic Outcome how to measure Impact as well. (I'm sometimes accused of pursuing a larger solution space, guilty as charged)   :) 

+John Kellden : 
If I would riff on Jean's building and design analogy: Sustainability is a house, housing our future society. Thrivability is enabling everyone to feel at home in our future society.﻿ 

+David Amerland : 
+John Kellden It is semantics at my level of approach but having read Jean's response I see that there is a point to differentiating them. Language provides its own traps, 'sustainable' defined too strictly also becomes limiting in ways that 'thriving' does not. Thank you! This was truly helpful. ﻿ 

+John Kellden : 
While I'm properly caffeinated, allow me to connect the dots over from thrivability to intangibles, metrics and future earning capability. 

In short, one proxy metric I would suggest to a client, to check the progress in a Social Business Design programme - would be retention of employees - from a house to a home, so to speak. 

Obviously, in actual practice, I would suggest betwen three and seven key proxy metrics, both to keep track on progress, as well as for building capability, ie enabling people to own the Social Business design themselves as much as possible. 

+Dave Gray : 
This is really excellent. Thanks for sharing.﻿ 

+Andrew Carpenter : 
Our cultural and economic over-emphasis on Globalization and large Corporations strikes me as similar to a network with a shortage of switches or IP addresses or maybe a better allegory would be that the bottleneck is the DNS. A person can only remember so many things and track so many people. About 150 people usually.﻿ 

+David Amerland : 
+Andrew Carpenter The ubiquitous Dunbar Number.﻿ 

+Andrew Carpenter : 
+David Amerland So what should it mean to us that we try to interact with more people than is optimal for us to efficiently process in day to day life? How can we maintain our global knowledge net and supply web but better make use of our interactions and conversations by respecting ourselves (dignity) enough to realize what we can handle? 

Any answers?﻿ 

+David Amerland : 
+Andrew Carpenter That’s an interesting question and one which directly addresses the signal-over-noise issue. Information Overload is a term frequently used when the accumulated inflow of information, unfiltered, begins to descend into meaninglessness because we can no longer discern what is important. Social networks allow us to follow 100,000 people if we want, but it is up to us to create the system in our behaviour which will filter that mass of people into subsets which are important to us at a particular time and capable of providing the meaning we need in the information we receive. Ultimately, the universe, is subject to our intelligence and that is subject to the rules we create to filter out the unimportant stuff. We have to become the filter which delivers improved signal over noise.  ﻿ 

+Andrew Carpenter : 
+David Amerland We're collectively being groomed as Neurons! It seems this way. I'm not sure we're well adapted for this role either. As addictive and cool as it may be to be on the edge of the things going on online all the time, I think we would be much better off if we "cascaded" ourselves a bit. (A succession of stages, operations, processes or units) 

It's well documented that we are not good at multitasking. Information overload may be a personal concern of mine that I am trying to address but I think that a lot of people are lately...even if they don't realize it. To try to set this into a framework, it's as if more people and channels are doing and saying the same things, and then people who could be doing beneficial things are actually tied up with extra "bandwidth." 

I think I'm experiencing the information and time versions of gluttony.﻿ 

+Andrew Carpenter : 
+David Amerland Talk about sustainable! s/﻿ 

+David Amerland : 
+Andrew Carpenter That's a good point you are making and it goes back to the discipline we can put into place. This is all new to us. For the first time we have access to so much information ta once. So the question has to be how do we filter it? How do we get to see what's important and what is not? This is not a new problem. Business decisions at corporate level are frequently made based upon intel where the picture is fluid. The best decisions I saw was when we decided what the underlying principles were and ignored the granularity coming in as noise. Then acted upon the 'larger picture'. Can we have such a framework at a personal level, you will ask. 

When I do not allow the web to act as a welcome distraction I use it very selectively. This works far from perfectly for me because I love the distraction it offers so at times it gets overwhelming. But when that happens I simply unplug. In the absence of incoming data what I know soon coalesces and things clear up. We will each have to develop our own survival tactics here. ﻿ 

Intangibles 
http://goo.gl/izckOZ 

Trust 
http://goo.gl/AwI6up 

Serendipity 
http://goo.gl/uD6Pvo 

Image source: 
11C : Eleven Conversations to Thrive in the Social Era 
http://www.slideshare.net/johnkellden﻿

Meer lezen (210 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7479_10_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-u5HTHNiUa_8/UujrWNkjDII/AAAAAAAAlVk/9snLw9Ym4D8/w426-h296/11c11play.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>