<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:54:28" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/115954123405219204605/albums/5791417730282949985/5791417733303519282</link><title>iPhone beats Galaxy SIII hands down in benchmarks ...noooot. 

It is funny how even The Inquirer [1], who is supposed to bring the worms out of the woodwork could fall for the same oversight as majority of other sites. 

What is true, is that that statement is correct for our poor American friends on various limiting contracts that have no choice but to run the cut-down dual-core version of SGS3. But for the rest of people, according to  ExtremeTech [2], the full quad-core version of SGS3, sits twice as high above iPhone5 as iPhone5 is above SGS3 dual-core version. 

Sounds complicated? It isn't. Here's a short table of approximate numbers from Geekbench tests: 

Galaxy S3 dual core: 1500 
iPhone5: 1600 
Galaxy S3 quad core: 1800 

(Disclaimer, I don't have either of the phones to test, I'm just referring to benchmark numbers from other sites) 

[1] http://www.theinquirer.net/inquirer/news/2206074/the-iphone-5-outperforms-samsungs-galaxy-s3-in-early-benchmark-tests 
[2] http://www.extremetech.com/computing/136291-iphone-5-benchmarks-slower-than-the-galaxy-s3-faster-than-the-nexus-7﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-sYaITb9WJjA/UF8_voN0SDI/AAAAAAAAGFg/j5CrL6vEkEc/w426-h240/iphone-5-lightning-connector-348x196.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/114059352295806120844/albums/5961326863569154705/5961326861638599186?sqi=100081426839230805681&amp;sqsi=98ba948a-1d8c-4d86-b979-bf7039227dfb</link><title>New nexus 7 for Christmas today woot 🙌🙌🙌🙌 merry Christmas everyone!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-EaewQIvso3w/UrrjMjn2ghI/AAAAAAAAFlk/wHem0ozj0BI/w426-h568/IMG_20131225_085041.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/108259120213046614156/albums/5788240289494557873/5788240290222948322</link><title>Is it just me or does this Play Store desktop page seem rather.... sexy? 

Whoa wait, why is the XOOM there instead of the Nexus 7?! Ah no worries I have both. 

Keep calm and carry on ;D﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_03_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SkvOt1mGoEo/UFP14GVXv-I/AAAAAAAAQ4M/aPTdv_CD4L4/w426-h240/1234.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/106631699076927387965/albums/5731269339329156641/5731269339128140642</link><title>Worms for Android. Not sure how I missed this. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_04_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-IO23t5HU-B0/T4mPGS7SE2I/AAAAAAAASPc/AXAfszNaWxs/w426-h266/12%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/102112891185134866168/albums/5937641602199175441/5937641608196729986</link><title>Got the new 7" Kindle Fire HDX from Amazon. Almost as thin and light as the iPad Mini, with better screen resolution, faster processor and more RAM. Also, have to give Amazon extra points for fast delivery. 

Unfortunately, their operating system, dubbed "Mojito" - a heavily reworked version of Android makes it a total no-go. 

In short: the HDX got returned to Amazon after 24 hours. 

Still using my two-year-old 1st generation Fire. Far from perfect, but mostly usable. Will look at the Nexus, which also has had some problems (see my earlier post on that). Maybe Google has ironed out some of those. 

Am trying to avoid any and all Apple products, but will take a closer look at the new iPad Mini. If it isn't wildly overpriced, like most Apple things, might at least check it out in more detail. 

UPDATE: The new iPad Air starts at $499, which is totally ludicrous. The new iPad Mini with the Retina display, starts at $399. Why? No idea, but I guess there's not shortage of Apple aficionados out there, who are willing to keep making the company even richer. 

The search for the "perfect" tablet continues :) 

UPDATE 2: Got a Google Nexus 7, to replace the returned Kindle Fire HDX. There's no comparison. The real Android OS is like a breath of fresh air, compared to Amazon's reworked version and for about the same price. 

Briefly considered either the present, or the new iPad Mini, but the ridiculous prices Apple insists on charging for their products go very much against my grain.﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ZnDm7XL8fqE/Uma9lWwlLII/AAAAAAAACVQ/KjUpf4PObpk/w426-h335/Kindle_FireHDX.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/118238984223748862323/albums/5850218803225400113/5850218804610593490</link><title>I #boycotappleforlife. This mean that you'll love this story, probably. I stopped my mom from committing to a purchase on QVC for a 16gb iPad. Yes, you too can see this very deal on QVC's webpage right now, and it's only $636...something dollars. You get it, a case, car charger, bluetooth keyboard case, free magazines (probably a year), blah, blah, 
and blah. When my mom said, "I ordered an iPad" all I could think was... "I told her not to get a iPad. It's not a good deal". TV has quite the effect on some people. Yes, she does need a new device of some kind to do basic internet things. Her old old old old Gateway 17.3 is not gonna cut it. Image this whole time it's been running Vista 32bit.... I did install Linux Ubuntu 12.04 32bit on it (dual boot) so she could at least handle basic things. I showed her, even more clearly again, how much she'll be spending and how much she'll be getting. First I showed her the #Asus Transformer (TF300) on QVC site $427, then I showed here the same product on ebay brand new (with the keyboard dock) $419.99. Then I showed her the same device on ebay (no dock) $300. QVC might have a 6 payment plan, but with ebay you can get the product then get all the accessories you want slowly over time. She won't spend $600 total dollars and get 32gb (+ 32gb more storage later on if she chooses). She really rather read the magazines she already recieve the old fashion way. She ordered the case in purple (which they ran out of on QVC) and later in the week has ordered a NEW blue Transformer with the dock $419.99. Then she can get whatever else she wants with it. 
As you can tell she is spending about $203 less and getting SO MUCH MORE then what she would have gotten if she got a 16gb ipad. You know what she could do with $203? buy a Nexus 7, have a nice meal 4 nights in a row, buy a new phone on contract, a purse, or a small TV for the Kitchen. Now as she said "I can sleep soundly, no worrying about making payments for the next 6 months. I don't say #boycottappleforlife just to be cool or trendy. I can go on about some of the practices that they (Apple) have done, but lets only deal with facts. Get more for your money and stop settling. Paying more for less is a scam. Showing love is saving them time or money. I love my mom that much.﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-RPHTdESfCCM/UTAnAcsf8tI/AAAAAAAAGZE/55aS7O_VKIA/w426-h237/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/105237212888595777019/albums/5628318062289990961/5663831106564613202</link><title>Okay Android Peeps... ! :) 

I've had an Android for a while now, and I want a new Android. Which one should I get? Should I wait on this new one from Google? 

Here are some things in my head: 

\- Like the photo below, should I get one before Ice Cream Sandwich? 

\- I currently feel inclined to get the new Google phone, but, I really don't know if it will be the best. Sometimes I hear that other manufacturers have better screens or more power. I don't know... I can't keep up with it all. 

\- I had a heck of a time upgrading my current HTC Desire to 2.2. I basically had to take it some underground chopshop in China and they did something crazy to it. I still have some rogue Thailand installation running. It works, but every now and then, things go Thai-crazy. So, of course, I want one that I can upgrade as easily as iPhones upgrade. 

\- I keep having memory problems. The main card my unlocked HTC Desire came with was very small. I looked up how to swap it out for a bigger card, but there was some special gold-master burn of some initialization file or something silly that was confusing... I have a bigger SD card on bay 2, but it seems like all the main apps (G+, Voice, Maps) etc, have to stay on the main card, which is always running out of memory. I feel like I'm back on my 66 Mhz running a Load /himem type stuff just so I could get Ultima IV to open correctly. 

\- I currently have unlimited data through AT&amp;T, and I love running my Android hotspot to connect both my laptop and iPad to (at the same time!)... it's really one of my favorite things about the phone. 

\- I would like a decent camera... we do have 100 Cameras in 1 coming to Android soon, and I'm looking forward to using that. 

\- Why don't you have an iPhone, I hear some asking... Well, I do love the apps, but, I really run all those apps on my iPad. I like the bigger screen on the iPad... Anyway, to me, in short, the coolest thing about the iPhone is the apps, so I feel covered there. And when I don't have my iPad, my Android has all the key apps I that are mission-critical... G+, gmail, Trip-it, Maps (which are better on Android anyway). 

\- Okay, so which phone to get? Help me Obi-Wan, you're my only hope.﻿

Meer lezen (41 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-nuSt0cafbR4/Tpn4YhaXZFI/AAAAAAABCtg/DVd6DgQ4f_U/w426-h292/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/101212404445568930918/albums/5947399811189086593/5947399813024800786</link><title>Got a sweet tooth? The #Nexus5  has arrived at Telstra! The world’s 1st phone running +Android 4.4 KitKat® is available now for pre-order. Order before Nov 26 and you will receive a bonus $100 Google Play voucher. Tempted? Visit Telstra Exchange for more information: http://bit.ly/IaGRpN﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_08_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-QRdS9HT0RCk/UolonoiRYBI/AAAAAAAAGY0/HPT1XhzXXp4/w426-h264/Nexus-5_google.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/110038350445855508357/albums/5818234708659568689/5818234709425779810</link><title>Behold, the top 10 gadgets of 2012: http://ti.me/ViVQh3 

What gadget have you bought this year that you cannot live without?﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-JCN3fjoFir0/UL6FpFMr9GI/AAAAAAAANWQ/Ga69UZq1LEY/w426-h299/zeb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7481-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/worms%20nexus%207/photos/107705531709996732852/albums/5920913551795571233/5920913550769876082?authkey=CNi175SArKqjxwE</link><title>Potsdamer Platz, Berlin 
Nexus 4 + Pixlr Express﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7481_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-t0KJ-c8tISE/UitPgQtvbHI/AAAAAAABioI/2PPo772CYCY/w426-h305/PANO_20130905_145348_20130905222448731_20130905222529057.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>