<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:03:24" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/100165677851155258072/albums/6006251779936736961/6006251783822228018</link><title>How to Turn Facebook Fans into Paying Customers 

Now that you’ve built a loyal group of followers that “like” your Facebook page, you need to attract their interest if you want to drive traffic to your site. The importance of engaging content that’s compelling and educational is central to any inbound marketing strategy, and it’s certainly true for your company’s social media presence. The majority of fans following you on Facebook aren’t ready to buy, and may not be for some time. However, you still need to obtain and maintain their attention so that they see you as a trusted source when they are ready to purchase. 

Here are our tips on turning facebook fans into paying customers: http://www.digitalsherpa.com/blog/how-to-turn-facebook-fans-into-paying-customers/﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-wf9Hk4J_ELQ/U1p-LMZHujI/AAAAAAAACRo/o712_Jgy5Yw/w426-h240/cebook%2Bfans.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/103400392486480765286/albums/5749803218324712641/5749803224066600578</link><title>How Facebook cheats paying clients - amazing 
If you purchases your likes through targeted FAcebook advertising.... how many will see it?  GUESS AGAIN 
About 10% of those likes are shown your actual updates. 
90% of people never see your updates because of a thing Facebook calls Edgerank. 
Is that not incredible.... so you spent money to get these likes and then Facebook prevents them from seeing your updates? BUT WAIT.... 
Now Facebook is introducing a tool so you can pay a second time, yes a second time :-) 
You are effectively paying twice to reach the same group of people if you start using this new tool on a regular basis to have your content seen. 
Can you charge your customers twice for the same service We cannot. 
You think Facebook will get away with this? 
More discussion: https://www.xing.com/net/smmetrics/trends-and-historical-facts-505431/another-facebook-first-gm-general-motors-stops-paying-for-ads-40740839/40839943/#40839943﻿

Meer lezen (16 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_02_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XQYS7_fySkU/T8tnkYriroI/AAAAAAAAAL4/UJr8pdLs3NM/w426-h299/2012-06-03-Paying-Facebook-Twice-to-make-sure-your-Likes-see-Your-Content.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/106648708306407050690/albums/5743681089611765105/5743681097776737330</link><title>How you help Facebook make billions: If you're not paying for it, you're not the customer. You're the product. 

Every post you "like." Every friend you add or fan page you join. Every place you check in, and every Web page you recommend. 

To you, those are ways to enjoy, expand and improve your experience on Facebook. To Facebook, they're the building blocks of a multibillion-dollar company. 

In business, there's a well-worn line that could apply to the social-networking behemoth: If you're not paying for it, you're not the customer. You're the product. 

In this case, you're a product worth, to Facebook, an average $4.84 a year.﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-rTVt-kc3bAo/T7WnhvAbrDI/AAAAAAAADDw/XgROuTiu-II/w426-h237/hh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5959177688087211985/5959177690858471378</link><title>Are You Paying Facebook’s Taxes? Again…  http://b4in.org/puu 

According to Senator Tom Coburn (R-Oklahoma) Facebook will be paying no tax again this year, in fact, it looks like they might even get a refund. 

Each year Senator Coburn publishes his ‘Wastebook’, a report that details how much money the government waste 

Of Facebook he says: 

“one of America’s largest companies avoided paying federal or state income taxes, and is poised to do so again this year. In fact, they will likely receive a check from the federal government in the form of a tax refund.” 

“Despite bringing in more than $1 billion in US pretax profits last year, the social-media giant Facebook reported a combined $429 million refund from their federal and state tax filings,” he continues, including roughly $295 million from Uncle Sam. 

According to Coburn’s report, last year Facebook relied on an employee stock option tax deduction to lower the amount of owed income taxes by around $1.03 billion. 

“By providing stock options as a major form of their compensation, to date Facebook has claimed $3.2 billion in federal and state stock option deductions, $1.03 billion of which was used to offset their total US pretax profit of $1.1 billion in 2012 and $429 million was refunded from its 2010 and 2011 tax bills,” he says. 

More http://b4in.org/puu﻿

Meer lezen (28 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-u2aNQkzG89c/UrNAiWkNP9I/AAAAAAAABvI/K_sRJRoVZoM/s426/facebook_logo2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/109931720898576608083/albums/5684968790260946705/5684968791712895538</link><title>Cab driver teaches guy a lesson for not paying on Facebook﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-kILWTaHFOIQ/TuUQ_u06kjI/AAAAAAAAZN0/FPFN6XEn-nA/w426-h237/469850659.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/107357887572939534909/albums/5765396921744950625/5765396920964230386</link><title>Facebook acquires mobile-bookmarking service Spool 

Facebook is paying for the company's five employees, not its technology. 

Here's the full announcement from Spool: 
_We started Spool to make content easy to consume on a mobile device. To accomplish this, we built some very sophisticated technology and developed a deep expertise in mobile software development. We firmly believe that solving these problems will be increasingly important as the world accesses the Internet primarily through mobile devices. 
We are proud to announce that today we will be pursuing our vision as a part of Facebook. If you were a Spool user, please read the instructions on retaining your bookmarks. 
We are extremely excited to accelerate our vision and help Facebook's users connect and share with the people in their lives. We wouldn't be in a position to have this sort of impact without our supporters and the Spool community. Please accept a heartfelt thank you for supporting us and for affording us this opportunity._ 

Via http://goo.gl/1ZCO1﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_06_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-yFnUSLtJdKs/UALN9Ac0LPI/AAAAAAAAACA/4rOKv3dysFc/w426-h237/Spool%2Bis%2Bjoining%2BFacebook%2B%25C2%25AB.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/112295067957104126211/albums/5812894707859649457/5812894711975996498</link><title>Use these 4 Tips to Increase Your Facebook Page Reach Without Paying for sponsored stories or promoted posts: 

1\. Create a Facebook List (Interest Lists) about a relevent topic - Add people and pages that provide that relevant info and make the list public. 
2\. Encourage your fans to subscribe to your page notifications 
3\. Try including more text-only posts in your Facebook Marketing mix (FB changed things again and text-only is helping with reach) 
4\. Track your performance per time slot in a spreadsheet to see what times perform best on which days (insights are helpful, but a spreadsheet may work better). Check out the pic as an example. 

Here's the full article: http://bit.ly/IncreaseReachTips﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_07_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-W5ZWGqkGg6U/UKuM8UgTbFI/AAAAAAAAAjg/CYr4eggEjog/w426-h237/Example%2BSpreadsheet.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/104294490742835639574/albums/5948817001480067649/5948817000561395058</link><title>Are you converting your Facebook followers into paying customers? Learn how at our Facebook Seminar tomorrow - http://bit.ly/1ekwz2c 
#facebook  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_08_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1dY0RYyk9Us/Uo5xizhERXI/AAAAAAAABUQ/z3uKBAM63nw/s426/Facebook-Money.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/114434037515303916034/albums/6006309868728947825/6006309873726534626?sqi=103475999580662647081&amp;sqsi=0da0e591-6fea-48a0-9fc4-f4be852fb073</link><title>How to respond to #Facebook's declining organic reach http://bit.ly/1pow6EM Via +SmartBrief. 

"Many marketers have yet to embrace the reality that as of March 2014, only a meager 1 in 20 of their Facebook fans are seeing their carefully crafted “organic” posts. At the risk of being painfully clear, to reach the other 95% of your fans on Facebook now requires paying Zuckerberg &amp; Co. his due. This of course begs the question, what’s a thrifty and socially savvy tactician to do now?" 

So what worked yesterday isn't working (nearly as well) today. Here's a good post on how to adjust. BIG TAKEAWAY: It's gonna cost you at the end of the day. 

#socmed #socialmedi #facebook #branding #marketing #socialmarketing ﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-oahIApWe13s/U1qzAeJkM-I/AAAAAAAAEJY/fb4b2Wop8DM/w426-h427/4-25-2014%2B12-56-40%2BPM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7483-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/facebook%20paying%3F/photos/118042949466913169971/albums/5656536936043782289/5656536934027008514</link><title>Don't worry guys... I'M PAYING FOR YOUR FACEBOOK AND GOOGLE... along with hundreds of thousands of internet marketers who advertise on these 2 networks to ensure you, the END USER, will NEVER EVER need to pay to use them. 

So please STOP spreading the hoax chain message that "you will have to start paying to use facebook as a NORMAL user unless you cut and paste that STUPID message". It's just a ploy by hackers to clog facebook's network traffic!﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7483_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-CZtZvfmF35I/ToAOXzOOmgI/AAAAAAAAAIQ/DTFyW31UDPk/w426-h266/facebook%2Bis%2Bfree.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>