<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:12" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/109855938860338751031/albums/5941274721536714897/5941274721000932018</link><title>Need a last-minute idea for #DayoftheDead? 

Make this easy skull mask &gt;&gt; http://oak.ctx.ly/r/g93a ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-FU9ZWVueU0I/UnOl4WpEwrI/AAAAAAAABKM/KPiKraH9xs8/w426-h320/4d31f368-82df-42e2-8e59-08cbfd35a121</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/106534614709047283662/albums/5665745753170591489/5665745754923209634</link><title>Sugar skull mask in progress. I'm making 5 of these for a friend and YES there will be a tutorial on how I do it, complete with tips to make your life easier.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QQa5KNb_tCY/TqDFvuXgE6I/AAAAAAAACOA/Amx5eMqgdkg/s426/6265226882_ca74d8391d_b.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/116450899676482348348/albums/5936038186031988929/5936038191327572914</link><title>Looking for something cool to wear for Halloween? We love this tutorial by the amazing Mary Winkler on how to make an awesome sugar skull felt mask: http://crafts.tutsplus.com/tutorials/how-to-make-a-bright-sugar-skull-felt-mask-for-halloween-free-pattern--craft-14690﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-uKBiI3yv97c/UmELSNc7c7I/AAAAAAAABM0/VV5LhBbWleA/w426-h286/mask-017.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/115212185875399904107/albums/5633356501699215601/5633356505367698242</link><title>Cap is the god of winning. - Kurt Busiek 

And you love him for it. See, Captain America is the reason why Superman bores me. I loved the Christopher Reeve Superman movie growing up, and I’m sure I’d still love it today. But when it comes to reading a comic, I just don’t give a crap about Supes. His powers are so all-encompassing that it’s just not believable to me that he could conceivably lose a fight with anybody. Cap is a kid from Brooklyn who doesn’t really even have super powers. He’s really strong, but you could still take him out with a well placed bullet. Doesn’t need to be a magic green space-rock bullet either. Just a hunk of lead through the chest, and he’s done. 

So, it’s a given that I love Cap. I love Cap almost as much as Iron Man. Which made Civil War so unreadable, as they’d taken both characters and twisted them beyond recognition. Seriously? A Cap who argues (without giving anybody the chance to talk to him) for unchecked vigilante justice, and a Tony who wants to round up everybody’s secret identities and put them in one really super-duper safe computer? Because nobody’s ever hacked a computer before? Riiight. 

Sorry. I get tangent-y sometimes. 

Like I said, I love me some Cap. So I was really hoping for this movie not to suck. And it super-doesn’t-suck. It almost wins. In fact, if I hadn’t seen X-Men First Class already this summer, I would probably be arguing more that it was the really great super hero flick of the year. It’s really good. 

But let me start off (ha, four paragraphs in, and you’re starting off) with my one gripe: Wimpy Steve. I get that they wanted to go the Benjamin Button route and slap Chris Evans’ face on some wimpy guy, but I think they did a sloppy job of it. There were scenes where it looked right. Mostly those scenes were not the close ups. Sometimes when I’m photoshopping something into an image, I need to step away and come back in order to notice that my proportions are off. This seemed to be a problem in some of these scenes. It was like they popped it in, but didn’t account for the fact that Chris Evans’ face is actually a different shape than this kid. So while the eyes, nose, and mouth may be in the right place, they’re not the right size. It’s a gripe that kept taking me out of the movie, and it was a movie that I wanted desperately to be in, because I was loving the story as it unfolded. 

Evans is great. He’s pitch perfect, and you’re rooting for him from the moment he steps on screen. He doesn’t give up, and he can take a punch (or fifty). You want him to get the girl, and you cringe when he’s forced to ham it up on stage. With Steve Rogers, there’s such a huge possibility for boring. If he’s written (or acted) wrong, you could have a steaming pile of ‘who cares’ on your hands. Evans makes us care about the boyscout, and he gives us a handle on the creation of Marvel’s “god of winning.” 

His relationships with Erskine and Peggy are the most poignant on screen, and Tucci is wonderful as always. Hayley Atwell looks as if she was plucked out of that time period, and makes sure that Peggy Carter is tough-as-nails, but sexy as a pin-up. She and Evans have great chemistry, and it makes me wonder if they’ll have her go blonde in a sequel and play her own niece, Sharon, who goes on to be Cap’s modern day girlfriend/partner. 

I’m glad about so many nuances in this flick, but a couple that stuck out are (SPOILERS): the fact that Bucky isn’t so much a sidekick as a fellow soldier, and the fact that we don’t get him tied to a rocket at the end of the movie. That’s one thing I was really hoping they’d avoid, and was so glad that they did. The Winter Soldier is still a possible storyline, the way it goes down, and that makes me happy too. The Howling Commandos are as cock-sure as they should be, and seeing Neal McDonough as Dum-Dum Dugan was a real treat. 

On the flipside, Hugo Weaving is creepy as hell as the Red Skull, and Toby Jones is a wonderful pick for Arnim Zola. There’s even a sweet nod to the future of Zola in his very first scene. Wonder if they’ll go there in the sequels. The Red Skull make up looked slightly better in the stills that we were shown before the movie came out, but I was very happy with it. I think it could have used just a little more shading to give it more depth, but I’m not really quibbling. It’s wonderful that it didn’t once make me go, “That’s a mask.” I bought it, totally. 

I could have used just a little more back story on the Skull. He was introduced in a kind of exposition-y bit of dialogue, and I think they could have given us just one small scene like we got in the beginning of the first X-men flick with young Magneto at the gates finding his power. Why is Schmidt so evil? Give me one reason to care. There was an issue of Cap written by Mark Waid that would have been a great resource for a screenwriter looking for a reason why the skull is who he is. Maybe we can get more of that in a sequel. 

I’ve taken enough of your time with this. Go see the flick. See it in 2-D. It’s a movie that you should enjoy with every color nuance and without the darkening effect of 3D glasses. You don’t need things busting out at you to enjoy it. Johnson did his job, and it’s all there on the screen. Also, if you haven’t learned yet, that you should stick around for the credits on a Marvel movie, then let me tell you now. Stay.﻿

Meer lezen (95 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-oHG0c1qrEnI/Ti2z5ROT20I/AAAAAAAABmc/-AXbOJ5tH0c/w426-h664/chris-evans-captain-america.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/103927208056809975762/albums/5894902323721390337/5894902323103449410?authkey=CLKMk5z69t-gsgE</link><title>Terminator Mask 
www.coolpeopleshop.com/products/electronics/terminator-mask/ 

Ever want a super-human #robot #skull!? Check out #Terminator #Head #Mask! Features lights, sounds, and #VOICE-CHANGE technology! 
Plus its steel plated in chrome to protect all the computer chips needed to make this #CYBORG cranium come to life! The deluxe Terminator Head is all you need to become an advanced T-600 robot of the future! Set in post-apocalyptic 2018, John #Connor is the man fated to lead the human resistance against Skynet and its army of #Terminators. But the future Connor was raised to believe in is altered in part by the appearance of Marcus Wright, a stranger whose last memory is of being on death row. Connor must decide whether Marcus has been sent from the future, or rescued from the past.﻿

Meer lezen (12 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-J0Y5uag4_EE/Uc7mbio0wUI/AAAAAAAAAWY/K4sUnbtG_fk/s426/Terminator-Mask.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/106987265842631987139/albums/5950222992972320593/5950222998812507106?sqi=115557860434442655096&amp;sqsi=85a68f55-3c9d-4d26-8804-286fcc0be813</link><title>Hello everyone, this my first time here and also the first Theory I'm posting... so be gentle haha. 

THE HAPPY MASK SALESMAN... A DEMON? 

Maybe this is already heard or writen down as creepy pastas and all, but however, I'll start with this: 

We know that in the universe of The Legend of Zelda exist several demon-like creatures very powerful (Demise, Ganon, Belum, Malladus). But what there might be others lower in rank but not so good either. 
Now, going right into my theory, if you notice the story and the facts in The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask, you'll see that EVERY mask is the soul of someone or something related to the game characters. Then again, Masks are the vessels for said souls. Majora is a mask with huge powers over darkness, what means (If we relate this to some facts in Twilight Princess) the soul of the very first twili before they turned into that shadowy form, were trapped there. So, how I say The Happy Mask Salesman is a demon? Well, He's very desperate looking for the mask and collects them. And when he lost Majora to Skull kid, he felt the urge to get it back, reason why he asked link's assistance to get it back (And he gets furious when he fails to get it the very first time when Link breaks the Deku scrub's curse). 
Having that in consideration, once you finish the game and deliver the now powerless mask to the man, he laments the mask having lost its power and says his "business" there are over, so he departs vanishing (I know this could be due to the lacking of graphical capacity on that time, but then again they could have only cut the scene of him leaving instead of showing him disappearing). SO! Knowing now this, it comes to my mind that even in Zelda's universe there are several kind of demons, and demons are the only creatures that make deals with souls and that. Then again, The Happy Mask Salesman could be one of those who, instead of making deals for souls, he waits till they get trapped in masks to collect them. 

I hope to hear you... Till next time!﻿

Meer lezen (35 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_06_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-RnOZVZ51p0g/UpNwSrKUO-I/AAAAAAAABdw/rjaFI81qBC4/w426-h637/Happy_Mask_Salesman_Artwork_%2528Majora%2527s_Mask%2529.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/109179578413389263097/albums/5850094883523355137/5850094883107237986?authkey=CP7FmM3zi46FTA</link><title>This would make a good halloween mask. The Skull Faced caterpillar of South East Asia. 
Photo courtesy of Melvyn Yeo .﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-uQaxQ3JlhYk/US-2TRHv8GI/AAAAAAAAzB4/svElq5ZwzKo/w426-h284/856695_489083337794324_26618294_o.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/103781188723568108134/albums/5881976994623476705/5881976998820533906?authkey=CMbx7ZXXoKCyVg&amp;sqi=103871897552393522085&amp;sqsi=7a995443-9c38-4b53-bc1a-81533c905773</link><title>Majora's Mask cosplay mask. 

It took about a month to make using paper mache, acrylic paint, and foam cones. 

Part of a WIP Skull Kid costume... 

(Sorry for bad image quality)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ZCtecCHtcwM/UaD66pe3VpI/AAAAAAAABdE/hRryj7MBXoI/w426-h284/Photo%2Bon%2B5-19-13%2Bat%2B8.51%2BPM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/107906093846039182490/albums/5818934716407798481/5818934718274123410</link><title>Freaking LOVE this Papercraft of Skull Kid from The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask!! 

#geek #papercraft #art from http://society6.com/StudioofMM/Skull-Kid_Print 

you can even make one yourself with this template! -&gt; http://www.nintendopapercraft.com/2008/05/skull-kid.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2dZGNIK7oOo/UMECS9XqtpI/AAAAAAAAH5I/hy04lP7nSIM/w426-h297/skull_kid_papercraft_by_studioofmm-d5nazs6.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7489-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/make%20skull%20mask/photos/112713735405531168929/albums/5677030883651984849/5677030881938363266</link><title>“We all have secrets, Rick; we’re all wearing masks - even Jennifer. Just remember; beneath the make-up, below the porcelain-smooth skin…behind those eyes so deep you could drown…there’s a hollow, bleached white skull - and it’s laughing at you.” \- Terror Mask﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7489_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-auHJ_w4Qn3s/Tsjdgkjb04I/AAAAAAAAABk/XfIUZg2InZo/w426-h240/tumblr_ls1pdfK7j41r3ocrzo1_1280.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>