<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:29:47" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/116611908007933524932/albums/5984299658187576049/5984299657873702690</link><title>MIA wins Most Iconic Cultural Brand on Social Media. We would like to thank Qatar Chronicle and, of course, all our many fans for voting for us. Social Media has enabled us to share, educate and create dialogue about our museum and its collection of Islamic Art with the world http://www.mia.org.qa/en/about/connect-with-mia﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-t-Y9-v3qoVA/UwyA1SkNvyI/AAAAAAAALxk/efkITjQAsNs/w426-h237/connect.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/116611908007933524932/albums/5976427915796725969/5976427915142819170</link><title>We’ve been nominated for ‘Most Iconic Cultural Brand on Social Media’ courtesy of Qatar Chronicle. Help us win by voting for MIA at http://www.qatarchronicle.com/happenings/48340/qatar-chronicle-social-media-awards-nominations-announced/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-emv6iMzd8Ws/UvCJhjvQ7WI/AAAAAAAALJA/z4yRE-s8-C0/w426-h284/20060911_121_Qatar.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/117899361956238561353/albums/6006108377108118369/6006108380407551474</link><title>Islam is one of the biggest religions and the fastest growing religions in the world. This infogrpahic takes a look at basic facts about Islam and Muslims 

As a believer in Islam, one should seek knowledge about people and also teach people what the Quran really says. All the verses from the Quran is not easy to interpret and therefore one should ask several Imams about specific verses. Islam actually means peace, even though the media is portraying 1.7 billion Muslims in the World negatively, the religion Islam is about Mercy, Peace and Justice. Do a good research upon it and you will see it for yourself. The FASTEST growing religion, Islam, is now on about 2.1 billion Muslims. May Peace be with you all. ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-nJuYp8aSzbM/U1n7wBCwVfI/AAAAAAAAfbE/n-QXd1fntYc/w426-h776/The%2BFASTEST%2Bgrowing%2Breligion%252C%2BIslam.bmp</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/103401472872744209975/albums/5983135691808332705/5983135698080653890</link><title>♦ BismillahiRahmaanirRaheem ♦ 

Social Media || Spread Islam 

"Social Media is very effective, Muslims should use this media to spread the true message of Islam." 

\- Dr Zakir naik 

There's no doubt the power the social media has over billions of people of today. It makes sense to use this to use it for the benefit of Our Deen. 

Share a Quranic Ayah, a Hadith, an Islamic Post or simply be someone who posts motivational and inspiring messages for mankind. 

REFLECT •|• ACT UPON •|• SHARE WITH OTHERS﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SWvlzMnap-s/UwheN6cOYkI/AAAAAAAAzkg/Yr25vleJnkw/w426-h481/1044301_10151520092647151_530741091_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/116062532630598069029/albums/5962362339081488321/5962362340882436626?sqi=111138198062048110053&amp;sqsi=bc4ffba6-607d-4629-88a3-dcba5f1c101e</link><title>superb members v can use social media for spreading islam dose who say dat social media is  wrong dy must know all thngs hve positive n negatve importance its depnd on ourselves:) 
share if u like r comment..........﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_5qNpLIhTNo/Ur6Q9YZ20hI/AAAAAAAAWGs/7O8MXNgzC-U/w426-h237/Dr%2BZakir%2BNaik%2BQuotes%2BSayings%2B%25287%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/105986449921389641226/albums/5868610606181833649/5868610603957378146?authkey=CIDxzPvs1-XKywE</link><title>Boston bombing suspects’ social media trail shows strong interest in Islam, Syria — but offers no motive http://natpo.st/XVl64z﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-LENgvoZoqyA/UXF-QEX4XGI/AAAAAAAAesc/nGebuOX4gyQ/w426-h319/1VEzB.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/100208140468371167022/albums/5812255508203263201/5812255515610901122</link><title>Dear Brothers &amp; Sisters.. 
I am a Muslim from the Sole-neuclear state in Muslim world called-Pakistan &amp; want to share my feelings and sympathy with my Palestaninians brothers and sisters especially those  from Gaza who are suffering from the horrible and brutal  attacks of Israeli Airstrikes for 5 days. 
The Terrorist state Israel has a very short history, illegally occupied Palestine and backed by U.S and western Countries especially E.U. As the world eading country, The U.S has great influence on worlds Electronic Media which is suppost to be transperant and reliable  are ignoring this  reality of assaulting attacks  of Israil's on Gaza. More than 1100 airstrikes destructed Gaza's important buildings  and civilian homes, even killed 6 journalists and claiming it was just done in self-defense as the Gaza extremist Org Hammas has Shot 700 short and long range rockets on Tel aviv, the second largest city of Israel which is a damn lie and Media are showing their biasness. 

Even the Claimer of world peace maintaining country, U.S president show his support for Israel &amp; briefed that Israel is doing nothing but self-defense and we provide full support to Israel which is shameful. Arab League is keeping silence on this important issue just like they are puppets of U.S and Israel. The social media is the only source left to update our Muslim Friends from Gaza's awful situations. We got evidence, videos, pictures, articles and keep it sharing but still many stone-hearted peoples are supporting  Israel which is too awful.  The oppressor Israeli may have started ground attack with 75000 reserved forces. This aggressiveness clearly shows that they are backed by U.S. More the 54 innocent civilians lives have been lost in Gaza, 
inclueding 16 children, 462+ civilians are seriously injured  including mostly children and woman. 

The Muslim world needs Unity against these evil forces who are so united against Muslims in different Countries. Few months ago the Burmese muslims faced the same ignorance of  Media &amp; world peace Org's. 90000+ Muslims remained homeless, 20000 Muslims were murdered but no body asked. Our Muslim brothers and sisters make their efforts on social Media and forced the World to stop innocent Muslims killings there. 

Dear Brothers and sisters, I appreciate two great countries  Egypt and Turkey for showing their sympathy and support to  Gaza openly and strongly condemned Israeli Attack on Gaza.Egyptian President M.Al-Mursi is trying for Negotiations b/w two sides which is quite praiseable and applaudable. The Kwaiti king visited Gaza was just spying for Israili attack on P.M H.Q in Gaza. 

Dear Friends, you don't have to ask in-operative world Peace Org, U.N or Arab League for help because they will never raise their voice till they are asked to speak. One humble request to all of you, Please don't just show 
your faith on social Media to show your sympathy here, Offer your salah &amp; nawafil, Recite the Holy Qur'an, Ask Allah for help and keep them remember in your prayers. 

Long Live Gaza, Long live palestine.. 

Insha ALLAH, we are with you Gaza. 

May Allah bring unity in Muslims for Gaza and Israel will 
face its shameful end Soon, Insha ALLAH.. 

Keep sharing this message, its my pain for Gaza :'( 

May Allah Bless you All, Ameen... 

From &lt;del&gt;Waqar Ahamd&lt;/del&gt; to Gaza...﻿

Meer lezen (63 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Rr5FWHUzJuU/UKlHmMfK6oI/AAAAAAAAE8A/TDg6tUjIKRM/w426-h284/080325-peled-transforming.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/116611908007933524932/albums/5936051855871312241/5936051854459777314</link><title>Share your Hajj Art &amp; Photography 

Help us celebrate and illuminate the holy pilgrimage of Hajj by sharing your art or photographs with captions on Social Media. Send your entries to hajj-mia@qma.org.qa, alternatively use the hashtag #Hajj_Art on Twitter or Instagram so we can share and credit your entry. 

Discover more about our new exhibition Hajj: The Journey Through Art http://hajj.mia.org.qa/en 

*Image - Kazuyoshi Nomachi 1996﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-u5XJ5xP7D74/UmEXtglfsSI/AAAAAAAAHsM/T0QR46BxS-E/w426-h267/KN1996Hajjphoto.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/111145036038024824961/albums/5963831014836213201/5963831015783172882</link><title>Certificate Awarded for the Significant Role in the Discussion on “Innovation in Public Service” Using Social Media Platform from Special Guest Mr. Mostafa Jabbar, President, Bangladesh Computer Samity, Mr. Abu Alam Md. Shahid Khan, Secretary, Local Government Division, Ministry of Local Government, Rural Development and Cooperatives. Mr. Md. Nojibur Rahman, Secretary, Statistics and Informatics Division, Ministry of Planning, and Mr. Golam Mostafa Kamal, Director General, Bangladesh Bureau of Statistics (BBS), high official from different Divisions/Ministries/Departments, BBS &amp; SID officials and Media personalities are presented in the Exceptional Social Media Gathering (Adda) Ceremony.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-8rOmGWNm_kY/UsPItgw2ixI/AAAAAAAAAF8/eEGj6zOYpJ4/w426-h240/1487800_3768422824379_1401054578_o.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7493-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/islam%20discussions%20social%20media/photos/116611908007933524932/albums/5985723617987473489/5985723622686392242</link><title>Osman, one of our MIA Social Media Admins is slightly obsessed with this 15th century war mask. Osman would like to share his love for this object by giving you the chance to win an amazing replica of the actual mask that is on display in our museum. 

To enter, print the mask cut-out http://www.mia.org.qa/docs/war-mask.pdf, take a selfie wearing the mask in a location and setting of your choosing. Upload your mask photo to Instagram with the hashtag ‪#‎MIAMask‬. 

We will repost to our Instagram account. The picture with the most likes on our account will win the beautifully detailed replica war mask and the runner up wins a war mask magnet. 

Terms and Conditions: 
1 March – 31 March 
Follow @MIAQatar on Instagram 
Hashtag all entries #MIAMask 
No limitation on entries﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7493_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1nwtr3Otl88/UxGP683i_7I/AAAAAAAAL6A/BVvwuHw3x1c/w426-h237/maskinstagram1.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>