<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:33:50" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/111300891418764987403/albums/5770905264518547921/5770905263736216322</link><title>Performing for Bettakultcha at The Magic Loungeabout festival  - cartoons in my life﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3AfP_Cfjg90/UBZfwwVt2wI/AAAAAAAAACs/APRyedWvgNU/s426/TML2012%2BCartoons.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/106369693717665847554/albums/5761872678228926833/5761872682512537010</link><title>Sports, tourism film fest opens 

The sixth Vietnam International Federation of Cinema and Television Sports (FICTS) Festival officially opened on July 4 at Hanoi Opera House to introduce films on sport and tourism. 

This year the festival received 25 domestic and 42 foreign film stations and television channels, including ESPN (US), Eurosport (France), Shootv Sport Economy ( Italy ) and Les Films Neptune (US). 

Some international agents who produce tourism and sports films from Cuba, Turkey, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Nigeria and Portugal will also send the works to the festival. 

 Audiences can enjoy 145 entries, including documentaries, scientific films, television films and cartoons on 9.30am and 2.30pm at the Vietnam Cinematography Association, 51 Tran Hung Dao street, Hanoi until the festival ends on July 7. 

The moved is aimed to encourage the writing of new works on culture, sports and tourism with some high art as well, said Nguyen Xuan Vinh, from the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism. 

Besides, the festival honours authors and artists of cinema and television featuring the contributions of some of the best art work in a process of integration and development of Vietnam cinema, sports and tourism. 
The festival will provide an opportunity to show Vietnam as a beautiful and friendly sports and tourism destination. On the occasion, the delegates will be brought to Bat Trang Pottery village and Thang Long Water Puppet Theatre to understand Vietnamese culture. 

"This year, the number of foreign delegates is double the previous festivals," said Vinh. 

In his launch speech, Deputy Minister Huynh Vinh Ai, head of the festival steering board, said Vietnam 's festival was recognised by the FICTS to honour valued works on culture, sports and tourism made by Vietnam and other countries 

"Vietnam FICTS is a chance to introduce the image of the nation and people which is sporty and has tourism potential," said Ai. 
The closing and awards ceremony will be broadcast live on VTV2 channel and Hanoi Television from the Hanoi Opera House on Saturday evening. 

http://www.vietnamtourism.com/e_pages/news/index.asp?loai=2&amp;uid=22704﻿

Meer lezen (45 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-KhkrvzhuX0Q/T_ZIrVIv1bI/AAAAAAAACEM/XekRDF98wL4/w426-h320/LHthethaoDL.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/108515551765941088256/albums/5875668538334210593/5875668539324709794?authkey=CKP2mM3E_NzITw</link><title>We are thrilled to announce the 2013 Coca-Cola Summer Film Festival which will go on sale this Friday! 

Raiders of the Lost Ark - June 14th 
Saturday Morning Cartoons – June 15th 
Oz, the Great and Powerful – June 15th 
42 – June 21st 
Finding Nemo – June 22nd 
Les Miserables – June 22nd 
The Birds – June 23rd 
Django Unchained – July 26th 
The Croods – July 27th 
Lawrence of Arabia – July 28th 
Saturday Morning Cartoons – August 17th 
Breakfast at Tiffany’s - August 18th 
TBA - August 29th 

Tickets go on sale this Friday at www.FoxAtlTix.com﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-qArVKyJYVxQ/UYqRZ-hjO6I/AAAAAAAABw8/6AbSwRbTq4g/w426-h428/942633_10152787671090648_1302037885_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/103427931601569320544/albums/5789498843990036625/5789498844206460866</link><title>Film greats are honoured at Bradford Animation Festival 

A creative chief behind the Oscar-winning Wallace and Gromit films will be a special guest at this year’s Bradford Animation Festival. 

Also appearing at the festival, at the National Media Museum next month, is a leading member of American studio LAIKA, which made this summer’s hit family movie ParaNorman. 

Aardman Animations, creators of the much-loved Wallace and Gromit series and the film Chicken Run, jointly headline this year’s festival alongside LAIKA. 

Will Becher, who joined Aardman as a trainee animator on Wallace and Gromit: Curse of the Were-Rabbit and has since established a reputation as one of the company’s top freelance animators, will offer an insight into his career and his work as lead character animator on Aardman’s latest movie, The Pirates! In an Adventure with Scientists! 
Mr Becher has worked with Aardman on commercials, TV shows Shaun the Sheep and Creature Comforts and films such as Wallace and Gromit: A Matter of Loaf and Death. 

LAIKA’s Mark Shapiro will present a behind-the-scenes look at the studio’s latest feature animation, ParaNorman, the tale of a misunderstood boy who takes on ghosts, zombies and grown-ups to save his town from a centuries-old curse. Mark, marketing and brand manager at LAIKA, will also take part in a question and answer session before ParaNorman is shown in 3D. 

This year’s Lifetime Achievement Award will be given posthumously to John Halas, co-writer/director of the first British animated feature film Animal Farm. The award commemorates the 100 anniversary of the birth of the animator. A documentary on his achievements, Animated Utopia: The Life and Achievements of John Halas, 1912-1995, will have its final-cut world premiere and his daughter, Vivien Halas, will sit on the BAF jury. 
Other festival guests include award-winning film-maker Robert Morgan, writer-director of The Cat With Hands, a dark tale of a cat that wants to be human, and stop-motion horror animation Bobby Yeah, which was screened at Bradford International Film Festival and Fantastic Films Weekend earlier this year. 

Animation legend Chuck Jones’s granddaughter Valerie Kausen will talk about her recollections of working with her grandfather, highlighting a BAF screening of classic shorts from the man behind cartoons such as Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck. 

The festival will showcase more than 140 films from around the world, including this year’s hit animation Brave. 

Headline speakers for the BAF Game strand include Neil Thompson, director of art and animation at Canadian studio BioWare, creators of Dragon Age and Mass Effects series. 

Festival director Deb Singleton said: “This year we have one of our most diverse line-ups ever, featuring one of America’s most vibrant and cutting-edge studios, established and new British talent and two of the most legendary figures in animation from the past century. We’ll also be showcasing a brilliant programme of films, from undiscovered gems to some of the most acclaimed feature animations of 2012.” 

thetelegraphandargus.co.uk﻿

Meer lezen (59 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-3-05N6L8CHM/UFhuhlR178I/AAAAAAAAAGU/Q2FQRn-VYrQ/w426-h240/paranorman-LAIKA.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/100623276740673202144/albums/5819593580247905617/5819593585303231218</link><title>I taught a comics workshop today at a community center comics festival in Yangjeong. 
It was kind of an odd experience, since the organizers kind of forgot I was coming and therefore didn’t schedule it/tell anyone. Sent me into an unused classroom 5 minutes after the festival ended to do a workshop unannounced. 
The guy running the thing ran downstairs to grab 5 random people, only one of whom wanted to be a cartoonist. 
But we. had. an. AMAZING TIME. 
At the end of it, 3 of the 5 wanted to be cartoonists. the other two were their parents, who wanted their kids to become cartoonists. 
AWESOME.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_05_thumb.gif">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-X8qKJUKcVmQ/UMNZiEUkGvI/AAAAAAAAYdw/cZaiZXd57bk/w426-h283/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/111439383080007025766/albums/5902020405516535217/5973986601791022866</link><title>ARE YOU IN MUMBAI ON 7 FEBRUARY 2014? 
Well, if you are, let's hangout IRL at the Kala Ghoda Arts Festival! I have a session for kids at the famous festival, scheduled for 5:00 PM at the Kitabkhana. Bring your little ones along (or someone else's as long as you haven't kidnapped or otherwise illegally detained them) and they can join my quick cartoon-drawing session. The India: A to Z session — with authour/editor +Vidya mani — is based on our book of the same name, published by Puffin. I did the cartoons for the book, in case you don't remember the connection ;-) 

For more details go here: http://www.kalaghodaassociation.com/eventdetails.aspx?subcatid=131&amp;catid=103&amp;id=102 

#mumbai #kalaghoda #greystroke﻿

Meer lezen (10 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-06J_L1uk9rU/UufdKayyZxI/AAAAAAAAJYI/FNK2YqXyj3I/w426-h852/KALA%2BGHODA.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/114804467432159116851/albums/5956690554766776897/5956690551317371858</link><title>René Pétillon (French: [petijɔ̃]; born December 12, 1945, Lesneven) is a French satirical and political cartoonist. 

Pétillon joined Pilote magazine in 1972. Since 1993, he has published cartoons in the Canard Enchaîné and he signs them as Pétillon. 

In addition to his editorial cartoons, he has published a series of humorous adventures of his hero, Jack Palmer, a goofy private detective. 

In 2001, he published L'Enquête Corse ("The Corsican Enquiry"), dealing with the "independentist" groups in Corsica. The album was a popular and critical success, with 300,000 printed in French plus 30,000 in Corsican. A movie of the same name, starring Jean Reno, was based on the book and released in 2004. 

In 1989, he was awarded the Grand Prix de la ville at the Angoulême International Comics Festival. In 2002 he get the Grand prix de l'humour vache at the Salon international du dessin de presse et d'humour in Saint-Just-le-Martel. 

from https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ren%C3%A9_P%C3%A9tillon 

René Pétillon in the Grand Comics Database: 
http://www.comics.org/search/advanced/process/?target=issue_cover&amp;method=icontains&amp;logic=True&amp;order1=date&amp;order2=series&amp;pencils=Ren%C3%A9+P%C3%A9tillon﻿

Meer lezen (23 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-0qdYHJHkBvs/Uqpqfxwym9I/AAAAAAAAM00/eWKuft7CuR4/w426-h574/3ZQsJ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/115346047351009302785/albums/5935016795083710209/5935016799638041282?sqi=106923716158448972124&amp;sqsi=eaa61175-e968-4618-8772-8dce2fc45b2b</link><title>Succotash Epi71: Podcastin' From the L.A. PodFest 
http://SuccotashShow.com 

Marc Hershon here, back from last weekend’s rousing 2nd Annual Los Angeles Podcast Festival! And what a festival it was. Held once again at the Delfina Hotel in Santa Monica. There were tons of live podcasts going off during the three days – or, really, two and a half days – of the festival. 

Looking back on the schedule for the PodFest, I count 40 shows and that’s not counting the folks like us that were recording our own shows and interviews in the Podcast Lab. Speaking of which, the next couple of episodes of Succotash will hopefully come out very quickly. Bam, bam, bam. Because they’ll be focused around interviews I did while I was at the festival. 

I’ll be playing clips from many of the episodes of the podcasts that were done at the festival as well. A big shout out to our Honorary Associate Producer Tyson Saner, who's been doing an amazing amount of clip harvesting on behalf of this show. 

I got to be a guest on Chillpak Hollywood Hour during their live appearance at the PodFest, and you'll hear not only hear a clip from that episode but also some chats I had in the Podcast Lab with Dean Haglund, Phil Leirness, and Lily Holleman - all three not only associated with Chillpak with the still-in-production film The Ladykillers as well. 

The 10 Most Active Show In The Stitcher Top 100 Comedy Podcast List 

This is the rundown of the ten shows on Stitcher's Top 100 Comedy Podcast list that have moved up or down the charts the most this past week. 

37\. The Smartest Man In The World +28 
42\. The Mark &amp; Lynda Podcast -34 
63\. The Dana Gould Hour +44 
64\. This Week In Blackness Radio +15 
65\. The Tenderloins Podcast +98 
68\. DVDASA with David Choe &amp; Asa Akira -32 
78\. Sawbones: A Marital Tour of Misguided Medicine +48 
79\. SModcast &gt;&gt; FeAB -40 
82\. Answer Me This! +16 
91\. Who’s Paying Attention +15 

The podcast at the top of the list - The Smartest Man In The World - is hosted by improv great and friend Greg Proops, who is also releasing a video special on October 22nd. Available online, you can find Greg Proops: Live at Musso &amp; Frank at Chill.com. 

The Clips 

The Steven Brody Steven Festival of Friendship 
Our friend Tyson Saner harvested this clip from The Steven Brody Stevens Festival of Friendship podcast and I’m glad. I really like Brody and hadn’t had a chance to even hear his podcast yet. Plus I also like James Adomian, who is an amazing vocal talent and funny as hell to boot. His “Maron in Space” bit on the IFC Channel is hilarious. 

Doug Loves Movies 
My first clip from one of the LA PodFest shows comes from Doug Loves Movies with Doug Benson – one of the few podcasts out of the 40 they had that I actually had the time to watch. The one this year wasn’t as crazy as last year’s, which was unhinged. (The RC helicopter nametag was back, but no sign of last year's infant…) He had Jimmy Pardo, Nick Thune, DC Pierson, and David Huntsberger on stage with him, but this clip is before the guests even came out, when Doug clears the air about Mr. Belvedere’s balls. 

Improv 4 Humans 
Matt Besser’s show was at the PodFest but THIS clip is from another live appearance that Tyson Saner grabbed. It’s from Bumbershoot in Seattle and Tyson says he liked this pull because it’s very “Hi, this is who we are and here we go!” Featuring Tim Meadows, Horatio Sanz &amp; Brian Huskey, it’s also based around the Harold structure for you improv wonks, which lends itself pretty well to a podcast. 

The Kira Soltanovich Show 
Comedian Kira Soltanovich was all over the LA PodFest. Every time I turned around, there she was, either interviewing someone or being interviewed herself. She hasn’t really been on my radar until now, but I got to see her perform live at the late Saturday night Standup Smash! Show they did there and now I’m a fan. In this clip that Tyson grabbed, we hear part of Kira’s interview with Laraine Newman. 

Just Jump To The End 
It’s interesting to see how many siblings pop up as podcast hosts. One of the best ones is My Brother, My Brother and Me but there also the Sibling Rivalry podcast, the Kamenetsky Brothers Land O’ Lakers podcast and a whole bunch of other ones. One I just found out about is Jump To The End, featuring brother-sister team Scott Fitzman and Molly Harris. Their show’s Twitter page describes the p’cast as “Two grown siblings talking shit about people, places, and things.” In our clip they talk about revisiting cartoons and other entertainment from their childhood, and what it’s like exposing THEIR kids to it. 

The Indoor Kids 
Back to the LA PodFest, we get a taste of the live-in-front-of-a-live-audience version of The Indoor Kids. Hosted by the husband-and-wife team of comics Kumail Nanjiani and Emily Gordon, this show focuses on video games. In this segment from the Fest with Blair Butler, they talk about video games that they’ve recently been depressed by and, also, games that they use as a carthasis. 

Chillpak Hollywood Hour 
For the last taste of the LA PodFest this episode, I pull a few minutes from the live Chillpak Hollywood Hour show, featuring Dean Haglund and Phil Leirness, with their special cameo guest…ME! 

So there will be more clips from LA PodFest shows in the next few episodes. After that (or maybe in between some of that), I will have interviews with some comedians and some filmmakers who are in the throes of getting their Kickstarter campaigns rolling. 

Rest up. 

In the meantime, don't forget to pass that damn Succotash. 

— Marc Hershon﻿

Meer lezen (118 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_08_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-VZGwcnWsrQY/Ul1qVY5mssI/AAAAAAAAELU/nSXcmtS8Nec/s426/succotash%252Blapodfest_logo_circle_100dpi.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/103857459148999991693/albums/5966745884157559889/5966745881785332018</link><title>Erotic Film Festival Poster 

Hmmm I don't think Disney would approve of this Star Wars poster 

Via: http://adsoftheworld.com/media/print/kino_praha_cinema_erotic_film_festival_star_wars﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-0-tF2N_kMWs/Us4jxCzW8TI/AAAAAAAAc6Q/UKQRDCsdcyE/w426-h593/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7494-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/cartoons%20festival/photos/108515551765941088256/albums/5742765929645461681/5742765929219116354</link><title>We are thrilled to announce the movies of the 2012 Coca-Cola Summer Film Festival! 

Casablanca (70th Anniversary) 
Thursday, June 14 at 7:30 p.m. 

Godfather (40th Anniversary) 
Friday, June 15 at 7:30p.m. 

Special Event: Sound of Music Sing-a-Long 
Sunday, June 24th at 2:00 p.m. 

Saturday Morning Cartoons (for the little ones) 
Saturday, July 14 at 10:00 a.m. 

The Princess Bride* (25th Anniversary) 
Sunday, July 15 at 6:30 p.m. 
*Chosen by the Fox Theatre’s Facebook Fans 

Deliverance (40th Anniversary) 
Friday, July 20 at 7:30 p.m. 

Additional films in the 2012 Coca-Cola Summer Film Festival will be announced later in the summer. 

Except for the Sing-a-long Sound of Music and the Saturday morning cartoons, tickets are $10 for adults, and $5 for kids under 12 and seniors ages 65 and up. All tickets for the Saturday morning cartoons are $5. 

Please note The Sound of Music Sing-a-Long is a special event screening. Tickets for the event are reserved seating and are $15 in advance and $20 the day of the show. Passes for the Coca-Cola Summer Film Festival can not be used for the Sing-a-Long event. 

Tickets, which go on sale Tuesday, May 22nd at 10 a.m., are available at the Fox Theatre Ticket Office, www.FoxAtlTix.com, 1-855-ATL-TIXX, and all Ticket Alternative locations. All tickets are general admission. 

Come early and join in a favorite Atlanta tradition of the Fox Theatre’s magical pre-show experience featuring Larry Douglas Embury at the “Mighty Mo” organ, the tradition of a sing-a-long and a classic cartoon.﻿

Meer lezen (40 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7494_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-XjOKao9IhwQ/T7JnL6dSTUI/AAAAAAAAAKA/xdiX5SWRVMg/w426-h428/550440_10151711061480648_141137570647_24317542_1351665530_n.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>