<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 20:02:49" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/112993898662880391149/albums/5948022086352444881/5948022089670235714</link><title>renewed IEEE membership* (16 years!) 
NOT proud 
until they offer open access for free to all world, forget about "Advancing Technology for  Humanity" 

*=because of discounts at conferences - that's all﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-YL6Mw8MZV9Y/Uouek5r4lkI/AAAAAAAAO2M/Su5t8-KjlvI/w426-h305/ieee-logo2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/113664776160150493710/albums/5776242758673871025/5776242762256594162</link><title>We will provide the leadership and vision to restore America's greatness. Stand with America's Comeback Team today!  http://mi.tt/QXOcdI﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-0dKve7WTagM/UClWMDy5tPI/AAAAAAAAKiA/NJHN2WW_l2I/w426-h321/Photo1%2B%25287%2529.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/112053177074571305383/albums/0/5823779752517990290</link><title>Apple sells these now at store... Micro USB to lightning﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/--G7bp7fSiSc/UNI41Ebyd5I/AAAAAAAAE_k/BylWu5sLo2M/w426-h568/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/111221057260756260538/albums/6011597594385357425/6011597600263454210</link><title>#ieee #ieeeregion10 #ieeebssn 

Surprise Revealed !! 

IEEE Region 10 ECIM Team brings to you an exclusive contest to express yourself. Simple steps to attain fame and win amazing goodies. 

1\. Tell us (in less than 140 characters) why you joined IEEE. 
2\. Get a chance to be featured on the IEEE Region 10 Page. 
3\. Two Winners receive a box full of IEEE Goodies. 

To participate: 
1\. Post a status (Within 140 characters) in quotes 
Eg: - "I am an IEEE member because... ". Do not forget to use #IjoinedIEEE,@IEEE Region 10, #IEEERegion10 in your post. The characters in the "" will be counted and the #hashtags will not be counted. 
2\. Send us a link of the post, a high resolution photo, your entry along with your Name, Section, Member number to Ijoinedieee@gmail.com. 

Prize Criteria: 
1\. One winner will be selected by the IEEE Region 10 ECIM Team based on the creativity. 
2\. One winner will be selected based on the highest number of likes for the post. 

Note: Open to IEEE Region 10 only. 

Start sending entries today !! 

#IjoinedIEEE #IEEERegion10 #140characters﻿

Meer lezen (28 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-iCUYeMwPlbs/U218KqhLPgI/AAAAAAAABSw/e3bfgiRHHgk/w426-h284/10296011_388866174585255_9167793479614135191_o.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/100782174925034975316/albums/5866163118680718529/5866170205817367362</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-WHNWmSBByUk/UWjSuM25a0I/AAAAAAAAEcs/FpXjTE-V2vg/w426-h284/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/115926626028083554164/albums/5886760624751651201/5886760630853099378?authkey=CLr03YT_mpO__QE</link><title>LUMINEX Joins AVnu Alliance Promoting 
Adoption of IEEE 802.1 AVB Standards 

Montreal (June 7, 2013) – LUMINEX Network Intelligence has joined the AVnu Alliance, the Beaverton, Oregon-based the industry consortium that certifies IEEE 802.1 Audio Video Bridging (AVB) products for interoperability. LUMINEX is a Belgium-based developer of lighting control, pro audio and video data distribution equipment for the entertainment industry. 

AVnu Alliance is a non-profit organization formed by member companies to create compliance test procedures and processes that ensure AVB interoperability of networked AV devices and help provide the highest quality streaming AV experience for end users. Utilizing AVB, the transmission of audio and video streams can be synchronized within a microsecond of each other with low delay and minimal lost data due to network congestion. The AVnu Alliance is currently focused on three markets: professional AV, automotive and consumer electronics. 

“Claiming to be an AVB-capable product is not enough these days,” says Hugo Larin, Managing director for Luminex Network Intelligence in America. “The industry is looking for commitments toward AVB, and this is why we are very excited to announce that LUMINEX has joined the AVnu Alliance.” 

AVnu Alliance’s Promoter members will write compliance and interoperability test guidelines, designed for the 802.1 AVB specifications, for bridge and endpoint products to undergo and then beAVnu certified. 

As an AVnu Alliance Adopter member, LUMINEX will have access to those completed test plans; it will also be eligible to have its products enter certification in an AVnu Alliance-approved test lab and participate in AVnu Alliance-hosted plug-fests. 

Larin notes that, “LUMINEX has been enjoying recent growth with users wanting to deploy audio over IP in a ruggedized and simplified way.” To further broaden its reach, LUMINEX is making its first appearance at InfoComm13, June 8-14, in booth #561 at the Orange County Convention Center in Orlando where it will show its new range of Gigabit Ethernet switches with updated web-based user interface. 

Bart Swinnen, Luminex CEO, concludes, “We're exited to get our hands on the technical documents and get our development in line. We’re really looking forward to be a professional solution provider for AVB and serve this innovative market.”﻿

Meer lezen (43 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Sw4GyCrr_6M/UbH5mrfA33I/AAAAAAAAAIM/xwIh1bFwRpQ/w426-h242/Member%2Bof%2BAVnu%2B%2528R%2529%2BAlliance%2BBADGE%2BRGB.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/113215976889659570939/albums/5850516296555600929/5850516302820242050?authkey=CKWZpM7t19-ezgE</link><title>I am looking for examples of scientific organizations, or even individual non-economist scientists, who have spoken out against austerity or in favor of progressive taxation-based budget solutions prior to the sequestration threat, i.e., January or earlier.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ivB_PX8TN00/UTE1lH47coI/AAAAAAAADG8/MbIcNBGKKh8/w426-h320/1A_austerity_original.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/117790530324740296539/albums/5823732555615860209/5823732559868887698?authkey=CJDbzbuwrJfS7wE</link><title>This week we chatted with Joseph Hellerstein (http://goo.gl/UbmHj), Software Engineering Manager in Seattle and a major contributor toward Google’s efforts in cloud infrastructure. He shared details of his group’s internal and external collaborations that address a number of science problems, especially in the areas of biochemistry, astronomy and brain biology. If you’re wondering what Google’s interests could possibly be in those areas, read on: 

Research at Google: Could you give us a quick run-through of your pre-Google career? 

Joe Hellerstein: Sure. I got my PhD in applied math and computer science from the University of California, Los Angeles. From there I went to IBM Research for 22 years, where I started the Adaptive Systems Department. We did projects like applying control theory to do resource management for IBM database systems and power management of IBM hardware. Between IBM and Google I did a stint at Microsoft for 2 years, where I worked on the .NET framework -- specifically, on reengineering .NET thread pools using control theory. Mathematical models of resource management has been interesting academically as well: I’ve published over 100 papers, two books, and taught at Columbia University and the University of Washington. A couple of years ago, I became an IEEE Fellow (largely because of my control theory work). And then I joined Google in 2008. 

R@G: And what are the grand challenges you’re addressing in your work at Google these days? 

JH: A little over a year ago I was interested in doing something different -- I’d been working for a while on stuff I’d done before, mostly mathematical models of our large compute clusters. Google’s cloud services are centered in Seattle, and I’ve always been interested in an applications focus for cloud services. I thought it would be best to start with non-commercial applications. So in that sense the academic world was perfect because 21st-century physical science faces challenges that are very compute- and data-intensive. 

For example, one big challenge today in biology and chemistry is that there are massive amounts of calculations and data manipulations that are required to relate laboratory data to scientific theory. Unfortunately, current methodologies for computational science make it so that these analyses are often not reproducible. Some steps are automated, but there are manual editing steps as well. The process lacks the kind of rigor used in the software industry to produce production systems like Google Search and Gmail. So while the scientific results might get published in top journals like Nature, other researchers cannot reproduce and build on those studies. This is one of the basic foundations of science -- that others can reproduce your work. The lack of “computational hygiene” in the sciences is well-recognized by bodies like the NSF and NIH. 

A related challenge for biologists, chemists, and other domain scientists is that software engineering skills are increasingly necessary to understand the work of other scientists and to extend their own work. This ties back to reproducibility. The problem arises because graduate schools and funding agencies are training scientists for the last millenium, not for the 21st century. 

I was at a National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) meeting a few months ago, and spoke with a NIH program manager about this. She was trained as a biochemist, and so really didn’t understand why training in software engineering is important for biochemists. What did make sense to her is when I described software as the lab notebook for 21st-century science. 

R@G: Could you give us an example of an initiative in your department? 

JH: One effort we have underway is the development of mentoring programs for domain scientists, enabling them to write software that others can understand and to design data sets that others can query. For example, we’re working with a non-profit based in Seattle called Sage Bionetworks, whose goal is to promote open biology and the use of common large scale computing systems to understand the relationship between genomes and disease. It’s headed by Dr. Stephen Friend, who previously led Merck &amp; Co.’s Oncology Research division. Their scientists are technically oriented and know how to program, but the complexities of engineering are not a focus for them -- they want to focus on the analysis of their data. Biologists tend to use the R open-source programming language, but R wasn’t designed to scale and typically runs on a single machine. That’s okay for a few gigabytes of data, but once you get into terabytes it becomes difficult for scientists to operate in the same manner without software engineering skills. That’s a real bottleneck. What we’re doing for this class of users is making it easy to run R in a parallel cluster environments such as Google Compute Engine. We allow scientists to scale computations without having to become software engineers. 

R@G: Very interesting! So how is your group organized in order to bring the most value to the outside partners you work with, as well as to Google? 

JH: There’s an engineering side and a research side. The engineering side has two projects: One relates to creating a low friction way for scientists and other analysts to use Google Compute Engine, like running R at scale. The second engineering project is Exacycle, a project developed by +Dan Belov and +David Konerding at Google (and largely built by David). Exacycle is a kind of supercomputer that provides massive scaling for “embarrassingly parallel” compute-intensive work. 

On the research side, we have a combination of Visiting Faculty doing science projects on Exacycle, and interns doing work with Google cloud services. Google’s Exacycle Program provides large scale computational capability for computationally intensive projects, like building detailed simulation of the movements of molecules or light rays. We posted results and progress from the Exacycle program earlier this week on the Research Blog: http://goo.gl/TA3aO. 

R@G: Could you give us examples of projects you’re working on that use Exacycle? 

JH: Sure, I have two examples, one in astronomy and one in chemistry. The Large Synoptic Survey Telescope, or LSST (http://www.lsst.org/lsst/) will likely be the most impactful astronomy project of our generation (maybe, our lifetime). The telescope will be placed high on a mountain in Chile, which is supposed to be the driest place on earth. Even so, one of the main challenges with LSST is how to remove the light distorting effects of the earth’s atmosphere. This means LSST designers must design algorithms to remove those distortions so that the telescope can properly see the sky and map the universe. We’re working with Andrew Connolly, who started working with Google back in 2006 as project lead for Google Sky, now a continuing Visiting Faculty member here and professor at the University of Washington, and Jeff Gardner of the eScience Institute. Prior to Exacycle, doing such computations would take them on the order of 6 months. With Exacycle, we have it down to 2 weeks. This has radically changed the way the LSST is being designed. We hope to get it down to 2 days. 

Another example is in computational chemistry. One of the challenges in drug design is to understand how the chemical pathways for disease operate and how we can introduce drugs to affect those pathways. A key question is how to control the chemical processes that go on inside a cell. One way is to control the molecules that interact with G-protein-coupled-receptors, or GPCRs, in the cell membrane. GPCRs sense the presence of certain molecules, bring them into the intra-membrane area, and this in turn causes changes to happen inside the cell. GPCRs are in fact the target for 40% of the drug market, so they’re very important proteins. Understanding GPCRs is key to drug design. In fact, recently Brian Kobilka of Stanford won the 2012 Nobel Prize in Chemistry for his work on GPCRs. Brian made huge advances, but the actual mechanisms at work happen to remain ill-understood. 

To that end, Kai Kohlhoff in my department (formerly a postdoctoral fellow at Stanford) is completing studies of GPCR dynamics. Computation is important because if you want to do molecular dynamics simulation, you have to bridge huge time scales. Molecular motions (called conformations) take place in 10e-12 to 10e-9 seconds. It turns out that conformational changes are key to the way proteins such as GPCRs do chemistry. This chemistry happens over 10e-3 seconds. Extensive computation is required to bridge time scales that differ by factors of a million to a trillion. Kai developed simulations for Exacycle that yielded some interesting results on activation and deactivation of molecules. We co-authored an article in IEEE’s Internet Computing, called Science in the Cloud: Accelerating Discovery in the 21st Century. For anyone who’s interested in reading more, see http://goo.gl/CA0NE. Kai is now preparing a publication for the biochemistry community. 

R@G: And is there something on the horizon that you are particularly excited about? 

JH: I’m generally excited about the deeper interactions between computer science and the domain sciences. Up to this point, computers have just been a necessary tool for physicists and other scientists. The relationship between computation and science started to change with the sequencing of the human genome. Since then, there’s been more integration between computing and domain science, in that new algorithms had to be invented to do this work at scale. 

Here’s an example of something I find very exciting based on work we’ve been doing with the Allen Institute for Brain Science. We’ve had the pleasure of working with Christof Koch, a very well-regarded neurobiologist. Christof regularly gets single paper citation rates in excess of 1500, and has co-authored papers with the late Nobel Laureate Francis Crick. Christof and I were talking about their need for higher-scale computing in order to simulate the several million complex nerve cells making up the mouse visual cortex. Often, this scaling is done using supercomputers, like the IBM Blue Gene. But supercomputers are very expensive and, if someone wants to reproduce your results, they need the same (very expensive) supercomputer. For this reason, we wanted to scale using conventional clusters. But doing so requires the use of distributed algorithms that don’t require low latency connections between computers. 

This created a challenge for us since it seems that brain simulations require a supercomputer with an expensive, high speed network to cope with the communication demanded by the trillions of connections between neurons in the human brain. At this point, Christof mentioned what he thought was another complexity of the problem --- signal transmission between neurons is very unreliable. That is, a neuron may have to fire many times before there is an effect on an adjacent neuron. However, this is potentially a great opportunity for computational scaling because it means that we could greatly reduce the communication between computers by sending only a fraction of the neuron firings and we could still achieve biologically accurate results. This work is being pursued by Tim Blakely, a PhD candidate in bioengineering at the University of Washington. 

R@G: What do you value most about Google’s culture and how does it enable you to maximize your impact? 

JH: You know, Google has been very supportive of me exploring this kind of work. You have to demonstrate that you can produce results, of course. But our mission is broad and the opportunity to work with a very smart interdisciplinary group of people to impact the world in these ways is very satisfying to me. 

Also, not to be cheesy, but the food here is awesome. A company that provides awesome food, for me, creates a very positive and warm environment that promotes communication and interaction. I really value that part of our culture. I bike to work -- 7 miles each way -- so as long as I bike to work I figure I can enjoy all the food! I’m very lucky. 

R@G: Are you tired of being endlessly mistaken for Berkeley’s Professor Joe Hellerstein? 

That certainly is a constant source of confusion! But it’s also been a fun connection for Joe and I.﻿

Meer lezen (223 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ltDKaDVBVsE/UNIN6GHcgpI/AAAAAAAAAso/GhjMkkeS29o/w426-h395/Joe_Hellerstein.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-11"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/112526208786662512291/albums/5908645286740167377/5908645286736953842?authkey=CIzxzMqz6uDz-QE</link><title>Microsoft has “no plans” to release open-source drivers for next-gen Kinect 

http://spectrum.ieee.org/automaton/robotics/robotics-hardware/video-friday-baxter-nao-robonaut 

============================ 
Last night, we heard from a member of the Kinect for Windows developer team that they have “no plans” to release open source drivers for the next generation Kinect, meaning that all of the awesome and magical things that the original Kinect enabled for robotics won’t evolve into even more awesome and more magical things with Microsoft’s new sensor. 

Sigh. 
================================= 

#xbox   #kinect  ﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_11_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-WN4gnR-8Pb4/Uf-5lTu-AfI/AAAAAAAAYQQ/qPXxOK_g5wc/w426-h261/0803135-Kinect-not-open-source-600x368.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7496-12"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/why%20IEEE%20member/photos/112063946124358686266/albums/5634234618381493713/5634234622742352754</link><title>Here's my recommendation if you're looking to do something besides G+ tonight. Go watch this Kurzweil / Singularity documentary. Technology will accelerate exponentially. Within 25 years, computers will have consciousness. Humans will soon be bionic. These predictions make bestselling author Ray Kurzweil (The Singularity Is Near) a prophetic genius to some, and a "highly sophisticated crackpot" to others. You can rent online via Amazon. http://amzn.to/pzHKkt It's also on Netflix, search "Trancsendent Man"﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7496_12_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-_V6ffZCbi3s/TjDSibXD03I/AAAAAAAAPpI/CoVTdEDzhnw/w426-h568/kurzweil.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>