<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7497">shostakovich life</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 20:05:43" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/100137334565677902948/albums/5975475899970449793/5990675060041800514</link><title>Brighton House: (Opus No. 7) — 
UK Premiere 
‘A thrillingly inventive production that tingles with sensation.’ New York Times 
Conceived and directed by Dmitry Krymov 

Set design by Vera Martynova and Maria Tregubova 
Dmitry Krymov is one of the most influential figures in Russian theatre. Rarely seen in the UK, his works are deeply moving, visually majestic theatrical experiences that conjure beguiling images on a grand scale – unmissable for anyone interested in bold, thought-provoking theatre. 
This bewitching, genre-blending performance pitches you headlong into a world in which objects, sounds and people can change in the blink of an eye. Progressing from a lyrical and starkly beautiful requiem for the Jews of Eastern Europe to an hallucinogenic exploration of the tortured life and career of the Soviet-era composer Dmitri 
Shostakovich, Opus No. 7’s ensemble of performers use simple materials and extraordinary skill to explore an elusive and frightening past. Featuring original music by Alexander Bakshi alongside Shostakovich’s harrowing Piano Trio No. 2 and his epic Seventh Symphony, Opus No. 7 is a theatrical explosion of invention that includes larger-than- life puppets, duelling pianos, living walls and blizzards of newsprint.. 
Sat 3 &amp; Sun 4 May, 5pm 

Mon 5 May, 3pm 

Tue 6 – Thu 8 May, 7pm﻿

Meer lezen (26 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Ms1ch55C-lk/UyMnOiaVW0I/AAAAAAAAAIU/6kjokxMaakk/w426-h239/opus.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/116523471304102911491/albums/6008739527804452737/6008739524419158130</link><title>Seated up close and personal on the stage, audiences enter a world of transformation where objects, sounds and people can change in the blink of an eye. Depicting the oppression of Soviet Jews followed by the censorship of Shostakovich under Stalin, Opus No 7 sees larger-than-life puppets, duelling pianos, living walls and blizzards of newsprint form part of a genre-defying double bill. 

Dmitry Krymov Lab Opus No. 7 UK Premiere. Conceived and directed by Dmitry Krymov set design by Vera Martynova and Maria Tregubova 

More @ http://bit.ly/1kq45Vj﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-bZiBGkHmv3A/U2NUwwTagHI/AAAAAAAAAwc/unCWr1emgZI/w426-h237/no7tw.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/107465447281069657152/albums/5762375327147753841/5762375335513463426</link><title>I am hitting my head against the walls, but the walls are giving way. 
\-- Gustav Mahler 

His grandmother was a street pedlar and his father a coachman and later an innkeeper in Bohemia, which was then part of Austrian Empire; he was born in 1860 and was to be the eldest surviving of no less than 14 children in the family. His first contact with music were street musicians and singers and army bands, which some say can be felt in his compositions. Becoming sort of a wunderkind playing his grandparents' piano he had his first public showing at ten and then went on to write an opera when he was just 14, as a memorial to his younger brother's death. This set him on the course of musical life that would eventually make him one of the most important composers and conductors of his time, deeply influencing such as Arnold Schoenberg, Alban Berg, Dmitri Shostakovich and Benjamin Britten. 

Today is his birthday :)﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1PcbpoP4w7Y/T_gR1lfAmoI/AAAAAAAAzlU/lHTSF2pLqoE/w426-h593/blog-gustav-mahler.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/106660876363786203340/albums/5750972309538549809/5750972314043758930</link><title>Daily Classical Music Post 

Today is the anniversary of the birth of the Armenian composer Արամ Խաչատրյան  (Aram Ilyich Khachaturian) (6 June 1903–1 May 1978). 

http://grooveshark.com/s/Khachaturian+Cello+Concerto+In+E+Minor+I+Allegro+Moderato/4FLOyC?src=5 

Khachaturian's music often contains elements of Armenian folk music as well as Russian classical music; of course, he spent much of his life in an Armenia that was part of the Soviet Union. He was a member of the Communist Party, although in the late 1940s he fell out of favour. The work that led to his temporary "exile" was, ironically, written as a tribute to communism -- his Symphonic Poem, later called the Third Symphony. 

He was in good company, however; the Zhdanov decree in 1948 named him as well as Shostakovich and Prokofiev, and the three of them had to apologise to the Soviet elite for their apparent formalism and anti-popular stance. Khachaturian later said, “Those were tragic days for me. . . . I was clouted on the head so unjustly. My repenting speech at the First Congress was insincere. I was crushed, destroyed. I seriously considered changing professions.” 

By the 1950s, however, Khachaturian was back in favour, and he won many prizes throughout the 1950s, 1960s, and 1970s. He was a great influence on Armenian classical composers in the 20th century, and he encouraged many younger composers to experiment with new sounds. 

Khachaturian's Cello Concerto was written in 1946, and it is meant to reflect his painful wartime memories. Armenian folk songs and dances are intermingled with the composer's own melodies. There is even a statement of the Dies Irae in the first movement, and many musicians feel that the brooding quality of this concerto, and particularly the first movement, is a reason why it has never achieved the popularity of his other concertos. This concerto was another one of the reasons why Khachaturian was denounced by the Soviet government in 1948. 

I love it, though, and so today for my classical music post I am sharing the first movement of Khachaturian's Cello Concerto in e minor.﻿

Meer lezen (41 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-ulrqs9zy94A/T8-O2YOvOVI/AAAAAAAAH7s/91I29odkmJI/w426-h550/khachaturian.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/108633455224826641550/albums/5853100889183525217/5853100893354921858?authkey=CN-znvCu2PicPA</link><title>Welcome to the ultimate Gacha experience! The Arcade Gacha Events features over 80 of the grid's most popular designers. 
http://bit.ly/TZIV4t﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_05_thumb.png">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-1JDmIVyvqwQ/UTpkQF7xD4I/AAAAAAAAIaY/-ooNrCt3v_0/w426-h255/gacha.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/108633455224826641550/albums/5915089567674238913/5915089567442574098</link><title>Bogon Flux is a scrap metal steampunk structure that defies gravity. Beware of falling parts! http://bit.ly/16B9RPS﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-A0TlQ1uNEcg/Uhaen0IImxI/AAAAAAAALoY/T22I-vbfdEQ/w426-h255/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/111091089527727420853/albums/5758956747155128033/5758956747795769346</link><title>Imagine their lives. They will learn to drive with a self-driving car. They wont remember what physical keyboards are like. They will put in glasses to watch videos, or make them. 

This is the class of 2018 and 2016. 

I love them so much and their entire world will be over the freaky line. 

What challenges will they face? Meet Ryan and Milan, YouTube addicts.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-eqxXMnHSKTU/T-vspl00qAI/AAAAAAAAk2g/aPjZFV6f9JE/w426-h320/E9A27744-A2AA-4119-8E9D-5ADF5816D303.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/104293557269756681667/albums/5853356650880322465/5853356655942649682</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-a-TZuSDB5Rg/UTtM3b0hR1I/AAAAAAAAv-k/JLXHR41NJrE/w426-h320/photo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/109502308789906202700/albums/5833687597937475585/5833687601781171010?authkey=CIO0zdrdn9KkJg</link><title>ご質問：ショスタコーヴィチのチェロ協奏曲第2番は不思議な曲ですがどのような曲だと解説されていますか 

お答え： 
 チェロ協奏曲第2番ト長調 作品126（1966年作曲） 
 シンプルな音型ですが、とてもわかりにくい曲です。 
 “この「チェロ協奏曲第2番」は、「アレクサンドル・ブルークの詩による歌曲」、「弦楽四重奏曲第11番」とともにこれらには、この後の作品で発展するすべての要素が含まれている".と指摘するのはイアン・マクドナルドです。 

ウイルソンの楽章ごとの解説は、以下の通りです。 

第1楽章　ラルゴの冒頭部分は、弦楽器の低音の伴奏でチェロが長い独白を表す（embarking on） 
ロストロポーヴィチは「スコアを見てみなさい、特別なものは何もない。しかしスコアの最初のページ、音で聴くと、その効果に圧倒される。これこそショスタコーヴィチが天才であることだ」という。 

第2楽章　はオデッサの俗謡（これ正確な訳ですかね？）」の「パンだよ、パン買いなよ」の主題。“グリークマンへの手紙で、“たまたま入り込んでしまった”と書いてますが“その主題の本来の性格は快活でやや皮肉なものですが　最終楽章の総奏の最高点では悪意ある脅迫的な響きとなっている・ 

 　第１番　と同じくチェロ協奏曲第2番ではホルンが顕著な役割を果たしているがここでは、第2楽章と第３楽章をつなぐカデンツァを1オクターブ低音の（doubled).グロテスクなファンファーレとして伴奏する。チェロは、四度の音程を二重音奏法するが、この音程は最終楽章の顕著な特徴である。 

第３楽章は予期しないテーマの変形や自己を指示するようなパラドックスの要素で構成されている。 
 　しめくくりは第１楽章の回想のような部分から始まり、過去となった少年期のイメージに関連した音の世界に豹変する。パーカッションが鳴りながら、チェロは長いD音をかなでる。この音がこの協奏曲をやや盛り上げながら終わらせる。この終わり方は終わりというよりも、冷たい不安の中にさらされている、回答のない疑問のようだ。 
 （ウイルソンA life Rememberedｐ４４５） 

マクドナルドは、 
 「１９６６年ショスタコーヴィチは心臓発作を起こし＂死”についてより考えるようになった。冷静で、達観的な、不透明で孤独な、やや簡明な構造で、まばらで最小限（の音）のこの3つの作品で聴衆は暗い原型的な領域に引き込まれる。 
 ここに、簡素さはやがて信条箇条となり、欺瞞と偽りに取り返しがつかないほど浸ってしまった世界に対するある種の万能薬となる。 
 弦楽四重奏曲第11番は技巧的でなく、子供や道化（yurodivy 、Russian: юродивый)の無垢な純朴さで、衒学的な要素を排して，至高の解決に至っている…これは、ミケランジェロの詩による歌曲、レビャートキン大尉の4つの詩による歌曲の終曲を思い起こさせる。 
 （キリストへの愚かさ＝聖なる愚か者は、人から見れば愚者でも意図的に愚か振る舞うもので間違って弱々しいこころのようで、挑発的な、刺激する、意図的である行動することを意味する), 
 より厳格に成熟した作品は　このチェロ協奏曲第2番で―そこには複合的に発展するためのいわゆる単純性の法則があるーさらに純化されたユロディヴィ（的洞察）が融合し、構造化されて現れる。 
 総括すると弦楽器のための協奏曲は、個人の群集に対する抗議のドラマである・・ヴァイオリン協奏曲第2番はその怒りを爽快に表しているが、チェロ協奏曲第2番の終楽章、とりわけfffのクライマクスはヴァイオリン協奏曲第2番のカデンツァを示唆している。」 
 （イアン・マクドナルド　The New Shostakovich 、P２６０~３の要約） 

なおMeyerは「スターリンの音楽的肖像などとされた」交響曲第10番第2楽章の主題について「旋律構成がムソルグスキーの“ボリスゴドノフ”の導入部に極めて似ており、興味深いことに、ショスタコーヴィチはこの主題をチェロ協奏曲第2番で変形した曲想［transformed context］中で再度使っている。」と指摘しています（ウイルソンA life Rememberedｐ３０２） 
http://kiyotaka-ishikawa-law.com/column/10.html﻿

Meer lezen (62 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-SDojaUhkrlc/UPVr9zLEY0I/AAAAAAAAAKM/kUBs9abq_qA/w426-h556/IMG_1056.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7497-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/shostakovich%20life/photos/107465447281069657152/albums/5721951551017390561/5721951552912409698</link><title>First he got interested in painting, through his aunt Tamara; later he taught himself to play piano, having got the basics from his pianist and composer father. When he finally got piano lessons - it was from one of the best - Heinrich Neuhaus; the story goes that upon hearing him play on audition Neuhaus said This man's a genius, a pupil he's been waiting for all his life. Sviatoslav Richter was highly admired by such as Glenn Gould, Arthur Rubinstein and Dmitri Shostakovich; Vladimir Horowitz said Of the Russian pianists, I like only one, Richter. 

See this documentary about him on his birthday 
Sviatoslav Richter - Documentary - The Enigma - vol. 1- 1/8 

Sviatoslav Teofilovich Richter (March 2 1915 – August 1, 1997) was a Soviet pianist well known for the depth of his interpretations, virtuoso technique, and vast repertoire. He is widely considered one of the greatest pianists of the 20th century. 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sviatoslav_Richter﻿

Meer lezen (14 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7497_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-0ki_AKMBG9A/T2h0nwVWxGI/AAAAAAAAiSo/zaF_XajXU9E/w426-h342/exercices-dadmiration-sviatoslav-richter-L-1.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>