<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:44:18" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/108038985259359575981/albums/6005929196325805585/6005929195883244146</link><title>The OPCW-UN joint mission confirmed that 92.5 per cent of Syria’s chemical weapons have been removed or destroyed. In addition, the majority of Syria’s chemical weapons storage and production sites are now reportedly closed. Read the press release here: http://ow.ly/w8aS8﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-V74YbFLti8M/U1lYyGrEqnI/AAAAAAAAUDg/L5Fe2w_mPrI/s426/5lMpo.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/105986449921389641226/albums/5922359974250814673/5922359972706843458</link><title>Syria’s chemical weapons now subject of tense UN negotiations, ‘severe consequences’ for non-compliance at issue http://natpo.st/15jxltx﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-DD4SNnDvOm8/UjBzBGUu-0I/AAAAAAABCl4/7AAIE-Tp074/w426-h319/37DWI.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5988164418578822705/5988164421663287842</link><title>Will Syria’s Chemical Weapons Arsenal Be Eliminated? http://b4in.org/a0jr 

By Lt. Col. (res.) Dr. Dany Shoham 

Efforts to dismantle Syria’s chemical weapons capability are running months behind schedule because the Syrian president is playing games with international inspectors. 

Moreover, it is far from clear that the 1,300 tons of chemical warfare agents and precursor chemicals declared by Assad when he signed the Chemical Weapons Convention represent the full amount he possesses. Furthermore, even if Assad abides by the commitment to completely jettison his chemical weapons, Syria’s equally dangerous biological weapon stocks will remain. 

Despite the transfer, Syria has demonstrated deep ambivalence, if not subterfuge, regarding its commitment to comply with UN and OPCW demands to destroy its chemical weapons arsenal and infrastructure. 

According to the UN-OPCW timetable, the removal of chemical weapons from Syria is now running approximately two months behind schedule. Damascus did request a reformulated timetable on February 21 to complete the export, but it is apparent that the June 30 deadline will not be met. 

More http://b4in.org/a0jr﻿

Meer lezen (24 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ROmhlW9Y8yQ/Uxo70JnfaiI/AAAAAAAAZrg/4CDkTnDNufI/w426-h321/chem%2Bweapons.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/108404515213153345305/albums/5931770433380340209/5931770440245852258</link><title>UN experts start work on eliminating Syria chemical weapons 

+AFP The United Nations said Sunday that a team of international experts had begun the process of destroying Syria's chemical weapons on Sunday. 

The group consists of international inspectors from the Netherlands-based watchdog Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons along with a U.N. team. 

Under their supervision, "Syrian personnel used cutting torches and angle grinders to destroy or disable a range of items," said Eri Kaneko, associate spokeswoman for U.N. Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon's office. 

This included missile warheads, aerial bombs and mixing and filling equipment. The process will continue in the coming days," she added. 
*Read more: http://www.theaustralian.com.au/in-depth/middle-east-in-turmoil/un-experts-start-work-on-eliminating-syria-chemical-weapons/story-fn7ycml4-1226733983866* 

Photo: U.N. vehicles transporting a team of chemical weapons experts return to their hotel in Damascus on Oct. 6. (Khaled Al-Hariri / Reuters)﻿

Meer lezen (21 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2H7eFzH1RJM/UlHhyZwEOGI/AAAAAAABPEc/C6_gJJ2DOn0/w426-h287/Syria.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/104158924758626757436/albums/5941331524828863617/5941331529727452066</link><title>Syria’s chemical weapons facilities are “inoperable,” the Joint Mission of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons (OPCW) and the UN overseeing the destruction of the country’s weapons programme confirmed on Thursday. No further inspection activities are currently planned. 

 Get the full story from United Nations News Centre: http://j.mp/1aJnvkL﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uL0hvKW44c0/UnPZjDo7o6I/AAAAAAAAatc/C15eMIS5zeo/w426-h284/Syria%2Bupdate.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5978134124045613041/5978134123399333650</link><title>Two ships loaded Syria’s chemical weapons to be buried off Crete; Greeks protest http://b4in.org/p0P6 

More than one thousand of chemical agents, Syria’s chemical weapons arsenal, are ready to be destroyed in international waters international waters in the Mediterranean Sea between Greece, Malta and Italy. The complex international process of decommissioning the hazardous chemical weapons sarin, mustard gas and sulphur organized by the Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons (OPCW). 

The first stage of destroying Syria’s chemical weapons has reportedly already begun with the aid of Norway, Denmark, Russia, China, Finland, UK and USA, among others. 

According to UK daily Telegraph, 

The first batch of the country’s chemicals safely loaded aboard a Danish cargo ship in the northwest Syrian port of Lattakia. 

The chemicals at 12 sites across Syria, two of which are in the middle of battlefields, and transporting them to the port. This is the responsibility of the Syrian army, which will be guarded en route by armoured trucks provided by Russia. 

More http://b4in.org/p0P6﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_06_thumb.png">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ttXs8D0GCPA/UvaZT8zbxxI/AAAAAAAAP6g/XxSjaM9U4eQ/w426-h237/Two%2Bships.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/100507759347915471937/albums/5818207347983543345/5818207352772168770</link><title>WORLD WARNS SYRIA AGAINST CHEMICAL WEAPONS ARMAMENT 

International leaders have warned Syria against employing chemical weapons in its ongoing civil war, after US satellite imagery showed regime forces moving chemical weapons into strategic positions in preparation for use. While Syrian leaders have denied any intentions towards chemical warfare, Israel has already asked Jordan for permission to bomb the weapon sites. 

Read world reactions: http://www.jspace.com/news/articles/international-warnings-against-syrian-chemical-weapons-armament/11922 

#ChemicalWeapons   #Syria   #Israel   #MiddleEast  ﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-lTGH8z02z9Q/UL5swtuNDEI/AAAAAAAAHeg/780Z0cw6fSs/w426-h312/Chemical-Weapons-Syria.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/113133992237143816650/albums/5938613612018621297/5938613617307302098</link><title>Norway rules out destroying Syrian chemical weapons on its soil 

Norway said it had to reject a request from the United States, stressing that the country doesn’t have the capabilities to do it by the given deadlines. 
Read more: http://voiceofrussia.com/news/2013_10_25/Norway-rules-out-destroying-Syrian-chemical-arms-on-its-soil-5532/ #US #Norway #Syria﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-uSx4K3z3NFM/Umoxnu3mONI/AAAAAAAAbiY/S5u18i3LBSw/w426-h248/7chim_oruzh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/107770026813114852164/albums/5819277844121743745/5819277846746628258?authkey=CPWg0Yq7rKGPDQ</link><title>Syria ‘has loaded chemical weapons into bombs’ 
ENGLISH 
the telegraph 

The Syrian regime has loaded the precursor chemicals for the nerve gas sarin into aerial bombs, according to a report from the United States. 

NBC News quoted an unnamed US official as saying there was evidence that the bombs, loaded with the chemical weapon, could be dropped on the Syrian people from fighter planes once president Basah al-Assad gives the order. 

If it proves to be true, the move would be a dramatic escalation in the conflict in Syria, which could lead to US involvement. 

Earlier this week, US officials said the regime had begun mixing the chemicals to make the deadly sarin gas. 

Sarin, used in two terrorist attacks in Japan in the 1990s, is a man-made nerve agent which can cause convulsions, respiratory failure and death. 

The Syrian regime has never overtly admitted having chemical weapons, though it is believed by western analysts to have the biggest stocks in the Middle East. It has also denied it would ever use chemical weapons against its own people. 

The official told NBC News that the chemicals had now been put into bombs, although the bombs had not been loaded onto planes and Mr Assad had not ordered them to be used. 

Hillary Clinton, the US secretary of state, has reiterated that Mr Assad would be crossing "a red line" if he used chemical weapons against his people.﻿

Meer lezen (31 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-V1599Olg7So/UMI6XqiiAKI/AAAAAAAAFEw/Z4e3u1eKFME/s426/NRBPZBVFBT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7498-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/syria%20chemical%20weapons/photos/117150671992820587865/albums/5918265980394206513/5918265983231737282?authkey=CLHJr-yFm8ePywE</link><title>Putin challenges US, says Syria chemical weapons use claim 'utter nonsense' 
http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/middle-east/Putin-challenges-US-says-Syria-chemical-weapons-use-claim-utter-nonsense/articleshow/22187016.cms?utm_source=facebook.com&amp;utm_medium=referral﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7498_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-B2CpfCnwNMg/UiHnjjDOPcI/AAAAAAABE8c/-RQcMcD3qBI/w426-h385/22187131.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>