<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:48:58" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/103151090528528008426/albums/6005818420228878497/6005818425714236530</link><title>Gold price gains for third day on sustained buying, global cues 

http://zeenews.india.com/business/bullion/bullion-news/gold-price-gains-for-third-day-on-sustained-buying-global-cues_98337.html 

Continuing its rising streak for the third day, gold gained Rs 150 to Rs 30,590 per ten grams in the national capital Thursday.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4VrAHUrOTR4/U1j0CboxXHI/AAAAAAAAAy0/xSJiEiOD3eU/w426-h313/gold-Delhi-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/101521018647628840624/albums/6006243756919409873/6006243760509170562</link><title>The Price of One Gram of Gold on Akshaya Tritiya will get you a Gold Plated Silver Necklace from Us! 
Visit us &amp; Check out our Fabulous Akshaya Tritiya Offer! http://goo.gl/6n1sti﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-x3oRqLN2VWo/U1p24LOOM4I/AAAAAAAAA84/C0XDhbRD02k/s426/fb2_sat.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/110031261362754119981/albums/5698631567500567985/5698631481164781378</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-hLW9ApU92SE/TxWbI7SvV0I/AAAAAAAAABA/eiGWCwkhnxQ/s426/goldpriceorguklogo-400x400.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/108992007110283236440/albums/5750468042074855569/5750468041541301442</link><title>Gold price reached its record low since 1999. 

The fall in gold prices that took place in recent months was the most prolonged in the XXI century, Bloomberg reports. The prices for gold declined for the fourth consecutive month reaching its lowest level since 1999 though in early 2012 the troy ounce of gold edged 0.7 pct. During the Asian trades of May 29 gold fell 0.6 pct to $1573 per ounce. In general, during the whole month of May the price was down 5.5 pct. This fall in prices on gold results mainly from the strengthening of the dollar, while the fundamental factors point at the growth of prices. In April the most of world’s central banks including those of Turkey, Ukraine, Mexico and Kazakhstan expanded their gold reserves. Moreover, the consumption of gold in China increases. According to various estimates, in 2011 the total volume of gold consumption varied from 761 to 769 tons. This year this figure will increase making China the leader among world’s biggest gold consumer and leaving behind the former leader – India that has been occupying this position in recent years. Gold is used by investors on world markets as the safe place for investing money in case of emergency. At the same time the growth of dollar prevents the growth of prices for gold. For the last 10 years the price on this precious metal increased more than 5 times reaching its record in 2011 when the price for gold was $1889 per ounce.﻿

Meer lezen (19 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-i8d4Qc56gbo/T83EN2xONMI/AAAAAAAABHo/SwM4i-C0lNU/s426/292221_456611187700892_352750098_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/108139973665377010876/albums/5818042547042942561/5818042549780827554</link><title>The Gold Price DIPS overnight as LOW as £1,056 per Troy Ounce presenting a great buying opportunity for GOLD... 

Take advantage today with our complete range of gold bars &amp; coins ideal for investment: http://www.bullionbypost.co.uk/ 

Also, track the live gold price updated EVERY 5 SECONDS:http://www.bullionbypost.co.uk/gold-price/live-gold-price/﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-uQhR2T34tZ0/UL3W36vLTaI/AAAAAAAAARE/D1mMBevTw3E/w426-h275/goldprice041212.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/106367437462193297169/albums/5973045370039708273/5973045370603968978</link><title>The Hows And Whys Of Gold Price Manipulation http://b4in.org/r0C3 

The deregulation of the financial system during the Clinton and George W. Bush regimes had the predictable result: financial concentration and reckless behavior. A handful of banks grew so large that financial authorities declared them “too big to fail.” Removed from market discipline, the banks became wards of the government requiring massive creation of new money by the Federal Reserve in order to support through the policy of Quantitative Easing the prices of financial instruments on the banks’ balance sheets and in order to finance at low interest rates trillion dollar federal budget deficits associated with the long recession caused by the financial crisis. 

The Fed’s policy of monetizing one trillion dollars of bonds annually put pressure on the US dollar, the value of which declined in terms of gold. When gold hit $1,900 per ounce in 2011, the Federal Reserve realized that $2,000 per ounce could have a psychological impact that would spread into the dollar’s exchange rate with other currencies, resulting in a run on the dollar as both foreign and domestic holders sold dollars to avoid the fall in value. Once this realization hit, the manipulation of the gold price moved beyond central bank leasing of gold to bullion dealers in order to create an artificial market supply to absorb demand that otherwise would have pushed gold prices higher. 

The manipulation consists of the Fed using bullion banks as its agents to sell naked gold shorts in the New York Comex futures market. Short selling drives down the gold price, triggers stop-loss orders and margin calls, and scares participants out of the gold trusts. 

More http://b4in.org/r0C3﻿

Meer lezen (29 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SXep_8_xygk/UuSFHjYkGdI/AAAAAAAALw8/emQSYGW8dYo/w426-h287/Uncle_sam_gold.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/114085939943834183247/albums/5745055185918138465/5745055186855334882</link><title>Gold Price vs National Debt Outstanding. 
Pretty revealing. Don't forget we have another debt-limit adjustment coming. The numbers are normalized so that $16 trillion of debt corresponds to a $1600 gold price.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_07_thumb.png">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-1OH3WPO9-t8/T7qJQPuHE-I/AAAAAAAAFw0/_P9bXeuEo6c/w426-h311/image001.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/105318168136154936472/albums/5785018381129840689/5785018385589183570</link><title>Today Gold Price...﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MU2_nGsAtCw/UEiDkkQlpFI/AAAAAAAAAis/inS2Vz6VBjA/w426-h266/419228_270703663039726_2054339607_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/112429100544710201595/albums/5721388458913052897/5721388462437742002</link><title>Check out our spot gold price gadget. It takes the gold price from all 3 major spot gold price providers and averages the price. Add it to your website using the link below! 

http://www.gmodules.com/ig/creator?synd=open&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fhosting.gmodules.com%2Fig%2Fgadgets%2Ffile%2F110627433649265440058%2Fspot-gold-price.xml&amp;lang=en﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_09_thumb.png">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ILka3Pll7Wo/T2Z0fk2etbI/AAAAAAAAABk/IqYTAAb3Y24/w426-h519/spot-gold-price-gadget.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7499-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/gold%20price/photos/105318168136154936472/albums/5773537752774455441/5773537759400581810</link><title>Gold price are hiking continuously and this prompts so many customer to buy silver jewelry but the majority still prefers gold jewelry because of the sheer luxurious look and feel of it.Trends have shown that a consumer purchasing gold prefers to spend more on a select few high quality pieces of gold jewelry and is willing to pay more for a higher karat gold knowing that the piece will last a lifetime.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7499_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-_q40FfDTuWQ/UB-6AK5gWrI/AAAAAAAAASU/NHLhNz808Cc/w426-h379/products1944_zoom.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>