<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 20:07:59" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/103121866597698777729/albums/5961762255652990129/5961762251625765058</link><title>I'm glad I spent past Saturday improving the thermal isolation of my roof, the sun is at its maximum radiation and it's currently 35 °C outside.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-VElkKPJt2ws/UrxvLlt8mMI/AAAAAAAAT1w/SnmMx5jGhtM/w426-h320/2013-12-26</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/116553784631121936574/albums/5994458953628347969/5994458948537369458?sqi=105024297797991337469&amp;sqsi=3c702c01-6a14-48f1-aa7a-baaf65c7b52e</link><title>singing to myself on the a roof with a smile on my face 

The wind blows heavey on the mountain tonight. 
Not a voice to be heard. 
A kingdom of isolation, 
and it looks like I'm next in line. 
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside 
Couldn't keep it in; 
Heaven knows I've tried 

Don't let them in, 
don't let them see 
Be the good girl you always have to be 
Conceal, don't feel, 
don't let them know 
Well now they know 

Let it blow, let it blow 
Can't hold it back anymore 

Let it blow, let it blow 
Turn away and slam the door 
I don't care 
what they're going to say 
Let the wind rage on. 
The breeze never bothered me anyway.﻿

Meer lezen (22 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-jbV6BdN5yTo/UzCYp1g7Q3I/AAAAAAAAb4U/uY_-cvxl43I/w426-h425/14%2B-%2B1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/107064925008642748853/albums/5959574198188561025/5959574204708623618</link><title>The Jespersen residence sits in virtual isolation atop Emigration Canyon. With its oversize sliding glass doors, flat roof, and meticulous attention to geometric principles, the recently completed home creates a haven in the mountain wilderness. 

http://www.dwell.com/house-tours/slideshow/modern-awakening﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-b7QU-SMDPSk/UrSpKfw9FQI/AAAAAAAAEKI/SU6-nha2VK0/w426-h527/jespersen-exterior-portrait.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/118130936224091043305/albums/6008860028026014497/6008860031812044898</link><title>Workers investigating the radiological release in the underground Waste Isolation Pilot Plant (WIPP) in New Mexico have found no evidence of a roof collapse but could not explain the discovery of damage to several bags of backfill. 

http://www.world-nuclear-news.org/RS-Mystery-of-WIPP-release-deepens-0205144.html﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_33hPoQdyyQ/U2PCXNUzCGI/AAAAAAAAA3g/ldo_3TXAPmU/w426-h240/WIPP%2BMgO%2Bbag%2B460.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/114401975100913640964/albums/5822847205031020017/5822847207630751602?authkey=CIb4wYCbo5eD9wE</link><title>Chevrolet unveiled the all-new 2014 Silverado 1500 full-size pickup. New from hood to hitch, Chevy Silverado is engineered to be the strongest, smartest, and most capable Silverado ever. 

The new Silverado builds on Chevrolet's 95 years of truck heritage, while raising the bar for full-size pickups. Among the many updates for 2014 are a new trio of powerful, efficient EcoTec3 engines; a stronger, quieter, more comfortable cab; revised steering, suspension and brakes; ingenious solutions for managing cargo in the bed and true truck capability for towing and hauling. 

"Our customers rely on their trucks to meet the day-to-day challenges of earning a living, running a business and taking care of their families," said Mark Reuss, president, GM North America. "Chevrolet is committed to giving truck customers the most-refined, best-engineered pickups in the market." 

The 2014 Silverado will become part of Chevrolet's three-truck portfolio, designed to let customers select the right truck for their needs. It joins the Chevrolet Silverado 2500 and 3500 HD pickups, the ultimate tools for towing and hauling, which were new for the 2011 model year. Chevrolet is also developing an all-new Colorado midsize pickup, which will offer proven truck capability in a space- and fuel-efficient package. 

Every detail of the 2014 Chevrolet Silverado 1500 was designed and engineered to meet the exacting requirements of full-size truck customers and to strengthen Chevrolet's reputation for building the most dependable, longest-lasting full-size trucks - trucks with the lowest overall cost of ownership. 

"Don't let the work boots fool you. Truck customers are among the most discerning and demanding in the business," said Jeff Luke, executive chief engineer for full-size and midsize trucks. 

"The designers and engineers who created the new Silverado share this passion for trucks. They have built this truck - and tested it to the extremes - to give customers the right tools for the tough jobs, and they have created dozens of solutions to the challenges truck customers encounter every day." 

For 2014, Chevrolet Silverado 1500 is designed and engineered to deliver the capability - without compromise - that customers have come to expect from Chevrolet pickups. 

Chevrolet Silverado's exterior design blends strong Chevy truck heritage with a refined, modern aesthetic. The new design is more muscular, more functional and more aerodynamic. A twin-port grille, full-width bumper and dual power dome hood create a strong presence, which is carried through in sculpted body sides and fender flares. 

The new Silverado design is about much more than just looks, however. The new front end is engineered to improve sealing for more efficient cooling, while the roof and tailgate spoiler were shaped in the wind tunnel to smooth airflow over the truck for reduced drag. New inlaid doors, which fit into recesses in the bodyside, reduce wind noise for a quieter cab. 

Under the hood, the 2014 Silverado 1500 features a family of three all-new EcoTec3 engines, a V-6 and two V-8s, engineered specifically for use in full-size trucks. All three engines incorporate direct fuel injection, cylinder deactivation and continuously variable valve timing, a combination of advanced technologies not found in other competitors' trucks. All three switch seamlessly to four-cylinder operation to improve efficiency during light load driving and all three are engineered provide more power, more torque and better efficiency than the previous versions. 

The engine family includes a new 4.3L V-6 that will have ample torque to power a crew cab pickup and tow a substantial trailer, as well as a new 5.3L V-8 designed for more power, more torque and better efficiency than the current version, which is currently the V-8 fuel economy leader. A new 6.2L V-8 is engineered to be the most capable engine in any light-duty pickup. 

SAE certified horsepower and torque ratings and EPA fuel economy estimates for the new Chevrolet Silverado will be final and available beginning early next year. 

The all-new interiors of the 2014 Silverado 1500 reflect the same focus on form and function. The upright instrument panel, six-gauge instrument cluster and multiple storage options are tailored specifically to the needs of truck customers. Controls are functional, logically placed and easy to operate with work gloves on. Rear doors on crew cabs are larger, for easier entry and exit, and rear doors on extended cab models are now hinged at the front for easier access, especially in tight spots. 

The new Chevrolet MyLink provides easy-to-use connectivity for the job site or the family vacation, with natural voice recognition and enough ports and power outlets to support multiple devices. 

The new truck cab is stronger, with nearly two-thirds of the structure made from high-strength steel for a confident feel and improved safety. Similarly, the main rails and key cross members of the updated frame are high-strength steel with major elements hydroformed for reduced mass and improved strength. 

New shear-style body mounts tune out both up-and-down and side-to-side movement for a quieter, more comfortable ride. Extended- and crew-cab models have a third set of hydraulic body mounts to further isolate the cabs. Combined with numerous other acoustic and NVH (noise vibration and harshness) enhancements, the intended result is a solid, refined feel with no loss in traditional truck capability. 

The pickup box also benefits from this focus on providing Chevrolet Silverado customers with the right tools for the job. The box is made from roll-formed steel for increased strength and reduced mass, compared with the stamped beds used by major competitors, and it features a range of smart solutions for everyday life. 

Silverado's CornerStep bumper, combined with handholds built into the new box rail protectors, makes it easier to access the box. The bed is also available with new upper tie-down hooks, under-rail light-emitting diode lighting, and an EZ Lift and Lower tailgate. 

For the first time, Silverado 1500 crew cabs will be available with a longer 6'6" foot box, in addition to the previous 5'8" box, enabling customers to carry more cargo while still being able to park in many garages. 

The chassis of the 2014 Chevrolet Silverado includes a number of customer-focused updates. A revised front and rear suspension and wider wheels provide a more comfortable ride and more confident handling. Electric power steering improves steering feel and reduces fuel consumption. New four-wheel-disc brakes with Duralife ™ rotors improve brake feel and extend rotor life. 

Silverado will be available with segment-exclusive safety features such as Forward Collision Alert, Lane Departure Warning with an Active Safety Seat, and Front and Rear Park Assist. StabiliTrak with Trailer Sway Control and Hill Start Assist are standard on all Silverados. 

"We have made significant upgrades in the key areas of the new Chevrolet Silverado, and improved almost every detail of the truck," said Luke. "We think both Chevrolet loyalists and competitive shoppers are going to find a lot to love about the new Silverado, beginning with the very first time they sit behind the wheel." 

Engineered and validated for demanding customers 
Truck customers are among the most discerning and demanding in the business. They know trucks inside out - many have owned trucks for decades. They work their trucks hard, under conditions that would shock many car owners. They have tough tasks to do, and they expect their trucks to do them, without complaint. And they expect their trucks to endure - the average age of a full-size pickup is now more than 10.4 years. 

The team that designed the new Silverado went to extremes to design a new truck that would exceed the demands of these customers. 

For example, GM's new full-size trucks will undergo more than 6 million miles of durability testing in the torture chambers at the Milford Proving Ground, over the deserts and mountains of Nevada and across the frozen flats of Kapuskasing, Ontario. That's equivalent to 240 trips around the earth. In addition, the trucks will accumulate more than 7 million real-world miles during final testing, bringing total test miles to more than 13 million. 

The increased power, torque and efficiency of the new EcoTec3 engine family resulted from an unprecedented level of computer analysis, including extensive computational flow dynamics, to optimize the burning of air and fuel in the cylinders. More than 10 million of hours of computational analysis went into the engine program. More than 6 million hours - about 685 years' worth - of analysis went into the advanced combustion system alone. 

Even the basics, like the new inlaid doors, were tested to the extreme, with the doors undergoing nearly 150 truck lives' worth of testing. 

The 2014 Silverado 1500 crew cab will start production in the second quarter of 2013, with other cab styles following later in the year. 

A modern interpretation of iconic Chevrolet design 
For the 2014 Chevrolet Silverado, designers sought to strike the ideal balance between Chevrolet's deep heritage in full-size pickups and a more modern, refined aesthetic. They also sought to give the new Silverado a more dramatic presence, with a heightened stance and more structural, muscular sheet metal, while also improving aerodynamics to make the new Silverado quieter and more efficient. 

"Creating the new Silverado while maintaining its heritage was a challenge, but I am confident that we struck the right balance," said Kevin O'Donnell, manager for the Chevrolet Silverado exterior design. "The 2104 Silverado will definitely stand out, in terms of both appearance and improved aerodynamic performance." 

The classic two-port Chevrolet truck grille, restyled headlamps and one-piece bumper wrap from fender to fender, giving the truck a wider, stronger stance. The grille of the new Silverado is designed to admit the just right amount of air, and the front is carefully sealed to provide efficient cooling with minimal aerodynamic drag. 

A modern interpretation of Chevrolet vertically stacked headlamps includes projector beam lamps on LTZ models. A new hood with twin power domes not only enhances visual presence, but it guides air over the windshield wipers for reduced wind noise. 

The more aggressive design continues down the body, with sculpted body sides and prominent fender flares. Available wheel well liners provide a more finished look. Wheels range from 17 to 20 inches in diameter and all are a half-inch wider than before, for reduced tire flex and enhanced cornering and steering. Twenty-two-inch wheels will be available as Chevrolet accessories. 

Special attention was paid to airflow over the truck, to improve efficiency and reduce wind noise. Most notable are the inlaid doors, which fit into body sides rather than wrapping over the roof. When combined with new triple door seals, the inlaid doors reduce wind noise and turbulence, helping quiet the cab. 

Other aerodynamic details include new cab-to-box seals, shields on the chassis to smooth under-vehicle air flow, and deflectors to guide air around the rear tires. Both the roof and the top of the tailgate were precisely shaped to help manage airflow over the back of the pickup. 

Also for 2014, rear doors on crew cab models are larger. The B-pillars were moved forward, the rear seat redesigned and the front seatbacks made thinner, adding about two inches to rear legroom and increasing the ease of entry and exit without adding length to the vehicle. On extended cab Silverados, the rear doors now hinge at the front, from the B-pillar, for easier access in parking lot and other tight spots. 

Three all-new EcoTec3 engines 
The heart of any truck is under its hood and the 2014 Chevy Silverado 1500 offers three new EcoTec3 engines developed specifically for the demands of truck duty cycles. All feature a trio of state-of-the-art technologies - direct injection, cylinder deactivation and continuously variable valve timing - that optimize power, torque and efficiency across a broad range of operating conditions. 

The new trio of engines is designed to match the needs of truck customers, and to provide more horsepower, more torque and better fuel economy than previous Silverado engines. 

All three engines feature an advanced combustion system for more efficiently turning fuel into work and all three are designed to seamlessly switch to four-cylinder mode to improve efficiency during light-load driving. 

"We believe these engines are the most technologically advanced engines ever offered in light-duty pickups, and they are specifically designed for the way customers use trucks in the real world," said Jordan Lee, Small Block chief engineer and program manager. 

"EcoTec3 engines offer technology no other truck maker can match, and we offer it in every one of our engines, for every one of our customers," said Lee. "It is not an extra cost feature. You get our best and most advanced technology regardless of trim level." 

To provide the dependability and low cost of ownership that truck customers count on, all three engines feature a work-tested, race-proven overhead valve design that is light and compact, and has inherently low friction for improved fuel efficiency. All three feature aluminum blocks and heads for lower weight. (For more details, see the accompanying EcoTec3 Engines release.) 

The new engine family includes: 
A new standard 4.3L V-6. Its large displacement delivers the torque to power a crew cab and pull a substantial trailer, yet it can seamlessly shift into four-cylinder mode under light loads for improved efficiency. 
A new 5.3L V-8. It is engineered to provide more horsepower, more torque and better fuel economy that the current 5.3L V-8, making it an excellent choice for mainstream customers. 

A new 6.2L V-8. It is engineered to be the most capable engine in any light-duty pickup. Like the other two engines in the family, it can seamlessly switch to four-cylinder mode under light load conditions for improved efficiency in daily driving. 

The 2014 Silverado 1500 is engineered to further improve efficiency by enabling the engines to operate in four-cylinder mode more of the time. For example, transmission and exhaust mounts tune out vibration that can occur when the engines are in four-cylinder mode, and an active exhaust system fine tunes backpressure and the exhaust note for smoother, quieter operation. Models with the 6.2L V-8 feature active noise cancellation to further quiet the cabin during four-cylinder mode. 

All three engines feature a six-speed automatic transmission with gear ratios and shift schedules optimized for performance and efficiency. The transmissions feature Auto Grade Braking, which downshifts on downgrades to help reduce brake wear. Due to the added torque of the new V-8 engines, new 9.5- or 9.76-inch rear axles are used. 

"Not only did we work to improve the horsepower, torque and EPA fuel economy estimates of all three EcoTec3 engines, but we worked hard to improve real-world efficiency as well, especially when towing and hauling," said Lee. "We look forward to journalists and other third parties having the opportunity to test our trucks head-to-head with the competition in real world conditions." 

More comfortable, more functional interior 
With crew cabs now accounting for more than two-thirds of light-duty sales industry-wide, pickups are increasingly becoming multi-purpose tools, used to run a business or earn a living during the day and transporting friends and family during the time off. To accommodate those needs Chevrolet Silverado designers sought to craft an interior that was quieter, roomier, more comfortable and more functional, without making it look like the interior of a car or crossover. 

The result: an all new interior that sets a benchmarks for full-size trucks. 
"Changes to the exterior of the 2014 Silverado can be described as evolutionary, but the updates to the interior are dramatic," said Helen Emsley, Silverado design director. "The meticulous attention to detail and the steps we took to ensure optimal driver and passenger comfort and convenience, are reflected in the fact that the new interiors rated off the charts in customer clinics." 

The upright instrument panel with its six-gauge instrument cluster is tailored specifically to the needs of truck customers, and most models also include a 4.2-inch color Driver Information Center displaying vehicle and infotainment data. 

Controls were located with the use of reach curves, and important controls were place closest to the driver and grouped functionally. Knobs, buttons and interfaces are large, easy-to-read and easy to operate, even with gloves on. 

For example, Chevrolet Silverado retained the traditional column shifter, with tap-up/tap-down and tow-haul functions integrated into the lever, because it clears space in the console and is easy to operate, even with heavy work gloves. Similarly, the available integrated trailer brake control is mounted high and to the left of the steering wheel, where the driver can more naturally reach for it. 

The result is a simple, well designed instrument panel - one in keeping with the ways customers use their full-size trucks. 

Silverado's available MyLink infotainment system is designed to be easy-to-use, highly customizable and capable of linking up to 10 devices. It features natural language voice recognition that allows customers to place calls, enter destinations, browse media, play music and control other functions simply by telling the vehicle what to do. There are no key phrases to remember and no need to look at a screen. 

MyLink also can be operated via large, clearly labeled knobs, through integrated steering wheel controls, or through the touch screen on models with the eight-inch screen. 

The system also can store up to 60 favorites including radio stations (AM/FM/XM), contacts, destinations, music and other media - a convenient feature for small businesses or owners who travel frequently. 

All models also have extensive interior storage, tailored to the way customers use their trucks. Multiple USB ports, along with 12-volt and110-volt power outlets, help connect multiple devices. 

A new high-wear seat cloth that is more durable and easier to clean is available and the front seats have more durable dual-density foam for improved comfort and longer life. 

The goal, in each case, was to create a level of comfort and convenience usually associated with upscale cars, but tailored to the way customers use actually use their trucks. 

Strengthened cabs and frames 
Truck customers have the highest expectations when it comes to durability and capability - they need to know that one of the most important tools in their toolbox is going to withstand the daily punishment of their work and their active lifestyles. And they expect their trucks to last - the average truck on the road is now more than 10.4 years old. 

To ensure that the new Silverado is up to the challenge, key elements of the updated frame, including the main rails and major cross members, are made from high-strength steel and hydroforming is used to improve strength and reduce mass of the front of the frame. 

The cab structures are all new, and incorporate high strength steel in the A-pillars, B-pillars, roof rails and rocker panels. Ultra-high-strength steel is used in areas of the rocker panels and underbody in anticipation of new shallow-offset crash tests. In all, about two-thirds of the cab structure is made from high-strength steels, for a quieter ride, a more confident feel and enhanced performance on new, tougher government and industry crash tests. 

The mounts that isolate the cab from frame have a major impact on both noise and vibration in the passenger compartment. All Silverado models now have shear-style mounts, which isolate both up-and-down and side-to-side movements, and extended- and crew-cab models have additional hydraulic mounts to provide further isolation. The result is a truck that feels much quieter, more refined and more solid than previous models. 

The 2014 Chevrolet Silverado 1500 also features a roll-formed steel pickup box, which is lighter, stronger and more durable than traditional stamped steel boxes used by major competitors. 

The use of high-strength steels and other lighter materials such as aluminum hoods, engine blocks and suspension helped offset the mass of new features such as stronger cabs, wider wheels, a larger battery and larger rear axles for V-8 Silverados. The 2014 Silverado continues to be lighter than comparable models from a key competitor. 

More confident ride, handling and braking 
The suspension, steering and brakes of the 2014 Silverado 1500 have been extensively updated to for a quieter, more refined ride and confident handling and braking. 

The coil-over-shock front suspension features aluminum upper and lower control arms on many models that are both lighter and stiffer than previous components, along with front springs are up to 30 percent stiffer than those on current models, for more confident handling. 

The rear suspension continues to use two-stage multi-leaf springs, for an optimal balance between a smooth ride and load carrying capability. The spring bushings have been revised for an improved ride, and both front and rear shocks feature a twin-tube design with new valving to improve damping at low speeds, for a smoother, more controlled ride. Z71 models use monotube Rancho shocks for enhanced off-road capability. 

The 2014 Silverado 1500 features new all-electric variable-assist power steering, which improves overall vehicle handling and reduces steering effort at low speeds. Because there is no engine-driven pump, electric power steering also reduces fuel consumption and eliminates the maintenance associated with hydraulic power steering. 

Four-wheel disc brakes with Duralife ™ rotors are standard. The rotors feature a hardened and strengthened surface that resists rusting, potentially doubling the life of the rotors and improving vehicle appearance. The brake pedal feel has been improved as well. 

Chevrolet Silverado also features Auto Grade Braking, which uses the engine and transmission controls to slow the vehicle on a long downgrade, helping maintain vehicle speed and reducing the need for the driver to use the brakes. 

Smarter pickup box 
For 2014, Silverado even makes the pickup box smarter. A CornerStep bumper and built-in hand grip pockets in the new bed rail protectors make it easier to step up into the bed and access items. 

The tailgate features an internal torsion bar that reduces the effort to raise and lower the tailgate, while a rotary damper allows for a controlled and more gradual lowering motion when opening the tailgate. A locking feature, two-tier loading and a box lamp are standard. Available features include upper tie-down hooks that make it easier to secure cargo, and LED lamps under the bed rails that make it easier to see items in the bed. 

The pickup box is available in three lengths - 5'8", 6'6"and 8'. Crew cab models add the 6'6" box as a new option in addition to the 5'8" box. Extended cab models come with 6'6" boxes and regular cab models are available with 6'6" or 8' boxes. Customers who tow will appreciate the four- and seven-pin trailer connector located in the rear bumper. 

Z71 for off-road capability 
For owners whose work or recreation takes them off road, Z71 returns as a unique model, available in LT and LTZ trim. For 2014, Z71 includes monotube Rancho shocks, front tow hooks, a transfer case skid plate and unique 18- or 20-inch all-terrain tires. The Z71 package also includes Hill Descent Control. Engaged by the driver using a button on the instrument panel, it uses the anti-lock braking system to enable a smooth and controlled descent in rough terrain. 

Z71 also includes unique 18-inch wheels (optional on LT, standard on LTZ) and unique interior trim, including brushed metal sill plates, a technical finish on interior trim pieces and Z71 graphics on the instrument cluster. 

Standard on Z71, and available on other Silverados, is a GM-exclusive automatic locking rear differential, which reacts in milliseconds in low-traction situations to improve safety and confidence on wet, snowy or muddy surfaces. 

Advanced safety features 
As mentioned above, the 2014 Silverado 1500 has an all-new cab, with approximately two-thirds of the structure built from high strength steels. It helps protect occupants in the event of a crash and enhances performance on new, tougher government and industry crash tests. 

Chevrolet Silverado continues to offer a comprehensive suite of standard safety technologies, including StabiliTrak electronic stability control with Trailer Sway Control and Hill Start Assist, head curtain side airbags with rollover protection and OnStar. 

New for 2014, Chevrolet Silverado will offer several segment-leading features. Lane Departure Warning alerts the driver if the vehicle starts to drift into another lane, via an audible warning or the available Safety Alert Seat. Also available is Forward Collision Alert, which monitors the space in front of the vehicle via a camera, and warns the drive if he or she is getting too close to the vehicle ahead. 

Other available safety features include front and rear park assist, a rear vision camera mounted in the tailgate and spotter mirrors that make it easier for drivers to see objects in the blinds spots.﻿

Meer lezen (503 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-4pQSvW6s4vI/UM7or0A0x3I/AAAAAAAARhE/A5ODGO-d5CE/w426-h304/Chevrolet.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/114401975100913640964/albums/5847058830823868145/5847058834417888226?authkey=CJa7_PqDiIfj_AE</link><title>Bentley establishes a new luxury performance sedan benchmark with the launch of the new Flying Spur. With its unrivalled blend of effortless drivability, exquisite luxury and craftsmanship, sculpted design and state-of-the-art technology, the new Bentley Flying Spur takes the worldwide success of its iconic predecessor further. Bentley's most powerful four-door model ever makes its global debut at the 2013 Geneva Motor Show. 

Bentley's styling team has developed an athletic design for the new Flying Spur that combines traditional Bentley styling cues with a sporting stance and contemporary details. Sharp feature lines complement muscular rear haunches, while LED day-time running lights, dipped headlights and taillights characterize the front and rear profiles. The interior designers have created a luxurious, spacious cabin that dresses advanced acoustic and electronic technologies in exquisite hand-crafted leather hides and wood veneers. 

Driver and passengers alike interface with the car and the outside world through touch-screen infotainment, mobile connectivity including Wi-Fi, a Rear Seat Entertainment suite and a new hand-held Touch Screen Remote which allows rear-cabin occupants to control an extensive range of features from the comfort of their seat. An eight-channel, eight-speaker audio system with Balanced Mode Radiators provides high quality sound clarity, with the 1100W Naim® for Bentley premium system available as an option. 

Powering the new Flying Spur is Bentley's renowned 6.0-litre, twin turbo W12 engine, coupled to a ZF eight-speed transmission. Developing 625 PS (616 bhp) and 800 Nm of torque, the new Flying Spur features more power than any other Bentley four-door in history. A 14 per cent improvement in the power-to-weight ratio over the outgoing model delivers a breath-taking 0-60 mph time of 4.3 seconds and a top-speed of 200 mph (322 km/h). In the modern Bentley tradition, power is delivered to the road via all-wheel drive with a 40:60 rear-biased torque split for a sure-footed, engaging drive in all road and weather conditions. 

Bentley Chairman and Chief Executive, Dr Wolfgang Schreiber, comments: "Bentley's new Flying Spur is the ultimate luxury performance sedan. Our engineers have worked tirelessly to ensure that the Flying Spur is the perfect combination of power, comfort, refinement and hand-crafted quality. Fitted with the very latest technology, the new Flying Spur is equipped both for business and relaxation whilst remaining a car to enjoy from behind the wheel." 

A SLEEK AND STRIKING EXTERIOR 
The styling of the new Bentley Flying Spur establishes a new design character for Bentley's performance sedan. An elegant direction is reflected by a lower, wider appearance with sharp lines and gently curvaceous surfaces. A lower roof line, deeply sculpted panels, precise feature lines and a muscular rear haunch give the Flying Spur a more aggressive stance and a powerfully dynamic profile. 

The front fenders feature a striking new wing vent complete with an elegant Bentley "B" motif. From here, an additional feature line forms a sharply defined edge running from the front wheel all the way to the rear bumper, underlining the shape's dynamic character. 

At the front of the car, a more upright chrome grille sits between the pairs of jewel-like LED headlamps. Emphasizing the lower, wider stance, the outer lamps are the larger of the two. Beneath the front grille, the lower intake is now full width with no vertical divisions, but instead with a chromed horizontal accent that completes the dramatic face of the new Flying Spur. 

At the rear, a longer and lower boot lid lends a more swept appearance to the side profile. Horizontal single ellipse LED tail lamps combine with a new interpretation of the Bentley "Horse Shoe" feature line, now running the full width of the car and encapsulating a graceful concave section. 

Beneath the elegant skin of the new Flying Spur, a wide range of materials is applied in an intelligent and efficient manner. Designed to improve overall body stiffness and refinement whilst meeting stringent crash performance targets and pedestrian protection legislation, the new body structure includes reinforcement to the B-posts, sills and front cross members together with deformable components in the floor pan for optimal load transfer. A deployable bonnet that includes both new reinforcement panels and deformation elements helps to improve pedestrian impact performance. 

The bonnet and front fenders are constructed in aluminum, with the fenders shaped using the aerospace-industry super forming technique, employing compressed air to shape heated sheets of alloy into the required form at over 500°C. Exceptionally clean lines with sharp radii and lighter-weight components are the result, giving the new Flying Spur an unmistakably Bentley front end with extremely taut shut lines. 

The new door structures are completely redesigned with fewer individual parts for improved quality and refinement. An optimization of the doors realized through efficient use of materials contributes to much improved door kinematics and feel. Meanwhile, further weight savings are achieved through the crafting of the bootlid in a polymer composite material that also integrates the main antennae for the car's electronic systems. 

The exterior design, manufacturing processes and carefully optimized materials selections combine to provide a bodyshell that is not only muscular and clean, with minimal shutlines, but also one that performs exceptionally well on the road. With a torsional stiffness of 36,500 Nm/degree, a 4% increase over the previous generation Flying Spur, the new bodyshell provides an extremely rigid platform for the chassis components and a stable foundation for NVH reduction. The sleek shape also has outstanding aerodynamic properties for a large sedan, with an overall drag coefficient of just 0.29 and ensuing benefits to emissions performance. 

Weight savings in the body structure and throughout the car mean that the new Flying Spur is 50 kg lighter than the first generation car, despite the additional refinement measures, enhanced technology specification and stronger structure. 

A CONTEMPORARY CABIN OF HAND-CRAFTED MATERIALS 
The sumptuous interior of the new Flying Spur includes 600 new parts, with only the sun visors, grab handles, armrests and some of the front console and controls carried over from the previous generation. Class-leading entertainment and information technologies are married with traditional hand-crafted materials and stunning contemporary design to create the ultimate high-luxury sedan cabin. 

Available in both four- and five-seat configurations, the new Flying Spur features redesigned front and rear seats trimmed in natural premium-quality leather. The new seats use a softer yet more durable hide unique to Bentley and available in twelve different colors. 

Careful use of different foam specifications and densities creates seats that are both supremely comfortable and supportive, with 14-way adjustment including memory and lumbar functions. Every occupant is offered seat heating as well as seat ventilation, while additional stowage sections are incorporated to the rear of the front seats. 

For the four-seat variant, the centre console sweeps from the front to the rear cabin and introduce an additional storage area together with a beautifully crafted stowage case, trimmed in veneer to match the car. 

The interior designers, together with the craftsmen and women of Bentley's renowned woodshop, have applied the finest wood veneers to finish the cabin of the new Flying Spur. Utilizing almost ten square metres of sustainably sourced natural wood per car, the Bentley Flying Spur features book-matched and mirror-polished veneer to the fascia panels, consoles, waist rails and picnic tables. To enhance the "wrap-around" feel of the forward cabin, the veneer of the dashboard meets that of the doors in a perfectly aligned curve, giving the impression of an unbroken arc of wood around the interior. Crafted entirely by hand, cured for 72 hours and clear-lacquered to enhance the natural beauty of the wood, a range of seven sophisticated veneers is available (two as standard - burr walnut or dark fiddle back eucalyptus). 

To complete the luxurious and opulent nature of the cabin, the roof lining and pillars are also trimmed in natural leather. Layers of supple foam are applied to all tactile surfaces beneath the hide, harmonizing the touch and feel of all areas of the cabin. Electrically-operated rear side blinds, fitted as standard, permit privacy for rear-seat passengers if desired. Customers may also specify an optional glass sunroof at no additional cost. Behind the central rear armrest, a nine-liter bottle cooler can be specified to keep drinks perfectly chilled. The interior designers also focused on improving interior stowage around the cabin, whilst including new electronic technologies discretely throughout the interior. 

CONNECTION TO THE OUTSIDE WORLD 
Complementing the hand-crafted interior, the Flying Spur is equipped with carefully selected state-of-the-art technology, for both the driver and passengers. Central infotainment is controlled through a high resolution 8" touch-screen interface, complete with Bentley's advanced satellite navigation system and Bluetooth connectivity, while infotainment features can be controlled by voice activation. 

An eight-channel, eight-speaker audio system featuring Balanced Mode Radiator technology for optimum sound clarity and frequency range can play music from an on-board hard drive, CDs, DVDs, SD cards and via an iPod. The Naim® for Bentley Premium Audio System, featuring redesigned separate subwoofers for improved bass extension and 1100 Watts of power, is available as an option for those wishing for the ultimate in-car audio experience. 

Rear seat passengers have access to an extensive array of infotainment technology. A new Touch Screen Remote (TSR), deployed from a housing in the rear console at the touch of a button, allows passengers to control a variety of different systems. From climate controls and seat heating and ventilation through to the satellite navigation and multimedia systems, the TSR means passengers can interface with the car from the comfort of their seat. 

Customers wishing to work on the move may order the new Flying Spur with the new Multi-Media Specification. Central to this is the Bentley Connectivity Unit (BCU) which allows portable devices, laptops and tablet computers to connect to the internet through the car's own Wi-Fi hotspot with an active SIM and includes 64 GB of internal storage capacity. Two 10" LCD screens are installed to the backs of the front seats, while top-loading multimedia players sit in pockets fitted beneath, allowing the user to load and enjoy video, photo and music content from DVDs, SD cards, USB devices including iPods and iPads, and HDMI devices. 

Each rear passenger can view separate content, or stream media from the BCU. A USB charging port keeps batteries fresh, and wired headphone ports complete the connections, allowing music and internet radio to be played directly through the BCU. Bentley wireless headphones complete the specification for the ultimate in rear-seat infotainment. 

DESIGNED FOR EXCEPTIONAL COMFORT 
Achieving class-leading comfort and refinement was a priority during the development of the new Flying Spur and the acoustic isolation of the cabin from external noise inputs was a particular focus. Bentley's development and use of lightweight acoustic under floor panels to minimize road noise continues, with aerodynamically optimized insulating sections applied to almost the entire under floor of the car. Side glazing and both front and rear screens are made in acoustic glass, featuring a specially developed interlayer that reduces noise transmission. An improved sealing system around the side glazing now features two individual sealing points to reduce wind noise to a minimum regardless of road speed. The redesigned doors are also fitted with additional insulation to the outer skin, reducing noise diffusion in to the cabin. Enlarged rear mufflers reduce exhaust noise by 12 dB at 3000 rev/min for enhanced passenger comfort. 

The heating and ventilation system is improved with the addition of a new Thermostatic Expansion Valve which drastically decreases the time taken to cool the cabin. An optional Climate Boost function features an enhanced blower system for improved cooling of the rear cabin. 

With comfort paramount for the new Flying Spur, a new 19" tire has been specifically developed, utilizing a 12% relative increase in sidewall height combined with greater vertical compliance to improve impact isolation. During development, 12 different tyre constructions were tested and refined to find the optimum balance between refinement and handling performance. 

EIGHT GEARS, SIX LITRES AND FOUR DRIVEN WHEELS 
As Bentley's most powerful engine, the 6.0-litre, twin turbocharged, 48-valve W12 is the natural choice to power the fastest ever Bentley four-door. Now delivering 625 PS (616 bhp) at 6,000 rev/min and a staggering 800 Nm (580 lb ft) of torque from only 2000 rev/min, the W12 has recently undergone a complete engine management system upgrade to the latest Bosch ME17 interface. Improved torque management, turbocharger control, drivability and emissions performance all result from the adoption and optimization of the new system, with a resulting improvement in low speed responsiveness. 

Coupled to the W12 is the very latest eight-speed, quick-shift automatic transmission from ZF. All Bentley models now feature this state-of-the-art gearbox. Delivering seamless and imperceptible shifts in under 200 milliseconds, the gearbox is not only designed to handle the mighty torque output of the W12 but also to ensure smooth and refined delivery of power to the wheels. An optimized set of gear ratios keeps the engine in its most efficient operating range under light loads and when cruising, contributing in an overall improvement in fuel consumption and CO2 emissions of more than 13 per cent over the outgoing model. The new Bentley Flying Spur delivers a combined cycle fuel economy of 19.2 mpg (14.7 liters/100 km), and CO2 emissions of 343 g/km - impressive figures for a 12-cylinder ultra-luxury, high performance sedan. 

The transmission feeds power to all four wheels via Bentley's renowned all-wheel drive system. With a standard torque split of 60 per cent to the rear wheels and 40 per cent to the front, but the ability to vary this division up to 85 per cent to the rear axle or 65 per cent to the front depending on available traction, the Flying Spur's drivetrain ensures optimal grip regardless of prevailing road or weather conditions. The assurance provided by such a sure-footed set-up means that the spirited driver can deploy all of the car's available power and torque in a controlled and dependable manner, in virtually any circumstances. 

A REFINED RIDE WITH DYNAMIC DELIVERY 
With outstanding ride comfort of vital importance, the independent computer-controlled air suspension of the new Flying Spur is redesigned to maximize impact absorption and isolation. Compared to the outgoing model, suspension spring rates are softened front and rear by 10 per cent and 13 per cent respectively, for improved ride comfort in the normal operating region. The rate of stiffness increase during harder cornering has been increased for improved control of heave, pitch and roll. Anti-roll bars are softened by 13 per cent and 15 per cent to improve single wheel impact absorption. Suspension lever bushes all-round are softened by at least 25 per cent for reduced road surface-induced noise and vibration. 

Working with the new springs, a damper hydraulic specification has been developed to maximize ride comfort. Working with a revised damper electronic control (CDC) strategy, this enables exceptional low speed ride performance while damping force increases significantly with speed, providing the optimum balance between body control and stability at all speeds. A four-position suspension control, with a widened range of settings, allows drivers to choose the level of damping to suit their preference. 

The power steering system provides a comfort-orientated balance whilst maintaining optimum steering feel and precision throughout the speed range. A new specification of steering gear, together with a new calibration of the speed-sensitive system that regulates hydraulic fluid flow, provides variable assistance depending on vehicle speed. The new system delivers both high levels of isolation from surface deformations whilst ensuring driver confidence through the combination of accurate steering precision and a measured increase in steering effort when cornering. 

As the new Flying Spur approaches its 200 mph (322 km/h) top speed, the ride height is automatically lowered via the air suspension system in order to compensate for aerodynamic forces. This helps not only to improve vehicle stability by optimizing aerodynamic balance along the car, but also reduces drag, with benefits both to top speed and CO2 output. The new car has a two-stage lowering strategy, firstly lowering by 5 mm at the front and 10 mm at the rear at 121 mph (195 km/h) and then by a further 8 mm and 13 mm respectively at 149 mph (240 km/h). 

The multiple-mode Electronic Stability Control (ESC) system is recalibrated to work in combination with the new chassis specification. The system is calibrated to ensure that the enthusiastic driver is not hindered by stability interventions and, where appropriate through the selection of the ESC Dynamic Mode, the driver can further explore the handling limits of the vehicle whilst still maintaining appropriate levels of stability control. 

THE PERSONAL CHOICES 
As with the entire Bentley range, the new Flying Spur is built to individual customers' exacting specifications. A range of seventeen standard exterior paint colours includes Dark Cashmere, a sophisticated and contemporary addition to the Bentley palette. The extended paint range of over 100 colors is joined by Damson, a rich hue inspired by the extremely rare purple diamond, and one that is complemented by an optional matching hide color. 

A new 19-inch Classic wheel is fitted exclusively to the new Bentley Flying Spur, either bright-painted or with a diamond turned finish. The new design consolidates a wider range of 20-inch five-spoke, 21-inch six-spoke and 21-inch ten-spoke wheels available as cost options. 

Customers wishing to extend the range of available options further can choose to include the Mulliner Driving Specification. This includes five additional hides, expanding the number of available shades to 17, and five further wood veneers. Bentley's traditional diamond quilting is incorporated to the seats and door panels, together with an indented leather headlining and embroidered Bentley wings to the headrests. Drilled alloy foot pedals, a knurled sports gear lever, jewel filler cap and 21" two-piece five-spoke alloy wheels in painted or polished finish complete the Mulliner suite of options. 

TECHNICAL SPECIFICATIONS 
Engine: 6-litre twin-turbocharged W12 
Max Power: 616 bhp / 460 kW / 625 PS @6000 rev/min 
Max Torque: 800 Nm / 590 lb.ft @ 2000 rev/min 
Transmission: ZF 8-speed automatic with Quickshift, Block Shifting and wheel-mounted paddleshift 

Driveline: Continuous all-wheel drive (40:60 rear bias) 
Ratios: 1st : 4.71; 2nd: 3.14; 3rd: 2.1; 4th: 1.67; 5th: 1.29; 6th: 1.00; 7th: 0.839; 8th: 0.667 
Final Drive: 2.85 

Brakes 
Front: 405mm ventilated discs (optional 420mm Carbon Silicon Carbide, cross drilled) 
Rear: 335mm ventilated discs (optional 356mm, Carbon Silicon Carbide, cross drilled) 
Wheels: New 19" (2 finishes), opt 9.5J x 20", opt 9.5J x 21" (3 designs) 

Tyres: 275/45 ZR19, 275/40 ZR20, 275/35 ZR21 
Steering: Rack &amp; pinion, power assisted, speed-sensitive ZF servotronic 
Turns lock-to-lock: 2.8 
Turning circle: 11.7 m / 38.4 feet 

Suspension 
Front: Four link double wishbones, computer controlled self-leveling air suspension, with anti-roll bar 
Rear: Trapezoidal multi-link, computer-controlled self-leveling air suspension, with anti-roll bar 
Damping: Continuous Damping Control 

Dimensions 
Wheelbase: 3065 mm / 120.7 in 
Overall length: 5295 mm / 208.5 in 
Width (across body): 1976 mm / 77.8 in 
Width (inc. mirrors): 2208 mm / 86.9 in 
Overall height: 1488 mm / 58.6 in 
Fuel tank: 90 liters / 20 UK gallons / 24 US gallons 
Boot volume: 475 liters / 16.8 cu ft 
Kerb weight (EU): 2475 kg / 5451 lb 
Gross vehicle weight: 2972 kg / 6546 lb 

Performance 
Top speed: 200 mph / 322 km/h 
0-60 mph: 4.3 secs 
0-100 mph: 9.5 secs 
0-100 km/h: 4.6 secs 
0-160 km/h: 9.5 secs 
Fuel Consumption (EU cycle) 
Urban: 12.6 mpg (22.4 litres/100 km) 
Extra Urban: 27.8 mpg (10.2 litres/100 km) 
Combined: 19.2 mpg (14.7 litres/100 km) 
CO2 emissions: 343 g/km 
Fuel Consumption (EPA cycle) 
City: 12 US mpg 
Highway: 20 US mpg 
Combined: 15 US mpg 
Emissions Controls: EU 5 and US LEV II﻿

Meer lezen (404 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-AAQtuniGZXc/USTtB-ZJq-I/AAAAAAAAV1o/06enT9yh6AM/w426-h237/Bentley-24.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/112744505908217834194/albums/6000543784947982433/6000543789335832514</link><title>Yesterday I ordered all the building materials, including the wooden frames that are necessary to build the small Hondo of Amidaji. This is a  picture/drawing with how this Hondo will look like - it also contains the length and width. More news, explanations of my plans and live pictures will be posted when I install this house on the property of the temple and start upgrading it with isolation, a better roof and so on, that is in two weeks. 

 You can read here about the project of building Amidaji temple and how you can help: 
http://www.amida-ji-retreat-temple-romania.blogspot.ro/2013/07/support-construction-of-amida-ji-temple.html 

Check the updates in the article and stay close for new ones! 
Thank you for your support! 
Namo Amida Butsu 

#amidaji #jodoshinshu #shinbuddhism #pureland #purelandbuddhism  ﻿

Meer lezen (15 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-wfk-bJcYxdw/U0Y2yL6J58I/AAAAAAAAGtA/OFPUMTaGfMs/w426-h248/Hondo+Amidaji.JPG</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7500-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/roof%20isolation/photos/102479302448294678302/albums/5943567586492431937/5943567583502767170</link><title>Below is a story I wrote for #VeteransDay #ThankAVet. I worked hard on this story despite the weird timelines, deadlines, and access that came with it. 

A version of this story was published today. I will not call it my own. I have instead posted the original text here. 

I was also the photographer. 

&lt;del&gt;\------------------------------------&lt;/del&gt; 
The Invisible Monster and one Homeless Female Veteran's Journey to Take Back Her Life 

Casondra Williams looks away when she speaks of the silent killer. She doesn't know when her invisible monster will attack, only that it has, that it will again, and that she doesn't have to let it win. 

Williams, 44, is sitting in a chair on the sixth floor of an office building staring at the impenetrable wall of a cloudy, gray building across a narrow alley. She grabs a tissue, blots her eyes, and speaks with the disciplined caution of one who has been forced, over time, to shut down in order to avoid getting hurt. She thinks about her struggle—the destructive thoughts, the personal vices, the five years she was alone and homeless—and the long suffering in silence from the abuses she endured in the army. It's a trigger, the memory of trauma, she explains, that brings her back to the places she's longed to forget. 

Her thoughts take her back to Fort Jackson when she was in Advanced Individual Training. It’s 1993 and she’s 24 years old. Another soldier had repeatedly sexually harassed her. Williams went to her female drill sergeant and reported the incidents. Though she feels the matter had been effectively resolved, there were other traumatic incidents later in her career that weren’t. Williams’ silent killer, her invisible monster, was borne of those events. 

“I was ashamed for a long time,” she says. “I didn’t talk to anyone about what had happened to me [in the army].” 

When she stares out the window, Williams’ eyes grow dark. In her thoughts, she fast-forwards to her time at Fort Hood, when another soldier from her unit sexually assaulted her. She had reported what happened, but was told to keep her mouth shut. The threat of further assault remained, and she was continually harassed for being a whistle blower. That’s when Williams took to self-isolation, often shunning after-duty socialization, a tactic she felt was a coping mechanism for survival. 

“I felt like I was no longer part of the team,” she says. “They made me feel like I was the enemy. It felt like I was thrown away. After that [assault], there’s no way to again feel like part of that team.” 

The invisible monster first struck in April 2001, not long after Williams separated from the army. She'd left active duty after 8 years in uniform for a civilian front desk job at the Pentagon, a job she held for almost 3 years until succumbing to what she calls were "personal issues" that affected her performance. It was the nightmares at first, then flashbacks, irritability, and then... she trails off. 

“It was a battle everyday,” she says. “I kept everyone at a distance. I couldn’t focus or interact with coworkers—I couldn’t complete basic tasks. I couldn’t communicate with my supervisor. Back then, there was no known PTSD condition. I was irritable all the time because I never knew when the invisible monster would attack, or why.” 

Williams left the Pentagon in 2003. Not long after, she lost her apartment. She bounced from temp job to temp job, but she could barely function. She was frustrated, panicked, and alone. 

“It was scary,” she says. “There were a lot of days where I took a suitcase to work, not sure where I was going to sleep that night.” 

For the next three years, Williams was homeless and mostly jobless. She had stayed in multiple group therapy houses in Virginia and Maryland, some of them catering to domestic violence cases, or to various hotels and houses of male acquaintances. None of them ever worked out or could provide her the safety and stability she needed to get back on her feet. 

“There were days where I had a roof, but no food,” she says. 

Finally, in 2006, Williams took what she felt was the biggest chance of her life: She went to the Veterans Affairs hospital in Washington, D.C. She was broke, hungry, emotionally scarred, and oblivious to the resources and benefits VA could help her with. 

“I was already at bottom, and I was desperate,” she says. “I wasn’t feeling well. I was sick—and that sucks. Being sick is one thing, but being sick and on the streets is just so much worse. I didn’t even know what VA could do for me, but I walked in anyway.” 

For Williams, the chance paid off. 

“That’s how I found out I had PTSD,” she exclaimed. “Before I went to the VA, I never connected the dots that the way I had been feeling—all the nightmares and flashbacks and anxiety and inability to function—all of that was related to what happened to me in the army. 

“It was difficult to talk about,” she admits. “Even today.” 

A month later, Williams was put in contact with someone from HUD-VASH, the Department of Housing and Urban Development – VA Supportive Housing program, a joint effort between HUD and VA to move Veterans and their families out of homelessness and into permanent housing. Until her Housing Choice Voucher was approved, VA arranged for Williams to stay at a homeless shelter in Virginia. 

“It wasn’t a picnic,” she says, “but it gave me the motivation to get out of that situation.” 

While there, Williams met other Veterans in similar predicaments. Though she was hesitant to tell her own story, she grew confident in hearing others tell theirs. She soon became a resident adviser, and enjoyed helping other Vets. She even managed to save a little bit of pay. 

“Not much, though” she adds, with a glimmer of a smile lighting up her face. 

With that newfound confidence, Williams began a slow return to normal life. She began volunteering at the VADC Hospital—and when she was ready, she started video recording her own story, uploading the videos to YouTube, a way for her to reach out and connect with other MST survivors. 

“Don’t isolate yourself,” she warns. “It’s easy to hide. It’s easy to push people away.” 

Today, Williams is still in the HUD-VASH voucher program, but she’s working to get into her first home. To get out of the apartment—away from the TV and self-imposed isolation—she joined a gym. And she’s also using her Chapter 31 Vocational Rehabilitation and Employment education benefits. She’s enrolled at University of Maryland University College, where’s she’s studying Cyber Security and Legal Studies. 

She’s still adapting, still battling the invisible monster. 

“PTSD encouraged me to build my own prison, and that was the nightmare. I thought I had to protect myself from everyone. I was in survival mode. I’m not out of the woods yet, but I’m getting there. I don’t want to isolate. I’m not going to feed it [the invisible monster]. 

“I’m taking my life back.”﻿

Meer lezen (147 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7500_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-I_W-gd43Cpg/UnvLOhE1lEI/AAAAAAAAAjk/gDZQE-On_MY/w426-h284/CasondraWilliams02.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>