<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:00:14" name="Picasa" id="FW14-e122"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-01"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/111622089687043471906/albums/5998365086337079025/5998365083362148802</link><title>"HAPPENING ON CAMPUS TODAY": 

Today we are hosting 14 counselors from different #international #schools from all over the world at #Webster #University #Leiden. 

To all counselors: Welcome to Leiden and enjoy our city and our campus! 

Fotos: Counselors in break-up sessions with Webster Staff on Counselor day 2014 http://ow.ly/i/581ZM http://ow.ly/i/581ZT﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_01_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-3_L5cWuexek/Uz55QzroQcI/AAAAAAAAB7k/mFR6SEqF0gs/w426-h319/581ZM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-02"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/106153737913560870434/albums/5888885363334226241/5888885366388369842?authkey=COfQj5zcuaqaVA</link><title>This is a part of a series of posts about the history of Zen, in this second part of posts, I´ll cover Chàn Buddhism. 

#8 
Hui-Neng 

Huineng (Hui-neng) is the famous “Sixth Patriarch” of the Chan or tradition, which is better known in Japanese as “Zen”). The focus of an immense body of lore that grew over the centuries, Huineng’s life mirrors the fortunes of Chan itself – a provincial Chinese version of Buddhism that rose to become a major religious and cultural force throughout East Asia. Tradition holds that Huineng was an uncouth “barbarian” youth who, because of his innate intuitive insight, surpassed his more cultured fellow monks to earn the official “dharma seal” certifying the authoritative transmission of Buddhist enlightenment, and thereby earning a lasting place in history. He is intimately associated with the Platform Sutra of the Sixth Patriarch, one of the most influential texts in all of Chinese Buddhism. Alleged to be a sermon from the lips of Huineng himself, this text provides a gripping first person account of the Master’s life. Its cryptic, yet insightful, discussion of Chan practice lays out the central concerns of Chan cultivation. Huineng’s discussion of the themes of inherent enlightenment, sudden awakening, and the non-dual nature of wisdom (Sanskrit: prajna) and meditation (Sanskrit: dhyana) resounds through later generations of Chan teachers, and continues to pose difficult philosophical challenges to this day. 

By the sixth century, certain monasteries in the mountainous areas of central and southwestern China became known as places reserved for intense meditation training. The masters at these centers taught methods so powerful that it was rumored that those willing to persevere could awaken in this very life. As time went on several of these meditation masters gained loyal followings and tales of them spread as their disciples established their own monasteries. It was out of this context that Chan as a distinct school (zong,“lineage”) and the legend of its most famous master arose. Modern scholars now agree that many of the stories surrounding Huineng are “mythical” reconstructions and elaborations by later generations of Chan writers. Nonetheless, this mythology tells us a lot about how Chan came to conceive itself as a distinct tradition, at once radically innovative and deeply conservative. This Chan self-conception finds its best articulation in a poem attributed to Bodhidharma, according to which Chan is “a separate transmission outside the scriptures, not relying on words and phrases, directly transmitted from mind to mind.” Such transmission can only occur within the relationship between Master and student; hence, the Master, and the connection to him, is of paramount importance in all Chan schools. 

As with many legendary figures, it is difficult to sort fact from fiction when it comes to Huineng. We have many sources of information on him but most were written long after his lifetime. Most scholars of Buddhism now consider the story of Huineng’s life and his role in establishing Chan as a direct line going back to Sakyamuni (the historical Buddha, ca. 6th to 5th centuries BCE) to be little more than pious fiction. While there may be a kernel of historical truth to them, all of the accounts of Huineng’s life (particularly as recorded in the Platform Sutra of the Sixth Patriarch) show evidence of later expansion and elaboration. In fact, scholars cannot even agree on the location of Dafan, the temple in which Huineng allegedly recited the Platform Sutra. 

Huineng spent his early years wandering, ending up with a Buddhist nun who was devoted to the Nirvana Sutra. After reciting passages from it one day she asked him to take a turn reading it aloud only to find that he was illiterate. Incredulous, she asked how he intended to learn Buddha’s truth if he could not read the sutras. The youth replied that the nature of Buddha does not depend on words and letters so what need was there to read texts? Amazed at his insight, she suggested he take up monastic life. At this point he declined, but went on to train under a meditation master. 

After three years of meditating in a mountain cave, Huineng went to Dongshan (East Mountain) monastery in Hubei, where he met Master Hongren, the “Fifth Patriarch.” Glaring at this supplicant, Hongren asked where he was from and why he was there. Huineng answered simply that he was from the south and had come to learn the dharma (Buddhist doctrine) from him. Hongren retorted that as a southerner, Huineng was a mere “barbarian,” adding, “How could you become Buddha?” Unfazed by the insult, Huineng replied, “Although my ‘barbarian’ body and yours differ, what difference is there in our buddha-nature?” Realizing at once the potential of this coarse youth, Hongren resolved to test him further. He took him in but assigned him to the threshing room, where he labored for nine months, treading the mill to separate the rice grains from their husks. 

The most famous incident in Huineng’s story concerns a dharma contest. One day Hongren challenged his charges to each write a verse (gatha) distilling their understanding of their “original natures.” He promised to read them and award his robe (a symbol of dharma transmission; some versions of the story include Hongren’s begging bowl) and the title “Sixth Patriarch” to the student demonstrating true realization. The task quickly devolved onto the shoulders of the head monk, Shenxiu, who, it was assumed, would be the Master’s likely successor. Shenxiu, however, was full of doubt and spent a tortured night considering his options. Finally he stole out and wrote his verse anonymously on the wall of the new dharma hall: 
The body is the bodhi tree. 
The heart-mind is like a mirror. 
Moment by moment wipe and polish it, 
Not allowing dust to collect. 
A straightforward articulation of the necessity of diligent practice, Shenxiu hoped this verse would show the Master that his students had at least some understanding. 

The next morning Hongren read the verse and praised it before the community. He burned incense before it and ordered them all to recite it before calling Shenxiu for an interview. In private he commended Shenxiu for his insight, stating that the verse showed he had reached the “gates of wisdom” but had yet to enter. He then suggested Shenxiu take a few more days to compose another verse worthy of being awarded the robe. 

Meanwhile, Huineng was still working in the threshing room when a novice wandered by reciting Shenxiu’s verse. Immediately Huineng realized the author of the verse lacked full understanding. Venturing out to the dharma hall, he got someone to write his reply: 
Bodhi originally has no tree. 
The clear and bright mirror also has no support. 
Buddha-nature is constantly purifying and clearing. 
Where could there be dust? 

Very soon word of this new verse spread and eventually the news reached Hongren. The Master came to read it and immediately recognized it as the work of Huineng and that this unknown prodigy was truly enlightened. However, he knew that passing his robe to an uncouth peasant would upset the monastic hierarchy. Therefore he publicly dismissed it as “not complete understanding.” Later, under cover of darkness, Hongren summoned Huineng for a secret audience in which he gave him further teachings. Passing on his robe, the Master admonished him to flee for his life, predicting, however, that eventually he would transmit the teachings. With that, Huineng fled south. After some months, Huineng was traced to a mountain by a band of pursuers intent on killing him and stealing the robe. Most of the pursuers turned back after climbing only halfway but one, Huiming (a former general) reached him on the summit. There, rather than slay the young master, he received the teaching and became enlightened. Thus being recognized as a true Chan Master, Huineng dispatched his new disciple to the north to spread the dharmaand convert the populace. 

One of the most colorful episodes in Huineng lore concerns his confrontation with a dragon that lived in a pond in front of Baolin temple. The dragon was particularly large and fierce, emerging regularly from the watery depths to create havoc and instill fear in the populace. Fearlessly, the Master taunted the beast for its weakness at only being unable to appear in a large as opposed to smaller form. At once the dragon disappeared only to re-emerge in small form and so show the monk his powers. Unimpressed, the Master challenged the monster to show its courage by entering his bowl. When it did so, the Master quickly scooped the dragon up, took him into the Buddha Hall, and preached dharma to it until it shed its body and departed. 

Much as with other great religious figures, so the stories of Huineng’s death are particularly dramatic. The Platform Sutra gives a confused account that may combine several different versions. In essence, however, it records that as he neared his death, the Master called his disciples for a final teaching in the form of a “dharma verse.” All the disciples broke into tears over the imminent departure of their beloved teacher except for one, Shenhui, whom the Master praised for having attained the status of awakening. Chiding the others for the foolishness of their tears, Huineng told them, “All of you sit down. I shall give you a verse, the verse of the true-false moving-quiet. All of you recite it, and if you understand the meaning, you will be the same as I. If you practice with it, you will not lose the essence of the teaching.” (section 48) After this final lesson (during which he outlined the Chan lineage back to the Buddha) Huineng died at the stroke of midnight on August 28, 713. Other traditions, however, have Huineng dying in deep meditation after finishing his last meal. His passing was marked by all manner of cosmic signs: a strange perfume pervading the temple for days, mysterious bright lights, a miraculous rainbow in the sky etc. The Platform Sutra says, “Mountains crumbled, the earth trembled, and the forest trees turned white. The sun and moon ceased to shine and the wind and clouds lost their colors.” (section 54) An inscription by the poet Wang Wei (d. 759) adds “the birds and monkeys cried in anguish.” 

Several posthumous stories of Huineng attest to the powerful spell he cast on later generations. Some decades after his passing the emperor sent an envoy to ask for his robe and bowl so that the court might pay them homage. These were sent back with great ceremony a few years later by the succeeding emperor, who purportedly dreamt Huineng asked that they be returned. Later, in 816, Huineng was awarded the official title “Dhyana Master Dajian” (Great Mirror). To this day there is a mummy reputed to be Huineng in the Nanhua monastery located in Caoxi. For centuries it was the focus of intense devotion, and at times was brought to the nearby city of Shanzhou to promote prosperity or ward off plagues and droughts. The mummy was also threatened several times and at least one time was nearly decapitated by rival monks seeking to gain power through possession of the Sixth Patriarch’s head. 

Next post: The five houses of Chán 

References: 
 Dumoulin, Heinrich. Zen Buddhism: A History. Vol. 1, India and China. New York: Macmillan, 1988. 
 Faure, Bernard. The Rhetoric of Immediacy: A Cultural Critique of Chan/Zen Buddhism. Princeton: Princeton University Press, 1995. 
 Faure, Bernard. The Will to Orthodoxy: A Critical Genealogy of Northern Chan Buddhism. Stanford: Stanford University Press, 1997. 
 Hershock, Peter D. Liberating Intimacy: Enlightenment and Social Virtuosity in Ch’an Buddhism. Albany: State University of New York Press, 1996. 
 Jorgenson, John. Inventing Hui-neng, the Sixth Patriarch: Hagiography and Biography in Early Ch’an. Leiden: E. J. Brill Academic Publishing, 2005. 
 McRae, John R. The Northern School and the Formation of Early Ch’an Buddhism. Honolulu: University of Hawaii Press, 1986. 
 Price, A.F., and Wong Mou-lam, trans. The Diamond Sutra and the Sutra of Hui-Neng. Boston: Shambhala Publications, Inc., 1990. 
 Suzuki, Daisetz Teitaro. The Zen Doctrine of No-mind: the Significance of the Sutra of Hui-Neng (Wei-Lang). York Beach, ME: Weiser Books, 1972.﻿

Meer lezen (217 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_02_thumb.jpg">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YklpoZIB_EU/UbmGCkKTKbI/AAAAAAAAFOU/Zk5rW439REs/w426-h584/huineng3.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-03"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/108404515213153345305/albums/5792311417114040833/5792311417380373106</link><title>Hubble Space Telescope reveals farthest view into universe ever 

+SPACE.com reports The Hubble Space Telescope has captured the farthest-ever view into the universe, a photo that reveals thousands of galaxies billions of light-years away. 

The picture, called eXtreme Deep Field, or XDF, combines 10 years of Hubble telescope views of one patch of sky. 

Read more: http://www.space.com/17755-farthest-universe-view-hubble-space-telescope.html 

Photo: Image released Sept. 25, 2012. (NASA, ESA, G. Illingworth, D. Magee, and P. Oesch (University of California, Santa Cruz), R. Bouwens (Leiden University), and the HUDF09 Team)﻿

Meer lezen (11 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_03_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-keAptOcRO_c/UGJsi41lgnI/AAAAAAAAdFw/SQE0oSRxn-I/w426-h354/120925-space-xdf-1p.grid-8x2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-04"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/105989807116077671770/albums/5861201702162301217/5861201706269422066?authkey=CI7-4pLvtNi8KA</link><title>Education﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_04_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-zTRofZASz3U/UVcr5dsaMfI/AAAAAAAAe_M/8yg5UruhOzU/w426-h420/school%2Bteaches%253F.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-05"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/114963786071989905755/albums/5807026553946078929/5807026558894429938</link><title>SPRINGFIELD AIRPORT; Grand Father Burial Plane to Greenville Sino County (Ritual Death)﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_05_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-40gTormsCK4/UJaz42wpVvI/AAAAAAAAKpI/QilW91TfLgM/w426-h297/Plane%2Bto%2BGreenville%2BSino%2BGrand%2BFather%2BBurial.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-06"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/107027957460781365440/albums/5976247528803352737/5976247526552147202</link><title>Kiezen voor #Sint-Lievencollege Keizerkarelstraat is kiezen voor… 

… een school waar je kind een naam heeft. 

Alle leerkrachten kennen je kind bij naam, ze zijn geen nummer. Ze worden als individu benaderd en iedereen kent elkaar. Er zijn veel klasoverschrijdende projecten en jouw kind leert omgaan met kinderen van alle leeftijden. Je kind leert dat hij/zij mag zijn zoals hij/zij is. 

… een school waar je kind zich thuis voelt. 

Sint Lievenscollege is een school met veel aandacht voor het welzijn van kinderen. Jouw kind krijgt extra aandacht daar waar hij of zij het nodig heeft. Zowel kinderen die het wat moeilijker hebben als kinderen die wat meer aankunnen worden persoonlijk begeleid. Naast de schoolse focus op leren en presteren is er een enorme zorg voor de beleving en de emoties van je kind. Dit stimuleert een positief zelfwaardegevoel waardoor faalangst geen kans krijgt. 

… een school die je kind stimuleert in discipline en creativiteit. 

Sint Lievenscollege is een school die de meerwaarde van klassiek onderwijs combineert met vernieuwende onderwijsmethoden. Jouw kind krijgt er de nodige structuur en discipline aangeboden. Tegelijkertijd wordt sterk gefocust op de inbreng van je kind waardoor creativiteit, autonomie, zelfredzaamheid en verantwoordelijkheidsgevoel gestimuleerd worden. 

… een school waar je kind leert leven in de maatschappij zoals die nu is. 

Waarden, normen en competenties zoals gelijkwaardigheid, verdraagzaamheid, samenwerken, luisteren naar elkaar, respect… worden in de verf gezet zodat je kind sterker wordt en leert omgaan met de realiteit van diversiteit in de maatschappij. 

… een school waar jij als ouder je welkom voelt. 

Sint Lievenscollege is een open school naar ouders, waar ouders inspraak hebben en steeds terecht kunnen bij de leerkrachten. Je hoeft geen probleem te hebben, er is steeds ruimte voor een gewone babbel over je kind, over hoe jij de dingen als ouder aanvoelt. Je voelt er ook een sfeer van verbondenheid onder de ouders die alledaagse zorgen, anekdotes en leuke dingen over de kinderen met elkaar delen. 

… een school met een dynamisch lerarenteam dat er elke dag voor gaat. 

Op Sint Lievenscollege komen leerkrachten werken met een hart voor de kinderen en een passie voor hun job. Elke dag zetten ze zich ten volle in om kwaliteitsvol onderwijs aan te bieden met oog voor vernieuwende methodieken. Zij investeren in klasoverschrijdende projecten die ze samen met de kinderen uitwerken en vorm geven. 

… een school in hartje #Gent met oog voor werkende ouders. 

De school ligt in het centrum van Gent en toch voldoende aan de rand zodat deze gemakkelijk bereikbaar is. De school is voor veel mensen op weg naar het werk, op weg naar huis, dicht bij het station,… zodat de verplaatsingstijd voor kind en ouder haalbaar is. 

…een school die investeert in studie- en huistaakbegeleiding voor alle kinderen. 

Elke avond krijgt jouw kind begeleiding bij huiswerkopdrachten. Leerkrachten ondersteunen, stimuleren en volgen je kind op bij het maken van huiswerk en instuderen van lessen. Op die manier heb jij als ouder de tijd om je werkdag rustig te beëindigen en samen met je kind thuis de dag af te sluiten. 

… een school waar de directie dicht bij de kinderen en de ouders staat. 

Een moderne invulling van de directiefunctie maakt dat naast het leiden van een school en een lerarenteam, zij alle kinderen kent en zeer toegankelijk is, ook voor ouders. 

… een school met een perspectief op een kwalitatieve doorstroom naar het secundair onderwijs. 

Sint Lievenscollege is meer dan een lagere school. Je kind kan doorstromen naar andere scholen binnen dezelfde #scholengroep met keuze uit verschillende richtingen. 

…een school die over de muren kijkt 

De leeromgeving van je kind wordt uitgebreid buiten de schoolmuren. Bijkomende uitstappen, bezoeken en activiteiten in de stad en daarbuiten maken dat je kind op een open manier kennis maakt en oog krijgt voor natuur, cultuur, sport en nog zoveel meer. De eigen sportterreinen van 20.000 m2 midden in het groen en een verbonden KSA-VKSJ groep en scouts groep zijn hiervan sprekende voorbeelden. 

Kiezen voor Sint Lievencollege Keizerkarelstraat is kiezen voor een school waar je jouw kind de kans geeft om ieder schooljaar op een fijne manier in een veilige en verrijkende context te leren, te ontwikkelen, groot te worden zodat ze uitgroeien tot kinderen met een persoonlijkheid die met zelfvertrouwen de wereld (van het secundair onderwijs) binnenstappen.﻿

Meer lezen (100 regels)Minder weergeven</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_06_thumb.jpg">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-maiX3bpxmzQ/Uu_ldj3ylQI/AAAAAAAAAWA/sgGBkDPQgJI/w426-h320/lager2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-07"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/103021935809653909010/albums/5994352222688845393/5994352229837787490?sqi=108920552920430241079&amp;sqsi=bf7479ed-bedf-4ea9-96a8-7fb9c1b0b3a2</link><title></title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_07_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-X3srrsTpWAA/UzA3l_YNUWI/AAAAAAAAGUg/xu0GKFq3HUs/w426-h480/1743724_576899819072369_499790465_n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-08"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/106054433142013306487/albums/5944249150097273601/5944249147647060322</link><title>Esotericism 
"Arcane" and "Esoteric" redirect here. For other uses, see Arcane (disambiguation) and Esoteric (disambiguation). 
Esotericism or Esoterism signifies the holding of esoteric opinions or beliefs,[1] that is, ideas preserved or understood by a small group of those specially initiated, or of rare or unusual interest.[2] The term derives from the Greek ἐσωτερικός (esôterikos), a compound of ἔσω (esô): "within", thus pertaining to interiority or mysticism. Its antonym is "exoteric". 

The term can also refer to the academic study of esoteric religious movements and philosophies, and religious movements or philosophies whose proponents distinguish their beliefs, practices, and experiences from mainstream exoteric and more dogmatic institutionalized traditions.[3] 

Examples of esoteric religious movements and philosophies include Alchemy, Astrology, Anthroposophy, early Christian Mysticism,[4] Freemasonry, Gnosticism, Kabbalah, Neoplatonism, Magic, Merkabah mysticism, Mesmerism, Rosicrucianism, Taoism, Numerology, Swedenborgianism, Spiritualism, the Alawites,[5] the Theosophy of Jacob Böhme and his followers, and the Theosophical revivalist movement associated with Helena Blavatsky. 

Although Esotericism refers to the exploration of the inner meanings and symbolism of various philosophical, historical and religious texts, these texts themselves are often central to mainstream religions. For example, the Bible and the Torah are examples of esoteric material.[6] 

EtymologyEdit 
Plato, in his dialogue Alcibíades (circa 390 BC), uses the expression ta esô meaning "the inner things", and in his dialogue Theaetetus (circa 360 BC) he uses ta exô meaning "the outside things". Aristotle applied this distinction to his own writings. The probable first appearance of the Greek adjective esôterikos is in Lucian of Samosata's "The Auction of Lives", § 26, written around AD 166.[7] 

The term esoteric first appeared in English in the 1701 History of Philosophy by Thomas Stanley, in his description of the mystery-school of Pythagoras; the Pythagoreans were divided into "exoteric" (under training), and "esoteric" (admitted into the "inner" circle). The corresponding noun "esotericism" was coined in French by Jacques Matter in 1828 and popularized by Eliphas Levi in the 1850s.[8] [1]. It entered the English language in the 1880s via the works of theosophist Alfred Sinnett. 

DefinitionEdit 
Among the competing understandings of what unites the various currents designated by "Esotericism" in the scholarly sense, perhaps the most influential has been proposed by Antoine Faivre. His definition is based on the presence in the esoteric currents of four essential characteristics: a theory of correspondences between all parts of the invisible and the visible cosmos, the conviction that nature is a living entity owing to a divine presence or life-force, the need for mediating elements (such as symbols, rituals, angels, visions) in order to access spiritual knowledge, and, fourthly, an experience of personal and spiritual transmutation when arriving at this knowledge. To this are added two non-intrinsic characteristics. Esotericists frequently suggest that there is a concordance between different religious traditions: best example is the belief in prisca theologia (ancient theology) or in philosophia perennis (perennial philosophy). Finally, esotericism sometimes suggests the idea of a secret transmission of spiritual teachings, through initiation from master to disciple.[9] It should, however, be emphasized that Faivre's definition is one of several divergent understandings of the most appropriate use of the term. 

The “perennialist” or “traditionalist” school is represented by authors like the French René Guénon (1886–1951), the Indian Ananda Coomaraswamy (1877–1947), the Swiss Frithjof Schuon (1907–1998), the Italian Julius Evola (1898–1974), the Iranian Seyyed Hossein Nasr (born in 1933), both scholars and esotericists. They postulate that there exists a Primordial Tradition of non-human origin. 

“We say that it [the origin of the traditions] is polar, and the pole is nomore Western than it is Eastern. It is only in a later epoch that the seat of the primordial tradition, transferred to other regions, was able to become either Western or Eastern. We consider the origin of the traditions to be Nordic, and even more to be polar, since this is expressly affirmed in the Veda as well as in other sacred books.” [10] [2] 
In perennialist usage, esotericism is a metaphysical concept referring to a supposed “transcendent unity” of all great religious traditions. Esotericism is the metaphysical point of unity where exoteric religions are believed to converge.[11] [3] 

“Our starting point is the acknowledgment of the fact that there are diverse religions which exclude each other. This could mean that one religion is right and that all the others are false; it could mean also that all are false. In reality, it means that all are right, not in their dogmatic exclusivism, but in their unanimous inner signification, which coincides with pure metaphysics, or in other terms, with the philosophia perennis.” (F. Schuon, 1995). 
After all, the esoteric tradition may be recovered if the seeker undergoes initiation. 

“Initiation is essentially the transmission of a spiritual influence, a transmission that can only take place through a regular, traditional organization, so that one cannot speak of initiation outside of an affiliation with an organization of this kind. We have explained that 'regularity' must be understood to exclude all pseudo-initiatic organizations, which, regardless of pretention and outward appearance, in no way possess any spiritual influence and thus are incapable of transmitting anything.” [12] 
HistoryEdit 
Since the field of esotericism is not a single tradition but a vast array of often unrelated figures and movements, there is no single historical thread underlying them all.[13] The developments that one might wish to emphasize in drawing up a history of esotericism furthermore depends on whether esotericism in the dictionary (non-scholarly) or the scholarly sense is intended. 

Several historically attested religions emphasize secret or hidden knowledge, and are thus esoteric in the dictionary sense, without necessarily being esoteric movements in the scholarly sense of the word. Thus, the Roman Empire had several mystery religions which emphasized initiation. Some saw Christianity, with its ritual of baptism, as a mystery religion. None of these are "esoteric" in the scholarly sense. The terms "Gnosticism" and "Gnosis" refer to a family of religious movements which claimed to possess secret knowledge (gnosis). Another important movement from the ancient world was Hermeticism or Hermetism. Both of these are often seen as precursors to esoteric movements in the scholarly sense of the word. 

Non-Western traditions can also display the characteristics of esoteric movements. The Ismaili Muslims also stress a distinction between the inner and the outer. It is believed that spiritual salvation is attained by receiving the 'Nur' (light) through the "esoteric", that is, spiritual search for enlightenment. Ismaili Islam also has some of the characteristics associated with esotericism as defined by Faivre, e.g. the belief in an intermediate spiritual sphere mediating between humans and the divine. Esoteric movements in Buddhism, which fall under the general category of Vajrayana Buddhism, employ esoteric training into Buddha's teachings, through use of symbols, mantra and hand-gestures, or mudra. Initiation rituals are typically given to students as they progress along these paths, and care is taken not to discuss specific rituals to those lacking the right empowerment. 

In order to distinguish esoteric currents based primarily on sources from late Antiquity and the European Middle Ages, from e.g. Islamic or Jewish currents with similar features, the more precise term "Western esotericism" is often employed. 

Western esoteric movements in the scholarly sense thus have roots in Antiquity and the Middle Ages. A major phase in the development of Western esotericism begins in the Renaissance, partly as the result of various attempts to revive such earlier movements. During the Italian Renaissance, for example, translators such as Ficino and Pico della Mirandola turned their attention to the classical literature of Neoplatonism, and what was thought to be the pre-Mosaic tradition of Hermeticism. Other pursuits of Antiquity that entered into the mix of esoteric speculation were astrology and alchemy. Beside such revived currents from late Antiquity, a second major source of esoteric speculation is the Kabbalah, which was lifted out of its Jewish context and adapted to a Christian framework by people such as Johannes Reuchlin. Outside the Italian Renaissance, yet another major current of esotericism was initiated by Paracelsus, who combined alchemical and astrological themes (among others) into a complex body of doctrines. 

In the early 17th century, esotericism is represented by currents such as Christian theosophy and Rosicrucianism. A century later, esoteric ideas entered various strands of Freemasonry. Later in the 18th century, as well as in the early 19th century, the diffuse movement known as Mesmerism became a major expression of esotericism. In the 19th century, esotericism is also represented by certain aspects of the philosophy, literature and science associated with Romanticism, by spiritualism, and by a notable French wave of occultism. 

The major exponent of esotericism in the latter part of the 19th century is the Theosophy of H. P. Blavatsky, not to be confused with the Christian Theosophy mentioned above. In the 20th century, Theosophy was further developed by Annie Besant and Charles Webster Leadbeater, while people like Alice Bailey, Rudolf Steiner and many others, became the source for a whole range of post-theosophical movements such as The Summit Lighthouse. The post-theosophical Anthroposophical movement is a synthesis of occultist, Christian and Neoplatonic ideas with Western esoteric concepts as formulated in the wake of Theosophy. Anthroposophy, which was founded by Rudolf Steiner in the early part of the 20th century, includes esoteric versions of education, agriculture, and medicine.[14] 

Yet another notable esoteric strain stems from the teachings of G. I. Gurdjieff and P. D. Ouspensky. 

Theosophy is also considered a major influence on the many less institutionally organized varieties of esotericism in metaphysical milieus, "Ascended Master Activities", and within the New Age. 

Finally, it can be noted that Carl Gustav Jung can be seen as an exponent of esotericism: his writings concern esoteric subject matter such as alchemy, and rephrased the concept of correspondences in a modern, psychologizing terminology in his theory of synchronicity. 

MethodologyEdit 
Wouter J. Hanegraaff is Professor of “History of Hermetic Philosophy and Related Currents” at the University of Amsterdam (1999). The Universiteit van Amsterdam (UvA) is the world's first academic institution to have created a complete program for research and teaching in the field of Western Esotericism.[4] He is also president of the European Society for the Study of Western Esotericism. Essential to Hanegraaff’s methodology is what he calls an “empirical” approach, with an informed, open, and, so much as possible, neutral mind. He makes a sharp division between a “religionist” perspective and an “empiricist” one. 

“Empirical research must be based on methodological agnosticism with regard to religious and philosophical ‘first principles’, and must fully recognize the historicity of religious phenomena. This empirical perspective is applied to the newly emerging academic field of esotericism.” [15] 
Secondly, Hanegraaff follows a distinction between an “emic” and an “etic” approach to religious studies. [5] The emic approach is that of the alchemist or theosopher as an alchemist or theosopher. The etic approach is that of the scholar as an historian, a researcher, with a critical look. An empirical study of esotericism needs “emic material and etic interpretation”. 

“The principal theoretical tool to safeguard scientific legitimity in this situation is the distinction between emic and etic. Emic denotes the believer’s point of view. On the part of the researcher, the reconstruction of this emic perspective requires an attitude of empathy which excludes personal biases as far as possible. Scholarly discourse about religion, on the other hand, is not emic but etic. Scholars may introduce their own terminology and make theoretical distinctions which are different from those of the believers themselves.” [16] 
Pierre A. Riffard (Ph.D., University of the French West Indies) studies the method used by esotericists themselves (alchemists, magicians, Rosicrucians, Anthroposophists...).[17] He examines some of their procedures. 1) Mythological origins. The esotericists trace the origins of their doctrine or practice to an extremely distant past. They situate the life of Hermes in times immemorial. 2) Cosmic cycles. For Gaston Georgel, “history is governed by cycles of 540, 1080 and 2160 years”. 3) The chains of initiation. Some Rosicrucians include Francis Bacon among their masters and trace their origins back to the time of Thutmosis III. 4) The secret books. Esotericists prefer to base their beliefs on secret writings, unknown to the majority of people and inaccessible to the uninitiated: for instance, among the Theosophists, The Book of Dzyan. 5) Spiritual interpretations. The esotericists are able to endow the most profane texts with an occult meaning. The alchemists discover within the Greek and Roman myths the Great Work of alchemy. 6) Magical uses. A book can be used as a talisman, a divinatory machine... The Sortes Sanctorum (Lots of the saints) were, in early Christianity, a divination which consists in taking passages of the Bible at chance, and drawing conclusions from them concerning future. [6] 

Arthur Versluis (Professor, Ph.D., Michigan State University) proposes the term “sympathetic empiricism” as the approach that he finds most amenable in the study of Western Esotericism. 

“While I am convinced of the critical importance of historiography in the study of esotericism (and for this reason all of my academic books are firmly grounded in historical method) I do not believe that historiography is adequate in itself to convey the complex, multivalent nature of esoteric thought, traditions, or most of all, experience. Esotericism, given all its varied forms and its inherently multidimensional nature, cannot be conveyed without going beyond purely historical information: at minimum, the study of esotericism, and in particular mysticism, requires some degree of imaginative participation in what one is studying.”[18] [7] 
See alsoEdit 
Behmenism 
Clairvoyance 
Druze 
Esoteric Buddhism 
Esoteric Christianity 
Esoteric cosmology 
Esoteric healing 
Esotericism in Germany and Austria 
Freemasonry 
Huna 
Illuminati 
Kabbalah 
Karma 
Leo Strauss 
List of Buddhist topics 
List of spirituality-related topics 
List of religious, esoteric, metaphysical and mystical symbols 
Magic and religion 
Martinism 
Merkabah 
Spirituality portal 
Mysticism 
New World Order 
Numerology 
Obscurantism 
Occult 
Odic force 
Plane (esotericism) (Planes of existence) 
Qigong 
Reincarnation 
Scientology 
Spiritual evolution 
Spirituality 
Telepathy 
Theosophy 
Western Esotericism (academia) 
Western mystery tradition 
ReferencesEdit 
Chambers 20thC dictionary, 1972 
"Merriam-Webster Online Dictionary: esoteric". Webster.com. 2007-04-25. Retrieved 2010-01-31. 
"What is Esotericism?". 
Stroumsa, G. (2005). Hidden wisdom: esoteric traditions and the roots of Christian mysticism. Leiden: Brill. 
Historical dictionary of Syria by David Dean Commins, Scarecrow Press, 2004, page 29 
Bland, Professor Kalman (1996). Jewish Mysticism (Audiobook). The Teaching Company. 
Lucian of Samosata, The Auction of Lives (also called The Auction of the Philosophical Schools), § 26. Pierre A. Riffard, L’ésotérisme. Qu’est-ce que l’ésotérisme?, Paris: Robert Laffont, coll. “Bouquins”, 1990, 65. "O que é o Esoterismo". Paginasesotericas.tripod.com. Retrieved 2010-01-31. 
Jacques Matter, Histoire critique du gnosticisme, Paris: Levrault, 1928, 83 (Jean-Pierre Laurant, L’ésotérisme chrétien en France au XIX° siècle, Lausanne: L’Âge d’homme, 1992, 13-48 ; L’ésotérisme, Paris: Cerf, 1993, 40-41.) 
Antoine Faivre, Access to Western Esotericism, Albany: State University of New York Press (“SUNY Series in Western Esoteric Traditions”), 1994, 10-15. Wouter J. Hanegraaff (ed.), Dictionary of Gnosis and Western Esotericism, Leiden / Boston: Brill, 2005, I, 340. 
René Guénon, Traditional forms and cosmic cycles (1925-1949, first published in 1970), New York: Sophia perennis, 2003, 16. 
Frithjof Schuon, The Transcendent Unity of Religions (1948), London: Faber and Faber, 1953. 
René Guénon, Perspectives on initiation (1946), New York: Sophia perennis, 2001, 48. 
Jean-Paul Corsetti, Histoire de l’ésotérisme et des sciences occultes, Paris: Larousse, coll. “Références”, 1992, 17-319. Kocku von Struckrad, Western Esotericism: A Brief History of Secret Knowledge (2004), London / Oakville: Equinox Publishing, 2005, 12-145. Arthur Versluis, Magic and Mysticism: An Introduction to Western Esotericism, Plymouth: Rowman and Littlefield, 2007, 11-264. 
Robert McDermott, The Essential Steiner, ISBN 0-06-065345-0, pp. 3-11 
Wouter J. Hanegraaff, “Empirical Method in the Study of Esotericism”, in Method and Theory in the Study of Religion, Florida State University, 7:2 (1995), 99-129. 
Wouter J. Hanegraaff, New Age Religion and Western Culture. Esotericism in the Mirror of Secular Thought, Albany: State University of New York Press, 1998, 6. 
Pierre A. Riffard, “The Esoteric Method”, in Western Esotericism and the Science of Religion, Leuven: Peeters, coll. “Gnostica”, 1998, 63-74. 
Arthur Versluis, “Methods in the Study of Esotericism, Part II: Mysticism and the Study of Esotericism”, in Esoterica, Michigan State University, V, 2003, 27-40. 
Further readingEdit 
Aries: Journal for the Study of Western Esotericism, Leiden: Brill, since 2001. [8] 
Aries Book Series: Texts and Studies in Western Esotericism, Leiden: Brill, since 2006. [9] 
Esoterica, East Lansing, Michigan State University (MSU). An online resource since 1999 [10]. I (1999) [11]; VIII (2006) [12]; IX (2007) [13] 
Antoine Faivre, Access to Western Esotericism (1986), Albany: State University of New York Press (“SUNY Séries in Western Esoteric Traditions”), 1994, X-369 p. [14] 
Antoine Faivre, Theosophy, Imagination, Tradition: Studies in Western Esotericism (1996), Albany: SUNY Press (“SUNY Séries in Western Esoteric Traditions”), 2000, XXXV-269 p. [15] 
René Guénon, Perspectives on initiation (1946), New York: Sophia perennis, 2004, 320 p. [16] 
Wouter J. Hanegraaff, “The Study of Western Esotericism: New Approaches to Christian and Secular Culture”, in Peter Antes, Armin W. Geertz and Randi R. Warne, New Approaches to the Study of Religion, vol. I: Regional, Critical, and Historical Approaches, Berlin / New York: Walter de Gruyter, 2004, 497 p. [17] 
Wouter J. Hanegraaff (ed.), in collaboration with Antoine Faivre, Roelof van den Broek, Jean-Pierre Brach, Dictionary of Gnosis and Western Esotericism, Leiden / Bristol: Brill, 2005, 2 vols., 1228 p. ISBN 90-04-14187-1. 
Édouard Schuré, The Great Initiates: A Study of the Secret History of Religions (1889), Blauvelt (N.Y.): Garber Books, 1992, 480 p. [18] “Rama, Krishna, Hermes, Moses, Orpheus, Pythagoras, Plato, and Jesus.” 
Kocku von Stuckrad, Western Esotericism: A Brief History of Secret Knowledge (2004), London / Oakville: Equinox Publishing, 2005, XVII-167 p. [19] 
Arthur Versluis, Magic and Mysticism: An Introduction to Western Esotericism, Plymouth: Rowman and Littlefield, 2007, 208 pages. [20] 
Benjamin Walker, Encyclopedia of Esoteric Man: The Hidden Side of the Human Entity, London: Routledge and Kegan Paul, 1977, 353 p. ISBN 0-7100-8479-X. New title: Body Magic, London: Granada Publishing, “Paladin Books”, 1979, 478 p. ISBN 0-586-08323-5. Arranged alphabetically. 
Benjamin Walker, Man and the Beasts Within: The Encyclopedia of the Occult, the Esoteric, and the Supernatural, New York: Stein and Day, 1978, 343 p. ISBN 0-8128-1900-4 
Bibliography; 
Wikipedia.com﻿

Meer lezen (403 regels)Minder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_08_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9KR1UXRSS7c/Un43GxXr6WI/AAAAAAAAAPM/Z4i6u4jMBtA/w426-h416/17d0ea43-c4b6-4e2a-bc6d-6fceea47ff69</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-09"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/112312354934377784239/albums/5672572341854986721/5674953561859920242</link><title>The picturesque city centre of Leiden.﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_09_thumb.jpg">https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-UhShiiyoH2I/TsF8MoN_kXI/AAAAAAAAASI/VAZkOfH7HBA/w426-h320/Leiden%2B017.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e122-7504-10"><link>https://plus.google.com/s/leiden%20schools/photos/116829662773256359149/albums/5759197163738675425/5790047009745814818</link><title>After the school - waiting for mom. 
A boy from "The Little Schools Of Father Bohnen" (OPEPB) 

#haiti   #portauprince   #opepb  ﻿

Meer weergevenMinder weergeven  ·  Vertalen</title><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e122/7504_10_thumb.jpg">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/--8cI0Yaikhw/UFphFBC2RSI/AAAAAAAAGZM/-7OHBCkfzmE/w426-h286/06-7278.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>