<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:47:22" name="SpringerLink" id="FW14-e013"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:47:23">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF00603947</link><title>Voltage oscillations and ionic conductances in hair cells isolated from the alligator cochlea</title><description>P. A. Fuchs, M. G. Evans in Journal of Comparative Physiology A (1988)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:48:01">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF00581152</link><title>Endolymphatic and intracellular resting potential in the alligator lizard cochlea</title><description>Thomas F. Weiss, David W. Altmann, Michael J. Mulroy in Pflügers Archiv (1978)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:48:48">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10739-009-9178-z</link><title>Dragons in Distress: Naturalists as Bioactivists in the Campaign to Save the American Alligator</title><description>Mark V. Barrow Jr. in Journal of the History of Biology (2009)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:49:10">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00359-002-0296-8</link><title>Amphibious auditory responses of the American alligator (Alligator mississipiensis)</title><description>D. Higgs, E. Brittan-Powell, D. Soares, M. Souza… in Journal of Comparative Physiology A (2002)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:49:44">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10531-005-3431-3</link><title>Genetic diversity of Chinese alligator (Alligator sinensis) revealed by AFLP analysis: an implication on the management of captive conservation</title><description>Yi-Quan Wang, Wei-Quan Zhu, Lei Huang, Kai-Ya Zhou… in Biodiversity &amp; Conservation (2006)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:50:12">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF00677914</link><title>Use of biological monitoring in the assessment of effects of mining wastes on aquatic ecosystems of the alligator rivers region, tropical Northern Australia</title><description>Christopher L. Humphrey, Keith A. Bishop… in Environmental Monitoring and Assessment (1990)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:50:58">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00360-010-0494-6</link><title>Role of the left aortic arch and blood flows in embryonic American alligator (Alligator mississippiensis)</title><description>John Eme, Dane A. Crossley II, James W. Hicks in Journal of Comparative Physiology B (2011)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:51:39">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1360/03wc0076</link><title>Complete mitochondrial DNA sequence of Chinese alligator, Alligator sinensis, and phylogeny of crocodiles</title><description>Xiaobing Wu, Yiquan Wang, Kaiya Zhou, Weiquan Zhu, Jishan Nie… in Chinese Science Bulletin (2003)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:52:13">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s100219900057</link><title>Unexpected Effects of Predators Upon Their Prey: The Case of the American Alligator</title><description>Cristina Bondavalli, Robert E. Ulanowicz in Ecosystems (1999)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:53:01">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11434-011-4622-9</link><title>Establishment and cryopreservation of liver, heart and muscle cell lines derived from the Chinese alligator (Alligator sinensis)</title><description>ChangJun Zeng, Qing Ye, ShengGuo Fang in Chinese Science Bulletin (2011)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>