<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:21:40" name="SpringerLink" id="FW14-e013"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:21:41">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10530-010-9771-2</link><title>Erratum to: Effects of belowground resource use complementarity on invasion of constructed grassland plant communities</title><description>Cynthia S. Brown, Kevin J. Rice in Biological Invasions (2010)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:22:20">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1046/j.1440-1703.1998.00260.x</link><title>Effects of arrival order and seed size on germination of grassland plants: Are there assembly rules during recruitment?</title><description>Ove Eriksson, Åsa Eriksson in Ecological Research (1998)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:23:17">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00572-005-0032-7</link><title>A preliminary survey of the arbuscular mycorrhizal status of grassland plants in southern Tibet</title><description>J. P. Gai, G. Feng, X. B. Cai, P. Christie, X. L. Li in Mycorrhiza (2006)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:23:40">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11104-007-9234-4</link><title>Phenanthrene toxicity and dissipation in rhizosphere of grassland plants (Lolium perenne L. and Trifolium pratense L.) in three spiked soils</title><description>G. Chiapusio, S. Pujol, M. L. Toussaint, P. M. Badot, P. Binet in Plant and Soil (2007)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:24:06">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1023/A%3A1012975605995</link><title>Increased solar UV-B radiation may reduce infection by arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi (AMF) in dune grassland plants: evidence from five years of field exposure</title><description>J. van de Staaij, J. Rozema, A. van Beem, R. Aerts in Plant Ecology (2001)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:24:49">http://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-94-017-2892-8_16</link><title>Increased solar UV-B radiation may reduce infection by arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi (AMF) in dune grassland plants: evidence from five years of field exposure</title><description>J. van de Staaij, J. Rozema, A. van Beem, R. Aerts in Responses of Plants to UV-B Radiation (2001)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:25:43">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11104-011-0747-5</link><title>Two biochemical forms of phenanthrene recovered in grassland plants (Lolium perenne L. and Trifolium pratense L.) grown in 3 spiked soils</title><description>Genevieve Chiapusio, Dorine Desalme, Sophie Pujol, Quynh Trang Bui… in Plant and Soil (2011)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:26:33">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11258-012-0031-7</link><title>Effects of earthworms and arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi depend on the successional stage of a grassland plant community</title><description>Lisa Mammitzsch, Anja Teply, Susanne Wurst in Plant Ecology (2012)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:27:24">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00442-010-1676-3</link><title>Spatially complex neighboring relationships among grassland plant species as an effective mechanism of defense against herbivory</title><description>Ling Wang, Deli Wang, Yuguang Bai, Yue Huang, Meng Fan, Jushan Liu, Yexing Li in Oecologia (2010)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e013-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e013/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 12:28:31">http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11104-011-0739-5</link><title>Medium-term fertilization of grassland plant communities masks plant species-linked effects on soil microbial community structure</title><description>Stavros D. Veresoglou, Andreas P. Mamolos, Barry Thornton… in Plant and Soil (2011)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>