<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:41" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:42">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24732494</link><title>Raven surgical robot training in preparation for da vinci.</title><description>Glassman D, White L, Lewis A, King H, Clarke A, Glassman T, Comstock B, Hannaford B, Lendvay TS.

Stud Health Technol Inform. 2014;196:135-41.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:59:38">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24711798</link><title>Working memory capacity and fluid abilities: the more difficult the item, the more more is better.</title><description>Little DR, Lewandowsky S, Craig S.

Front Psychol. 2014 Mar 21;5:239. doi: 10.3389/fpsyg.2014.00239. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:26">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24702350</link><title>Measurement of the B¯s0→Ds-Ds+ and B¯s0→D-Ds+ Effective Lifetimes.</title><description>Aaij R, Adeva B, Adinolfi M, Affolder A, Ajaltouni Z, Albrecht J, Alessio F, Alexander M, Ali S, Alkhazov G, Alvarez Cartelle P, Alves AA Jr, Amato S, Amerio S, Amhis Y, Anderlini L, Anderson J, Andreassen R, Andreotti M, Andrews JE, Appleby RB, Aquines Gutierrez O, Archilli F, Artamonov A, Artuso M, Aslanides E, Auriemma G, Baalouch M, Bachmann S, Back JJ, Badalov A, Balagura V, Baldini W, Barlow RJ, Barschel C, Barsuk S, Barter W, Batozskaya V, Bauer T, Bay A, Beddow J, Bedeschi F, Bediaga I, Belogurov S, Belous K, Belyaev I, Ben-Haim E, Bencivenni G, Benson S, Benton J, Berezhnoy A, Bernet R, Bettler MO, van Beuzekom M, Bien A, Bifani S, Bird T, Bizzeti A, Bjørnstad PM, Blake T, Blanc F, Blouw J, Blusk S, Bocci V, Bondar A, Bondar N, Bonivento W, Borghi S, Borgia A, Borsato M, Bowcock TJ, Bowen E, Bozzi C, Brambach T, van den Brand J, Bressieux J, Brett D, Britsch M, Britton T, Brook NH, Brown H, Bursche A, Busetto G, Buytaert J, Cadeddu S, Calabrese R, Callot O, Calvi M, Calvo Gomez M, Camboni A, Campana P, Campora Perez D, Carbone A, Carboni G, Cardinale R, Cardini A, Carranza-Mejia H, Carson L, Carvalho Akiba K, Casse G, Castillo Garcia L, Cattaneo M, Cauet Ch, Cenci R, Charles M, Charpentier P, Cheung SF, Chiapolini N, Chrzaszcz M, Ciba K, Cid Vidal X, Ciezarek G, Clarke PE, Clemencic M, Cliff HV, Closier J, Coca C, Coco V, Cogan J, Cogneras E, Collins P, Comerma-Montells A, Contu A, Cook A, Coombes M, Coquereau S, Corti G, Couturier B, Cowan GA, Craik DC, Cruz Torres M, Cunliffe S, Currie R, D'Ambrosio C, Dalseno J, David P, David PN, Davis A, De Bonis I, De Bruyn K, De Capua S, De Cian M, De Miranda JM, De Paula L, De Silva W, De Simone P, Decamp D, Deckenhoff M, Del Buono L, Déléage N, Derkach D, Deschamps O, Dettori F, Di Canto A, Dijkstra H, Donleavy S, Dordei F, Dorosz P, Dosil Suárez A, Dossett D, Dovbnya A, Dupertuis F, Durante P, Dzhelyadin R, Dziurda A, Dzyuba A, Easo S, Egede U, Egorychev V, Eidelman S, van Eijk D, Eisenhardt S, Eitschberger U, Ekelhof R, Eklund L, El Rifai I, Elsasser Ch, Falabella A, Färber C, Farinelli C, Farry S, Ferguson D, Fernandez Albor V, Ferreira Rodrigues F, Ferro-Luzzi M, Filippov S, Fiore M, Fiorini M, Fitzpatrick C, Fontana M, Fontanelli F, Forty R, Francisco O, Frank M, Frei C, Frosini M, Furfaro E, Gallas Torreira A, Galli D, Gandelman M, Gandini P, Gao Y, Garofoli J, Garosi P, Garra Tico J, Garrido L, Gaspar C, Gauld R, Gersabeck E, Gersabeck M, Gershon T, Ghez P, Gianelle A, Gibson V, Giubega L, Gligorov VV, Göbel C, Golubkov D, Golutvin A, Gomes A, Gordon H, Grabalosa Gándara M, Graciani Diaz R, Granado Cardoso LA, Graugés E, Graziani G, Grecu A, Greening E, Gregson S, Griffith P, Grillo L, Grünberg O, Gui B, Gushchin E, Guz Y, Gys T, Hadjivasiliou C, Haefeli G, Haen C, Hafkenscheid TW, Haines SC, Hall S, Hamilton B, Hampson T, Hansmann-Menzemer S, Harnew N, Harnew ST, Harrison J, Hartmann T, He J, Head T, Heijne V, Hennessy K, Henrard P, Hernando Morata JA, van Herwijnen E, Heß M, Hicheur A, Hill D, Hoballah M, Hombach C, Hulsbergen W, Hunt P, Huse T, Hussain N, Hutchcroft D, Hynds D, Iakovenko V, Idzik M, Ilten P, Jacobsson R, Jaeger A, Jans E, Jaton P, Jawahery A, Jing F, John M, Johnson D, Jones CR, Joram C, Jost B, Jurik N, Kaballo M, Kandybei S, Kanso W, Karacson M, Karbach TM, Kenyon IR, Ketel T, Khanji B, Klaver S, Kochebina O, Komarov I, Koopman RF, Koppenburg P, Korolev M, Kozlinskiy A, Kravchuk L, Kreplin K, Kreps M, Krocker G, Krokovny P, Kruse F, Kucharczyk M, Kudryavtsev V, Kurek K, Kvaratskheliya T, La Thi VN, Lacarrere D, Lafferty G, Lai A, Lambert D, Lambert RW, Lanciotti E, Lanfranchi G, Langenbruch C, Latham T, Lazzeroni C, Le Gac R, van Leerdam J, Lees JP, Lefèvre R, Leflat A, Lefrançois J, Leo S, Leroy O, Lesiak T, Leverington B, Li Y, Liles M, Lindner R, Linn C, Lionetto F, Liu B, Liu G, Lohn S, Longstaff I, Lopes JH, Lopez-March N, Lowdon P, Lu H, Lucchesi D, Luisier J, Luo H, Luppi E, Lupton O, Machefert F, Machikhiliyan IV, Maciuc F, Maev O, Malde S, Manca G, Mancinelli G, Maratas J, Marconi U, Marino P, Märki R, Marks J, Martellotti G, Martens A, Martín Sánchez A, Martinelli M, Martinez Santos D, Martins Tostes D, Martynov A, Massafferri A, Matev R, Mathe Z, Matteuzzi C, Mazurov A, McCann M, McCarthy J, McNab A, McNulty R, McSkelly B, Meadows B, Meier F, Meissner M, Merk M, Milanes DA, Minard MN, Molina Rodriguez J, Monteil S, Moran D, Morandin M, Morawski P, Mordà A, Morello MJ, Mountain R, Mous I, Muheim F, Müller K, Muresan R, Muryn B, Muster B, Naik P, Nakada T, Nandakumar R, Nasteva I, Needham M, Neubert S, Neufeld N, Nguyen AD, Nguyen TD, Nguyen-Mau C, Nicol M, Niess V, Niet R, Nikitin N, Nikodem T, Novoselov A, Oblakowska-Mucha A, Obraztsov V, Oggero S, Ogilvy S, Okhrimenko O, Oldeman R, Onderwater G, Orlandea M, Otalora Goicochea JM, Owen P, Oyanguren A, Pal BK, Palano A, Palutan M, Panman J, Papanestis A, Pappagallo M, Pappalardo L, Parkes C, Parkinson CJ, Passaleva G, Patel GD, Patel M, Patrignani C, Pavel-Nicorescu C, Pazos Alvarez A, Pearce A, Pellegrino A, Penso G, Pepe Altarelli M, Perazzini S, Perez Trigo E, Perret P, Perrin-Terrin M, Pescatore L, Pesen E, Pessina G, Petridis K, Petrolini A, Picatoste Olloqui E, Pietrzyk B, Pilař T, Pinci D, Playfer S, Plo Casasus M, Polci F, Polok G, Poluektov A, Polycarpo E, Popov A, Popov D, Popovici B, Potterat C, Powell A, Prisciandaro J, Pritchard A, Prouve C, Pugatch V, Puig Navarro A, Punzi G, Qian W, Rachwal B, Rademacker JH, Rakotomiaramanana B, Rama M, Rangel MS, Raniuk I, Rauschmayr N, Raven G, Redford S, Reichert S, Reid MM, Dos Reis AC, Ricciardi S, Richards A, Rinnert K, Rives Molina V, Roa Romero DA, Robbe P, Roberts DA, Rodrigues AB, Rodrigues E, Rodriguez Perez P, Roiser S, Romanovsky V, Romero Vidal A, Rotondo M, Rouvinet J, Ruf T, Ruffini F, Ruiz H, Ruiz Valls P, Sabatino G, Saborido Silva JJ, Sagidova N, Sail P, Saitta B, Salustino Guimaraes V, Sanmartin Sedes B, Santacesaria R, Santamarina Rios C, Santovetti E, Sapunov M, Sarti A, Satriano C, Satta A, Savrie M, Savrina D, Schiller M, Schindler H, Schlupp M, Schmelling M, Schmidt B, Schneider O, Schopper A, Schune MH, Schwemmer R, Sciascia B, Sciubba A, Seco M, Semennikov A, Senderowska K, Sepp I, Serra N, Serrano J, Seyfert P, Shapkin M, Shapoval I, Shcheglov Y, Shears T, Shekhtman L, Shevchenko O, Shevchenko V, Shires A, Silva Coutinho R, Simi G, Sirendi M, Skidmore N, Skwarnicki T, Smith NA, Smith E, Smith E, Smith J, Smith M, Snoek H, Sokoloff MD, Soler FJ, Soomro F, Souza D, Souza De Paula B, Spaan B, Sparkes A, Spradlin P, Stagni F, Stahl S, Steinkamp O, Stevenson S, Stoica S, Stone S, Storaci B, Stracka S, Straticiuc M, Straumann U, Stroili R, Subbiah VK, Sun L, Sutcliffe W, Swientek S, Syropoulos V, Szczekowski M, Szczypka P, Szilard D, Szumlak T, T'jampens S, Teklishyn M, Tellarini G, Teodorescu E, Teubert F, Thomas C, Thomas E, van Tilburg J, Tisserand V, Tobin M, Tolk S, Tomassetti L, Tonelli D, Topp-Joergensen S, Torr N, Tournefier E, Tourneur S, Tran MT, Tresch M, Tsaregorodtsev A, Tsopelas P, Tuning N, Ubeda Garcia M, Ukleja A, Ustyuzhanin A, Uwer U, Vagnoni V, Valenti G, Vallier A, Vazquez Gomez R, Vazquez Regueiro P, Vázquez Sierra C, Vecchi S, Velthuis JJ, Veltri M, Veneziano G, Vesterinen M, Viaud B, Vieira D, Vilasis-Cardona X, Vollhardt A, Volyanskyy D, Voong D, Vorobyev A, Vorobyev V, Voß C, Voss H, de Vries JA, Waldi R, Wallace C, Wallace R, Wandernoth S, Wang J, Ward DR, Warrington N, Watson NK, Webber AD, Websdale D, Whitehead M, Wicht J, Wiechczynski J, Wiedner D, Wiggers L, Wilkinson G, Williams MP, Williams M, Wilson FF, Wimberley J, Wishahi J, Wislicki W, Witek M, Wormser G, Wotton SA, Wright S, Wu S, Wyllie K, Xie Y, Xing Z, Yang Z, Yuan X, Yushchenko O, Zangoli M, Zavertyaev M, Zhang F, Zhang L, Zhang WC, Zhang Y, Zhelezov A, Zhokhov A, Zhong L, Zvyagin A; (LHCb Collaboration).

Phys Rev Lett. 2014 Mar 21;112(11):111802. Epub 2014 Mar 19.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:04:13">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24686637</link><title>CROW bottles.</title><description>Sumetsky M.

Opt Lett. 2014 Apr 1;39(7):1913-6. doi: 10.1364/OL.39.001913.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:08:49">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24671752</link><title>Susceptibility of European Jackdaws (Corvus monedula) to Experimental Infection with Lineage 1 and 2 West Nile Viruses.</title><description>Lim SM, Brault AC, van Amerongen G, Sewbalaksing VD, Osterhaus AD, Martina BE, Koraka P.

J Gen Virol. 2014 Mar 26. doi: 10.1099/vir.0.063651-0. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:18">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24671252</link><title>Using the Aesop's Fable Paradigm to Investigate Causal Understanding of Water Displacement by New Caledonian Crows.</title><description>Jelbert SA, Taylor AH, Cheke LG, Clayton NS, Gray RD.

PLoS One. 2014 Mar 26;9(3):e92895. doi: 10.1371/journal.pone.0092895. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:12:39">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24661999</link><title>Atrazine contamination at the watershed scale and environmental factors affecting sampling rates of the polar organic chemical integrative sampler (POCIS).</title><description>Dalton RL, Pick FR, Boutin C, Saleem A.

Environ Pollut. 2014 Mar 21;189C:134-142. doi: 10.1016/j.envpol.2014.02.028. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:26">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24655242</link><title>Observation of B¯(s)0→J/ψ f1(1285) Decays and Measurement of the f1(1285) Mixing Angle.</title><description>Aaij R, Adeva B, Adinolfi M, Adrover C, Affolder A, Ajaltouni Z, Albrecht J, Alessio F, Alexander M, Ali S, Alkhazov G, Alvarez Cartelle P, Alves AA Jr, Amato S, Amerio S, Amhis Y, Anderlini L, Anderson J, Andreassen R, Andreotti M, Andrews JE, Appleby RB, Aquines Gutierrez O, Archilli F, Artamonov A, Artuso M, Aslanides E, Auriemma G, Baalouch M, Bachmann S, Back JJ, Badalov A, Baesso C, Balagura V, Baldini W, Barlow RJ, Barschel C, Barsuk S, Barter W, Batozskaya V, Bauer T, Bay A, Beddow J, Bedeschi F, Bediaga I, Belogurov S, Belous K, Belyaev I, Ben-Haim E, Bencivenni G, Benson S, Benton J, Berezhnoy A, Bernet R, Bettler MO, van Beuzekom M, Bien A, Bifani S, Bird T, Bizzeti A, Bjørnstad PM, Blake T, Blanc F, Blouw J, Blusk S, Bocci V, Bondar A, Bondar N, Bonivento W, Borghi S, Borgia A, Bowcock TJ, Bowen E, Bozzi C, Brambach T, van den Brand J, Bressieux J, Brett D, Britsch M, Britton T, Brook NH, Brown H, Bursche A, Busetto G, Buytaert J, Cadeddu S, Calabrese R, Callot O, Calvi M, Calvo Gomez M, Camboni A, Campana P, Campora Perez D, Carbone A, Carboni G, Cardinale R, Cardini A, Carranza-Mejia H, Carson L, Carvalho Akiba K, Casse G, Castillo Garcia L, Cattaneo M, Cauet Ch, Cenci R, Charles M, Charpentier P, Cheung SF, Chiapolini N, Chrzaszcz M, Ciba K, Cid Vidal X, Ciezarek G, Clarke PE, Clemencic M, Cliff HV, Closier J, Coca C, Coco V, Cogan J, Cogneras E, Collins P, Comerma-Montells A, Contu A, Cook A, Coombes M, Coquereau S, Corti G, Couturier B, Cowan GA, Craik DC, Cruz Torres M, Cunliffe S, Currie R, D'Ambrosio C, David P, David PN, Davis A, De Bonis I, De Bruyn K, De Capua S, De Cian M, De Miranda JM, De Paula L, De Silva W, De Simone P, Decamp D, Deckenhoff M, Del Buono L, Déléage N, Derkach D, Deschamps O, Dettori F, Di Canto A, Dijkstra H, Dogaru M, Donleavy S, Dordei F, Dosil Suárez A, Dossett D, Dovbnya A, Dupertuis F, Durante P, Dzhelyadin R, Dziurda A, Dzyuba A, Easo S, Egede U, Egorychev V, Eidelman S, van Eijk D, Eisenhardt S, Eitschberger U, Ekelhof R, Eklund L, El Rifai I, Elsasser Ch, Falabella A, Färber C, Farinelli C, Farry S, Ferguson D, Fernandez Albor V, Ferreira Rodrigues F, Ferro-Luzzi M, Filippov S, Fiore M, Fiorini M, Fitzpatrick C, Fontana M, Fontanelli F, Forty R, Francisco O, Frank M, Frei C, Frosini M, Furfaro E, Gallas Torreira A, Galli D, Gandelman M, Gandini P, Gao Y, Garofoli J, Garosi P, Garra Tico J, Garrido L, Gaspar C, Gauld R, Gersabeck E, Gersabeck M, Gershon T, Ghez P, Gibson V, Giubega L, Gligorov VV, Göbel C, Golubkov D, Golutvin A, Gomes A, Gorbounov P, Gordon H, Grabalosa Gándara M, Graciani Diaz R, Granado Cardoso LA, Graugés E, Graziani G, Grecu A, Greening E, Gregson S, Griffith P, Grillo L, Grünberg O, Gui B, Gushchin E, Guz Y, Gys T, Hadjivasiliou C, Haefeli G, Haen C, Hafkenscheid TW, Haines SC, Hall S, Hamilton B, Hampson T, Hansmann-Menzemer S, Harnew N, Harnew ST, Harrison J, Hartmann T, He J, Head T, Heijne V, Hennessy K, Henrard P, Hernando Morata JA, van Herwijnen E, Heß M, Hicheur A, Hicks E, Hill D, Hoballah M, Hombach C, Hulsbergen W, Hunt P, Huse T, Hussain N, Hutchcroft D, Hynds D, Iakovenko V, Idzik M, Ilten P, Jacobsson R, Jaeger A, Jans E, Jaton P, Jawahery A, Jing F, John M, Johnson D, Jones CR, Joram C, Jost B, Kaballo M, Kandybei S, Kanso W, Karacson M, Karbach TM, Kenyon IR, Ketel T, Khanji B, Kochebina O, Komarov I, Koopman RF, Koppenburg P, Korolev M, Kozlinskiy A, Kravchuk L, Kreplin K, Kreps M, Krocker G, Krokovny P, Kruse F, Kucharczyk M, Kudryavtsev V, Kurek K, Kvaratskheliya T, La Thi VN, Lacarrere D, Lafferty G, Lai A, Lambert D, Lambert RW, Lanciotti E, Lanfranchi G, Langenbruch C, Latham T, Lazzeroni C, Le Gac R, van Leerdam J, Lees JP, Lefèvre R, Leflat A, Lefrançois J, Leo S, Leroy O, Lesiak T, Leverington B, Li Y, Li Gioi L, Liles M, Lindner R, Linn C, Liu B, Liu G, Lohn S, Longstaff I, Lopes JH, Lopez-March N, Lu H, Lucchesi D, Luisier J, Luo H, Luppi E, Lupton O, Machefert F, Machikhiliyan IV, Maciuc F, Maev O, Malde S, Manca G, Mancinelli G, Maratas J, Marconi U, Marino P, Märki R, Marks J, Martellotti G, Martens A, Martín Sánchez A, Martinelli M, Martinez Santos D, Martins Tostes D, Martynov A, Massafferri A, Matev R, Mathe Z, Matteuzzi C, Maurice E, Mazurov A, McCann M, McCarthy J, McNab A, McNulty R, McSkelly B, Meadows B, Meier F, Meissner M, Merk M, Milanes DA, Minard MN, Molina Rodriguez J, Monteil S, Moran D, Morawski P, Mordà A, Morello MJ, Mountain R, Mous I, Muheim F, Müller K, Muresan R, Muryn B, Muster B, Naik P, Nakada T, Nandakumar R, Nasteva I, Needham M, Neubert S, Neufeld N, Nguyen AD, Nguyen TD, Nguyen-Mau C, Nicol M, Niess V, Niet R, Nikitin N, Nikodem T, Nomerotski A, Novoselov A, Oblakowska-Mucha A, Obraztsov V, Oggero S, Ogilvy S, Okhrimenko O, Oldeman R, Onderwater G, Orlandea M, Otalora Goicochea JM, Owen P, Oyanguren A, Pal BK, Palano A, Palutan M, Panman J, Papanestis A, Pappagallo M, Parkes C, Parkinson CJ, Passaleva G, Patel GD, Patel M, Patrick GN, Patrignani C, Pavel-Nicorescu C, Pazos Alvarez A, Pearce A, Pellegrino A, Penso G, Pepe Altarelli M, Perazzini S, Perez Trigo E, Pérez-Calero Yzquierdo A, Perret P, Perrin-Terrin M, Pescatore L, Pesen E, Pessina G, Petridis K, Petrolini A, Phan A, Picatoste Olloqui E, Pietrzyk B, Pilař T, Pinci D, Playfer S, Plo Casasus M, Polci F, Polok G, Poluektov A, Polycarpo E, Popov A, Popov D, Popovici B, Potterat C, Powell A, Prisciandaro J, Pritchard A, Prouve C, Pugatch V, Puig Navarro A, Punzi G, Qian W, Rachwal B, Rademacker JH, Rakotomiaramanana B, Rangel MS, Raniuk I, Rauschmayr N, Raven G, Redford S, Reichert S, Reid MM, Dos Reis AC, Ricciardi S, Richards A, Rinnert K, Rives Molina V, Roa Romero DA, Robbe P, Roberts DA, Rodrigues AB, Rodrigues E, Rodriguez Perez P, Roiser S, Romanovsky V, Romero Vidal A, Rotondo M, Rouvinet J, Ruf T, Ruffini F, Ruiz H, Ruiz Valls P, Sabatino G, Saborido Silva JJ, Sagidova N, Sail P, Saitta B, Salustino Guimaraes V, Sanmartin Sedes B, Santacesaria R, Santamarina Rios C, Santovetti E, Sapunov M, Sarti A, Satriano C, Satta A, Savrie M, Savrina D, Schiller M, Schindler H, Schlupp M, Schmelling M, Schmidt B, Schneider O, Schopper A, Schune MH, Schwemmer R, Sciascia B, Sciubba A, Seco M, Semennikov A, Senderowska K, Sepp I, Serra N, Serrano J, Seyfert P, Shapkin M, Shapoval I, Shcheglov Y, Shears T, Shekhtman L, Shevchenko O, Shevchenko V, Shires A, Silva Coutinho R, Sirendi M, Skidmore N, Skwarnicki T, Smith NA, Smith E, Smith E, Smith J, Smith M, Sokoloff MD, Soler FJ, Soomro F, Souza D, Souza De Paula B, Spaan B, Sparkes A, Spradlin P, Stagni F, Stahl S, Steinkamp O, Stevenson S, Stoica S, Stone S, Storaci B, Straticiuc M, Straumann U, Subbiah VK, Sun L, Sutcliffe W, Swientek S, Syropoulos V, Szczekowski M, Szczypka P, Szilard D, Szumlak T, T'jampens S, Teklishyn M, Tellarini G, Teodorescu E, Teubert F, Thomas C, Thomas E, van Tilburg J, Tisserand V, Tobin M, Tolk S, Tomassetti L, Tonelli D, Topp-Joergensen S, Torr N, Tournefier E, Tourneur S, Tran MT, Tresch M, Tsaregorodtsev A, Tsopelas P, Tuning N, Ubeda Garcia M, Ukleja A, Ustyuzhanin A, Uwer U, Vagnoni V, Valenti G, Vallier A, Vazquez Gomez R, Vazquez Regueiro P, Vázquez Sierra C, Vecchi S, Velthuis JJ, Veltri M, Veneziano G, Vesterinen M, Viaud B, Vieira D, Vilasis-Cardona X, Vollhardt A, Volyanskyy D, Voong D, Vorobyev A, Vorobyev V, Voß C, Voss H, Waldi R, Wallace C, Wallace R, Wandernoth S, Wang J, Ward DR, Watson NK, Webber AD, Websdale D, Whitehead M, Wicht J, Wiechczynski J, Wiedner D, Wiggers L, Wilkinson G, Williams MP, Williams M, Wilson FF, Wimberley J, Wishahi J, Wislicki W, Witek M, Wormser G, Wotton SA, Wright S, Wu S, Wyllie K, Xie Y, Xing Z, Yang Z, Yuan X, Yushchenko O, Zangoli M, Zavertyaev M, Zhang F, Zhang L, Zhang WC, Zhang Y, Zhelezov A, Zhokhov A, Zhong L, Zvyagin A; (LHCb Collaboration).

Phys Rev Lett. 2014 Mar 7;112(9):091802. Epub 2014 Mar 4.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:17:32">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24653032</link><title>From parasitism to mutualism: unexpected interactions between a cuckoo and its host.</title><description>Canestrari D, Bolopo D, Turlings TC, Röder G, Marcos JM, Baglione V.

Science. 2014 Mar 21;343(6177):1350-2. doi: 10.1126/science.1249008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:52">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24619315</link><title>Ethoxyresorufin-O-deethylase (EROD) induction by TCDD, PeCDF and PCB 126 in bobwhite quail hepatocytes.</title><description>Jones SP, Farmahin R, Kennedy SW.

Ecotoxicology. 2014 Mar 12. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>