<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:01" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:02">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24740291</link><title>Association of blood lead level with neurological features in 972 children affected by an acute severe lead poisoning outbreak in zamfara state, northern Nigeria.</title><description>Greig J, Thurtle N, Cooney L, Ariti C, Ahmed AO, Ashagre T, Ayela A, Chukwumalu K, Criado-Perez A, Gómez-Restrepo C, Meredith C, Neri A, Stellmach D, Sani-Gwarzo N, Nasidi A, Shanks L, Dargan PI.

PLoS One. 2014 Apr 16;9(4):e93716. doi: 10.1371/journal.pone.0093716. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:54">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24739034</link><title>Presumptive cocaine toxicosis in 19 dogs: 2004-2012.</title><description>Thomas EK, Drobatz KJ, Mandell DC.

J Vet Emerg Crit Care (San Antonio). 2014 Mar;24(2):201-7. doi: 10.1111/vec.12159.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:18:44">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24729021</link><title>A 30-year experience of Millin's retropubic prostatectomy: Has this classic operation derived by a President of the College in Ireland stood the test of time?</title><description>Long RM, Thomas AZ, Browne C, Alsinnawi M, Ul-Islam J, McDermott TE, Grainger R, Thornhill JA.

Ir J Med Sci. 2014 Apr 13. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:21:22">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24726424</link><title>Pre-operative mortality risk assessment in patients with continuous-flow left ventricular assist devices: Application of the HeartMate II risk score.</title><description>Thomas SS, Nahumi N, Han J, Lippel M, Colombo P, Yuzefpolskaya M, Takayama H, Naka Y, Uriel N, Jorde UP.

J Heart Lung Transplant. 2014 Feb 14. pii: S1053-2498(14)00973-5. doi: 10.1016/j.healun.2014.02.011. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:26:10">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24726228</link><title>Old stones' song: Use-wear experiments and analysis of the Oldowan quartz and quartzite assemblage from Kanjera South (Kenya).</title><description>Lemorini C, Plummer TW, Braun DR, Crittenden AN, Ditchfield PW, Bishop LC, Hertel F, Oliver JS, Marlowe FW, Schoeninger MJ, Potts R.

J Hum Evol. 2014 Apr 10. pii: S0047-2484(14)00064-5. doi: 10.1016/j.jhevol.2014.03.002. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:51">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24725435</link><title>Design, synthesis and pharmacological evaluation of novel polycyclic heteroarene ethers as PDE10A inhibitors: Part I.</title><description>Das S, Harde RL, Shelke DE, Khairatkar-Joshi N, Bajpai M, Sapalya RS, Surve HV, Gudi GS, Pattem R, Behera DB, Jadhav SB, Thomas A.

Bioorg Med Chem Lett. 2014 Mar 28. pii: S0960-894X(14)00281-9. doi: 10.1016/j.bmcl.2014.03.054. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:00">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24723852</link><title>Dynamical criticality during induction of anesthesia in human ECoG recordings.</title><description>Alonso LM, Proekt A, Schwartz TH, Pryor KO, Cecchi GA, Magnasco MO.

Front Neural Circuits. 2014 Mar 25;8:20. doi: 10.3389/fncir.2014.00020. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:37:19">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24720288</link><title>Piloting a Nationally Disseminated, Interactive Human Subjects Protection Program for Community Partners: Design, Content, and Evaluation.</title><description>Solomon S, Eakin B, Kirk R, Piechowski P, Thomas B.

Clin Transl Sci. 2014 Apr 10. doi: 10.1111/cts.12154. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:42:01">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24719269</link><title>Noncancer-related mortality risks in adult survivors of pediatric malignancies: the childhood cancer survivor study.</title><description>Cox CL, Nolan VG, Leisenring W, Yasui Y, Ogg SW, Mertens AC, Neglia JP, Ness KK, Armstrong GT, Robison LL.

J Cancer Surviv. 2014 Apr 10. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:38">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24717097</link><title>Prognostic value of inflammation or granuloma after intravesival BCG in non-muscle-invasive bladder cancer.</title><description>Jallad S, Goubet S, Symes A, Larner T, Thomas P.

BJU Int. 2013 Dec 20. doi: 10.1111/bju.12334. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>