<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:15:37" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:15:39">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24305548</link><title>Guiding the osteogenic fate of mouse and human mesenchymal stem cells through feedback system control.</title><description>Honda Y, Ding X, Mussano F, Wiberg A, Ho CM, Nishimura I.

Sci Rep. 2013 Dec 5;3:3420. doi: 10.1038/srep03420.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:16:59">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24226770</link><title>Commensal microbe-derived butyrate induces the differentiation of colonic regulatory T cells.</title><description>Furusawa Y, Obata Y, Fukuda S, Endo TA, Nakato G, Takahashi D, Nakanishi Y, Uetake C, Kato K, Kato T, Takahashi M, Fukuda NN, Murakami S, Miyauchi E, Hino S, Atarashi K, Onawa S, Fujimura Y, Lockett T, Clarke JM, Topping DL, Tomita M, Hori S, Ohara O, Morita T, Koseki H, Kikuchi J, Honda K, Hase K, Ohno H.

Nature. 2013 Dec 19;504(7480):446-50. doi: 10.1038/nature12721. Epub 2013 Nov 13. Erratum in: Nature. 2014 Feb 13;506(7487):254.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:18:04">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23792918</link><title>From placode to labyrinth: Culture of the chicken inner ear.</title><description>Honda A, Freeman SD, Sai X, Ladher RK, O'Neill P.

Methods. 2014 Apr 1;66(3):447-53. doi: 10.1016/j.ymeth.2013.06.011. Epub 2013 Jun 20.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:19:45">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23583447</link><title>CIZ1, a p21Cip1/Waf1-interacting protein, functions as a tumor suppressor in vivo.</title><description>Nishibe R, Watanabe W, Ueda T, Yamasaki N, Koller R, Wolff L, Honda Z, Ohtsubo M, Honda H.

FEBS Lett. 2013 May 21;587(10):1529-35. doi: 10.1016/j.febslet.2013.03.034. Epub 2013 Apr 11.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:22:10">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23457535</link><title>Biomarkers and bacterial pneumonia risk in patients with treated HIV infection: a case-control study.</title><description>Bjerk SM, Baker JV, Emery S, Neuhaus J, Angus B, Gordin FM, Pett SL, Stephan C, Kunisaki KM; INSIGHT SMART Study Group.

PLoS One. 2013;8(2):e56249. doi: 10.1371/journal.pone.0056249. Epub 2013 Feb 15.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:23:17">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23323731</link><title>Tapping-mode AFM study of tip-induced polymer deformation under geometrical confinement.</title><description>Zhang H, Honda Y, Takeoka S.

Langmuir. 2013 Feb 5;29(5):1333-9. doi: 10.1021/la304280h. Epub 2013 Jan 23.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:23:54">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23169138</link><title>Kinematic Comparison of the Hybrid III and Q-Series Pediatric ATDs to Pediatric Volunteers in Low-Speed Frontal Crashes.</title><description>Seacrist T, Samuels M, García-España JF, Arbogast KB, Mathews EA, Balasubramanian S, Maltese MR, Longhitano D, St Lawrence S.

Ann Adv Automot Med. 2012;56:285-98.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:26:23">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22673877</link><title>The induction of Treg cells by gut-indigenous Clostridium.</title><description>Nagano Y, Itoh K, Honda K.

Curr Opin Immunol. 2012 Aug;24(4):392-7. doi: 10.1016/j.coi.2012.05.007. Epub 2012 Jun 4. Review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:28:21">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22612501</link><title>Leucine-rich glioma inactivated 1 (Lgi1), an epilepsy-related secreted protein, has a nuclear localization signal and localizes to both the cytoplasm and the nucleus of the caudal ganglionic eminence neurons.</title><description>Kusuzawa S, Honda T, Fukata Y, Fukata M, Kanatani S, Tanaka DH, Nakajima K.

Eur J Neurosci. 2012 Aug;36(3):2284-92. doi: 10.1111/j.1460-9568.2012.08129.x. Epub 2012 May 22.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:28:57">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22434909</link><title>Comparative genomics of Ceriporiopsis subvermispora and Phanerochaete chrysosporium provide insight into selective ligninolysis.</title><description>Fernandez-Fueyo E, Ruiz-Dueñas FJ, Ferreira P, Floudas D, Hibbett DS, Canessa P, Larrondo LF, James TY, Seelenfreund D, Lobos S, Polanco R, Tello M, Honda Y, Watanabe T, Watanabe T, Ryu JS, Kubicek CP, Schmoll M, Gaskell J, Hammel KE, St John FJ, Vanden Wymelenberg A, Sabat G, Splinter BonDurant S, Syed K, Yadav JS, Doddapaneni H, Subramanian V, Lavín JL, Oguiza JA, Perez G, Pisabarro AG, Ramirez L, Santoyo F, Master E, Coutinho PM, Henrissat B, Lombard V, Magnuson JK, Kües U, Hori C, Igarashi K, Samejima M, Held BW, Barry KW, LaButti KM, Lapidus A, Lindquist EA, Lucas SM, Riley R, Salamov AA, Hoffmeister D, Schwenk D, Hadar Y, Yarden O, de Vries RP, Wiebenga A, Stenlid J, Eastwood D, Grigoriev IV, Berka RM, Blanchette RA, Kersten P, Martinez AT, Vicuna R, Cullen D.

Proc Natl Acad Sci U S A. 2012 Apr 3;109(14):5458-63. doi: 10.1073/pnas.1119912109. Epub 2012 Mar 20. Erratum in: Proc Natl Acad Sci U S A. 2012 May 22;109(21):8352. San, Ryu Jae [corrected to Ryu, Jae San].</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>