<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7431">navalni trial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:49:40" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:49:41">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23536935</link><title>Reply: endobronchial ultrasound–guided transbronchial needle aspiration versus cervical mediastinoscopy: case selection is needed to maintain clinical as well as cost benefits.</title><description>Navani N, Janes SM; REMEDY Trial Management Group.

Am J Respir Crit Care Med. 2013 Feb 15;187(4):449. No abstract available.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:50:41">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23211715</link><title>Interim data from the Medical Research Council QUARTZ Trial: does whole brain radiotherapy affect the survival and quality of life of patients with brain metastases from non-small cell lung cancer?</title><description>Langley RE, Stephens RJ, Nankivell M, Pugh C, Moore B, Navani N, Wilson P, Faivre-Finn C, Barton R, Parmar MK, Mulvenna PM; QUARTZ Investigators.

Clin Oncol (R Coll Radiol). 2013 Mar;25(3):e23-30. doi: 10.1016/j.clon.2012.11.002. Epub 2012 Dec 2.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:52:33">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22652031</link><title>Endobronchial ultrasound-guided transbronchial needle aspiration prevents mediastinoscopies in the diagnosis of isolated mediastinal lymphadenopathy: a prospective trial.</title><description>Navani N, Lawrence DR, Kolvekar S, Hayward M, McAsey D, Kocjan G, Falzon M, Capitanio A, Shaw P, Morris S, Omar RZ, Janes SM; REMEDY Trial Investigators.

Am J Respir Crit Care Med. 2012 Aug 1;186(3):255-60. Epub 2012 May 31.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:53:42">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22142440</link><title>Screening for lung cancer: is this the way forward?</title><description>Spiro SG, Navani N.

Respirology. 2012 Feb;17(2):237-46. doi: 10.1111/j.1440-1843.2011.02114.x. Review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:54:32">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20932667</link><title>Induction chemotherapy and continuous hyperfractionated accelerated radiotherapy (chart) for patients with locally advanced inoperable non-small-cell lung cancer: the MRC INCH randomized trial.</title><description>Hatton M, Nankivell M, Lyn E, Falk S, Pugh C, Navani N, Stephens R, Parmar M.

Int J Radiat Oncol Biol Phys. 2011 Nov 1;81(3):712-8. doi: 10.1016/j.ijrobp.2010.06.053. Epub 2010 Oct 6.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:56:08">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20435873</link><title>Inaccurate clinical nodal staging of non-small cell lung cancer: evidence from the MRC LU22 multicentre randomised trial.</title><description>Navani N, Nankivell M, Stephens RJ, Parmar MK, Gilligan D, Nicolson M, Groen HJ, van Meerbeeck JP.

Thorax. 2010 May;65(5):463. doi: 10.1136/thx.2009.118471. No abstract available.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:57:16">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19390554</link><title>Mediastinal staging of NSCLC with endoscopic and endobronchial ultrasound.</title><description>Navani N, Spiro SG, Janes SM.

Nat Rev Clin Oncol. 2009 May;6(5):278-86. doi: 10.1038/nrclinonc.2009.39. Review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:59:17">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17270340</link><title>Tamoxifen as prophylaxis for prevention of gynaecomastia and breast pain associated with bicalutamide 150 mg monotherapy in patients with prostate cancer: a randomised, placebo-controlled, dose-response study.</title><description>Fradet Y, Egerdie B, Andersen M, Tammela TL, Nachabe M, Armstrong J, Morris T, Navani S.

Eur Urol. 2007 Jul;52(1):106-14. Epub 2007 Jan 16.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:01:14">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17102802</link><title>Bicalutamide (Casodex) 150 mg plus standard care in early non-metastatic prostate cancer: results from Early Prostate Cancer Trial 24 at a median 7 years' follow-up.</title><description>Wirth M, Tyrrell C, Delaere K, Sánchez-Chapado M, Ramon J, Wallace DM, Hetherington J, Pina F, Heyns CF, Navani S, Armstrong J.

Prostate Cancer Prostatic Dis. 2007;10(1):87-93. Epub 2006 Nov 14.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7431-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7431_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:02:29">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/12088807</link><title>The effects of thiopental and generic and nongeneric propofol on respiratory resistance during anesthetic induction in patients with reactive airways.</title><description>Arain SR, Navani A, Ebert TJ.

J Clin Anesth. 2002 Jun;14(4):257-61.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>