<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:48:13" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:48:14">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24748394</link><title>IFNL4 ss469415590 Variant Shows Similar Performance to rs12979860 as Predictor of Response to Treatment against Hepatitis C Virus Genotype 1 or 4 in Caucasians.</title><description>Real LM, Neukam K, Herrero R, Guardiola JM, Reiberger T, Rivero-Juarez A, Salazar J, Mandorfer M, Merino D, Soriano V, Rivero A, Macías J, Pineda JA, Caruz A.

PLoS One. 2014 Apr 18;9(4):e95515. doi: 10.1371/journal.pone.0095515. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:49:58">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24746914</link><title>Recommendations for the use of methotrexate in rheumatoid arthritis: Up and down scaling of the dose and administration routes.</title><description>Tornero Molina J, Ballina García FJ, Calvo Alén J, Caracuel Ruiz MA, Carbonell Abelló J, López Meseguer A, Moreno Muelas JV, Pérez Sandoval T, Quijada Carrera J, Trenor Larraz P, Zea Mendoza A.

Reumatol Clin. 2014 Apr 16. pii: S1699-258X(14)00059-X. doi: 10.1016/j.reuma.2014.02.012. [Epub ahead of print] English, Spanish.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:51:41">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24731787</link><title>Next-generation Sequencing of Urologic Cancers: Next Is Now.</title><description>Real FX, Boutros PC, Malats N.

Eur Urol. 2014 Apr 5. pii: S0302-2838(14)00281-4. doi: 10.1016/j.eururo.2014.03.028. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:53:16">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24725617</link><title>Strategic Plan for the Spanish Academy of Dermatology and Venerology (AEDV): FuturAEDV 2013-2017.</title><description>Ribera Pibernat M, Moreno Jiménez JC, Valcuende Cavero F, Soto de Delás J, Vázquez Veiga H, Lázaro Ochaíta P, Giménez Arnau A; en nombre de la junta directiva de la AEDV.

Actas Dermosifiliogr. 2014 Apr 9. pii: S0001-7310(14)00100-8. doi: 10.1016/j.ad.2014.02.008. [Epub ahead of print] English, Spanish.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:54:06">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24629637</link><title>Tumor, node and metastasis classification of lung cancer - M1a versus M1b - Analysis of M descriptors and other prognostic factors.</title><description>Sánchez de Cos Escuín J, Abal Arca J, Melchor Íñiguez R, Miravet Sorribes L, Núñez Ares A, Hernández Hernández JR, García Arangüena L, Núñez Delgado M, Pavón Fernández MJ, Francisco Corral G, de Esteban Júlvez L, González Budiño MT, Abad Cavaco F, Ansótegui Barrera E, Andreo García F, Serra Mitjans M, Hernández Rodríguez H.

Lung Cancer. 2014 Feb 23. pii: S0169-5002(14)00092-0. doi: 10.1016/j.lungcan.2014.02.006. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:55:36">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24611019</link><title>Antibiotic expected effectiveness and cost under real life microbiology: evaluation of ertapenem and ceftriaxone in the treatment of community-acquired pneumonia for elderly patients in Spain.</title><description>Grau S, Lozano V, Valladares A, Cavanillas R, Xie Y, Nocea G.

Clinicoecon Outcomes Res. 2014 Feb 13;6:83-92. doi: 10.2147/CEOR.S55265. eCollection 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:56:31">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24595004</link><title>LINE-1 methylation in leukocyte DNA, interaction with phosphatidylethanolamine N-methyltransferase variants and bladder cancer risk.</title><description>Tajuddin SM, Amaral AF, Fernández AF, Chanock S, Silverman DT, Tardón A, Carrato A, García-Closas M, Jackson BP, Toraño EG, Márquez M, Urdinguio RG, García-Closas R, Rothman N, Kogevinas M, Real FX, Fraga MF, Malats N; Spanish Bladder Cancer/EPICURO Study investigators.

Br J Cancer. 2014 Apr 15;110(8):2123-30. doi: 10.1038/bjc.2014.67. Epub 2014 Mar 4.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:57:19">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24576784</link><title>John Singer Sargent, Spain and the horrors of chemical warfare.</title><description>González Martín-Moro J, Azurza Rivas G.

Arch Soc Esp Oftalmol. 2014 Mar;89(3):e16-e18. doi: 10.1016/j.oftal.2013.09.005. Epub 2014 Feb 24. English, Spanish. No abstract available.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:57:49">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24461732</link><title>[FRAX® thresholds to identify people with high or low risk of osteoporotic fracture in Spanish female population.]</title><description>Azagra R, Roca G, Martín-Sánchez JC, Casado E, Encabo G, Zwart M, Aguyé A, Díez-Pérez A; en representación del grupo de investigación GROIMAP.

Med Clin (Barc). 2014 Jan 23. pii: S0025-7753(13)00844-0. doi: 10.1016/j.medcli.2013.11.014. [Epub ahead of print] Spanish.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7440-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7440_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:58:14">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24461346</link><title>Prevalence of plasma lipid abnormalities and its association with glucose metabolism in Spain: The di@bet.es study.</title><description>Martinez-Hervas S, Carmena R, Ascaso JF, Real JT, Masana L, Catalá M, Vendrell J, Vázquez JA, Valdés S, Urrutia I, Soriguer F, Serrano-Rios M, Rojo-Martínez G, Pascual-Manich G, Ortega E, Mora-Peces I, Menéndez E, Martínez-Larrad MT, López-Alba A, Gomis R, Goday A, Girbés J, Gaztambide S, Franch J, Delgado E, Castell C, Castaño L, Casamitjana R, Calle-Pascual A, Bordiú E.

Clin Investig Arterioscler. 2014 Jan 22. pii: S0214-9168(13)00131-9. doi: 10.1016/j.arteri.2013.12.001. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>