<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:13:35" name="PubMed" id="FW14-e017"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:13:36">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24602079</link><title>Atrial Arrhythmias Following Surgical AF Ablation: Electrophysiological Findings, Ablation Strategies, and Clinical Outcome.</title><description>Huo Y, Schoenbauer R, Richter S, Rolf S, Sommer P, Arya A, Rastan A, Doll N, Mohr FW, Hindricks G, Piorkowski C, Gaspar T.

J Cardiovasc Electrophysiol. 2014 Mar 6. doi: 10.1111/jce.12406. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:14:16">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24556188</link><title>Does a patent foramen ovale matter when using a remote-controlled magnetic system for pulmonary vein isolation?</title><description>Gate-Martinet A, Da Costa A, Romeyer-Bouchard C, Bisch L, Levallois M, Isaaz K.

Arch Cardiovasc Dis. 2014 Feb;107(2):88-95. doi: 10.1016/j.acvd.2014.01.003. Epub 2014 Feb 18.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:16:18">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24421207</link><title>Two-staged hybrid treatment of persistent atrial fibrillation: short-term single-centre results.</title><description>Kurfirst V, Mokraček A, Bulava A, Canadyova J, Haniš J, Pešl L.

Interact Cardiovasc Thorac Surg. 2014 Apr;18(4):451-6. doi: 10.1093/icvts/ivt538. Epub 2014 Jan 12.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:18:09">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24370218</link><title>[Clinical characteristics and long-term outcome of non-pulmonary vein foci ablation in patients with paroxysmal atrial fibrillation].</title><description>Chen HW, Chen ML, Yang B, Ju WZ, Zhang FX, Gu K, Li MF, Gao KJ.

Zhonghua Xin Xue Guan Bing Za Zhi. 2013 Nov;41(11):922-6. Chinese.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:18:36">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24363353</link><title>In vivo contact force analysis and correlation with tissue impedance during left atrial mapping and catheter ablation of atrial fibrillation.</title><description>Makimoto H, Lin T, Rillig A, Metzner A, Wohlmuth P, Arya A, Antz M, Mathew S, Deiss S, Wissner E, Rausch P, Bardyszewski A, Kamioka M, Li X, Kuck KH, Ouyang F, Tilz RR.

Circ Arrhythm Electrophysiol. 2014 Feb;7(1):46-54. doi: 10.1161/CIRCEP.113.000556. Epub 2013 Dec 20.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:19:30">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24315152</link><title>Does the amount of atrial mass reduction improve clinical outcomes after radiofrequency catheter ablation for long-standing persistent atrial fibrillation? Comparison between linear ablation and defragmentation.</title><description>Han SW, Shin SY, Im SI, Na JO, Choi CU, Kim SH, Kim JW, Kim EJ, Rha SW, Park CG, Seo HS, Oh DJ, Hwang C, Lim HE.

Int J Cardiol. 2014 Jan 15;171(1):37-43. doi: 10.1016/j.ijcard.2013.11.041. Epub 2013 Nov 23.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:19:58">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24178313</link><title>A modelling study of long term green roof retention performance.</title><description>Stovin V, Poë S, Berretta C.

J Environ Manage. 2013 Dec 15;131:206-15. doi: 10.1016/j.jenvman.2013.09.026. Epub 2013 Oct 27.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:21:09">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24118250</link><title>Relationship Between Complex Fractionated Atrial Electrograms during Atrial Fibrillation and the Critical Site of Atrial Tachycardia That Develops After Catheter Ablation for Atrial Fibrillation.</title><description>Ban JE, Chen YL, Park HC, Lee HS, Lee DI, Choi JI, Lim HE, Park SW, Kim YH.

J Cardiovasc Electrophysiol. 2013 Oct 3. doi: 10.1111/jce.12300. [Epub ahead of print]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:15">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23915587</link><title>Very long-term results of surgical and transcatheter ablation of long-standing persistent atrial fibrillation.</title><description>Gaita F, Ebrille E, Scaglione M, Caponi D, Garberoglio L, Vivalda L, Barbone A, Gallotti R.

Ann Thorac Surg. 2013 Oct;96(4):1273-8. doi: 10.1016/j.athoracsur.2013.05.054. Epub 2013 Jul 31.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e017-7500-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e017/7500_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:48">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23906679</link><title>Remote-controlled magnetic pulmonary vein isolation using a new three-dimensional non-fluoroscopic navigation system: a single-centre prospective study.</title><description>Da Costa A, Ben H'dech M, Romeyer-Bouchard C, Bisch L, Gate-Martinet A, Levallois M, Isaaz K.

Arch Cardiovasc Dis. 2013 Aug-Sep;106(8-9):423-32. doi: 10.1016/j.acvd.2013.04.008. Epub 2013 Jul 29.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>