<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:51:22" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7026-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/keanu-reeves-film-based-on-true-japanese-story660f8c7da1da4d7cb98d75042b14e272-232299651.html</link><title>Keanu Reeves film based on true Japanese story</title><description>TOKYO (AP) The director of the Keanu Reeves 3-D film "47 Ronin" says he hopes his adaptation of a true Japanese story becomes a Hollywood blockbuster. Film director Carl Rinsch, Reeves and co-stars appeared together in front of a Tokyo audience on Monday. The film is based</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7026-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7026_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:51:57">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/movies/keanu-reeves-pummels-man-of-tai-chi-from-both-sides-of-the-camera-b99128096z1-230107231.html</link><title>Movie Review: 2 stars | Keanu Reeves pummels 'Man of Tai Chi' from both sides of the camera</title><description>First-time feature-film director Keanu Reeves’ “Man of Tai Chi” is a pretentious, silly and totally bogus journey. If this year's Winter Olympics were run like a mixed martial arts competition, an ice dancer, a speedskater and a hockey player would be locked in an octagonal cage and forced to fight</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7026-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/asian-star-karen-mok-looks-west-with-jazz-album9bc3302a722a4afba47d1ccead705cee-189758361.html</link><title>Asian star Karen Mok looks West with jazz album</title><description>HONG KONG (AP) After years of stardom in Asia, Hong Kong actress and singer Karen Mok hopes her first English album and an action film directed by Keanu Reeves translate into success in the West. Mok has released 15 Chinese language albums and starred in more than 40</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7026-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7026_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:58:45">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/139216359.html</link><title>Film is dead, here is its epitaph</title><description>Film is dead and here is its epitaph, written by "Matrix" star Keanu Reeves of all people who directs "Side by Side," a documentary about the rise of digital cinema showing at the Berlin Film Festival. "I felt like I should call film on my phone and tell it</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7026-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7026_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:01:57">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/movies/holiday-movie-preview-2013-the-hobbit-leonardo-dicaprio-julia-roberts-ron-burgundy-and-more-b9914820-233527041.html</link><title>Holiday Movie Preview 2013: 'The Hobbit,' Leonardo DiCaprio, Julia Roberts, Ron Burgundy and more</title><description>Seven films opened Thanksgiving week, another seven are scheduled to open in Milwaukee Dec. 25 — and nine between now and then. Here’s what’s opening when. It's Black Friday at the multiplex, too. Seven films opened Thanksgiving week, and although dates may change, another seven are scheduled to open</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>