<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:04:53" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:04:55">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/business/45870322.html</link><title>What's a preferred share?</title><description>When a company’s balance sheet is in tatters, is an investor any better off holding preferred stock? It’s a question that’s coming up more often these days, as struggling corporations slash dividends, issue stock offerings to raise cash and, in many cases, file for bankruptcy. Amid all</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:49">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/63601592.html</link><title>Hungry men prefer larger women?</title><description>A new study suggests that hungry men prefer larger women . The research, published in the Journal of Social, Evolutionary and Cultural Psychology , confirms and expands upon two previous papers: a 2005 study  that concluded heavier women are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:09:38">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/165625926.html</link><title>Stressed men prefer heavier women, study finds</title><description>Men who are stressed out prefer heavier women, a new study has revealed. Judgments of human attractiveness seem to change depending on environmental conditions that require different adaptive strategies, according to the report published in the journal PLoS ONE . British researchers showed stressed and non-stressed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:14:34">http://www.jsonline.com/news/milwaukee/milwaukee-agrees-to-repeal-ordinance-on-contract-preferences-b9931562z1-211079611.html</link><title>Milwaukee agrees to repeal ordinance on contract preferences</title><description>Under the settlement of a federal lawsuit brought by the Hispanic Chamber of Commerce of Wisconsin, Milwaukee has agreed to repeal an ordinance that was aimed at dealing with race- and gender-based contract preferences for city business. Under the settlement of a federal lawsuit brought by the Hispanic Chamber</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>