<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:36" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:38">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/191271221.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: For Brewers pitchers, it's back to the basics</title><description>On the second day of Spring Training, Brewers pitchers hit the back fields of Maryvale Baseball Park and worked on fundamentals as old as the game - comebackers to the mound, fielding bunts and covering first base.   Righthanded pitcher Mike Fiers gloves a comebacker.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:12">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/191876221.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Welcome to Maryvale, spring home of the Milwaukee Brewers</title><description>The temperature this time of year averages 71 degrees, perfect weather for Brewers workouts at Maryvale Baseball Park in Phoenix. Here's a look at the team's sprawling facility, which will get a minor makeover next year.  Brewers fans get a towering welcome upon entering the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:16:10">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/192359501.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: An icy morning greets the Brewers</title><description>The Brewers might have felt like they were back at home Thursday morning as a winter storm left patches of ice on the field...that's right, ICE in Phoenix.  Go figure! Wednesday's storm left thick blankets of ice around the infield at Maryvale</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:08">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/192579041.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Brewers prep for spring opener</title><description>The Brewers open their exhibition season Saturday against the Oakland A's. To get into the swing of games, they hit the main field at Maryvale Baseball Park for an intrasquad game.   Game day routine started off with batting practice.  Friday's game featured the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:01">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/192753551.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Opening day for the Brewers</title><description>The Brewers kicked off their first exhibition against the Oakland A's on Saturday.  Carlos Gomez slides safely back to first base on a pickoff attempt. Rickie Weeks takes a cut in the first inning.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:25:14">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/193392361.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Milwaukee favorites at Maryvale</title><description>If you’re worried about missing some of your Milwaukee favorites at Maryvale Baseball Park, worry no more.  On deck at the Maryvale concession stands: Bratwurst sausage! ‘Wisconsin Nachos’-Waffle fries, cheese, sour cream, bacon bits and chives are also on the menu.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:29:00">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/194034221.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Maryvale offers different views of Brewers</title><description>With more than 10,000 seating options, Maryvale Baseball Park doesn't fall short on good seats. But who has the best? The fan in the boxseat? The family lounging on the lawn? The P.A. announcer in the press box? Or the usher down the first base line?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:32:10">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/195448011.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Team Canada visits the Brewers</title><description>There was high energy Tuesday at Maryvale Baseball Park especially when Team Canada came up to bat in an exhibition game against the Brewers.  Both the American and Canadian flags fly over the field. Jameson Taillon warms up with</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:33:12">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/196150931.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Brewers Alex Gonzalez making a big splash at first</title><description>With starting first baseman Corey Hart out with an injury for at least the first month of the season, the Brewers are looking to Alex Gonzalez, among others, to fill his spot. On Thursday, he hit a two run homer in the third inning of the Brewers 4-3 victory</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7033-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7033_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:37:05">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/199072491.html</link><title>PHOTO LOOK: Baseball's sign language</title><description>You've got American Sign Language and then you've got baseball. Of course, you know the most basic signs used by umpires like strike and safe. But can you decipher the complex sequences used by players and coaches to talk to each other without opening their mouths? Probably not. And</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>