<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:45:41" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:45:44">http://www.jsonline.com/news/education/sexual-misconduct-hazing-alleged-at-marquette-fraternities-b99248588z1-255370551.html</link><title>Sexual misconduct, hazing alleged at Marquette fraternities | University issues official warnings to 3 fraternities</title><description>The university issued warnings to the three fraternities where sexual misconduct was alleged, and one also was warned for a hazing incident. Marquette University's Division of Student Affairs has issued official warnings to three fraternities following allegations of sexual misconduct and hazing. The warnings related to allegations of sexual</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:48:52">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/250631021.html</link><title>Marquette University alum in 'How I Met Your Mother' spinoff</title><description>Nick D'Agosto, a 2002 Marquette University graduate, has been named one of the co-stars of "How I Met Your Father." The spinoff series of "How I Met Your Mother," will debut this fall.  The 2002 cum laude graduate of the Diedrich College of Communications is currently appearing in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:50:56">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/252046781.html</link><title>On Tap Today: Paul McComas 'Unplugged'</title><description>Twelve years ago, Milwaukee native Paul McComas wrote the book "Unplugged," about a young musician and rape survivor trying to overcome depression and come to terms with her troubled childhood. On Tuesday, the now Evanston-based McComas, along with Chicago-based musician Maya Kuper, will present "Unplugged"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:51:32">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/215904781.html</link><title>Marquette University names new vice president for advancement</title><description>Marquette University has named Michael VanDerhoef as its new vice president for university advancement, a position that leads the university’s fund-raising efforts. VanDerhoef, who currently serves as the president of the Virginia Mason Foundation , a branch of the Virginia Mason</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:55:27">http://www.jsonline.com/news/education/bio-michael-lovell-incoming-marquette-university-president-b99233820z1-252453281.html</link><title>Bio: Michael Lovell, incoming Marquette University president</title><description>A snapshot of UWM Chancellor Michael Lovell’s career as he prepares to take over as president at Marquette University. A snapshot of University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Chancellor Michael Lovell's career as he prepares to take over as president at Marquette University . ■ Education: Earned a bachelor's (1989),</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:59:07">http://www.jsonline.com/news/education/divestment-in-israel-is-topic-of-marquette-university-student-program-b99233418z1-252440481.html</link><title>Divestment in Israel is topic of Marquette University student program</title><description>The issue of divestment in Israel is being raised at Marquette University this week in a series of programs sponsored by a student group. The controversial issue of divestment in Israel was being raised at Marquette University this week in a series of programs sponsored by a student group sympathetic</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:00:01">http://www.jsonline.com/news/education/marquette-university-students-ambivalent-excited-about-new-president-b99234182z1-252506681.html</link><title>Marquette University students ambivalent, excited about new president</title><description>Campus reactions to the first lay president in Marquette University’s 133-year history ranged from ambivalence to excitement Wednesday. Campus reactions to the first lay president in Marquette University's 133-year history ranged from ambivalence to excitement Wednesday as students and faculty learned that Michael Lovell will soon lead the Jesuit</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:16">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/musicandnightlife/author-paul-mccomas-to-perform-at-marquette-university-b99229078z1-251714131.html</link><title>The Week Ahead | Author Paul McComas to perform at Marquette University</title><description>Along with “Time Trek” collaborator Maya Kuper, Paul McComas will be performing songs and scenes inspired by his book “Unplugged,” about a rape survivor in search of inner peace. Milwaukee native Paul McComas doesn't seem like the most serious guy. The last project he presented in town, "Time</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:06:28">http://www.jsonline.com/news/education/former-marquette-university-leader-pilarz-named-head-of-prep-school-b99230558z1-251473121.html</link><title>Former Marquette University leader Pilarz named head of prep school</title><description>Father Scott R. Pilarz, who unexpectedly resigned last fall as president of Marquette University, will start a new job July 1 leading Georgetown Preparatory School. Father Scott R. Pilarz, who unexpectedly resigned last fall as president of Marquette University , will start a new job July 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:07">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/lovell-to-lead-marquette-university-b99233912z1-252460331.html</link><title>Lovell to lead Marquette University</title><description>Lovell will replace Father Scott R. Pilarz, who unexpectedly announced his resignation in September after two years on the job. Interim President Father Robert Wild will remain in the role until Lovell assumes the new position. Lovell will replace Father Scott R. Pilarz, who unexpectedly announced his resignation in September after</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>