<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:13" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/amazon-launches-kindle-content-service-for-kidsd51f602505a34c1ba7ab627c2c39a5f9-182124441.html</link><title>Amazon launches Kindle content service for kids</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Amazon is launching a subscription service for children's games, videos and books aimed at getting more kids to use its Kindle Fire tablet devices. Amazon.com Inc. announced Wednesday that the Kindle FreeTime Unlimited service will be available in the next few weeks as part of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:22:18">http://www.jsonline.com/business/69858427.html</link><title>Journal Sentinel debuts on Amazon's Kindle reader</title><description>The Kindle edition contains all articles that appear in the print edition of the Journal Sentinel. At this time, ads do not appear in the Kindle edition. The Journal Sentinel is available on Amazon's Kindle electronic reading device, the company said Thursday. The Kindle edition contains all articles</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:26:07">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/127448383.html</link><title>Kindle Cloud Reader for iOS &amp; Chrome</title><description>Amazon announced its Kindle Cloud Reader today, a mobile site using HTML5 to let readers enjoy Kindle books using the Safari Web browser iPad, Safari on desktop computers and Google's Chrome. Similar to all of the Kindle apps, Kindle Cloud Reader automatically synchronizes a digital</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:26:38">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/133538623.html</link><title>Amazon highlights apps on the Kindle Fire</title><description>Teasing to the impending release of its budget-friendlier Kindle Fire next week, Amazon today highlighted several of the apps that will be available on the tablet at launch, including Netflix, Rhapsody, Pandora, Twitter and Facebook. The list -- which also includes games from Zynga, EA,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:31:08">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/44453922.html</link><title>With Kindle as a competitor, Sony gets no respect</title><description>So is Sony just getting left in the dust by Amazon? Amazon, uber-book seller and marketer of the Kindle 2, is expected to announce an electronic book reader today that will make it easier to peruse newspapers, magazines and textbooks online. The thing will likely</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:36:27">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/122232923.html</link><title>Amazon selling more e-books than print editions</title><description>Amazon is now selling more Kindle e-books than print books. The company introduced the Kindle in Nov. 2007, and by July 2010 Kindle book sales had surpassed hardcover book sales, the company says. Six months later, Kindle books passed paperbacks, becoming the most popular format sold on the</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>