<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:43:41" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/plan-b-among-nominees-for-britains-mercury-prizeb4a4dd34acaa43cd92a52a4e89342bf1-169496286.html</link><title>Plan B among nominees for Britain's Mercury Prize</title><description>LONDON (AP) Rapper Plan B and singer-songwriter Richard Hawley are the favorites among 12 finalists for Britain's prestigious Mercury music prize. Plan B is nominated for the soundtrack to his film "Ill Manors" and Hawley for his album "Standing at the Sky's Edge." The award was established</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7077_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:45:04">http://www.jsonline.com/news/opinion/django-unchained-represents-a-triumph-of-style-and-substance-8r8us4m-193934571.html</link><title>'Django Unchained' represents a triumph of style and substance</title><description>"Django Unchained" is fresh because it reveals how much of the heart of the story resides, even today, in the style of the telling. I'm glad "Django Unchained" won best original screenplay at the Oscars on Sunday. For months, I avoided "Django Unchained," assuming that it would be another</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tarantino-unchained-quentin-unleashes-django17837ce7449d481cb24d1f4e80eb1002-184294961.html</link><title>Tarantino unchained: Quentin unleashes 'Django'</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Quentin Tarantino enters a West Village Italian restaurant through the back, a quiet arrival for a filmmaker who is anything but stealthy. More than most any other director working today, Tarantino's movies are propelled by a ceaseless urge to entertain, both the audience and himself.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7077_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:47:01">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/192918961.html</link><title>Best supporting actor Oscar goes to Christoph Waltz for "Django"</title><description>The first Academy Award went to Christoph Waltz supporting actor in "Django Unchained." He previously won for "Inglorious Basterds." Both films were written and directed by Quentin Tarantino." In "Django" he plays a bounty hunter who accompanies a freed slave, played by Jamie Foxx, on a mission of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7077_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:48:39">http://www.jsonline.com/news/opinion/slavery-as-fantasy-in-django-r787umv-185710681.html</link><title>In My Opinion | Slavery as fantasy in 'Django'</title><description>Much of my problem with "Django Unchained" arises from a personal preference. With all the political turmoil surrounding New Year's Day, it was a little surprising my biggest argument of 2013 centered on a Hollywood movie. The movie was "Django Unchained," the newly released film directed by rebel auteur</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/china-pulls-django-unchained-on-day-premiere2e30dadbf2c341cf923c1dbd09f8f555-202463591.html</link><title>China pulls 'Django Unchained' on day of premiere</title><description>BEIJING (AP) "Django Unchained" became "Django Unscreened" as Quentin Tarantino's violent slave-revenge saga was pulled from Chinese theaters on its opening day, with the importer blaming an unspecified technical problem. The rare suspension order by China Film Group Corp. was confirmed by theater employees throughout China, and has</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/django-unchained-action-figures-discontinued67089bcc1c1a471fb2903e62ff6530b8-187474991.html</link><title>'Django Unchained' action figures discontinued</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) The Weinstein Co. has asked a toy maker to discontinue a line of "Django Unchained" action figures after receiving complaints that they were offensive. The studio said Friday that such collectibles have been created for all of director Quentin Tarantino's films, including "Inglourious Basterds," and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7077_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:53:06">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/184957521.html</link><title>Spike Lee calls 'Django' disrespectful</title><description>I have not seen Quentin Tarantino's new Civil War-era Western "Django Unchained" yet, but I plan to take my father to see it.   Pops</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tarantino-unchains-bloody-django-at-comiccon330a6fd8b9de48eb8ffe52519fa56f9c-162472376.html</link><title>Tarantino unchains bloody 'Django' at Comic-Con</title><description>SAN DIEGO (AP) Quentin Tarantino is redefining race relations in the pre-Civil War South with "Django Unchained," his Western-style saga that he previewed at the Comic-Con fan convention. Tarantino said Saturday that he has been wanting to do a Western for ages and that the idea for "Django</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7077-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/action-figures-for-django-unchained-draw-protest7965e7342f5e4c5f9762ca50bdeba9fa-186047031.html</link><title>Action figures for 'Django Unchained' draw protest</title><description>Slavery-era action figures tied to Quentin Tarantino's "Django Unchained" are raising questions about whether they're appropriate. A line of figures of the movie's main characters are on sale online, manufactured by toy maker NECA in partnership with the Weinstein Co. Najee Ali, director of the advocacy group</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>