<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7115">pittsburgh steelers news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:09:18" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:09:20">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/250472641.html</link><title>James Starks to visit with the Pittsburgh Steelers Monday</title><description>The Green Bay Packers spent most of the first week of free agency re-signing their own players. One they didn't lock up is running back James Starks . A source told the Journal Sentinel that Starks, 28, will visit the Pittsburgh Steelers on Monday. Last season,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/nfl-tells-steelers-they-wont-lose-draft-pick98ecc5f999db4002bf328f242e32aaec-251279671.html</link><title>NFL tells Steelers they won't lose draft pick</title><description>PITTSBURGH (AP) Pittsburgh Steelers president Art Rooney II says the NFL has told the team it will not be docked a pick in this year's draft for coach Mike Tomlin's foray onto the field against Baltimore last November. Tomlin was fined $100,000 for stepping onto the field during</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-03"><link>http://jsonline.stats.com/fb/recap.asp?g=20090111023&amp;home=23&amp;vis=24</link><title>Box score: Steelers 35, Chargers 24</title><description>There is a home-field advantage in the NFL playoffs after all, and it belongs to the Pittsburgh Steelers.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:11:55">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/Packers-vs-Steelers-236958191.html</link><title>Steelers 38, Packers 31</title><description>Photos from Lambeau Field as the Green Bay Packers hosted the Pittsburgh Steelers on Sunday afternoon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:12:40">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/Packers-vs-Steelers-236944691.html</link><title>Fans tailgate before Packers-Steelers game</title><description>Photos from Lambeau Field as the Green Bay Packers host the Pittsburgh Steelers on Sunday afternoon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:13:32">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/115441004.html</link><title>Super Bowl XLV: Packers vs. Steelers</title><description>Photos of Super Bowl XLV between the Green Bay Packers and Pittsburgh Steelers at Cowboys Stadium in Arlington, Texas.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-07"><link>http://jsonline.stats.com/fb/recap.asp?g=20090201022&amp;home=22&amp;vis=23</link><title>SUPER BOWL: Steelers 27, Cardinals 23 | TD catch by Holmes helps Pittsburgh win a thriller</title><description>Santonio Holmes caught a six-yard touchdown pass with 35 seconds left to cap one of the best fourth quarters in Super Bowl history, giving the Pittsburgh Steelers a thrilling 27-23 victory over the Arizona Cardinals. SUPER BOWL: Steelers 27, Cardinals</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:15:15">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/packers/114991189.html</link><title>Steelers notes | Rodgers has the attention, and the respect, of Pittsburgh</title><description>The Pittsburgh Steelers got their first up-close look at Aaron Rodgers in 2009, when the Green Bay Packers' quarterback threw for 383 yards and three touchdowns against them. Fort Worth, Texas — The Pittsburgh Steelers got their first up-close look at Aaron Rodgers in 2009, when</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:16:01">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/114488209.html</link><title>Instant replay: the last Packers-Steelers game</title><description>As a service to our football fans, here is the link to the Dec. 20, 2009 game between the Green Bay Packers and the Pittsburgh Steelers. First, the Journal Sentinel story. And the game story from the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette .</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7115-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7115_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:16:52">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/40871912.html</link><title>Packers sign Steelers safety Smith</title><description>The Packers are on the free-agent board: They agreed to terms today on a contract with Pittsburgh Steelers safety Anthony Smith, a league source said. Terms of the deal were not immediately</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>