<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:37:17" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ea-sports-tiger-cut-ties-on-golf-video-gameb785fc7bd268425f9a1392864717b1a2-229686651.html</link><title>EA Sports, Tiger cut ties on golf video game</title><description>EA Sports' popular PGA Tour game will no longer be named for Tiger Woods. The company announced on its blog that it and Woods have made a "mutual decision to end our partnership" and that the company would keep working with the PGA Tour on its next golf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/obama-and-espn-commentators-play-golf-in-virginiab429d3231b5241c48d8843436fb4e5d4-215373421.html</link><title>Obama's gift to ESPN's Kornheiser is game of golf</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) President Barack Obama's birthday gift to ESPN commentator Tony Kornheiser is a game of golf. With the president. The White House said Obama teed off Saturday with Kornheiser and Michael Wilbon, co-hosts of the sports network's "Pardon the Interruption" talk show. Saturday was Kornheiser's 65th birthday.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:38:32">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/golf/new-gadgets-for-your-golf-game-oo8vq72-194577471.html</link><title>New gadgets for your golf game</title><description>Here are a few products I came across at the PGA Merchandise Show in Orlando in January that should help golfers make a more comfortable transition from couch to fairway. There are three truths about spring golf in Wisconsin: The weather is raw, the turf is soggy and the swing</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:39:26">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/91855309.html</link><title>Suddenly, strangely, golf is a perfectly respectable game</title><description>Funny how presidential golf is respectable again in the press, writes Mark McKinnon in the Daily Beast . And press conferences? Who notices now? McKinnon points out it’s been nearly a year since President Obama’s held a formal press conference. Compare that to the rate President George</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:40:22">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/84354177.html</link><title>Golf at the (Winter) Games?</title><description>Woke up to sunshine for the first time since I got here Tuesday and it felt like a mid-May day in Wisconsin. By the time I got to the UBC Thunderbird Arena at noon (2 p.m. Milwaukee time) to cover Team USA vs. China, the temperature had to be over 50.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:40:57">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/older-golfers-b99112255z1-226246241.html</link><title>Older golfers</title><description>Area golfers in their 80s and 90s still living for their regular golf game, many of them shooting their age and even getting better with age. Area golfers in their 80s and 90s still living for their regular golf game, many of them shooting their age and even getting better</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:41:54">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/disc-golf-at-estabrook-park-b99182543z1-239832671.html</link><title>Disc golfers enjoy break from winter's chill</title><description>A group hitting the 18-hole course at Estabrook Park in Milwaukee for a disc golf game were among people in the area enjoying the warmer temperatures</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:42:56">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/golf/119128869.html</link><title>Wilson masters the mental part of his golf game | Falls native finds success after accepting who he is</title><description>Just days before teeing it up in his first Masters Tournament at age 36, Menomonee Falls native Mark Wilson is not the least bit stressed about Augusta National, or anything else. Elmhurst, Ill. — Mark Wilson has a practice putting green and a golf simulator in the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:44:15">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/golf/ramiro-romos-golf-game-shows-plenty-of-improvement-b9989710z1-222281431.html</link><title>On Golf | Ramiro Romo's golf game shows plenty of improvement | Father of Dallas Cowboys quarterback shows how to get it done on links</title><description>Fifteen years ago, Ramiro Romo’s golf handicap was in the double digits. Fifteen years ago, Ramiro Romo's golf handicap was in the double digits. A relative latecomer to the game — he started playing at age 29 — he would have been out of his element in a Wisconsin State</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:44:57">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/golf/41714972.html</link><title>Woods and eagles: Golf booming up north</title><description>The steady stream of cars, SUVs and campers heading north on Highway 51 over the Memorial Day weekend was filled with fishermen eager to cast their lot on the hundreds of pristine lakes in Wisconsin's north woods. The anglers packed their favorite lures, their biggest coolers and enough</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>