<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:52:13" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/oprah-to-interview-lance-armstrongd3d9cf42068a4bb29aa24c2429223ae2-186151101.html</link><title>Oprah to interview Lance Armstrong</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Lance Armstrong has agreed to a tell-all interview with Oprah Winfrey where he will address allegations that he used performance-enhancing drugs during his cycling career. According to a release posted on Oprah's website on Tuesday, it's the first interview with Armstrong since his athletic career</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/lance-armstrong-left-it-all-on-table-with-oprahdb1340ef001f42cc821621bdbca5d438-187261231.html</link><title>Lance Armstrong left it 'all on table' with Oprah</title><description>All the speculation is about to end. In a matter of hours, viewers can judge for themselves whether Lance Armstrong told the truth this time. Armstrong's confession to Oprah Winfrey about using performance-enhancing drugs to win the Tour de France a record seven times in a row will</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7138_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:53:58">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/186938051.html</link><title>Video: Oprah gives details of Lance Armstrong interview to CBS</title><description>Oprah Winfrey spoke at length Tuesday morning about the interview she conducted with cyclist Lance Armstrong about his use of performance-enhancing drugs. In the interview, Armstrong admits to the doping. "He did not come clean in the manner I expected," says Winfrey. "He answered the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/wada-lance-armstrong-needs-to-confess-under-oathe2e28251225444e09cf92e188aaf876d-186975901.html</link><title>WADA: Lance Armstrong needs to confess under oath</title><description>MONTREAL (AP) The World Anti-Doping Agency says Lance Armstrong must confess under oath to seek a reduction in his lifetime ban from sports for doping during seven Tour de France victories. WADA says it "read with interest media reports suggesting a television 'confession' made by Lance Armstrong" to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/the-hollywood-reporters-best-of-the-weekbd93f06dac0443cba891255fd5b5dfa3-187313071.html</link><title>The Hollywood Reporter's best of the week</title><description>The Hollywood Reporter's list of its 10 best stories of the week: SUNDANCE 2013: THE 10 MOST BUZZED-ABOUT FILMS From the most anticipated titles to potential breakouts and must-see docs, everything buyers need to get shopping in Park City. http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/gallery/sundance-2013-10-hot-films-412960 THR COVER: NICOLE KIDMAN ON</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/armstrong-admits-doping-to-oprah96c6967b562f4bf9810efb6cf927a5aa-187392201.html</link><title>Armstrong admits doping to Oprah</title><description>Lance Armstrong confessed to using performance-enhancing drugs to win the Tour de France during an interview with Oprah Winfrey, reversing more than a decade of denial. CHICAGO (AP) Lance Armstrong confessed to using performance-enhancing drugs to win the Tour de France during an interview with Oprah Winfrey, reversing more than</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/jj-abrams-to-produce-lance-armstrong-biopicbf0b3c61a3254e41866dff0a3ffc663a-187546691.html</link><title>J.J. Abrams to produce Lance Armstrong biopic</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) He's already gotten the Oprah treatment. Now Lance Armstrong is headed for the silver screen. Paramount Pictures and J.J. Abrams' production company, Bad Robot, are planning a biopic about the disgraced cyclist, a studio spokeswoman said Friday. They've secured the rights to New York</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/armstrong-ready-as-oprah-comes-to-town2d30d01baa134812a3ef2d5093061d5f-186736501.html</link><title>AP source: Armstrong tells Oprah he doped</title><description>Lance Armstrong confessed to Oprah Winfrey during an interview Monday that he used performance-enhancing drugs to win the Tour de France, a person familiar with the situation told The Associated Press. AUSTIN, Texas (AP) Lance Armstrong confessed to Oprah Winfrey during an interview Monday that he used performance-enhancing drugs to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7138_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:57:42">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/187584451.html</link><title>Trek: we will monitor development of Armstrong's statements</title><description>Trek Bicycle Corp., based in Waterloo, released a statement shortly after the second of two Lance Armstrong interviews with Oprah Winfrey aired on Friday night on the OWN network. Here is the statement: " All of us at Trek love the sport of cycling and want athletes to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7138-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/report-lance-to-admit-doping-in-oprah-interviewdf02b8cff1114f5db9286d09305ca301-186585181.html</link><title>Lance to admit doping in Oprah interview</title><description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) Lance Armstrong will make a limited confession to doping during his televised interview with Oprah Winfrey next week, according to a person with knowledge of the situation. Armstrong, who has long denied doping, will also offer an apology during the interview scheduled to be taped</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>