<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7142">Amsterdam museums</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:09:25" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7142-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/red-light-secrets-museum-opens-in-amsterdame25bf3b427de45519841f03c08130c03-243674601.html</link><title>Red Light Secrets Museum opens in Amsterdam</title><description>AMSTERDAM (AP) On any given evening, thousands of tourists stroll down the narrow canal-side streets of Amsterdam's famed Red Light District, gawking at ladies in lingerie who work behind windows, making a living selling sex for money. Now a small educational museum is opening Thursday in the heart of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7142-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/rembrandts-night-watch-back-at-amsterdam-museumfd02ada616b043e093424becccec4343-200222731.html</link><title>Rembrandt's 'Night Watch' back at Amsterdam museum</title><description>AMSTERDAM (AP) Rembrandt's iconic masterpiece the "Night Watch" has been painstakingly returned to the main building of Amsterdam's Rijksmuseum before its re-opening next month after a decade of renovations. Removing the priceless painting from a temporary wing and moving it to the main building Wednesday was an operation</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7142-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/van-gogh-museum-unveils-new-willow-watercolorf7f7f988b0ec4ec998b3f4c8d2087700-150920345.html</link><title>Van Gogh museum unveils new willow watercolor</title><description>AMSTERDAM (AP) A young Vincent van Gogh was so struck by a dead willow leaning "lonely and melancholy" over a pond near The Hague that he knew at once he had to paint it. "I'm going to attack it tomorrow morning," he wrote to his brother Theo on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7142-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/dutch-van-gogh-museum-closes-masterpieces-moved8e3a0b8273fc4c6d803ba50ebb47cb7b-171012801.html</link><title>Dutch Van Gogh Museum closes, masterpieces moved</title><description>AMSTERDAM (AP) The operation began moments after the Van Gogh Museum in Amsterdam closed Sunday evening. Men removed alarm tags from behind some of Vincent Van Gogh's greatest masterpieces, including "Sunflowers," ''Irises" and the famously crooked "Bedroom," and quickly pulled the paintings down from the museum's walls. Fortunately,</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>