<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:37:40" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:37:42">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/israelis-get-satisfaction-with-rolling-stones-showd5b75c2d3c594ad092dce9523b5084d1-252257361.html</link><title>Israelis get satisfaction with Rolling Stones show</title><description>JERUSALEM (AP) Israeli fans of the Rolling Stones have complained for years that they can't get no satisfaction. Until now. Promoter Shuki Weiss said Tuesday the legendary band will play its first concert in Israel in Tel Aviv on June 4. Israeli rock fans often get the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:38:25">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/musicandnightlife/at-540-he-hopes-for-satisfaction-from-rolling-stones-b9917917z1-208967081.html</link><title>At $540, he hopes for satisfaction from Rolling Stones | Stones roll into Chicago for three concerts</title><description>Peter Jest is going to find out Tuesday if $540 is a fair price to get some satisfaction. That’s how much the owner of Milwaukee music venue Shank Hall forked over to see the Rolling Stones at the United Center Tuesday. Peter Jest is going to find out Tuesday if</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7154-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/devo-guitarist-bob-casale-dies-at-age-614d1ce23acfd54c59be83b504d25681aa-246017721.html</link><title>Devo guitarist Bob Casale dies at age 61</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Bob Casale, the guitarist for Devo, best known for the 1980 hit "Whip It," has died of heart failure, his brother and band member Gerald Casale said Tuesday. He was 61. Devo founding member Casale said in a statement that his younger brother's death Monday</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7154-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/rock-hall-of-fame-to-open-rolling-stones-exhibit0479083209b0463ca201ba077d9ebde3-193509601.html</link><title>Rock Hall of Fame to open Rolling Stones exhibit</title><description>CLEVELAND (AP) The story of The Rolling Stones is so huge it takes 2Â½ floors of The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum to tell. The Cleveland-based museum will open "Rolling Stones: 50 Years of Satisfaction," an exclusive exhibit celebrating the archetypal rock band, on May</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>