<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:33:40" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:33:41">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/statecolleges/44334747.html</link><title>Monday state college roundup</title><description>Milwaukee School of Engineering and UW-Stout have earned bids to the NCAA Division III men's championships. In addition, Tyler Wollberg of Carthage also received a berth in the tournament. Wollberg tied for 15th place in last year's meet. UW-Stevens Point and UW-Eau Claire were among</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:35:01">http://www.jsonline.com/news/milwaukee/34337489.html</link><title>Paralyzed man's claim against ex-police officer should go to trial, judge rules</title><description>A federal judge has ruled in favor of a man who says he was paralyzed by a Milwaukee police officer while in custody five years ago. U.S. District Judge Lynn Adelman wrote in a decision this week that there was evidence that Curtis Harris was paralyzed by former</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:35:55">http://www.jsonline.com/business/128222008.html</link><title>Johnson Controls to appeal California jury award</title><description>Johnson Controls Inc. says it will appeal a California jury's finding that one of its seats contributed to injuries a woman sustained in a 2006 crash. Johnson Controls Inc. says it will appeal a California jury's finding that one of its seats contributed to injuries a woman sustained in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:36:59">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/verdict-in-philadelphia-abortion-doctor-trial-reported-e09ueg3-207249691.html</link><title>Jury finds Philadelphia abortion doctor guilty</title><description>A jury has reached a guilty verdict in the murder trial of a doctor accused of killing babies and a patient during late-term abortions at his clinic. Philadelphia - A jury has reached a guilty verdict in the murder trial of a doctor accused of killing babies</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>