<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7205">turkey leftover recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:32:56" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:32:58">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/105217104.html</link><title>Share your leftover turkey recipe</title><description>When the big feast is done, what do you do with the rest of the turkey? If you can answer that question with a dynamite recipe, you might win a $50 gift certificate to your favorite local cookware shop or grocery store. The Journal Sentinel is accepting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:33:51">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/Thanksgiving-leftovers-recipes-233352901.html</link><title>Thanksgiving leftovers recipes</title><description>Everyone — at least, every cook — knows the best part of Thanksgiving dinner: leftovers! And sure, you can find creative recipes that use leftover mashed potatoes, cranberry sauce or sweet potato casserole, but when it comes right down to it, what you really need fresh ideas for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:35:23">http://www.jsonline.com/features/home/105651333.html</link><title>New Products, Great Ideas | Good light; Turkey redux; Root storage plan</title><description>Cooking Good light Candles cast a lovely glow but create a hazard if left unattended. Battery-operated tea lights are a great solution but they have a limited lifespan. OXO's Candela Demi-Glow Rechargeable Lights ($69.99) offer eight hours of glow time before they need to be</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:36:26">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/options-abound-for-meals-made-with-thanksgiving-leftovers-qg7k1lm-180171511.html</link><title>Options abound for meals made with Thanksgiving leftovers</title><description>With oodles of turkey, stuffing, cranberry sauce and potatoes left, there are only so many Thanksgiving repeat meals one can handle. But where one cook sees dismay, Inger Wilkerson sees possibilities. We spend weeks planning for Thanksgiving and nearly as long eating all the leftovers (or so it seems).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:37:56">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/sandwiches-are-perfect-for-day-after-thanksgiving-k3324b3-134291918.html</link><title>Sandwiches are perfect for day after Thanksgiving</title><description>Right now, we're all counting down to zero hour, that amazing moment when everything comes together. But what about the day after Thanksgiving? Right now, the day before Thanksgiving, we're all counting down to zero hour, that amazing moment when everything comes together - the bird, the sides, the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:39:33">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/110974369.html</link><title>Web Bites: Turkey hash; baked spaghetti; cranberry frozen yogurt; healthy in winter</title><description>Web Bites is a weekly roundup of recipes, cooking tips, news and blog posts from around the Internet. Look for it on Mondays to help you</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:40:33">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/109988389.html</link><title>Thanksgiving links, resources, recipes and more</title><description>For all your last-minute Thanksgiving planning, here is a roundup of links to resources and recipes that have been helpful or inspiring to me (even though I'm not cooking much this year). Breakfast Breakfast on Thanksgiving morning is a delicate balance of eating something light, but</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:42:35">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/109978569.html</link><title>A never-ending leftovers feast</title><description>Second only to the meal itself, the best thing about Thanksgiving dinner - at least for the cook - is the prospect of all those leftovers. Second only to the meal itself, the best thing about Thanksgiving dinner - at least for the cook - is the prospect of all</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7205-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7205_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:43:21">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/35002989.html</link><title>Give leftover turkey an international flavor</title><description>There are plenty of other options for leftover turkey besides soup, sandwiches and the standard turkey tetrazzini. Turkey melt, turkey hash, creamed turkey. . . the list goes on. If you're looking for something lighter, there's always turkey salad. Try a Nicoise salad with tender cooked green beans, cooked sliced</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>