<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:53:43" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:53:46">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/magnitude72-earthquake-shakes-mexican-capitald5ddd6dd30914d5183364da360f6d94f-255781741.html</link><title>Magnitude-7.2 earthquake shakes Mexican capital</title><description>ACAPULCO, Mexico (AP) A powerful magnitude-7.2 earthquake shook central and southern Mexico on Friday, sending panicked people into the streets. Some walls cracked and fell, but there were no reports of major damage or casualties. The U.S. Geological Survey said the quake at about 9:30 a.m. (10:30 a.m.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:55:12">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/magnitude51-earthquake-shakes-los-angeles9697e88342b14e35abb0e4222fc37735-253006051.html</link><title>Magnitude-5.1 earthquake shakes Los Angeles</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) A magnitude-5.1 earthquake was widely felt in the Los Angeles area and surrounding counties Friday evening, but authorities said there were no immediate reports of significant damages or injuries. The U.S. Geological Survey said the quake struck at about 9:09 p.m. and was centered near</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:56:19">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/252496471.html</link><title>Government video shows devastating Alaskan earthquake, tsunami</title><description>Fifty years ago on Thursday, southern Alaska was rocked by the most powerful earthquake ever recorded in the U.S., 9.2 on the richter scale. A devastating tsunami then swept away entire villages. The quake, the second most powerful of the century behind a 9.5 magnitude quake in Chile</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:56:59">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/250635211.html</link><title>How TV anchors reacted to the LA earthquake</title><description>Here's how morning TV anchors at KTLA reacted to a St. Patrick's Day earthquake that occurred while they were on the air. The earthquake's magnitude was a 4.4 , which prompted the anchors to dive under their newsdesk and others in the studio to run across the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/earthquake-strongly-felt-across-los-angelese1bc798a11c74099a590e0d52cc51534-250604371.html</link><title>Earthquake strongly felt across Los Angeles</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) A predawn earthquake rolled across the Los Angeles basin Monday, rattling nerves and shaking buildings along a 150-mile swath of Southern California but causing no major damage. The 4.4-magnitude quake was centered 2 miles from Encino and 15 miles west-northwest of the downtown civic center,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:59:48">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/133331703.html</link><title>Oklahoma earthquake</title><description>A look a the damage from a 5.9-magnitude earthquake Saturday night in Oklahoma that was felt in downtown Milwaukee. Oklahoma's 5.6-magnitude earthquake Saturday night caught many residents off guard and could even be felt in downtown Milwaukee.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:00:54">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/42530887.html</link><title>Earthquake in Italy</title><description>A powerful earthquake in mountainous central Italy knocked down whole blocks of buildings early Monday as residents slept, killing more than 70 people in the country's deadliest quake in nearly three decades. Tens of thousands were homeless and 1,500 were injured.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:01:34">http://landing.newsinc.com/shared/video.html?freewheel=90078&amp;sitesection=ap&amp;VID=23600545</link><title>mexico_earthquake_video_belt</title><description>A strong 7.6-magnitude earthquake hit Mexico on Tuesday, shaking central and southern parts of the country and swaying buildings in Mexico City. A strong 7.6-magnitude earthquake hit Mexico on Tuesday, shaking central and southern parts of the country and swaying buildings in Mexico City.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:02:12">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/143547736.html</link><title>Earthquake shakes Mexico</title><description>News reports say an earthquake measuring a magnitude of  7.4 shook areas near Mexico City today. CNN reports that the epicenter of the quake was 15 miles east of Ometepec in the state of Guerrero. No injuries were immediately reported.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:03:38">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/128269363.html</link><title>East Coast earthquake rocks D.C.</title><description>A 5.9 magnitude earthquake centered in Virginia forced evacuations of all the memorials and monuments on the National Mall in Washington and rattled nerves from South Carolina to Martha's Vineyard. A 5.9 magnitude earthquake centered in Virginia forced evacuations of all the memorials and monuments on the National Mall in</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>