<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:30:57" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:30:59">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/no-surgery-for-former-bills-qb-kelly-for-cancer1c37ac3fad564e208e779c91cc2aa79c-252534441.html</link><title>No surgery for former Bills QB Kelly for cancer</title><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) Doctors treating Hall of Fame quarterback Jim Kelly said Wednesday he will not immediately undergo surgery for a recurrence of cancer. Instead, the longtime Buffalo Bills star will likely first be treated with chemotherapy and radiation, according to a statement from Lenox Hill Hospital in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:32:14">http://www.jsonline.com/news/crime/support-grows-for-milwaukee-police-lieutenant-with-cancer-b99217895z1-248360361.html</link><title>Support grows for Milwaukee police lieutenant with cancer</title><description>Lt. Chris Blaszak thought he had an infected wisdom tooth but was diagnosed with stage 4 squamous cell carcinoma of the mandible. A 43-year-old Milwaukee police lieutenant and Air Force veteran has been diagnosed with an aggressive form of cancer, and fundraising efforts are underway to help pay for medical</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:33:24">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/34671669.html</link><title>Drinking linked to specific esophageal cancer</title><description>Drinking alcohol is strongly linked to esophageal squamous cell carcinoma, a cancer of the esophagus, a group of Dutch researchers says.   The  Netherlands Cohort Study , which followed some 120,000 people over 16 years, found that a person drinking four glasses of alcohol a day has five times</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:35:10">http://www.legacy.com/obituaries/jsonline/obituary.aspx?page=lifestory&amp;pid=151793661</link><title>Jeffrey James Smith</title><description>Smith, Jeffrey James "Banoon" "Unk" June 10, 1955 to June 2, 2011. son of Robert and Norma Jean. After a 2 year battle with vocal cord squamous cell carcinoma, he is spending his 56th birthday with Jesus. Fishing was his passion with buddies Mike and Peter. He enjoyed watching</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/twins-gm-ryan-out-of-hospital-after-cancer-surgery50c888ccd6154a7bb26e50f02ca5d24c-245577581.html</link><title>Twins GM Ryan out of hospital after cancer surgery</title><description>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) Minnesota Twins general manager Terry Ryan has been released from the hospital, the first step in his recovery from cancer surgery. The Twins announced Friday that Ryan left the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, three days after the operation. According to team spokesman Dustin Morse, Ryan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/speedy-recovery-expected-after-kelly-has-surgeryf67e2b52fefb472fa281b54424b15bd8-210585831.html</link><title>Speedy recovery expected after Kelly has surgery</title><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) Buffalo Bills Hall of Fame quarterback Jim Kelly is anticipated to have a speedy recovery and successful outcome after having surgery to remove cancer from his upper jaw, according to doctors who performed the operation. The operation, conducted on Friday morning, was described as going</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:37:26">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/169173926.html</link><title>Scientists delve into lung cancer genome</title><description>Scientists involved in a massive project aimed at characterizing the genomes of 20 different cancers have completed work on the genetic script of the second most common form of lung cancer. Reporting online in the journal Nature , researchers involved in the the Cancer Genome Atlas project said they have finished</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sponsoredarticles/health-wellness/step-carefully-this-summer-prevent-common-foot-cancers8072240312-210824961.html</link><title>Step carefully this summer: Prevent common foot cancers</title><description>Common cancers have a high level of awareness among Americans - and rightly so. Prevalent cancers like breast, colon or prostate affect a large number of people, and it's important to be aware of preventive and diagnostic measures. But cancer can also strike in an area of the body many</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-09"><link>http://www.stltoday.com/stltoday/lifestyle/stories.nsf/healthfitness/story/C540D9D89F9A39C686257721006889BD?OpenDocument</link><title>Steering around skin cancer | Research shows drivers have risk to the left side of their bodies</title><description>If physician Scott Fosko had his way, truckers would slather on sunscreen as routinely as they log their miles. As the sun's rays get stronger, Fosko, chairman of dermatology at St. Louis University Medical School, wants people to know that driving increases the risk for skin cancer on the left</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7215-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/twins-gm-ryan-says-he-has-treatable-cancerc6ad7cf74ca3450289ce5ed08bdd0e1f-244772911.html</link><title>Twins GM Ryan says he has treatable cancer</title><description>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) Diagnosed with cancer in his neck, Minnesota Twins general manager Terry Ryan has taken leave from his job for treatment and recovery. The timetable for his return is unclear, but the prognosis is optimistic. Though sobered by and concerned about the news, the Twins expressed confidence</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>