<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:42:11" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:42:13">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/230085441.html</link><title>Import spices pose salmonella risk, FDA study says</title><description>If you have an exotic palate, you might be willing to expose yourself to some adventurous flavors. But did you know that imported spices might be exposing you to illnesses such as salmonella, and filth such as bug parts? Today, the FDA released a draft of a study into</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:43:04">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/219793661.html</link><title>Iams, Eukanuba dog and cat food recalled because of possible salmonella contamination</title><description>Procter &amp; Gamble is voluntarily recalling several kinds of Iams and Eukanuba dog and cat food because it has potential to contain salmonella. Salmonella may infect both the pets eating the food and owners handling the products without thoroughly washing their hands afterward, the company says. "The</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:44:26">http://www.jsonline.com/news/health/2-sickened-by-salmonella-linked-to-cantaloupes-j66hm99-166608286.html</link><title>2 sickened by Salmonella linked to cantaloupes</title><description>Two people in Wisconsin have been sickened in a Salmonella outbreak linked to cantaloupes from southwestern Indiana, state health officials said Friday. People should not eat cantaloupes with stickers showing they originated from southwestern Indiana, the Wisconsin Department of Agriculture, Trade and Consumer Protection said. If cantaloupes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:45:35">http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/judge-to-decide-whether-to-reopen-bids-on-sunlanda5c2bed56fb64520bbc343cc98d3b803-252312061.html</link><title>Judge to decide whether to reopen bids on Sunland</title><description>ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) A federal bankruptcy judge on Tuesday ordered a new auction for an eastern New Mexico peanut butter plant involved in a 2012 salmonella outbreak. The trustee overseeing the liquidation of the now defunct Sunland Inc. in Portales had asked to be able to consider a</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:46:14">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/40096992.html</link><title>More pet peanut butter treats recalled</title><description>Here's more on an expanded recall of pet treats for salmonella.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:47:09">http://www.jsonline.com/news/health/39179642.html</link><title>Salmonella found in Wisconsin-grown sprouts</title><description>Alfalfa sprouts from a Wisconsin-based grower have been recalled from stores in Wisconsin and Minnesota after routine food safety tests turned up positive for Salmonella, bacteria that can cause food-borne illness. The alfalfa sprouts and alfalfa onion sprout mix, sold in 5-ounce clamshell packages, are manufactured by Jack</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:48:37">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/43810977.html</link><title>Salmonella spreads to alfalfa sprouts</title><description>Don’t eat raw alfalfa sprouts. That’s a warning from the Food and Drug Administration and the Centers for Disease Control. The stringy sprouts have been linked to salmonella cases in several states, but not yet Wisconsin,  according to the federal agencies  and Consumer Reports . The FDA is</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/hundreds-of-salmonella-cases-tied-to-chicks3844038d7e0147b6bd95b1c560a71ad6-155824705.html</link><title>Hundreds of salmonella cases tied to chicks</title><description>ATLANTA (AP) Those cute mail-order chicks that wind up in children's Easter baskets and backyard farms have been linked to more than 300 cases of salmonella in the U.S. mostly in youngsters since 2004. An estimated 50 million live poultry are sold through the mail each year in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/salmonella-outbreak-linked-to-nm-poultry-hatchery89ceb4c17873419f91156ff532c30c4c-220262141.html</link><title>Salmonella outbreak linked to NM poultry hatchery</title><description>SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) A national outbreak of salmonella has been linked to an eastern New Mexico hatchery that sells live baby chickens, ducks and other poultry by mail and supplies them to feed stores, state health officials announced Monday. The state Department of Health said a strain</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:51:51">http://www.jsonline.com/news/health/five-in-wisconsin-sickened-by-salmonella-in-cantaloupes-mangoes-ga6n11f-168204216.html</link><title>Five in Wisconsin sickened by salmonella in cantaloupes, mangoes</title><description>Five people in Wisconsin have been sickened by salmonella in a multistate outbreak caused by eating cantaloupe from Indiana and mangoes from Mexico, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported Thursday. Most of the sick, four in Wisconsin and 200 in 21 other states, were confirmed to</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>