<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:53:49" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:53:50">http://www.legacy.com/obituaries/jsonline/obituary.aspx?page=lifestory&amp;pid=169548736</link><title>Helen Kennedy</title><description>Kennedy, Helen Was reunited with her husband Harry on February 1, 2014. Loving mother of Edward Kennedy, Laura (Tim) Coralline, the late JoAnn Kennedy-Duran and the late Richard Kennedy. Proud grandmother of Sandra (Chuck) Barsky, Nancy Duran, Edward Kennedy Jr., Ericka (Michael) Kennedy-Burzynski, Brian (Stacy) Kennedy, Erin</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:55:23">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/54927592.html</link><title>Sen. Edward M. Kennedy dies at age 77</title><description>Sen. Edward M. Kennedy, the liberal lion of the Senate and haunted bearer of the Camelot torch after two of his brothers fell to assassins' bullets, has died after battling a brain tumor. He was 77.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:56:13">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/55386537.html</link><title>Edward M. (Ted) Kennedy | 1932 – 2009 | Last of a political dynasty</title><description>Edward Kennedy, a liberal Democrat, served in the Senate during 10 presidential administrations, including that of his brother John. When he died, Kennedy was the third-longest serving senator in history, at 46 years and nine months. Read more: Senator recalled fondly by state politicians</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:57:22">http://www.jsonline.com/news/wisconsin/55116987.html</link><title>Wisconsin politicians react to death of Sen. Kennedy</title><description>Following are public statements released Wednesday by Wisconsin politicians in the wake of the death of U.S. Sen. Edward Kennedy: Gov. Jim Doyle U.S. Sen. Russ Feingold U.S.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:58:44">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/55039907.html</link><title>Ted Kennedy</title><description>After nearly 50 years serving his country in the Senate, Edward Kennedy has died . May his soul, and the souls of all the faithful departed, through the mercy of God rest in peace. Also:   WSJ's James Taranto on Kennedy's idealism,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-06"><link>http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/U/US_OBIT_TED_KENNEDY?SITE=WIMIL&amp;SECTION=HOME&amp;TEMPLATE=DEFAULT</link><title>Mass. Sen. Edward M. Kennedy dies at age 77 after battle with brain tumor</title><description>Sen. Edward M. Kennedy, the liberal lion of the Senate and haunted bearer of the Camelot torch after two of his brothers fell to assassins' bullets, has died after battling a brain tumor. He was 77. Boston - Sen. Edward M. Kennedy, the liberal lion of the Senate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/schenkkan-obrien-win-award-honoring-sen-kennedyc6c812ddbeb944f98728f7c53cee733f-192423071.html</link><title>Schenkkan, O'Brien win award honoring Sen. Kennedy</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Dan O'Brien's "The Body of an American" and Robert Schenkkan's "All the Way" have been named the inaugural winners of a theater award honoring the late U.S. Sen. Edward Kennedy. Columbia University on Friday said the playwrights will share the award and $100,000, one of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7218-08"><link>http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/U/US_MASSACHUSETTS_SENATE?SITE=WIMIL&amp;SECTION=HOME&amp;TEMPLATE=DEFAULT</link><title>In epic upset, GOP's Brown wins Massachusetts Senate race</title><description>In an epic upset in liberal Massachusetts, Republican Scott Brown rode a wave of voter anger to win the U.S. Senate seat held by the late Edward M. Kennedy for nearly half a century, leaving President Barack Obama's health care overhaul in doubt and marring the end of his first</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>