<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:41:35" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7241-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/flight-simulators-used-by-enthusiasts-worldwide931a405964d044b69bffc32d3ad211f8-251123211.html</link><title>Flight simulators used by enthusiasts worldwide</title><description>Malaysian authorities have asked the FBI to help analyze data from a flight simulator found at the home of Zaharie Ahmad Shah, the Malaysia Airlines pilot whose plane has been missing since March 8. WHAT'S A FLIGHT SIMULATOR? The purpose of a flight simulator is to recreate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:43:01">http://www.jsonline.com/news/milwaukee/80946667.html</link><title>Milwaukee to host Navy Week celebration</title><description>The Navy is coming to Milwaukee for a Navy Week celebration in June. As part of Navy Week, the Blue Angels precision flight team will perform at the Milwaukee Air &amp; Water Show June 12 and 13. The U.S. Navy schedules about 20 Navy Weeks each year</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:44:12">http://www.jsonline.com/business/fastgrowth-vetowned-firms-to-make-presentations-es7nj63-180181791.html</link><title>Fast-growth, vet-owned firms to make presentations</title><description>Eight high-growth companies founded by military veterans will make presentations next week at an event sponsored by VETransfer, a nonprofit organization that helps veterans start companies. Eight high-growth companies founded by military veterans will make presentations next week at an event sponsored by VETransfer, a nonprofit organization that helps veterans</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:46:07">http://www.jsonline.com/business/at-eaa-airventure-inventors-look-for-funding-to-attain-liftoff-b9966926z1-218233171.html</link><title>At EAA AirVenture, inventors look for funding to attain liftoff | Convention is an ideal environment for inventions to find investors</title><description>To get his idea off the ground, pilot instructor and inventor Chris Johnson is looking for seed funding — which is why he was at EAA AirVenture. Oshkosh — The Wright Brothers didn't have angel investors or seed funding. But it's a much different world now for</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>