<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:14:54" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/6-killed-by-hot-lava-as-indonesia-volcano-erupts656fc49cff4247f98749f94ecf808b54-219104741.html</link><title>6 killed by hot lava as Indonesia volcano erupts</title><description>MAUMERE, Indonesia (AP) Hot lava from an erupting volcano killed six people sleeping in a beach village on a small island in eastern Indonesia on Saturday, after ash and smoke from the volcano shot about a mile into the air, officials said. Mount Rokatenda in East Nusa Tenggara</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/etna-volcano-erupts-lighting-up-sky-over-sicilyd9fc9ce2c2424d19971917acd62e06e2-232250661.html</link><title>Etna volcano erupts, lighting up sky over Sicily</title><description>ROME (AP) Mount Etna, Europe's most active volcano, has erupted again, lighting up the sky over much of eastern Sicily and shooting up a towering column of ash. The eruption, which began late Saturday and tapered off Sunday morning, didn't endanger any of the villages dotting the mountain's</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/guatemala-volcano-erupts-outside-tourist-center323ba682fa4e46fab8f9aa13abfcbc97-169681516.html</link><title>Guatemala volcano erupts outside tourist center</title><description>ESCUINTLA, Guatemala (AP) A long-simmering volcano exploded into a series of powerful eruptions outside one of Guatemala's most famous tourist attractions on Thursday, hurling thick clouds of ash nearly two miles (three kilometers) high, spewing rivers of lava down its flanks and prompting evacuation orders for more than 33,000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/indonesia-volcano-erupts-3-killed-100k-evacuatedd6eff88aaeed459eb8bb27d195d699d8-245525101.html</link><title>Indonesia volcano erupts; 3 killed, 100K evacuated</title><description>SUGIHWARAS, Indonesia (AP) A powerful volcanic eruption on Indonesia's most populous island blasted ash and debris 18 kilometers (12 miles) into the air Friday, killing three people and forcing authorities to evacuate more than 100,000 and close seven airports. The eruption of Mount Kelud on Java island could</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:18:40">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/musicandnightlife/118546499.html</link><title>After slow burn, Volcano Choir erupts</title><description>It's been six years in the making, but the experimental pop group featuring Bon Iver's Justin Vernon and current and former contributors to Milwaukee's instrumental rockers Collections of Colonies of Bees - is finally playing a home state show at Turner Hall Ballroom. It's been six years in the making,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/4-climbers-killed-in-philippine-volcano-eruption6180c8d261ce485f823f0e0a915b5a9b-206361311.html</link><title>Philippine volcano spews rocks, killing 5 climbers</title><description>MANILA, Philippines (AP) One of the Philippines' most active volcanoes spewed huge rocks and ash after daybreak Tuesday, killing at least five climbers and trapping more than a dozen others near the crater in its first eruption in three years, officials said. Rescue teams and helicopters were sent</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/indonesia-volcano-erupts-again-kills-at-least-14e11af637325f4c94866f7ce0cf6fb011-243073091.html</link><title>Death toll rises to 16 from Indonesia volcano</title><description>MOUNT SINABUNG, Indonesia (AP) The death toll from an Indonesian volcano that has been rumbling for months rose to 16 Sunday after rescuers found another charred corpse and a critically injured college student died in a hospital, officials said. Mount Sinabung erupted again Saturday just a day after</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/philippine-volcano-spews-rocks-killing-5-climbers9819f9ed64fe4ffe847b3c3eae0f3d7a-206380561.html</link><title>Philippine volcano spews rocks, killing 5 climbers</title><description>MANILA, Philippines (AP) One of the Philippines' most active volcanoes rumbled to life Tuesday, spewing room-sized rocks toward nearly 30 surprised climbers, killing five and injuring others that had to be fetched with rescue helicopters and rope. The climbers and their Filipino guides had spent the night camping</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:21:37">http://www.jsonline.com/features/travel/96676674.html</link><title>Travel Briefing | Buying travel insurance</title><description>It's only June, and already what a year it's been for travelers: volcanic ash clouds shutting down dozens of European airports; unrest in Thailand, Jamaica and Greece; an oil spill undermining the plans of vacationers bound for the Gulf of Mexico coast. The summer - with its risk of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7326-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/eu-seeks-better-passenger-rightsc0a575249c6a4483a4c1fd4461e16846-197756721.html</link><title>EU seeks better passenger rights</title><description>BRUSSELS (AP) The European Union is considering beefed up measures to help stranded passengers get compensation and find quicker ways to get home. EU Transport Commissioner Siim Kallas said Wednesday that a new package with improved measures would also boost carriers from the 27 member nations in global</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>