<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:38:09" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:38:11">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/59146602.html</link><title>USC 18, Ohio State 15 | Trojans answer late | TD drive buries host Buckeyes</title><description>Backed up to their own goal line, Matt Barkley and Joe McKnight drove into Southern California lore. Barkley, the freshman quarterback, and McKnight, the shifty tailback, made big play after big play, and Stafon Johnson capped one of the great drives in USC's storied history with a 2-yard</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ncaa/lowly-caltech-joins-mighty-usc-with-ncaa-sanctions11ed917ceded4e88b2223a0a3bbee823-162301036.html</link><title>Lowly Caltech joins mighty USC with NCAA sanctions</title><description>PASADENA, Calif. (AP) Another storied Southern California university has joined the USC Trojans under the hammer of NCAA sanctions. The UCLA Bruins? Nope. Would you believe the Caltech Beavers? The California Institute of Technology has been given a reprimand and penalties for fielding players who were academically</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:40:00">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/packers/usc-a-source-of-talent-for-pack-te56n5m-149757855.html</link><title>Quiz: USC a source of talent for Pack | Over the years, team has drawn from well in draft</title><description>Since the National Football League draft was instituted in 1936, the Green Bay Packers have chosen a USC Trojan in the first round four times entering the 2012 draft. Make it five. The Packers selected defensive end / linebacker Nick Perry with its first-round pick (No. 28</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ncaa/usc-fires-kiffin-after-7th-loss-in-11-gamesa8c262d22bed4a9083b23713adeae500-225702471.html</link><title>USC fires Lane Kiffin; Orgeron is interim coach</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Southern California fired Lane Kiffin early Sunday morning, ending the coach's tumultuous tenure a few hours after the Trojans lost 62-41 at Arizona State. Ed Orgeron was picked as USC's interim head coach by athletic director Pat Haden, who dismissed Kiffin at the airport following</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ncaa/ap-source-steve-sarkisian-accepts-usc-joba4b1938ddc2f4e69860668e8f982d79f-234112221.html</link><title>Coach Steve Sarkisian takes over at USC</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) A few hours after Steve Sarkisian was hired by Southern California, the coach bounded up the steps of the palatial McKay Center and went to work on getting the Trojans back to national title contention. USC hired Sarkisian away from Washington on Monday, bringing back</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/usc-fires-baseball-coach-for-ncaa-violationsc4ec260f98b8452da8198b413ad850f6-191119761.html</link><title>USC fires baseball coach for NCAA violations</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Southern California has fired baseball coach Frank Cruz for violating NCAA rules regarding limits on practice time and organized team activities. Trojans athletic director Pat Haden announced Wednesday that Cruz has been dismissed and that the school has self-imposed a reduction in the number of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ncaa/allen-runs-for-3-tds-usc-tops-oregon-st-3114de38ef89cc374a928354d3be95bfcd5a-230307291.html</link><title>Allen runs for 3 TDs, USC tops Oregon State 31-14</title><description>CORVALLIS, Ore. (AP) Finally winning at Reser Stadium after a long drought, the USC Trojans lifted interim coach Ed Orgeron to their shoulders in celebration. Southern California defeated Oregon State 31-14 Friday night in Corvallis for the first time since 2004, and in the process became bowl eligible</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:43:46">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/152324775.html</link><title>USC coach O'Neill paid $1.7 million in 2010, report says</title><description>University of Southern California head basketball coach Kevin O’Neill received about $1.68 million in salary and benefits from the Trojans in 2010, according to the Los Angeles Times , which obtained USC’s federal tax return. Records for 2011 are not yet available. The former Marquette coach was</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/usc-fires-kiffin-after-7th-loss-in-11-gamesa8c262d22bed4a9083b23713adeae500-225702471.html</link><title>USC fires Lane Kiffin; Orgeron is interim coach</title><description>Southern California fired Lane Kiffin early Sunday morning, ending the coach's tumultuous tenure a few hours after the Trojans lost 62-41 at Arizona State. LOS ANGELES (AP) Lane Kiffin triumphantly flew in from Tennessee nearly four years ago as the unlikely choice to extend Southern California's football renaissance. When</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7403-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/ncaa/usc-will-investigate-report-of-gifts-to-athletese71ba2753616403aabe3eb1f2bc58fb2-168274296.html</link><title>USC will investigate report of gifts to athletes</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Southern California athletic director Pat Haden says USC will investigate a Los Angeles Times report claiming two Trojans athletes received gifts from an employee of the Los Angeles County assessor's office. The Times reported Saturday that former tailback Joe McKnight and former men's basketball player</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>