<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:45:59" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/kobe-bryant-wont-be-coming-back-this-season4a0db8148d0c493db8d4f4dbf2d18aae-249906671.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant won't be coming back this season</title><description>EL SEGUNDO, Calif. (AP) Immediately after the Los Angeles Lakers declared Kobe Bryant out for the season, he already was thinking about how to make sure the Lakers will be much less miserable when he returns. Bryant expressed only mild frustration Wednesday after the long-expected decision to end</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/kobe-bryant-im-on-twitter-nowfc7201d86e364ecaa9707f5c878bbde0-185697271.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant: I'm on Twitter now</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Kobe Bryant is no longer a holdout. He's on Twitter. With five words "The antisocial has become social" the Los Angeles Lakers guard sent the first tweet from his account Friday. More than 250,000 people followed his verified account, @kobebryant, within four hours. Bryant</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/kobe-bryant-im-on-twitter-nowd62a6b87e7564fffbc29def725a49c6b-185719221.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant: I'm on Twitter now</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Kobe Bryant is no longer a holdout. He's on Twitter. With five words "The antisocial has become social" the Los Angeles Lakers guard sent the first tweet from his account Friday. About 270,000 people followed his verified account, @kobebryant, within a few hours and he</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/lawyers-in-bryant-auction-case-head-to-court441f35fa22684e5e9b37dabf791ee3ba-207325901.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant auction dispute headed for June trial</title><description>CAMDEN, N.J. (AP) Kobe Bryant and an auction house that wants to sell memorabilia from his high school days and early pro career are heading for a trial next month, unless they can work out a deal before then. U.S. District Judge Renee Bumb on Monday set June</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:49:27">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/etc/bryant-answers-the-wakeup-call-gt6e7h0-165523006.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant answers the wake-up call</title><description>Kobe Bryant felt the game getting close, then put it away from long range. London - Kobe Bryant felt the game getting close, then put it away from long range. Bryant made six straight three-pointers in the second half, LeBron James finished with a triple-double, and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/kobe-bryant-has-bone-spur-in-left-foot507d307cdee64ded914c91a3a487b21c-200549341.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant has bone spur in left foot</title><description>MILWAUKEE (AP) Kobe Bryant has a bone spur in his left foot. Following Los Angeles' 113-103 loss to the Milwaukee Bucks on Thursday night, the Lakers revealed the injury. He left the arena using one crutch, but appeared to be walking without pain. Bryant led the Lakers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/lakers-kobe-bryant-listed-probable-with-bone-spur1cb0e1b092ca4049b8abe8768edabc5e-200674841.html</link><title>Lakers' Kobe Bryant listed probable with bone spur</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Kobe Bryant is likely to play for the Los Angeles Lakers on Saturday night against the Sacramento Kings despite a bone spur in his left foot. The Lakers listed Bryant as probable on Friday. The fifth-leading scorer in NBA history left the Bradley Center</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/kobe-bryant-wife-vanessa-call-off-their-divorce195613d9d9bb435abbda862aeee73961-186573671.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant, wife Vanessa call off their divorce</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Kobe and Vanessa Bryant are staying together. The Los Angeles Lakers superstar and his wife both announced they've called off their divorce Friday on social media. Shortly after Vanessa posted the news on Instagram, Kobe confirmed it on Facebook less than an hour before</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/kobe-bryant-battles-mom-nj-business-over-auction12e4ab2e774d4e068e527cb9bc0ac304-205956841.html</link><title>Kobe Bryant battles mom, NJ business over auction</title><description>TRENTON, N.J. (AP) Kobe Bryant is in a court battle to try to keep his mother from auctioning off mementoes from his high school days in Pennsylvania and his early years with the Los Angeles Lakers. A New Jersey auction house filed a lawsuit in U.S. District Court</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:53:01">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/121264899.html</link><title>Aaron Rodgers vs. Kobe Bryant in Spike's 'Unstoppable Jock'</title><description>Spike TV today announced its fifth annual "Guys Choice" show will air 8 p.m. June 10, and Aaron Rodgers is among this year's contenders. Voting started today for the show, which celebrates the "kingdom of guydom," and Rodgers is up against Kobe Bryant in the Unstoppable Jock</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>