<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:57:58" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:58:00">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/multimedia/photos/161116215.html</link><title>Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise to divorce</title><description>A look into the marriage and life of Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise who announced their divorce June 29, 2012  A look into the marriage and life of Katie Holmes and Tom Cruise, who announced their divorce June 29.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:58:46">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/report-tom-cruise-katie-holmes-divorcing-vv5uve1-160852455.html</link><title>Tom Cruise, Katie Holmes divorcing</title><description>Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes are divorcing after nearly five years of marriage, People.com reports. "This is a personal and private matter for Katie and her family," Holmes' attorney, Jonathan Wolfe, tells People. A representative for Cruise later issued a statement to People :</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:59:29">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/92400804.html</link><title>Mrs. Tom Cruise as Jackie O?</title><description>Lots of TV news to report this morning. Steve Carell, who plays Michael Scott in "The Office," hints that next season may be his last for the show, E! reports. And in Variety , the History channel is planning a miniseries on "The Kennedys," with Greg Kinnear</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/tom-cruise-and-katie-holmes-divorcing822e9bdf3180483291cd6914c0a320ed-160855005.html</link><title>Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes divorcing</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) It always seemed more than a little weird, didn't it? The whirlwind romance of Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes with its very public, very emphatic proclamations of love. It all occurred too quickly and too loudly to seem real. Now, after nearly six years of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tom-cruise-tabloids-settle-defamation-lawsuit67ece2d75e854d51afe573dca3cc36b0-236797651.html</link><title>Tom Cruise, tabloids, settle defamation lawsuit</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) The publisher of two tabloid magazines says it never intended to imply that Tom Cruise had abandoned his daughter after his divorce. The statement from Bauer Publishing on Friday accompanied news that Cruise and the tabloids had reached a confidential settlement in a defamation case</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tom-cruise-makes-visit-to-maracana-stadiumb736071017224757812aef4e2d441f74-200821081.html</link><title>Tom Cruise makes visit to Rio's Maracana stadium</title><description>RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) Tom Cruise took time off from promoting his latest movie in Brazil by visiting Maracana stadium and meeting former Brazilian soccer star Zico. Cruise posed for photos at the stadium's newly installed field holding a Brazil jersey with his name on the back.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:02:29">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/70609322.html</link><title>Who will let Tom Cruise flip out?</title><description>Now that Oprah Winfrey has decided to shut down her talk show, who among us will step up and land the kind of guests she was used to having? And in honor of her show, we present one of the great moments in Oprah history: The very strange behavior</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/def-leppard-talk-tom-cruise-rock-of-ages03d3fe9c362341d5bb826eeeb8458614-158873985.html</link><title>Def Leppard talk Tom Cruise, 'Rock of Ages'</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Def Leppard has no shame. When it comes to riding the fur-covered, animal print-lined coattails of "Rock of Ages," the big-screen musical opening Friday about love and hair bands in the 1980s, the group isn't shying away from commandeering some of the film's spotlight to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tom-cruise-movie-star-not-rock-starbe2dbf0c58a84c6f8336d46aea526f16-158370565.html</link><title>Tom Cruise: movie star, not rock star</title><description>LONDON (AP) Tom Cruise attended the European premier of his new film "Rock of Ages" in London's Leicester Square on Sunday and was joined on the red carpet by fellow stars Julianne Hough, Russell Brand, Paul Giamatti and Mary J. Blige. Cruise plays the tattooed and frequently shirtless</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7408-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/tom-cruise-receives-friars-icon-award-in-nyaa000552c56c49618cff59b608e93998-158846085.html</link><title>Tom Cruise receives Friars Icon award in NY</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) The Friars Club, best known for searing celebrity roasts, held the insults when it toasted Tom Cruise. The actor received the fourth ever Friars Club Entertainment Icon Award on Tuesday night, placing him in the same company as Douglas Fairbanks, Cary Grant and Frank Sinatra.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>