<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7409">rihanna chris brown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:06:22" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/rihanna-exboyfriend-chris-brown-kiss-at-vmas65bafa446a354f4a846316a094217fea-168940386.html</link><title>Rihanna, ex-boyfriend Chris Brown kiss at VMAs</title><description>Rihanna hugged, then briefly kissed ex-boyfriend Chris Brown just moments after her big win at the MTV Video Music Awards. The sometimes turbulent relationship between the two turned sweet for a brief interlude Thursday night during a commercial break after the pop star won video of the year</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7409_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:07:22">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/245534631.html</link><title>Top 'love' song on YouTube: 'Love the Way You Lie'</title><description>When it comes to love, YouTube apparently has a different definition of romance - or we do.  The world-dominating video channel said Friday that of the 5 million or so songs with the word "love" in the title on YouTube, the most-played song is "Love the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7409_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:08:31">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/235966301.html</link><title>Top of the Charts: Eminem bounds to No. 1</title><description>After last week's viral anomaly that raised Miley Cyrus' "Wrecking Ball" back to number one on the back of a YouTube comedian's parody video , things are back to normal on the Billboard Hot 100. After steadily climbing in recent weeks, Eminem finds himself on top of the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/rihanna-on-dating-brown-a-mistake-my-mistake5a8da288303e4281a19f8655daa9c947-189012751.html</link><title>Rihanna on dating Brown: A mistake? My mistake</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Rihanna says if dating Chris Brown is mistake, she's OK with that. The singer tells Rolling Stone in an interview that dating Brown makes her happy and "if it's a mistake, it's my mistake." She adds that she's ready to go public with her singer-boyfriend.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/rihanna-minaj-lead-american-music-awards-nomineesd5c461a9aad54765a3ff5f722385ca0d-173323221.html</link><title>Rihanna, Minaj lead American Music Awards nominees</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) Rihanna and Nicki Minaj are the leading nominees at the 40th annual American Music Awards with four nods each. Christina Aguilera announced the nominations Tuesday in Los Angeles. She also said she plans to perform at the ceremony next month. Drake, Justin Bieber, Maroon</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7409_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:10:18">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/41154507.html</link><title>Beat downs the new (lame, inexcusable) way of dating these days?</title><description>A post on AskMen.com about men being the victims of physical abuse caught our attention for two reasons: 1)because the last few weeks of news has included tons of reports and conversations about the alleged incident between musical artists Rihanna and Chris Brown and 2)because, as the post states,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7409-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/ny-students-satirize-rihanna-assault-in-blackface6a791e205c0541259546f543856dda12-174422991.html</link><title>NY students satirize Rihanna assault in blackface</title><description>WAVERLY, N.Y. (AP) A pep rally skit by three white high school students who wore blackface and parodied Chris Brown's arrest for assaulting Rihanna has officials in the largely white New York district vowing to set clearer expectations for school events. An alumnus, Matthew Dishler, posted a photo</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>