<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7421">story magic flute</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:22:31" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:22:33">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/arts/43214092.html</link><title>Review | Lots to love in this 'Magic Flute'</title><description>I'm glad the Florentine Opera put on Mozart's "The Magic Flute" in Andrew Porter's English translation. The language is charming and vernacular. The words fall in with the notes so as to ease both singing and intelligibility. The supertitles are nearly superfluous. I'm glad the Florentine Opera put on Mozart's</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:23:05">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/arts/43073082.html</link><title>Buck is back for 'Magic Flute' | She plays Queen of the Night in Mozart opera</title><description>Heather Buck, one of the shiniest gems in the Florentine Opera's sparkling "The Merry Widow" in 2007, is back. Buck, a brilliantly flirtatious Valencienne in Lehar's "Widow," will be the Queen of the Night in Mozart's "The Magic Flute" on Friday through Sunday. The Queen is among</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/boat-overturns-at-austrian-opera-fest-singers-weta503d6efb231488bafb8133441a75a07-218709091.html</link><title>Boat overturns at Austrian opera fest, singers wet</title><description>VIENNA (AP) A Mozart opera performed at one of Austria's premier music festivals has made an unscheduled splash after a boat carrying three singers overturned and dumped them into a lake. The Bregenz Festival features an open-air stage in Lake Constance and this year's production of "The Magic</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/met-gives-barber-a-cut-in-english-versionfb68cdc34ceb47e68c9f999c3b75d0d1-185064241.html</link><title>Met gives 'Barber' a cut in English version</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) For the first time since Rossini's most famous work was given its Metropolitan Opera premiere in 1883, "The Barber of Seville" is being presented by the company in English rather than Italian, a shortened holiday version intended to entice families during school break. To cut</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:25:11">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/43304397.html</link><title>The Florentine and the Met auditions</title><description>The Florentine Opera , under William Florescu, has gone out of its way to forge a close relationship with the Wisconsin District of the Metropolitan Opera Auditions. Florentine people attend the auditions and have offered contracts on the spot to some singers. The company also sponsors</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:25:56">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/arts/44888407.html</link><title>Acting with their feet | Mark Godden excels in letting dancers' steps, gestures tell the story</title><description>Mark Godden has given the Milwaukee Ballet three great dances: "Angels in Architecture" in 2001, "Miroirs" in 2003, and the evening-length "Magic Flute" in 2005. Godden is back, brewing a new piece about James Joyce and his troubled daughter, Lucia. Mark Godden has given the Milwaukee Ballet three great</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:26:48">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/43114317.html</link><title>The Queen of the Night</title><description>The coloratura thrills and dramatic chills of "The Queen of the Night" aria, from Mozart's "The Magic Flute," make the piece one of the crowning glories of opera. It is among the most difficult and rewarding pieces in the repertoire. Many sopranos have triumphed with it, and many have gone down in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7421_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:27:50">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/104435204.html</link><title>Three fun things to do with the family this weekend</title><description>Friday Rainforest Night at the Domes Mitchell Park Domes, 524 S. Layton Blvd. 6:30-9 p.m. $6.50 adults, $5 for children 6 to 17 Bring your flashlights and spend an adventurous night in the rainforest. Enjoy an educational tour of the tropical dome (for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7421-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/glass-britten-highlight-la-operas-201314-season1fe876eb530d453bae2139c7ea224829-186094261.html</link><title>Glass, Britten highlight LA Opera's 2013-14 season</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) The Los Angeles Opera's 2013-14 season will include the company premiere of Philip Glass' "Einstein on the Beach" and a revival of Britten's "Billy Budd" as part of celebrations of the 100th anniversary of the composer's birth. The LA Opera said Tuesday that "Einstein" will</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>