<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7431">navalni trial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:38:24" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7431-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7431_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:38:25">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/russias-navalny-found-guilty-in-libel-casec0bd307f6c41455e91ad2d18c73f0fc8-256157791.html</link><title>Navalny's conviction in Russia a chilling message</title><description>MOSCOW (AP) A Moscow judge on Tuesday left open the possibility of jailing President Vladimir Putin's main critic for years, a sign of Putin's increasingly hard-line rule against opponents. Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny was fined $8,400 on Tuesday for slandering a lawmaker. His second trial starts Thursday,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7431-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/antiputin-activist-alexei-navalny-ready-for-trialcdeef218dbe14f13aa81172d98c6bbc1-203038981.html</link><title>Anti-Putin activist Alexei Navalny ready for trial</title><description>MOSCOW (AP) Far from the streets of Moscow where he galvanized tens of thousands in anti-government protests, Alexei Navalny faces trial this week on charges that could send him to prison for 10 years. The trial, starting Wednesday in Kirov, 800 kilometers (500 miles) northeast of Moscow, accuses</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7431-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/putin-foe-navalny-defiant-as-trial-opens-in-russiabre93g05u-203417731.html</link><title>Putin foe Navalny defiant as trial opens in Russia</title><description>By Gabriela Baczynska KIROV, Russia (Reuters) - Protest leader Alexei Navalny accused Russian authorities of fabricating charges against him at the start of a trial on Wednesday that he says is intended to crush opposition to Vladimir Putin. The anti-corruption blogger, 36, was calm and defiant during</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7431-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/a-glance-at-kremlins-top-foe-alexei-navalnyd24fc02f48ba4d12a2416fa06b83c00b-203415181.html</link><title>A glance at Kremlin's top foe, Alexei Navalny</title><description>KIROV, Russia (AP) Alexei Navalny, an obscure adviser to a provincial governor just four years ago, shot up to become the Kremlin's public enemy No.1. The web-savvy 36-year-old lawyer overcame a state-imposed national media blackout and minimal funds by exploiting his blog and Twitter account to reach hundreds of</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>