<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7433">747-8</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:42:41" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7433_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:42:42">http://www.jsonline.com/business/us-faa-tells-boeing-to-fix-747-8-software-to-avoid-crash-b99233453z1-252356971.html</link><title>U.S. FAA tells Boeing to fix 747-8 software to avoid crash</title><description>The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Tuesday ordered an immediate fix to the latest version of Boeing Co.’s 747-8 plane, saying a software glitch could cause it to lose thrust when close to landing and crash. Washington — The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration on Tuesday ordered an immediate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/boeing-advises-about-engine-icing-problems923f4b4075e2441a9a8a055f90f275f8-233160341.html</link><title>Boeing advises about engine icing problems</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) Boeing is alerting airlines about possible engine icing problems on some of its new planes. It is recommending that planes with a specific General Electric engine avoid flying near thunderstorms that might contain ice crystals. Boeing spokesman Marc Birtel said Saturday that Boeing issued the advisory</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/in-wing-design-boeing-knows-when-to-fold-em-517j3gj-178494241.html</link><title>In wing design, Boeing knows when to fold 'em | 777X likely to have space-saving innovation</title><description>For the immense wings planned for the 777X, engineers at Boeing Co. are studying a design in which the wingtips fold upward to reduce the jet's span when it sits at the gate or rolls along a taxiway. Seattle - Boeing's next big jet may actually spread its</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/united-airlines-ceo-smisek-talks-787s-and-mojo5d2138817be34337a7a8deec068b829c-171672011.html</link><title>United Airlines CEO Smisek talks 787s and mojo</title><description>For years, airline executives were criticized for falling in love with shiny new airplanes, to the detriment of their shareholders. United Continental Holdings Inc. CEO Jeff Smisek makes the hard-headed business case for the new Boeing 787 his company got this week. But it sure is pretty, too.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/boeing-engineers-use-spuds-to-improve-inair-wifi6e71b94f2cc6492f9ad8ec9e8c6d9afb-184564401.html</link><title>Boeing engineers use spuds to improve in-air Wi-Fi</title><description>CHICAGO (AP) If the wireless Internet connection during your holiday flight seems more reliable than it used to, you could have the humble potato to thank. While major airlines offer in-flight Wi-Fi on many flights, the signal strength can be spotty. Airlines and aircraft makers have been striving</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7433-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/boeing-benefits-from-faster-airplane-deliveries46cabc0eda454667bee64f51dcc09f1d-175640701.html</link><title>Boeing benefits from faster airplane deliveries</title><description>Boeing is cranking out planes faster, and it's paying off. The big U.S. aerospace company is on track to meet delivery targets for the year, and on Wednesday raised its profit guidance and reported a better-than-expected profit for the third quarter. Boeing has been speeding up production,</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>