<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:50:39" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:50:41">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/255650291.html</link><title>New General Mills privacy policy prevents consumers from filing lawsuits</title><description>If you think you might file a lawsuit against General Mills at some point -- say for nearly choking on a bit of plastic that made its way into your Cheerios or Progresso soup -- you better not have used coupons to buy General Mills products, visited the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:51:20">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/78971877.html</link><title>Facebook's privacy controls</title><description>If you've logged into Facebook today, you've seen an announcement directing members to check out new privacy tools that the social networking site says are designed to simplify privacy settings. Before you change anything, I'd recommend you read up on how these updates affect you. You can start with</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:52:11">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/221795751.html</link><title>Facebook can use your photo in ads under new policy</title><description>Facebook is proposing new changes to its policies that will allow Facebook to use your name, profile photo and content in ads without compensation. The proposed update is set to go into effect in about a week, in September. A judge mandated the clarifying language as part</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:52:40">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/39783762.html</link><title>Facebook's privacy chief speaks out</title><description>Facebook's Chief Privacy Officer Chris Kelly, in his first interview about what has become a public relations debacle, spoke with Kiran Chetry on CNN's American Morning today about the changes the social network made to its "terms of use" policy . The video is here , compliments</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/german-group-gives-facebook-privacy-deadline36f5da596caf4a248cc808b24211b035-167595815.html</link><title>German group gives Facebook privacy deadline</title><description>BERLIN (AP) A consumer protection group Germany has sent Facebook a 'cease and desist' letter that claims the social-networking website breaches German privacy law. The Federation of German Consumer Organizations says Facebook has one week to stop automatically giving third party applications information about its users without their</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:54:16">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/news/227686451.html</link><title>How to prevent Google from using your name and profile photo in shared endorsements ads</title><description>Google is changing its privacy policy so that the default setting will allow Google to use your name and profile photo in product reviews in ads it sells to businesses. Google touts it as a way for users to get recommendations from their friends in searches, maps, the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/ftc-finalizes-privacy-settlement-with-facebook1fc66d4d00204821932cc6ef8101ead3-165736336.html</link><title>FTC finalizes privacy settlement with Facebook</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) The Federal Trade Commission voted Friday to finalize its settlement with Facebook, resolving charges that the social network exposed details about users' lives without getting the required legal consent. Facebook Inc. agreed to submit to government audits of its privacy practices every other year for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/facebook-poised-to-roll-out-more-privacy-controls1db715f07d864080a0fb9765b7124b26-183175651.html</link><title>Facebook poised to roll out more privacy controls</title><description>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) Facebook is trying to make its privacy controls easier to find and understand in an effort to turn the world's largest social network in to a more discreet place. The fine-tuning announced Wednesday will include several revisions that will start rolling out to Facebook's more</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/facebook-to-let-users-vote-on-privacy-changes43515b3548cd41c08f15533a3f82d648-156344145.html</link><title>Facebook to let users vote on privacy changes</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Facebook is letting its nearly 1 billion users vote on changes to its privacy policy. The previously announced changes include new sections explaining how it uses people's information. The updates also reflect recently added features such as a new profile format called Timeline. The</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7438-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/facebook-proposes-to-end-voting-on-privacy-issuesf132131909524ecf93ba3d3f148ce01a-180374951.html</link><title>Facebook proposes to end voting on privacy issues</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Facebook is proposing to end its practice of letting users vote on changes to its privacy policies, though it will continue to let users comment on proposed updates. The world's biggest social media company said in a blog post Wednesday that its voting mechanism, which</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>