<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:58:29" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/barcelona-messi-stay-top-of-ap-global-soccer-poll9ea70ddfb7bc48d39c795f9cebdbe84f-252252411.html</link><title>Barcelona, Messi stay top of AP global soccer poll</title><description>Lionel Messi's hat trick in Barcelona's win against Real Madrid gave voters an easy choice in the individual and team categories for The Associated Press weekly soccer poll. Messi received 206 points out of a possible 210 from the panel of 21 voters, while Barcelona got 202.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/barcelona-messi-stay-top-of-ap-global-soccer-pollc953fc41d1aa4b169c3be22f20bf117d-252270671.html</link><title>Barcelona, Messi stay top of AP global soccer poll</title><description>Lionel Messi's hat trick in Barcelona's win against Real Madrid gave voters an easy choice in the individual and team categories for The Associated Press weekly soccer poll. Messi received 206 points out of a possible 210 from the panel of 21 voters, while Barcelona got 202. They</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:59:46">http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/marco-reus-liverpool-top-ap-weekly-soccer-pollf5d00fadbf01447cb2239606a9d98b67-253415751.html</link><title>Marco Reus, Liverpool top AP weekly soccer poll</title><description>Liverpool earned team of the week honors for the third time this season in The Associated Press soccer poll after a 4-0 win over Tottenham propelled it back to the top of the English Premier League. Marco Reus leads the player vote after scoring a hat trick for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/lampard-breaks-chelsea-scoring-record-in-villa-win598fa04474fb4672adb60fd4fb5ab6e5-207042361.html</link><title>Barcelona wins Spanish league with Real Madrid tie</title><description>MADRID (AP) Barcelona collected its 22nd Spanish league trophy on Saturday when Real Madrid played to a 1-1 draw at Espanyol. Barcelona wrapped up a title that had been a foregone conclusion for months. Real Madrid's draw gave Barca a seve-point lead in the standings. It's the fourth</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/real-madrid-tops-forbes-most-valuable-teams-listbb6d5652c7954869bcecc6e1c977f2da-215534511.html</link><title>Real Madrid tops Forbes' most valuable teams list</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Real Madrid tops Forbes' list of 50 most valuable sports teams, with Manchester United and Barcelona holding the next two spots. Forbes says Real Madrid is worth $3.3 billion. The Spanish power moved up a spot from No. 2 last year. Man United, which</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/barcabayern-madriddortmund-in-champions-leagueb77e1c67a5964b3da0122998335a5cf8-202717511.html</link><title>Barca-Bayern, Madrid-Dortmund in Champions League</title><description>NYON, Switzerland (AP) It's a Spain vs. Germany double bill in the Champions League semifinals. Barcelona will play Bayern Munich and Real Madrid will face Borussia Dortmund as Friday's draw kept the Spanish and German teams apart. "I find it very thrilling to be playing against the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/real-madrid-leads-ap-rankings-after-clasico-wins7f5c9fee9ba04e4b9e93076f30ff073a-195257591.html</link><title>Real Madrid leads AP rankings after Clasico wins</title><description>LONDON (AP) Two victories in four days over rival Barcelona propelled Real Madrid to first place in the AP global soccer rankings. Cristiano Ronaldo's role in Real's victories was not enough to make him player of the week in The Associated Press survey of 22 global soccer journalists.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/neymar-leads-barcelona-to-21-win-over-madrid0062d7ddc1b14ccd81b3c4a3c187d17a-229388111.html</link><title>Neymar leads Barcelona to 2-1 win over Madrid</title><description>BARCELONA, Spain (AP) Neymar scored one goal and set up Alexis Sanchez's winning chip shot in the 78th minute, carrying Barcelona past Real Madrid 2-1 in the first "clasico" since the defending champions added Neymar and Real signed Gareth Bale. With Lionel Messi oddly quiet for Barcelona, Neymar</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/barcelona-madrid-routed-by-german-clubs8fe551c83a0248eab4a186ab6ea5c387-204705971.html</link><title>Barcelona, Madrid routed by German clubs</title><description>STUTTGART, Germany (AP) The expectation of seeing Lionel Messi line up against Cristiano Ronaldo in the Champions League final, of watching Barcelona and Real Madrid fight for supremacy in the ultimate "Clasico," has been all but washed away. Instead of seeing Spain's two biggest teams play for the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7440-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/neymar-signs-5year-contract-with-barcelonab56d31dab4c34699b428d5190d591401-209963231.html</link><title>Neymar signs 5-year contract with Barcelona</title><description>BARCELONA, Spain (AP) Neymar completed his transfer to Barcelona on Monday in a deal that unites the Brazilian star with Lionel Messi in what should be a formidable attacking partnership. Neymar signed a five-year contract with club president Sandro Rosell after choosing Barcelona over Real Madrid. The</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>