<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:19:45" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:19:46">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/98852629.html</link><title>Chicago follows the Milwaukee lead with marathon training run</title><description>The Badgerland Striders appear to have started a trend with their long-standing build up program for the Lakefront Marathon. The folks at My Chicago Athlete Magazine announced Tuesday their own version, a run dubbed the 20-Miler in the Busse Woods Forest Preserve in Elk Grove Village, on Sept.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:20:53">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/89009632.html</link><title>New study links marathon training and coronary plaque buildup</title><description>A study presented this week at the American College of Cardiology adds another factor to the cost-benefit equation of long-term marathon training by linking the training to increased coronary calcium and plaque. Researchers at the Minneapolis Heart Institute studied 25 runners who competed in the Twin Cities Marathon</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:21:57">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/119938159.html</link><title>Veteran runner will test his 12-day Boston Marathon training plan</title><description>If a tree falls on your ankle, will it keep you from running the Boston Marathon? Not if you’re Rick Stefanovic and you have your heart set on making that left turn onto Boylston St. a 20th consecutive time. Even during surgery on Dec. 4,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:22:44">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/64949252.html</link><title>The Drop Bag: Marathon tragedies and trains, rolling stops</title><description>The "Drop Bag" is a collection of news and events from the Off the Couch sporting world. The name refers to the drop bags that competitors use to get their post-race necessities from the start line to the finish line of point-to-point races. Hope I</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:23:28">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/104344308.html</link><title>Train slowed about 100 in Milwaukee Lakefront Marathon</title><description>About 100 runners in the Milwaukee Lakefront Marathon were stopped by a train that crossed a road near the 1.6-mile mark, according to Race Director Kristine Hinrichs. She has been following up on the train delay in the days following the race, and had this to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:24:31">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/102024488.html</link><title>Marathon Nation lays out a rapid ramp-up program</title><description>In preparation for the Lakefront Marathon, I’ve followed a relatively standard, 16-week training program, based on the Competitive Runner’s handbook written by Bob Glover and Shelly-Lynn Florence Glover. I’ve been a bit short on the recommended weekly volume, which should be in the 40-plus range for my</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>