<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:26:13" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:26:14">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/219754411.html</link><title>In search of the best running shoe</title><description>I took a step toward life as a practical grown up recently when I went to the athletic store and bypassed the very cute, very colorful, fun little running and cross training shoes that are so popular now and headed right for the ugly, awful, leather encased, gel conglomerated,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/sports/national/running-over-shoe-extends-danicas-run-of-bad-luck9351d45c09634e17895e702819f9ce45-167316365.html</link><title>Running over shoe extends Danica's run of bad luck</title><description>BRISTOL, Tenn. (AP) Danica Patrick channeled her best Austin Powers impersonation to characterize her recent run of bad luck. "Who throws a shoe?" Patrick asked Friday in a faux English accent. "I mean, really?" The line from the original "Austin Powers" movie applies to Patrick after she</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:27:22">http://www.jsonline.com/business/gawlittas-shoe-store-taking-final-step-closing-nq9nl0v-204934361.html</link><title>Gawlitta's shoe store taking final step: Closing | The family-run West Allis shop opened in 1929</title><description>An 84-year-old West Allis shoe store is closing soon, ending a legacy that began with a German immigrant who worked in a Chicago shoe factory. An 84-year-old West Allis shoe store is closing soon, ending a legacy that began with a German immigrant who worked in a Chicago shoe factory,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:27:55">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/sports/100281234.html</link><title>For spectators, pack your hiking shoes</title><description>Haven - It's a golf course after all, not the Kettle Drumlin trail. But for golf fans who want to see as many holes as possible at Whistling Straits, it's best to be prepared for a long hike. This is a very hilly course. And</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:28:40">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/lifestyle/243242751.html</link><title>Renewed Resolutions: Workout Wear</title><description>Take a look at some trends in fitness fashion. A new year, a new outlook, a new financial plan, or perhaps even a new career. In with the good habits and out with the bad. The New Year brings many resolutions, but the most popular is a new fitness routine.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:29:14">http://www.germantownnow.com/news/timeless-profession-qv7k9pl-181044321.html</link><title>In Your Shoes | Germantown librarians keep a popular place running smoothly</title><description>About a month ago someone asked me how libraries are able to remain open. I found out firsthand last week when I stepped into the shoes of a librarian, thanks to Germantown Library Director Roberta Olson. "If only you could walk a mile in my shoes." We've all read</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>