<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:39:59" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:40:00">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/71973857.html</link><title>Reader Recipe Exchange | Rice balls</title><description>Henni Bartel, Brown Deer, sent a recipe for rice balls that were filled with cheese and included a meat sauce, in response to a request from Dot Nemitz, Cudahy. Bartel wrote: "I have enclosed a very good recipe. It is a bit time consuming, but well worth the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:40:33">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/peter-sciortinos-rice-balls-2t8ak16-187897121.html</link><title>Restaurant Recipes | Peter Sciortino's rice balls</title><description>C.D., Greenfield, requested the recipe for arancini or rice balls from Peter Sciortino Bakery, which she has at Festa Italiana every year. C.D. , Greenfield, requested the recipe for arancini or rice balls from Peter Sciortino Bakery, 1101 E. Brady St. She said she has the dish at Festa</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:41:27">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/outpost-natural-foods-wild-rice-tofu-salad-b9931821z1-212025411.html</link><title>Restaurant Recipes | Outpost Natural Foods Wild Rice Tofu Salad</title><description>Joan Gaska of West Allis requested the recipe for Wild Rice Tofu Salad from Outpost Natural Foods. Joan Gaska of West Allis requested the recipe for Wild Rice Tofu Salad from Outpost Natural Foods, 7000 W. State St., Wauwatosa. She wrote: "I needed a quick lunch both gluten-free</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:42:29">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/flannerys-pan-fried-walleye-with-wild-rice-and-vegetable-medley-b9964095z1-218521761.html</link><title>Restaurant Recipes | Flannery's pan-fried walleye with wild rice and vegetable medley</title><description>Katherine Krueger, Milwaukee, requested the recipe for pan-fried walleye with a wild rice medley from Flannery's at the Fire Ridge Golf Club. Katherine Krueger , Milwaukee, requested the recipe for pan-fried walleye with a wild rice medley from Flannery's at the Fire Ridge Golf Club, 2241 County Road W,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:42:52">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/102305889.html</link><title>Restaurant Recipes | BackStreet Cafe Mushroom Wild Rice Soup</title><description>Linda Belich, Mukwonago , requested the recipe for a mushroom and wild rice soup from BackStreet Café, 2566 Sun Valley Drive, Delafield. She wrote: "This absolutely the best soup I have ever had. Full of mouth watering flavor yet not overly salty. It is a meal in itself.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:43:43">http://www.jsonline.com/features/food/103893064.html</link><title>Restaurant Recipes | Eagle Waters Resort Chicken &amp; Wild Rice Soup</title><description>Shirley Jagler, Oak Creek, requested the recipe for a creamy chicken and wild rice soup from Eagle Waters Resort in Eagle River. She wrote: "Several of us 'wined and dined' in Eagle River recently. We had a bowl of this awesome soup before our meal and it was</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>