<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:54:25" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:54:27">http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/musicandnightlife/jada-pinkett-smith-taking-metal-band-to-shank-hall-b99108681z1-225593142.html</link><title>Concert Announcement | Jada Pinkett Smith taking metal band to Shank Hall</title><description>The actress, wife to Will and mother to Jaden and Willow, will play the role of rock frontwoman Nov. 11. Hollywood actress Jada Pinkett Smith — wife to Will Smith , and mother to Jaden and Willow — will take on the role</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7463-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/venice-fans-wait-hours-for-scarlett-johansson40d81776310643d293f0f64c02a5f622-222192351.html</link><title>Venice fans wait hours for Scarlett Johansson</title><description>VENICE, Italy (AP) Fans of Scarlet Johansson waited for hours under a hot sun for the Hollywood actress to arrive in a water taxi for a news conference at the Venice Film Festival, and she rewarded them with a smile and autographs. Johansson was in Venice on Tuesday</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7463-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/hollywood-daughter-wins-miss-golden-globee136bb21255b487d882e4445ed55e2cf-232955291.html</link><title>Hollywood daughter wins Miss Golden Globe</title><description>WEST HOLLYWOOD, Calif. (AP) The Golden Globe season has officially begun with the crowning of aspiring actress Sosie Bacon, the daughter of Globe winners Kevin Bacon and Kyra Sedgwick, as Miss Golden Globe 2014. Chosen each year by the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, Miss Golden Globe assists with</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7463-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/1950s-hollywood-leading-lady-patricia-medina-dieseae3b3c4de594b2f823dadc57eea6fd8-149871285.html</link><title>1950s Hollywood leading lady Patricia Medina dies</title><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) The actress who became a leading lady of Hollywood films in the 1950s opposite Glenn Ford, Alan Ladd, Karl Malden and Fernando Lamas has died in Los Angeles. Patricia Medina was 92. Her friend, Meredith Silverbach, told the Los Angeles Times (http://lat.ms/K1ouks) that</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>