<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:15:49" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/chinas-bird-flu-response-shows-new-openness6853b124cb884d698e47048c00d5afbd-202488361.html</link><title>China's bird flu response shows new openness</title><description>SHANGHAI (AP) After a new and lethal strain of bird flu emerged in Shanghai two weeks ago, the government of China's bustling financial capital responded with live updates on a Twitter-like microblog. It's a starkly different approach than a decade ago, when Chinese officials silenced reporting as a deadly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/chinas-bird-flu-response-shows-new-openness94c0328d01f84a2aab4f449d92fb6024-202468331.html</link><title>China's bird flu response shows new openness</title><description>SHANGHAI (AP) After a new and lethal strain of bird flu emerged in Shanghai two weeks ago, the government of China's bustling financial capital responded with live updates on a Twitter-like microblog. It's a starkly different approach than a decade ago, when Chinese officials silenced reporting as a deadly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/tablet/topstories/who-says-no-poultry-contact-in-some-china-bird-flu-casesbre93g04b-203413021.html</link><title>WHO says no poultry contact in some China bird flu cases</title><description>GENEVA/BEIJING (Reuters) - The World Health Organization said on Wednesday that a number of people who have tested positive for a new strain of bird flu in China have had no history of contact with poultry, adding to the mystery about the virus that has killed 16 people to date.WHO</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/chinas-bird-flu-death-toll-rises-to-20bre93k0by-204017871.html</link><title>China's bird flu death toll rises to 20</title><description>GENEVA (Reuters) - Two more people have died from a new strain of avian influenza, bringing to 20 the number of deaths from the H7N9 virus, the World Health Organization (WHO) said on Sunday. Chinese authorities have notified the WHO of six new cases, bringing the total to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/china-says-new-bird-flu-case-found-in-northeastern-chinabre93l0ef-204068951.html</link><title>China says new bird flu case found in northeastern China</title><description>BEIJING (Reuters) - A man in the northeastern Chinese province of Shandong has been infected by a new strain of bird flu, the first case found in the province, state news agency Xinhua said on Monday, bringing the total number of infected victims in China to 105. The</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/death-toll-from-bird-flu-in-china-rises-to-133d0bd710767d4fbc9c669abe3f6db017-202909821.html</link><title>Death toll from bird flu in China rises to 13</title><description>BEIJING (AP) Two more people have died in China from a new strain of bird flu, raising the death toll from the virus to 13, state media reported Sunday. The official Xinhua News Agency said the two deaths were reported in Shanghai and that three new cases were</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/china-reports-2-more-cases-of-new-bird-flu-virus167af9573edd4f74aacdfbe9408bda42-201826671.html</link><title>China reports 3 more cases of new bird flu virus</title><description>BEIJING (AP) China reported three more cases of human infection of a new strain of bird flu on Sunday, raising the total number of cases to 21. Six of those who contracted the H7N9 virus have died. All 21 cases have been reported in the eastern part of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:20:52">http://www.jsonline.com/news/health/bird-flu-virus-adapting-to-human-cells-sparking-pandemic-fear-2t9he0u-202704561.html</link><title>Milwaukee Health Department issues bird flu bulletin as fears of potential pandemic grow | Travelers to China urged to use caution as H7N9 strain expands</title><description>Anyone who travels to China and comes down with a respiratory illness within 10 days of returning should be screened for a bird flu virus that has killed at least 11 people in central-eastern China, a Milwaukee Health Department official said Friday. Anyone who travels to China and comes down</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>