<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:49:57" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:49:59">http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/expert-syria-has-dumped-86-pc-of-chemical-weaponsbe014b6df57c49a1969868eefe4fe36b-256203771.html</link><title>Expert: Syria has dumped 86 pc of chemical weapons</title><description>AMSTERDAM (AP) Syria's government has disposed of more than 86 percent of its total chemical weapons stockpile, according to the watchdog agency charged with overseeing its removal. Director-General Ahmet Uzumcu of the Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons says Syria has just surrendered another batch of raw</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/watchdog-plan-syria-arsenal-inspections-by-oct-1978f482563e74c46b77db8fd122fe1a1-225482022.html</link><title>UN votes to eliminate Syria's chemical weapons</title><description>UNITED NATIONS (AP) The U.N. Security Council voted unanimously Friday night to secure and destroy Syria's chemical weapons stockpile, a landmark decision aimed at taking poison gas off the battlefield in the escalating 2 1/2-year conflict. The vote after two weeks of intense negotiations marked a major breakthrough</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:51:14">http://www.jsonline.com/multimedia/photos/syria-silent-as-russia-us-strike-chemical-weapons-deal-b9998324z1-223771981.html</link><title>Syria silent as Russia, U.S. strike chemical weapons deal</title><description>A diplomatic breakthrough Saturday on securing and destroying Syria's chemical weapons stockpile averted the threat of U.S. military action for the moment and could swing momentum toward ending a horrific civil war. A diplomatic breakthrough Saturday on securing and destroying Syria's chemical weapons stockpile averted the threat of U.S. military</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/watchdog-discusses-syria-weapons-destruction-planf30ee16435d6478fb1d0c5fd7d965e25-232019411.html</link><title>Albania refuses to accept Syria's chemical weapons</title><description>TIRANA, Albania (AP) The mission to destroy Syria's poison gas stockpile was dealt a serious blow Friday when Albania refused to host the destruction, but the global chemical weapons watchdog said it is still confident it can eradicate the arsenal outside Syria by the middle of next year.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/lawmakers-syria-chemical-weapons-could-menace-use3bb7a5548914b86894465c754671c35-205176211.html</link><title>Lawmakers: Syria chemical weapons could menace US</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) Syria's stockpile of chemical weapons could be a greater threat after that nation's president leaves power and could end up targeting Americans at home, lawmakers warned Sunday as they considered a U.S. response that stops short of sending military forces there. U.S. officials last week declared</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/in-us-arsenal-lessons-for-syria-chemical-weapons7c477ce658d24547bfd44ab760bef22c-223583001.html</link><title>In US arsenal, lessons for Syria chemical weapons</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) It's not easy or quick to get rid of a nation's chemical weapons. Just ask the United States. Three decades after the U.S. started destroying its own chemical weapons, the nation's stockpile stands at more than 3,000 tons about three times what the U.S. now says</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/us-options-limited-on-syria-despite-weapons-reportef1e8593b2e748a4a6028627255c9b77-204807411.html</link><title>Red line: Obama cautious on Syria chemical weapons</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) Proceeding cautiously, President Barack Obama insisted on Friday that any use of chemical weapons by Syria would change his "calculus" about U.S. military involvement in the 2-year-old civil war but said too little was known about a pair of likely sarin attacks to order aggressive action now.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/obama-warns-syria-against-using-chemical-weapons95bb7fa709f44283a8b4185bc3c6bdf5-181903551.html</link><title>Obama warns Syria against using chemical weapons</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) President Barack Obama warned Syria on Monday that the use of chemical weapons would be "totally unacceptable" and that the country's leaders would be held accountable. Obama said that if Syrian President Bashar Assad made the "tragic mistake" of deploying chemical weapons, there would be consequences.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/syria-sends-opcw-chemical-weapons-inventoryc9be8499d0104b7aa019247dfe0193dd-224561941.html</link><title>Syria sends watchdog chemical weapons inventory</title><description>THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) Syria has sent the Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons an "initial declaration" outlining its weapons program, the organization said Friday, in keeping with the agreement Russia and the U.S. brokered to have Syria give up its chemical weapons arsenal. Michael Luhan, the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7498-10"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/us-weighs-talk-of-syria-dumping-chemical-weapons26dcfebd5f654f90a0899b0882f99ec7-222998121.html</link><title>Sudden plan: Syria to dispose of chemical weapons?</title><description>WASHINGTON (AP) In a rapid and remarkable chain of events, Syria welcomed the idea of turning over all of its chemical weapons for destruction on Monday, and President Barack Obama, though expressing deep skepticism, declared it a "potentially a significant breakthrough" that could head off the threats of U.S.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>