<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:56:25" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:56:28">http://www.jsonline.com/business/party-seems-to-be-winding-down-for-gold-prices-b99154903z1-234893381.html</link><title>Historical Perspectives | Party seems to be winding down for gold prices</title><description>There are multiple reasons for the recent sell-off. From a technical standpoint, gold was overextended, making it vulnerable to profit taking. "Turn out the lights, the party's over," the late Monday Night Football analyst Don Meredith would croon when the outcome was no longer in doubt. "They say that 'all</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:56:59">http://www.jsonline.com/business/does-gold-price-foreshadow-another-slowdown-9399chb-204915641.html</link><title>Historical Perspectives | Does gold price foreshadow another slowdown?</title><description>It is worth asking what the current bear market in gold is telling investors. Despite a rebound last week, the yellow metal is still down almost 25% from its peak. "Salvation lies within," lectured the corrupt Warden Samuel Norton while handing a Bible to the wrongfully convicted Andy Dufresne in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:57:55">http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/business/53044002.html</link><title>Before selling gold, get appraisal, then call for best prices</title><description>Like lots of folks, my mom has plenty of gold jewelry that she doesn’t wear anymore. And as gold prices remain high, it’s awfully tempting for her to consider selling. She worries about getting fleeced. Which raises the questions: How does she, or anyone, know a good deal,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:58:28">http://www.jsonline.com/business/120521074.html</link><title>Gold turns investors' heads | How high will it go? Political uncertainty fuels interest</title><description>The luster of gold has been catching the eye of humans for millenniums, but it shines even brighter when the world around it gets messy. Gold set a record last week when it topped $1,500 an ounce. The luster of gold has been catching the eye of humans for millenniums,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e104/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:59:18">http://www.jsonline.com/news/wisconsin/127496288.html</link><title>Mining projects pick up steam in Wisconsin | Rising metal prices, particularly gold, revive exploration interest</title><description>The proposed Gogebic mine near Hurley has attracted the lion's share of attention on mining matters in Wisconsin this year, but other projects are also picking up momentum. Spring Green - The proposed Gogebic mine near Hurley has attracted the lion's share of attention on mining matters</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/gold-plunges-to-lowest-in-more-than-two-years439f707312894f74b5727586800e220e-203013031.html</link><title>Gold plunges to lowest in more than two years</title><description>The price of gold is plummeting its lowest level in more than two years. The precious metal extended its decline after plunging on Friday, when the U.S. government reported that wholesale prices fell in March by the most in 10 months. Investors tend to buy gold when they</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/swiss-central-bank-reports-2013-loss-on-gold137e5962c9c84bdf897dadd32b09b90c-238823681.html</link><title>Swiss central bank reports 2013 loss on gold</title><description>GENEVA (AP) Switzerland's central bank has reported a loss of 9 billion Swiss francs ($9.9 billion) for 2013, denying shareholders and local governments any annual profit sharing. The Swiss National Bank said Monday that it lost 15 billion francs in the value of its gold holdings, but that</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7499-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/business/national/barrick-removes-ceo-on-disappointing-share-price8dd3f9e84d034a90a7af7ef5926b721b-157453475.html</link><title>Barrick removes CEO on disappointing share price</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) Canada's Barrick Gold Corp., the world's largest gold producer, has ousted CEO and President Aaron Regent, citing its disappointing share price performance. The announcement was sudden and the decision effective immediately. But questions over the company's explanation for the change were growing louder. The company</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>