<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 11:07:06" name="JSOnline" id="FW14-e104"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-01"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/56-dead-in-new-ethnic-violence-in-myanmar47d6b98a8b534bd187a02f6d22e2ca47-175789831.html</link><title>56 dead in renewed ethnic violence in west Myanmar</title><description>KYAUKTAW, Myanmar (AP) At least 56 people have been killed and 1,900 homes destroyed in renewed ethnic violence in western Myanmar as the government warned perpetrators and the international community appealed for calm. About 75,000 people remain in refugee camps since an outbreak of violence in June between</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-02"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/ethnic-traditions-vanishing-as-myanmar-opens-up4790354092ae4795bbdb6634e4fb720b-237272011.html</link><title>Ethnic traditions vanishing as Myanmar opens up</title><description>KAMPALET, Myanmar (AP) High in the hills of Myanmar's Chin state, Shwe Mana plays a gentle song on a bamboo flute using only her nostrils one of the last of her tribe to preserve this ancient skill. A dark, intricate web of tattoos covers her face, harking back to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-03"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/death-toll-tops-100-in-myanmar-ethnic-strifec28b93f5e8aa4471a1951f827639544c-175949311.html</link><title>Myanmar says ethnic strife killed 67</title><description>SITTWE, Myanmar (AP) Myanmar authorities on Friday revised downward the death toll from this week's ethnic violence in the country's west after warning that the strife risks harming the country's reputation as it seeks to shift to democratic rule. State television reported Friday night that 67 people had</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-04"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/jackie-chan-to-combat-myanmar-child-trafficking0d35605bb05f4dfcaa72fa1b8aae0980-161203065.html</link><title>Jackie Chan to combat Myanmar child trafficking</title><description>YANGON, Myanmar (AP) Hong Kong action star Jackie Chan is going to Myanmar this week on a three-day mission to help combat child trafficking in the Southeast Asian nation. UNICEF announced Tuesday that in his capacity as a good-will ambassador, Chan will visit the agency's projects for supporting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-05"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/ap-photos-myanmar-ready-for-historic-obama-visit0b8ef01adff44ab786ada16141fc4b54-179846421.html</link><title>AP PHOTOS: Obama visits once-pariah state, Myanmar</title><description>YANGON, Myanmar (AP) President Barack Obama's historic visit to Myanmar on Monday is meant to show America's support for the country's transition to democracy. The White House has cautioned that Obama's trip to the former pariah state should not be viewed as a "victory celebration" but as an</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-06"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/myanmar-explains-power-cuts-to-calm-rare-protests486967d2a36448d892126cb187ea166c-152597365.html</link><title>Myanmar explains power cuts to calm rare protests</title><description>YANGON, Myanmar (AP) Myanmar's government made an uncharacteristic plea for understanding Tuesday after chronic power cuts set off rare protests in the Southeast Asian country that is easing toward democracy after decades of military rule. A candlelight vigil was planned at Yangon's City Hall on Tuesday evening, following</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-07"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/obama-on-asia-trip-first-pays-visit-to-thailand28e0d4ef30304d3098e54ab6716a3f6c-179847051.html</link><title>Obama: Myanmar visit about sustaining momentum</title><description>YANGON, Myanmar (AP) In a historic trip to a long shunned land, President Barack Obama on Monday showered praise and promises of more U.S. help to Myanmar if the Asian nation keeps building its new democracy. "Our goal is to sustain the momentum," he declared with pride as the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-08"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/national/freedom-brings-new-challenges-for-myanmar-writerse6452466bb5a4d9693dfa102f1ef55c4-189775061.html</link><title>Freedom brings new challenges for Myanmar writers</title><description>YANGON, Myanmar (AP) Poet Saw Wai parked himself on the lawn, unfurled a map of Myanmar with a blob of blood-red paint dripping down from a spot up north and invited people to make poetry with him. "He's calling for more trouble," said a passerby. What the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e104-7505-09"><link>http://www.jsonline.com/news/usandworld/national/ap-exclusive-myanmar-verifying-muslim-citizenship51c1dd14f3ba42c39e3a56c8221d2f58-181495391.html</link><title>AP Exclusive: Myanmar verifying Muslim citizenship</title><description>SIN THET MAW, Myanmar (AP) Guarded by rifle-toting police, immigration authorities in western Myanmar have launched a major operation aimed at settling an explosive question at the heart of the biggest crisis the government has faced since beginning its nascent transition to democracy last year. It's a question</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>