<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:01" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:02">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-people-putting-responsibility-to-the-test-or-the-downfall-of-the-kitchen-cabinet-and-collar-presses</link><title>The People Putting Responsibility To The Test Or The Downfall of The Kitchen Cabinet and Collar Presses</title><description>The People Putting Responsibility To The Test Or The Downfall of The Kitchen Cabinet and Collar Presses

A prediction of dire consequences to follow from Jackson's withdrawal of federal ... (more)

A prediction of dire consequences to follow from Jackson's withdrawal of federal funds from the Bank of the United States, initiated late in 1833. The artist is harshly critical of Jackson's move to distribute federal treasury funds among several state or so-called "pet" banks. He also condemns the influence of both Jackson's informal circle of advisors, the "Kitchen Cabinet," and the newspapers friendly to the Administration, the "Collar Presses." Jackson declared his own personal "responsibility" for the controversial order to remove the feredal deposits from the Bank. Here a mob of farmers, laborers, and tradesmen riot, holding papers saying "Broken Bank," and shouting "Send back the deposites! Recharter the Bank!" and "Come back old responsibility." They pursue Jackson, who flees to the right carried on the back of Jack Downing. Jackson: "By the Eternal Major Downing; I find Ive been a mere tool to that Damn'd Amos [Kendall] and his set, the sooner I cut stick the better." Downing: "I told you I'd get you off Jinral but it will be a tarnel tight squeeze I guess." In the center Thomas Ellicott and Reuben Whitney, anti-Bank fiscal advisors to the administration, try to pull down the statue of Justice (here labeled "Supreme Court") resting on a pedestal "Constitution." A man in judge's robes, Supreme Court Justice John Marshall, warns "Miscreants forbear, the day of retribution is at hand and Justice shall be no longer set at defiance!" Five dogs, representing newspapers supportive of Jackson's program, including the "Globe, Albany Argus, Evening Post, Standard," and "Journal of Commerce" scamper away with their collars chained together. These are called "Collar Presses, " a derisive nickname playing on their status as newspapers or "presses" subservient to the administration. On the far left Henry Clay tells Daniel Webster and John Calhoun, "Behold Senators the fulfilment of my predictions!" Below them two blacks converse: "Hurrah Bob two or three more rows like dis and nigger free, for there will be no more Goberment." "Hurrah! for Massa Garison [i.e. abolitionist William Lloyd Garrison], den he shall be King!" On a step at lower left a sailor offers a Jewish broker a ten dollar bank-note. Sailor: "I say Moses give us some ballast for this here bit of rag." Banker: "Mine Got that ish one of the Pet Bankhs I'll give you one Dollar for the Ten."|Entered . . . Southern District of New York by T.W. Whitley 1834, and for sale at 104 Broadway.|T.W. Whitley alias Sir Joshua invt.|The print was recorded as deposited for copyright by Whitley on February 1, 1834. The print was probably printed and sold by Anthony Imbert, since his address is given in the imprint. The print is also very close in style to Imbert's "Old Nick's New Patent Plan ... (no. 1834-5).|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 35.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1834-7. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76378/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:28:59">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/dsp-development-environment-introductory-exercise-for-ti-tms320c55x</link><title>DSP Development Environment: Introductory Exercise for TI TMS320C55x</title><description>DSP Development Environment: Introductory Exercise for TI TMS320C55x

This exercise introduces the hardware and software used in the course. By ... (more)

This exercise introduces the hardware and software used in the course. By the end of this module, you should be comfortable with the basics of testing a simple real-time DSP system with Code Composer Studio, the debugging environment we will be using thro (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Homework and Assignments
Readings
Syllabi
Collection:

Connexions
Provider:

Rice University
Author:

Lee Potter
Thomas Shen

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/4805/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:18">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/using-dermatoglyphics-from-down-syndrome-and-class-populations-to-study-the-genetics-of-a-complex-trait</link><title>Using Dermatoglyphics from Down Syndrome and Class Populations to Study the Genetics of a complex trait</title><description>Using Dermatoglyphics from Down Syndrome and Class Populations to Study the Genetics of a complex trait

Dermatoglyphics is the study of epidermal ridges on the hands and feet. ... (more)

Dermatoglyphics is the study of epidermal ridges on the hands and feet. Ridge patterns and counts develop prenatally, are inherited, and show quantitative variation. This exercise introduces the preparation and interpretation of finger and palm prints for quantitative analysis. The techniques are simple, inexpensive, and can be adapted as an exercise on genetics for beginning or advanced students. Palm prints from individuals with Down Syndrome serve as a population sample to statistically test for differences with the class population and also create an opportunity to discuss the cause and effects of Down Syndrome. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

Association for Biology Laboratory Education (ABLE)
Provider:

St. Mary's College
Author:

Thomas Fogle

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_03_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/32552/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:34:46">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/15-310-managerial-psychology-laboratory-spring-2003</link><title>Managerial Psychology Laboratory, Spring 2003</title><description>Managerial Psychology Laboratory, Spring 2003

Surveys social psychology and organization theory interpreted in the context of the ... (more)

Surveys social psychology and organization theory interpreted in the context of the managerial environment. Shares lectures with 15.301, with a separate recitation required. 15.301 is intended primarily for non-Sloan students, both graduate and undergraduate. Deals with a number of diverse subjects, including motivation and reward systems for engineers and scientists in industry; the aging of technical groups; the management of R&amp;D matrix organizations; and the architecture of R&amp;D laboratories and its effect on communication patterns in the organization. 15.301 is a core subject for students majoring in management science. A laboratory is a required element of the course for these students. It involves projects of an applied nature in behavioral science. Emphasizes use of behavioral science research methods to test hypotheses concerning organizational behavior. Instruction and practice in communication include report writing, team decision-making, and oral and visual presentation. (less)

Subject:

Business
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Lecture Notes
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Allen, Thomas John

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/259/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:38:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/13-017-design-of-ocean-systems-i-spring-2003</link><title>Design of Ocean Systems I, Spring 2003</title><description>Design of Ocean Systems I, Spring 2003

A two-semester subject sequence (of which this is the first half) that ... (more)

A two-semester subject sequence (of which this is the first half) that demonstrates the design process through its application to a working model-scale ocean system. Emphasis is on carrying out the design and implementation of the system, including demonstration of its operation in the marine environment. Spring Term: Introduction to the design process and its application to ocean engineering. Design project with students developing system definition and completing its preliminary design. Students are instructed in the design process, embedded systems programming and interfacing techniques, sensors, actuators, and the control of marine systems. Communications skills are honed through written and oral reports and engineering ethics are discussed. Fall Term: Students work as a group to design, plan, construct, test, and operate the model-scale ocean system defined in 13.017. Special emphasis is placed on testing the system in the marine environment and analyzing its performance in relation to the original system specification. The social aspects of engineering are discussed including group dynamics and time management. The specific design project varies from year to year and is announced to the students on the first day of class in 13.017. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Full Course
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Thomas R. Consi

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/182/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:39:50">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/2-019-design-of-ocean-systems-i-13-017-spring-2002</link><title>Design of Ocean Systems I (13.017), Spring 2002</title><description>Design of Ocean Systems I (13.017), Spring 2002

A two-semester subject sequence (of which this is the first half) that ... (more)

A two-semester subject sequence (of which this is the first half) that demonstrates the design process through its application to a working model-scale ocean system. Emphasis is on carrying out the design and implementation of the system, including demonstration of its operation in the marine environment. Spring Term: Introduction to the design process and its application to ocean engineering. Design project with students developing system definition and completing its preliminary design. Students are instructed in the design process, embedded systems programming and interfacing techniques, sensors, actuators, and the control of marine systems. Communications skills are honed through written and oral reports and engineering ethics are discussed. Fall Term: Students work as a group to design, plan, construct, test, and operate the model-scale ocean system defined in 13.017. Special emphasis is placed on testing the system in the marine environment and analyzing its performance in relation to the original system specification. The social aspects of engineering are discussed including group dynamics and time management. The specific design project varies from year to year and is announced to the students on the first day of class in 13.017. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Full Course
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Thomas R. Consi

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7031_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/517/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>