<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:04:33" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:04:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/technology-and-nature-in-american-history-spring-2008</link><title>Technology and Nature in American History, Spring 2008</title><description>Technology and Nature in American History, Spring 2008

Subject considers how the visual and material world of "nature" has been ... (more)

Subject considers how the visual and material world of "nature" has been reshaped by industrial practices, beliefs, structures, and activities. Readings in historical geography, aesthetics, American history, environmental and ecological history, architecture, city planning, and landscape studies. Several field trips planned to visit local industrial landscapes. Assignments involve weekly short, written responses to the readings, and discussion-leading. Final project is a photo-essay on the student's choice of industrial site (photographic experience not necessary). (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Lecture Notes
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Pietruska, Jamie

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/19968/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:08:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/thomas-moran</link><title>Thomas Moran</title><description>Thomas Moran

Thomas Moran was one of the major landscape painters of his day, ... (more)

Thomas Moran was one of the major landscape painters of his day, and painted some of America's most prominent natural treasures, including the Rocky Mountains, the Grand Canyon, and Yellowstone. He also arranged for the first government-sponsored survey of Yellowstone, and his images were later reported to have played a decisive role in the debate that led to the establishment of Yellowstone as the first national park in March 1872. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

National Gallery of Art
Provider:

National Gallery of Art

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17944/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:11:17">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-evolution-of-the-conservation-movement-1850-1920</link><title>The Evolution of the Conservation Movement, 1850-1920</title><description>The Evolution of the Conservation Movement, 1850-1920

This site documents the movement to conserve and protect America's natural heritage. ... (more)

This site documents the movement to conserve and protect America's natural heritage. The site features books, pamphlets, government documents, manuscripts, prints, photographs, and motion picture footage drawn from collections of the Library of Congress. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

American Memory
Provider:

Library of Congress

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/15133/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:12:10">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/poet-william-carlos-williams-describes-the-crowd-at-the-ballpark</link><title>Poet William Carlos Williams Describes the Crowd at the Ballpark</title><description>Poet William Carlos Williams Describes the Crowd at the Ballpark

Baseball's growing popularity in the 1920s can be measured by structural and ... (more)

Baseball's growing popularity in the 1920s can be measured by structural and cultural changes that helped transform the game, including the building of commodious new ballparks; the emergence of sports pages in daily urban newspapers; and the enormous popularity of radio broadcasts of baseball games. Baseball commentators and critics expended much ink during the 1920s discussing the exact nature and composition of this new and expanding fan population. Some derided the influx of new fans to urban ballparks, in part because of the growing visibility in the bleachers of the sons and daughters of working-class Italian, Polish, and Jewish immigrants, and in part because the game seemed to be straying from its origins in traditional rural and small-town America. Poet William Carlos Williams evoked the growing diversity of baseball's fans and their impact on the game in "The Crowd at the Ball Park," published in the Dial in 1923. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Material Type:

Primary Source
Readings
Collection:

Many Pasts (CHNM/ASHP)
Provider:

American Social History Project / Center for History Media and Learning
Author:

Center for History and New Media/American Social History Project

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/70823/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:15:04">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/at-home-on-the-prairie</link><title>At Home on the Prairie</title><description>At Home on the Prairie

The Western landscape which George Catlin encountered on his travels was dominated ... (more)

The Western landscape which George Catlin encountered on his travels was dominated by the great expanse of the tall and short grass prairies. Home to countless species of plant and animal life, the great prairies once spanned millions of acres across North America. Today less than ten percent of the complex ecosystem remains, largely under the protection of parks and nature preserves. In this lesson students will gain an understanding of the interdependence of living organisms on the prairie and the fragility of their existence by investigating life on the prairie and relating their findings to their own experience. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

Smithsonian Institutions
Provider:

Smithsonian American Art Museum Campfire Stories

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/19623/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:17:14">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/dam-hetch-hetchy-john-muir-contests-the-hetch-hetchy-dam</link><title>"Dam Hetch Hetchy!": John Muir Contests the Hetch-Hetchy Dam</title><description>"Dam Hetch Hetchy!": John Muir Contests the Hetch-Hetchy Dam

The Progressive Era's most controversial environmental issue was the 1908-1913 struggle over ... (more)

The Progressive Era's most controversial environmental issue was the 1908-1913 struggle over federal government approval for building the Hetch Hetchy dam in a remote corner of federally-owned land in California's Yosemite National Park. The city of San Francisco, rebuilding after the devastating 1906 earthquake, believed the dam was necessary to meet its burgeoning needs for reliable supplies of water and electricity. At Congressional hearings on Hetch Hetchy held in 1913, supporters of the plan like Gifford Pinchot, the first Chief Forester of the United States and a noted environmentalist, argued that conservation of natural resources was best achieved through management of the wilderness. Preservationist and Sierra Club founder John Muir did not testify before Congress, but he argued against the Hetch Hetchy plan in this excerpt from his 1912 book, The Yosemite. In the end Congress chose management over aesthetics, voting 43-25 (with 29 abstentions) to allow the Hetch Hetchy dam on federal land. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Material Type:

Primary Source
Readings
Collection:

Many Pasts (CHNM/ASHP)
Provider:

American Social History Project / Center for History Media and Learning
Author:

Center for History and New Media/American Social History Project

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7045_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72419/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>