<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:22" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:24">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/wise-the-web-based-inquiry-science-environment</link><title>WISE - The Web-Based Inquiry Science Environment</title><description>WISE - The Web-Based Inquiry Science Environment

The Web-based Inquiry Science Environment (WISE) is a free on-line science learning ... (more)

The Web-based Inquiry Science Environment (WISE) is a free on-line science learning environment for students in grades 4-12. In WISE, students work on exciting inquiry projects on topics such as genetically modified foods, earthquake prediction, and the deformed frogs mystery. Students learn about and respond to contemporary scientific controversies through designing, debating, and critiquing solutions, all via the internet. Curriculum projects are complete and ready to use in the classroom. The projects are designed to meet standards and complement existing science curricula. The Teacher Area lets instructors explore new projects and grade students' work on the web, as well as to collaborate with other teachers and researchers. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

University of California, Berkeley
Provider:

U.C. Berkeley

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17270/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:04:34">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/water-on-the-web-basic-science</link><title>Water on the Web Basic Science</title><description>Water on the Web Basic Science

WOW lessons are designed for infusion into the existing science curriculums for ... (more)

WOW lessons are designed for infusion into the existing science curriculums for college freshmen and advanced high school students. The lessons use the aquatic environment and real lake data to explore basic science concepts through two different approaches: a directed study “Studying” and an inquiry “Investigating” approach. The directed studies allow students to apply and learn concepts through direct, guided experience. The inquiry lessons provide a more open-ended opportunity for students to discover the same concepts. Each teacher's lesson plan provides general direction for guiding students to understand the topic through the directed study and the inquiry approach. Student lessons are organized into a thinking framework of six sequential components that are critical for improving scientific and technological literacy: knowledge base, experimental design, data collection, data management and analysis, interpretation of results, and reporting results. The teacher lesson plans follow the same format. Lesson titles are simple and descriptive so that you may easily find useful materials. We recommend you begin by reviewing the student lessons that may be appropriate for your class. When you've found a student lesson to use, return to the menu below to review the associated teacher's lesson plan. There are tutorials to help you and your students get familiar with the site, they may be accessed from the menu below, or at the top of any 'teacher' page. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

University of Minnesota
Provider:

University of Minnesota

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_02_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/19658/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:09:46">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/web-development</link><title>Web Development</title><description>Web Development

This course will expose you to the basic fundamentals of the Internet ... (more)

This course will expose you to the basic fundamentals of the Internet and Web protocols, the different architectures that Web-related applications use, and the programming languages that enable the development of Web applications. The student will also cover matters of security and reliability in the development of web applications via the use of transport encryption and authentication. Upon completion of this course, students will be able to: demonstrate an understanding of the Internet and Web Protocols; demonstrate an understanding of Client-Server Architecture; explain how Web Software works; demonstrate an understanding of Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) Programming concepts; demonstrate an understanding of basic JavaScript, AJAX, and Java Server Pages (JSP); demonstrate an understanding of Web Security and Encryption. (Computer Science 305) (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Assessments
Audio Lectures
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Readings
Syllabi
Video Lectures
Collection:

Saylor Foundation
Provider:

The Saylor Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/35781/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:13:52">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/spider-web</link><title>Spider web</title><description>Spider web

Spiders build webs as a way to catch food. Flying and crawling ... (more)

Spiders build webs as a way to catch food. Flying and crawling insects can easily be caught in this sticky web and eaten if they aren't careful. Spiders also live on these webs and store their eggs cases on webs. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Collection:

Video and Image Data Access
Provider:

U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/31836/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/spider-on-a-web</link><title>Spider on a web</title><description>Spider on a web

Spiders build web structures from a material they make inside their bodies. ... (more)

Spiders build web structures from a material they make inside their bodies. The web is used to catch insects and provides a place for the spider to live. Some webs have decorations on them, or thicker areas of web, that may make them more visible to birds and humans and less likely to be damaged. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Collection:

Video and Image Data Access
Provider:

California State University, Fullerton

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/31834/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:18:08">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/perspectives-on-case-based-multimedia-web-projects-in-science</link><title>Perspectives on Case-based Multimedia Web Projects in Science</title><description>Perspectives on Case-based Multimedia Web Projects in Science

This article discusses the merits of case-based learning in an interactive online ... (more)

This article discusses the merits of case-based learning in an interactive online environment. Researchers used both qualitative and quantitative research over a 2-year period to examine the learning that occurred in a high school context when students were engaged in a case-based multimedia project. Part of the Case It! project, students played both the role of laboratory technician performing and presenting research as well as professionals using the information in their practice. Students were required to use three types of simulation software developed exclusively for the Case It! project. Results were measured using both pre- and post-tests, artifacts students created such as Web posters, records of Internet conferences, and interviews from both the students and the teacher involved in this project. Researches found the online format of the lesson fostered a higher level of questioning and problem solving skills, as well as extended explanations and discussions of ethics in science. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

NAGT Cutting Edge (SERC)
Provider:

SERC at Carlton College
Author:

Mary Lundeberg

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_06_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/11598/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:22">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/information-on-the-web</link><title>Information on the Web</title><description>Information on the Web

The World Wide Web is a vast information resource. This unit will ... (more)

The World Wide Web is a vast information resource. This unit will provide you with the foundation skills to use search engines confidently to locate both information and images on the Web. You will also learn how to critically assess and reference the information you have found for study purposes. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Readings
Syllabi
Collection:

Open University OpenLearn
Provider:

Open University

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/7919/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:59">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/a-study-of-spider-webs</link><title>A Study of Spider Webs</title><description>A Study of Spider Webs

Many people do not like spiders and consider them pests. However, spiders ... (more)

Many people do not like spiders and consider them pests. However, spiders provide a service to humans. They eat many of the insects that bother people. In this 7th grade life science activity, students will study 4-6 spider webs and discover what and how much spiders eat. They will identify the spiders building the webs, collect data and make observations related to the webs and what the spiders eat. They will use the information to develop a conclusion. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

Pedagogy in Action (SERC)
Provider:

SERC at Carlton College
Author:

Lyle Gomarko

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/57980/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:24:16">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/food-webs-in-the-bay</link><title>Food Webs in the Bay</title><description>Food Webs in the Bay

In this Science NetLinks lesson, students will research plants and animals that ... (more)

In this Science NetLinks lesson, students will research plants and animals that live in the submerged aquatic vegetation (SAV) of a bay area. After researching the organisms, students will do class presentations and create a food web using pictures of all of the organisms. At the end of the lesson, they will discuss ideas of organisms sharing food, space, water, air, and shelter. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Teaching and Learning Strategies
Collection:

Science Netlinks
Provider:

AAAS

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/60387/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:25:47">http://www.oercommons.org/community/access-excellence</link><title>Access Excellence</title><description>Access Excellence

Access Excellence, launched in 1993, is a national educational program that provides ... (more)

Access Excellence, launched in 1993, is a national educational program that provides health, biology and life science teachers access to their colleagues, scientists, and critical sources of new scientific information via the World Wide Web. The program was originally developed and launched by Genentech Inc., and in 1999 joined the National Health Museum, a non-profit organization founded by former U.S. Surgeon General C. Everett Koop as a national center for health education. Access Excellence will form the core of the educational component of the National Health Museum Website that is currently under development. . (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7057_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/community/7/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>