<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:49:38" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:49:39">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/cystic-fibrosis</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Cystic Fibrosis

This patient education program explains cystic fibrosis or CF, including the causes, ... (more)

This patient education program explains cystic fibrosis or CF, including the causes, symptoms, diagnosis, treatments, prevention, and key facts about the disease. This resource is a MedlinePlus Interactive Health Tutorial from the National Library of Medicine, designed and developed by the Patient Education Institute. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Audio Lectures
Collection:

H.E.A.L.
Provider:

National Library of Medicine

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/23099/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:53:47">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/cystic-fibrosis-spanish</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis (Spanish)</title><description>Cystic Fibrosis (Spanish)

This patient education program explains cystic fibrosis or CF, including the causes, ... (more)

This patient education program explains cystic fibrosis or CF, including the causes, symptoms, diagnosis, treatments, prevention, and key facts about the disease. This resource is a MedlinePlus Interactive Health Tutorial from the National Library of Medicine, designed and developed by the Patient Education Institute. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Audio Lectures
Collection:

H.E.A.L.
Provider:

National Library of Medicine

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/23002/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:55:28">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/woe-to-that-child-a-case-of-cystic-fibrosis</link><title>Woe to That Child: A Case of Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Woe to That Child: A Case of Cystic Fibrosis

Alvin's parents are worried about him. He has had a cough for ... (more)

Alvin's parents are worried about him. He has had a cough for almost a week, and he's wheezing a lot more than they think is normal for a child with a cold, which is what their family pediatrician says he has. When they take him to the ER, however, the pediatric pulmonologist on duty tells them their son is suffering from something much more serious than a cold. This case study was developed for second-year pharmacy students to help them tie together elements of cell physiology, osmosis and tonicity, and membrane transport processes. The questions, which focus on disease mechanisms, symptoms, and treatment options, could be modified for non-pharmacy students. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Case Study
Lesson Plans
Collection:

Case Study Teaching in Science
Provider:

National Center for Case Study Teaching in Science
Author:

Dayton J. Ford

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/37357/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:00:18">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/antibiotics-toxins-and-protein-engineering-spring-2007</link><title>Antibiotics, Toxins, and Protein Engineering, Spring 2007</title><description>Antibiotics, Toxins, and Protein Engineering, Spring 2007

The lethal poison Ricin (best known as a weapon of bioterrorism), Diphtheria ... (more)

The lethal poison Ricin (best known as a weapon of bioterrorism), Diphtheria toxin (the causative agent of a highly contagious bacterial disease), and the widely used antibiotic tetracycline have one thing in common: They specifically target the cell's translational apparatus and disrupt protein synthesis. In this course, we will explore the mechanisms of action of toxins and antibiotics, their roles in everyday medicine, and the emergence and spread of drug resistance. We will also discuss the identification of new drug targets and how we can manipulate the protein synthesis machinery to provide powerful tools for protein engineering and potential new treatments for patients with devastating diseases, such as cystic fibrosis and muscular dystrophy. This course is one of many Advanced Undergraduate Seminars offered by the Biology Department at MIT. These seminars are tailored for students with an interest in using primary research literature to discuss and learn about current biological research in a highly interactive setting. Many instructors of the Advanced Undergraduate Seminars are postdoctoral scientists with a strong interest in teaching. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Lecture Notes
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Sassanfar, Mandana

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7103_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/1870/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>