<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:02:49" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:02:50">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/using-online-lectures-to-support-active-learning-case-study</link><title>Using online lectures to support active learning - Case study</title><description>Using online lectures to support active learning - Case study

Download the supporting PDF file for this episode http://bit.ly/mpbROh from the Learning ... (more)

Download the supporting PDF file for this episode http://bit.ly/mpbROh from the Learning to Teach Online project website.This case study examines how technology can be used to support an active learning strategy within face-to-face Chemistry classes. Both in-class polling software and online lectures are used as part of a comprehensive teaching strategy, designed to enable students to develop critical thinking and analytical skills. While in-class polling is not an online process, it is included within this case study to highlight how different types of technology can be used together to effectively support classroom teaching, when integrated with a carefully considered pedagogical approach.What do you think of this resource? Please click http://svy.mk/e6BP1G to complete a quick survey. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Business
Humanities
Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Case Study
Teaching and Learning Strategies
Collection:

Learning to Teach Online
Provider:

University of New South Wales (UNSW)
Author:

Karin Watson
Simon McIntyre

Share Only</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/33337/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:06:31">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/survey-of-environmental-science-envs-100</link><title>Survey of Environmental Science (ENVS 100)</title><description>Survey of Environmental Science (ENVS 100)

This is a survey course in which we will discuss the science ... (more)

This is a survey course in which we will discuss the science behind historical and current environmental issues. We will discuss the major threats to biodiversity and ecosystem function. We will study how human activities have affected the limited resources of our planet. We will learn how air, water and soil degradation have affected human health. Lastly, we will explore the emerging field of sustainability, what it means, and how it is being applied in todayęs world. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Assessments
Full Course
Readings
Syllabi
Collection:

Open Course Library
Provider:

Washington State Board for Community &amp; Technical Colleges

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72859/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:11:06">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/pizza-anyone</link><title>Pizza Anyone?</title><description>Pizza Anyone?

Students survey their class and analyze data about favorite pizza toppings. This ... (more)

Students survey their class and analyze data about favorite pizza toppings. This activity is meant to be fun and engaging, with the class participating and making decisions as a whole. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

LEARN NC Lesson Plans
Provider:

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill School of Education
Author:

Jack Hunter

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/11849/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:24">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/where-were-you-born-a-graphing-lesson</link><title>Where Were You Born...A Graphing Lesson</title><description>Where Were You Born...A Graphing Lesson

Students will gather data and graph the results. Lake Norman Elementary's student ... (more)

Students will gather data and graph the results. Lake Norman Elementary's student population has a wide range of native states. Many of the students were born in states other than North Carolina. This activity allows the students to survey each class to see what states are represented in our school. After the survey results have been tallied, students will use the data to create different types of graphs. The class will then compare the graphs and will decide which type of graph represents the information most clearly. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

LEARN NC Lesson Plans
Provider:

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill School of Education
Author:

Erin Bradfeldt
Joan Milliken
Kathy Beck

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17166/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:16:52">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/couch-potato-or-inertia-victim</link><title>Couch Potato or Inertia Victim?</title><description>Couch Potato or Inertia Victim?

Students design a simple behavioral survey, and learn basic protocol for primary ... (more)

Students design a simple behavioral survey, and learn basic protocol for primary research, survey design and report writing. Note: The literacy activities for the Mechanics unit are based on physical themes that have broad application to our experience in the world concepts of rhythm, balance, spin, gravity, levity, inertia, momentum, friction, stress and tension. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

TeachEngineering
Provider:

TeachEngineering
Author:

Denise Carlson
Jane Evenson
Malinda Schaefer Zarske

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/25233/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:20:39">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/interdisciplinary-integrated-unit-on-dna-genetics-part-b-math</link><title>Interdisciplinary Integrated Unit on Dna/Genetics Part B: Math</title><description>Interdisciplinary Integrated Unit on Dna/Genetics Part B: Math

This lesson is part of an interdisciplinary integrated unit on DNA and ... (more)

This lesson is part of an interdisciplinary integrated unit on DNA and genetics. The idea is for students to complete a week's worth of activities in science, math, and language arts. This lesson is Part B: Math. Students will complete a math survey interviewing people on whether they believe humans should or should not be cloned. They will take the data they gather and create computer generated spreadsheets, charts/graphs. Using the charts/graphs, students will answer mathematical percent and ratio questions and write a final journal entry on the information they collected and discovered. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

LEARN NC Lesson Plans
Provider:

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill School of Education
Author:

Jane Lentz
Jimmy White
Marlene Smith
Tori Goldrick

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/8053/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:23:10">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/forests-of-the-world-making-the-global-connection</link><title>Forests of the World - Making the Global Connection</title><description>Forests of the World - Making the Global Connection

In this activity, students will conduct a survey to help them assess ... (more)

In this activity, students will conduct a survey to help them assess what they and others know about forests and to consider ways that people are linked to forests around the world. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Assessments
Collection:

Project Learning Tree
Provider:

American Forest Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/61562/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:24:45">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/discovering-antarctica</link><title>Discovering Antarctica</title><description>Discovering Antarctica

Take a guided tour of Antarctica by watching brief video segments of ... (more)

Take a guided tour of Antarctica by watching brief video segments of its landscape and wildlife in this interactive activity adapted from the British Antarctic Survey. ***Access to Teacher's Domain content now requires free login to PBS Learning Media. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

Teachers' Domain
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/24190/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:25:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/usgs-earthquakes-for-kids</link><title>USGS: Earthquakes for Kids</title><description>USGS: Earthquakes for Kids

This site provides comprehensive information about earthquakes for students. Teachers will find ... (more)

This site provides comprehensive information about earthquakes for students. Teachers will find animations, images, and real-time data of earthquake activity, and students will learn about the career of a geophysicist and how seismology works. Games, puzzles and quizzes provide additional learning opportunity. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Games
Simulations
Collection:

USGS
Provider:

USGS
Author:

United States Geological Survey (USGS)

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/33530/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:39">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-earthquake-hazards-program</link><title>The Earthquake Hazards Program</title><description>The Earthquake Hazards Program

This site offers frequently asked questions about earthquakes, research on earthquakes, and ... (more)

This site offers frequently asked questions about earthquakes, research on earthquakes, and more. Visitors can follow recent seismic activity around the world, view hazard maps, or learn what a geophysicist does. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

USGS
Provider:

U.S. Geological Survey

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7106_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/15096/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>