<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:04:27" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:04:28">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/place-value-rocks</link><title>Place Value Rocks!</title><description>Place Value Rocks!

Play these educational math games and test your knowledge of Place Value! ... (more)

Play these educational math games and test your knowledge of Place Value! Can you use Place Value Blocks to help you represent different digits? Test your ability to write out given numbers into sentences with Cookies! How sharp are your place value skills? Test your knowledge with Golfing with numbers!! (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Games
Collection:

Instructional Architect
Provider:

Instructional Architect
Author:

Ms. Roberts

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7131_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/27152/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:05:24">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/energy-of-motion</link><title>Energy of Motion</title><description>Energy of Motion

By taking a look at the energy of motion all around us, ... (more)

By taking a look at the energy of motion all around us, students learn about the types of energy and their characteristics. They first learn about the two simplest forms of mechanical energy: kinetic and potential energy, as illustrated by pendulums and roller coasters. They come to understand that energy can change from one form into another, and be described and determined by equations. Through the example of a waterwheel, the concepts of and differences between work and power are explained and calculated. Conservation of momentum and collisions are explored, with analogies to popular sports (billiards, baseball, golf), and how elastic and inelastic collisions are considered in the games' design. To show another energy transformation concept, the behavior of energy dissipating into heat by means of friction is presented. Students learn to recognize static friction, kinetic friction and drag, how they work, and how to calculate frictional force. A final lesson integrates the energy of motion concepts, showing how they are interconnected in everyday applications such as skateboards, scooters, roller coasters, trains, cars, planes, trucks and elevators. Through numerous hands-on activities, students swing pendulums, use plastic two-liter bottles to construct model waterwheels, bounce different types of balls, use weights to generate friction data, and roll balls down ramps to collide into cups. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

TeachEngineering
Provider:

TeachEngineering

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7131_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/25732/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>