<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:07:02" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:07:04">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/american-museum-of-natural-history-resources-for-learning</link><title>American Museum of Natural History-Resources for Learning</title><description>American Museum of Natural History-Resources for Learning

This site presents a collection of scientific learning resources for educators, parents, ... (more)

This site presents a collection of scientific learning resources for educators, parents, kids, after-school coordinators, informal learning center staff, and anyone else interested in teaching or learning about science. The site provides a searchable database of resource materials, including activities (computer based and otherwise), curriculum materials, articles, evidence and analytical tools and procedures, exhibition materials, reference lists, and special collections of resources organized around a particular theme. Users can browse resources by topic, sub-topic, grade level, or resource type. Each resource is displayed with a concise description that includes the title, resource type, grade level, and key concepts. Clicking the icon next to the title displays the full resource description. If available, other icons link to the resource in print format, Web format, or both. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/1645/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:11:49">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/worldwide-museum-of-natural-history-wmnh</link><title>Worldwide Museum of Natural History (WMNH)</title><description>Worldwide Museum of Natural History (WMNH)

The Worldwide Museum of Natural History is an online natural history museum ... (more)

The Worldwide Museum of Natural History is an online natural history museum with galleries that focus on vertebrates, butterflies, minerals, and meteor impacts. This site contains a lot of useful information and nice images regarding the above subjects. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

Starting Point (SERC)
Provider:

SERC at Carlton College

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17378/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:01">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/imagine-nature</link><title>Imagine Nature</title><description>Imagine Nature

This showcase of digital broadsides is devoted to nature poets and their ... (more)

This showcase of digital broadsides is devoted to nature poets and their work. Imagine Nature explores the convergence of poetry, graphic arts, and the technology of the Internet. Along with the text of the poem, some broadsides includes an audio reading (often by the author), photographs or original artwork, related nature sounds, or videos. The featured works include: "The Snakes of September" by Stanley Kunitz| "Sleeping In the Forest" by Mary Oliver| "St. Francis and the Sow" by Galway Kinnell| "For Luis" by Michael McClure| "The Butterfly Obtains" by Emily Dickinson| "Little Cosmic Dust Poem" by John Haines|"Sitting by a Swamp" by David Wagoner. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17790/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:21:23">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/create-your-own-mesozoic-museum</link><title>Create Your Own Mesozoic Museum</title><description>Create Your Own Mesozoic Museum

This OLogy activity offers kids a fun way to show off their ... (more)

This OLogy activity offers kids a fun way to show off their dinosaur knowledge. The activity begins by telling kids to pick a topic and title for their Mesozoic Museum, and provides a book list to help them research their selection. It then provides a list of materials and directions for setting up an exhibit that includes explanatory caption cards. Kids are urged to invite friends and family to the Mesozoic Museum, soliciting feedback and testing how well their exhibit communicated knowledge. As inspiration, the activity also includes a pictorial look at the construction of a dinosaur exhibit at the AMNH. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17555/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:22:03">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/wpa-posters-have-a-date-with-us-free-to-you-and-your-friends-motion-pictures-concert-music-exhibit-talks-guided-tours-american-museum-of-natural-history</link><title>WPA Posters: Have a Date With Us Free to You And Your Friends, Motion Pictures, Concert Music, Exhibit Talks, Guided Tours : American Museum of Natural History</title><description>WPA Posters: Have a Date With Us Free to You And Your Friends, Motion Pictures, Concert Music, Exhibit Talks, Guided Tours : American Museum of Natural History

Poster announcing opportunity for the public to attend free programs, such as ... (more)

Poster announcing opportunity for the public to attend free programs, such as movies, concerts, exhibits, and tours, at the American Museum of Natural History, Central Park West and 79 St., New York City, showing a totem pole. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Reference
Collection:

Library of Congress - WPA Posters
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/97471/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:24:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/science-bulletins-current-research-about-the-natural-world</link><title>Science Bulletins: Current research about the natural world</title><description>Science Bulletins: Current research about the natural world

Science Bulletins is a video program that brings you the latest developments ... (more)

Science Bulletins is a video program that brings you the latest developments in the fields of astrophysics, Earth science, biodiversity and human biology and evolution through documentary feature stories about scientists in the field and regular brief research updates using scientific visualizations and imagery. In the exhibition halls of the American Museum of Natural History and other museums and science centers throughout the world, Science Bulletins presents Astro, Earth, Human, and Bio Bulletins as updating streams of high-definition video content and interactive media. On this Web site, Science Bulletins presents current videos and provides an archive of past stories, all with resource links, as well as educator resources and a guide for educators interested in using Science Bulletins in the classroom. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Video Lectures
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17818/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:29:15">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/a-nature-and-nurture-walk-in-mendel-park</link><title>A Nature and Nurture Walk in Mendel Park</title><description>A Nature and Nurture Walk in Mendel Park

"Ryan loves to eat black licorice. He would gladly share it with ... (more)

"Ryan loves to eat black licorice. He would gladly share it with his friend, but she thinks it's gross." Nature? Or nature and nurture? "Whenever you look at Frieda and her son Filippo, you can tell they're related. Both have a hairline called a 'widow's peak.' Nature? Or nature and nurture?" Kids connect to genetics through the comics-style pictures and everyday park scenes in this game. By collecting the green stars from each genetics question, kids can solve the genetic riddle. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Readings
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17793/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:33:28">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/darwin</link><title>Darwin</title><description>Darwin

This Web site, created to complement the Museum's Darwin exhibit, examines the ... (more)

This Web site, created to complement the Museum's Darwin exhibit, examines the man and theory that changed the course of science and society. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Readings
Video Lectures
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17820/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/earth-scientist-gallery</link><title>Earth Scientist Gallery</title><description>Earth Scientist Gallery

This gallery of online resources is from the Museum's Seminars on Science, ... (more)

This gallery of online resources is from the Museum's Seminars on Science, a series of distance-learning courses designed to help educators meet the new national science standards. The Earth Scientist Gallery, part of the Earth:Inside and Out seminar, features: A Video Gallery with four brief video clips, each with a printable PDF transcripts; Introduction to Ed Mathez, Introduction to Ro Kinzler, Creating the Hall of Planet Earth I, and Creating the Hall of Planet Earth II; An Image Gallery with three annotated looks inside the museum's collection; Drawers of Rock Samples, Collection Preparation, and Dr. Mathez in the Collection. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Teaching and Learning Strategies
Video Lectures
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17845/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:38:57">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/fossil-halls</link><title>Fossil Halls</title><description>Fossil Halls

The American Museum of Natural History is home to the world's largest ... (more)

The American Museum of Natural History is home to the world's largest collection of vertebrate fossils, totaling nearly one million specimens. This Web site offers visitors a virtual visit to the Museum's famed Fossil Halls. It features seven sections along with a brief introduction, a Teacher's Guide, and information about the Museum's Division of Paleontology. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Video Lectures
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7133_10_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17819/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>