<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:29" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:30">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-challenge-of-world-poverty-fall-2009</link><title>The Challenge of World Poverty, Spring 2011</title><description>The Challenge of World Poverty, Spring 2011

This is a course for those who are interested in the challenge ... (more)

This is a course for those who are interested in the challenge posed by massive and persistent world poverty, and are hopeful that economists might have something useful to say about this challenge. The questions we will take up include: Is extreme poverty a thing of the past? What is economic life like when living under a dollar per day? Why do some countries grow fast and others fall further behind? Does growth help the poor? Are famines unavoidable? How can we end child labor - or should we? How do we make schools work for poor citizens? How do we deal with the disease burden? Is micro finance invaluable or overrated? Without property rights, is life destined to be "nasty, brutish and short"? Has globalization been good to the poor? Should we leave economic development to the market? Should we leave economic development to non-governmental organizations (NGOs)? Does foreign aid help or hinder? Where is the best place to intervene? (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Assessments
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Lecture Notes
Readings
Syllabi
Video Lectures
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Abhijit Banerjee
Esther Duflo

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7146_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/35181/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:14:33">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-great-american-steeple-chase-for-1844</link><title>The Great American Steeple Chase For 1844</title><description>The Great American Steeple Chase For 1844

An imaginative and elaborate parody on the upcoming 1844 presidential campaign. The ... (more)

An imaginative and elaborate parody on the upcoming 1844 presidential campaign. The artist favors Whig nominee-apparent Henry Clay and is highly critical of incumbent John Tyler. The "chase" for the presidency leads to the White House (upper left) where Robert Tyler arouses his sleeping father saying, "Come wake up old Sampson, the Philistines are upon you!" President Tyler replies with a yawn: "Why Bobby my Pippin! I do believe I've been asleep! no matter I'm the People's favorite and belong to no Party. They will reelect me! If they don't I'll veto the whole concern d--n me!" His statement and the presence of a "Veto" paper on his desk allude to his liberal use of the presidential refusal to stymie Whig congressional efforts to establish a National Bank. In Robert Tyler's pocket is a scroll "Irish Repeal," referring to his support of that international movement. Approaching the steps of the White House, riding a beast which is half-horse and half-alligator (a mythical animal associated in popular lore with Clay's Kentucky), is Henry Clay. He exclaims triumphantly, "Hurrah! Old Kentuck will distance them all yet, and then the views of the lamented Harrisson will be carried out in full, and treachery will meet its reward." The sun rises behind him and an eagle with a streamer reading "E pluribus unum" flies ahead. Clay is followed by South Carolina Democrat John Calhoun, who remarks, "My old nullification Coota Turtle is rather a slow Coach! I am afraid he won't get out of this Clay Bank!" Taking the lower road (in keeping with his reputation for intrigue) is Martin Van Buren, riding a fox and exclaiming, "Confound Calhoun! He is right in my way! I'll take a short cut and though the path is crooked and rather dirty, I don't care so that I get in." Van Buren was derisively nicknamed "the Kinderhook fox." On the same path are two more presidential aspirants, James K. Polk(?) and Richard M. Johnson. The first, sitting on a donkey and waving a club, yells, "I'am an Old Soldier, but I shall never get in unless I can turn this Donkeys head the right way." Johnson, who has fallen off his horse, exclaims, "My old amalgamation Nag has got the blind staggers! and I can stump it no longer!" "Amalgamation" was common parlance for the melding of races, more specifically referring here to Johnson's common-law marriage and offspring with a mulatto woman, Julia Chinn. Off to the right, Massachusetts senator Daniel Webster sits by an open fire, cooking a cauldron of "Chowder" (a staple of his native New England), vowing, "I shant leave my Chowder! unless my country calls me." Behind him on horseback is Gen. Winfield Scott who calls over to War of 1812 Commodore Charles Stewart, seated in a boat on a lake, "Odds bullets and bayonets! I don't care about being President but if my friends insist upon it I'll serve! I say Commodore, cant you or I get in by a Coup-de-main!" Stewart replies, "I think not General! so I'll haul my wind! I am better fitted to govern the helm of old Ironsides than the helm of State." In the lower right corner, a man (possibly Supreme Court Justice John McLean) falls head first down an incline, saying, "If I thought I had a drop of Democratic blood in my veins I would let it out."|Entered . . . 1843 by H.R. Robinson.|H.R. Robinson 142 Nassau St. Lithy. in all its branches.|Signed with monogram: C (Edward Williams Clay).|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 72.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1843-8. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7146_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76343/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>