<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:31" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:32">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/ten-o-clock-news-broadcast-in-honor-of-martin-luther-king-jr-s-birthday</link><title>Ten O'Clock News broadcast in honor of Martin Luther King, Jr.'s birthday</title><description>Ten O'Clock News broadcast in honor of Martin Luther King, Jr.'s birthday

Christopher Lydon introduces a Ten O'Clock News special broadcast marking the birthday ... (more)

Christopher Lydon introduces a Ten O'Clock News special broadcast marking the birthday of Martin Luth King, Jr. (civil rights leader). Lydon reviews King's life and accomplishments. This report features footage of King during the civil rights movement. Paul Solman reports on unemployment in the African American community. Solman notes that many young African Americans are not given the training, education, and support necessary to succeed in the workplace. Solman's report includes footage from interviews with Paul McLemore (Boston resident), Sarah Flint (McLemore's aunt), and Tom Jones (Vice President, John Hancock Mutual Insurance). Gail Harris reports on development in the Roxbury/Dorchester/Mattapan neighborhoods. Harris reports that the area is becoming more attractive to developers and that property values are expected to rise. Harris adds that many residents are suspicious of development plans by the Boston Redevelopment Authority (BRA) and fear being displaced from their homes. Harris' report features footage from interviews with Mamie Mabine (tenant, Orchard Park Housing Project), John Cruz (developer), Ken Guscott (developer), Byron Rushing (State Representative), Otto Snowden (co-founder, Freedom House), Muriel Snowden (co-founder, Freedom House), and a BRA official. Meg Vaillancourt reports on the long-term effects of school desegregation on the Boston Public School system. Vaillancourt notes that attendance and test scores have dropped since 1974. Vaillancourt reports that many African American parents support a 'freedom of choice' plan in which a certain number of seats in each school are set aside for students of each racial group. Vaillancourt interviews Robert Peterkin (Former Deputy Superintendent, Boston Public Schools), Robert Spillane (Superintendent, Boston Public Schools), Kenneth Haskins (Harvard School of Education), Charles Willie (Court Appointed Master for Desegregation), Mildred Reid (Jamaica Plain resident), and Kim Reid (student, Brighton High School) for the report. Vailancourt's report also includes footage of students at Brighton High School, Jackson/Mann Elementary School, South Boston High School, and English High School. Dr. Virgil Woods and Dr. Helen Edmonds discuss civil rights. Christopher Lydon interviews in-studio guests Dr. Virgil Wood (Pond Street Baptist Church) and Dr. Helen Edmonds (Visiting Professor, MIT) about King's legacy and progress in the civil rights movement since King's death. Wood says that society has regressed in the areas of racism, war and poverty since the death of King. Wood and Edmonds talk about African American students at white universities. Wood and Edmonds discuss the gap between the African American middle class and the African American underclass. Callie Crossley (WGBH reporter) talks about her memories of King as a teenager growing up in Memphis, Tennessee. The newscast closes over footage of Stevie Wonder (pop singer) and Jesse Jackson (African American political leader) at a celebration in honor of King in Washington DC. Produced by Glenda Manzi. Directed by Heather Aveson. (less)

Subject:

Business
Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7165_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/70971/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>