<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:59" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:27:00">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/salmonella-video</link><title>Salmonella Video</title><description>Salmonella Video

Salmonella are a common bacteria associated with food poisoning. Dr. Finlay shows ... (more)

Salmonella are a common bacteria associated with food poisoning. Dr. Finlay shows live Salmonella under the microscope to demonstrate how far and fast they can move. This video is also featured on the DVD 2000 and Beyond: Confronting the Microbe Menace, available free from HHMI. This video is 37 seconds in length, and available in MOV (13 MB) and WMV (18 MB). All Infectious Disease videos are located at: http://www.hhmi.org/biointeractive/disease/video.html. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Video Lectures
Collection:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute
Provider:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/62355/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-02"><link>http://www.oercommons.org/courses/salmonella-infection-demonstration</link><title>Salmonella Infection Demonstration</title><description>Salmonella Infection Demonstration

In this video Dr. Finlay and a student volunteer illustrate how Salmonella ... (more)

In this video Dr. Finlay and a student volunteer illustrate how Salmonella infects a cell, using a marble, plastic wrap, and some yellow gelatin. This video is also featured on the DVD 2000 and Beyond: Confronting the Microbe Menace, available free from HHMI. This video is one minute and 20 seconds in length, and available in MOV (13 MB) and WMV (18 MB). All Infectious Disease videos are located at: http://www.hhmi.org/biointeractive/disease/video.html. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Video Lectures
Collection:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute
Provider:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute
Author:

Dr. Brett Finlay

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb>http://www.oercommons.org/courses/62258/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:31:15">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/intracellular-infection-by-salmonella</link><title>Intracellular Infection by Salmonella</title><description>Intracellular Infection by Salmonella

In this animation, you can see how one S. typhimurium invades an ... (more)

In this animation, you can see how one S. typhimurium invades an epithelial cell of the intestinal tract, survives the intracellular defense mechanisms of the host cell, and multiplies. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Video Lectures
Collection:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute
Provider:

Howard Hughes Medical Institute

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_03_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/62358/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:33:20">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/spot-overlay-ames-test-of-potential-mutagens</link><title>Spot-Overlay Ames Test of Potential Mutagens</title><description>Spot-Overlay Ames Test of Potential Mutagens

This protocol represents a cost-effective modification of the Ames Test that allows ... (more)

This protocol represents a cost-effective modification of the Ames Test that allows students to investigate the mutagenic potential of various common substances. Potential mutagens are tested using well-characterized auxotrophic strains of Salmonella typhimurium. By analyzing the results, students determine if any of their compounds may be mutagenic. Follow-up experiments are designed to determine the dose response of these potential mutagens. Using this protocol, we have achieved reproducible results with several known mutagens, including sodium azide and ultraviolet irradiation. This approach enables faculty to control costs and results to improve student understanding of mutagenesis, biochemical pathways, experimental design, and data analysis. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

Association for Biology Laboratory Education (ABLE)
Provider:

Davidson College|Davidson IB Middle School
Author:

A. Malcolm Campbell
David Wessner
John Kenyon
Peggy Maiorano
Ralph Pillsbury

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_04_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/32488/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:35:14">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/microbeworld-video-ep-11-the-maloy-lab</link><title>MicrobeWorld Video Ep. 11 - The Maloy Lab</title><description>MicrobeWorld Video Ep. 11 - The Maloy Lab

MicrobeWorld visits The Maloy Lab at San Diego State University to talk ... (more)

MicrobeWorld visits The Maloy Lab at San Diego State University to talk with Professor Stanley Maloy and three grad students, Dave Matthews, Gerardo Perez and Veronica Casas, about their research. The Maloy Lab focuses on the genetics and physiology of Salmonella and bacteriophage that infect Salmonella. Maloy and his students use a combination of genetic, molecular, biochemical, and genomic approaches to answer questions about the uptake of DNA from bacteriophage, transfer of genes between bacteria and phage, and the evolution of pathogenesis. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Video Lectures
Collection:

SciVee
Provider:

SciVee
Author:

MicrobeWorld

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/71389/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:54">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/color-coded-dna</link><title>Color-Coded DNA</title><description>Color-Coded DNA

Many people now get their DNA tested for hereditary diseases, including Huntington's ... (more)

Many people now get their DNA tested for hereditary diseases, including Huntington's Disease and some cancers. But soon, DNA may also be used to diagnose infectious diseases, from salmonella to HIV. In this Science Update, you'll hear about a developing technology that could make this possible. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Audio Lectures
Collection:

Science Netlinks
Provider:

AAAS

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/60186/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:40:11">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/med-myst-mission-5-zero-hour-zoonoses</link><title>Med Myst: Mission 5, Zero Hour Zoonoses</title><description>Med Myst: Mission 5, Zero Hour Zoonoses

This is an interactive learning adventure for middle school students and has ... (more)

This is an interactive learning adventure for middle school students and has accompanying classroom activities and magazines. In Mission Five: Zero Hour Zoonoses, students learn about zoonotic pathogens and the diseases they cause, while trying to prevent a bioterror attack. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Games
Lesson Plans
Collection:

Rice Center for Technology in Teaching and Learning
Provider:

Rice Center for Technology in Teaching and Learning

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/42817/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:40:53">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/great-moments-in-science-light-of-life-2</link><title>Great Moments in Science: Light of Life 2</title><description>Great Moments in Science: Light of Life 2

This Great Moments in Science radio transcript describes the three types of ... (more)

This Great Moments in Science radio transcript describes the three types of bioluminescence (bacterial, extracellular, and intracellular) and associated medical applications. The audio version of this program can be downloaded and requires RealPlayer. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Audio Lectures
Collection:

Microbial Life (MLER) (SERC)
Provider:

Australian Broadcasting Corporation
Author:

Karl S. Kruszelnicki

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/7026/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:41:39">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/coffee-break</link><title>Coffee Break: Tutorial for NCBI Tools</title><description>Coffee Break: Tutorial for NCBI Tools

This is a collection of short reports on recent biological discoveries. Each ... (more)

This is a collection of short reports on recent biological discoveries. Each report is about 400 words, and is based on a discovery recently published peer-reviewed literature. It incorporates interactive tutorials that show how bioinformatics tools are used as a part of the research process. Past topics include how salmonella gains entry into human cells, new clues on Alzheimer's pathology, how living organisms tune in to the time of day, and many more. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

National Center for Biotechnology Information
Provider:

National Center for Biotechnology Information

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_09_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/3362/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:43:05">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-mixed-up-microbe-mystery</link><title>The Mixed-Up Microbe Mystery</title><description>The Mixed-Up Microbe Mystery

This activity from our family magazine series challenges kids to help solve ... (more)

This activity from our family magazine series challenges kids to help solve the Case of the Dragon That Caused Diarrhea. The online activity begins with an overview of "The Facts" behind this challenge given to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, along with suggestions for "How to Solve a Microbe Mystery."Before starting the online challenge, kids are taken to a page that explains their "mission" and how to play. A series of six tabs contains details about Cindy's steps towards solving the mystery; using the guidance from "How To Solve a Microbe Mystery," students are asked to correctly order her steps. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Games
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7216_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17603/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>