<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:50" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/ten-o-clock-news-broadcast-5</link><title>Ten O'Clock News broadcast</title><description>Ten O'Clock News broadcast

Christopher Lydon and Gail Harris are hosts of a Ten O'Clock News ... (more)

Christopher Lydon and Gail Harris are hosts of a Ten O'Clock News broadcast. Lydon reads news headlines about the Middle East. Brian Barron reports that the US government may have underreported US casualties during the US invasion of Grenada. Harris reports on a visit to Japan by Ronald Reagan (US President) and Nancy Reagan (US First Lady). Harris reports that Michael Dukakis (Governor of Massachusetts) visited Washington D.C. to lobby for acid rain legislation to protect Quabbin Reservoir and for federal funding for the Central Artery/Tunnel Project. Kate McGrath reports on the approval by the Massachusetts House of Representatives of Dukakis' controversial capital outlay bill. McGrath notes that the bill passed despite Republican opposition. McGrath's report includes footage from interviews with William Robinson (House Minority Leader), Charles Flaherty (Massachusetts House of Representatives) and Frank Keefe (State Secretary for Administration and Finance).Harris reports that Dr. Edward Teller (scientist) and Hans Bethe (Nobel Prize winning scientist) debated the Reagan administration's Strategic Defense Initiative proposal at the John F. Kennedy School of Government. Lydon reads headlines about elections nationwide. Lydon interviews in-studio guest David Wiegand (Editor, Cambridge Chronicle) about the referendum in Cambridge to ban all nuclear weapons research in the city. Wiegand describes the debate surrounding the referendum and predicts that it will not pass. Lydon presents one of the reports in a series on mayoral candidates Mel King and Ray Flynn. This report explores Mel King's background and early days as a social worker in a settlement house in the South End. The report includes footage from interviews with John O'Bryant (Boston School Committee), Paul Parks (architect), Joyce King (wife of Mel King), Ed McClure (US Justice Department), Herbert Gleason (former Chairman, United South End Settlements) and Chuck Turner (teacher). Lydon also interviews Robert Shagoury (computer manufacturer), Edward Domit (social worker) and Thomas Shea (retailer), all of whom comment on King's social work. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7218_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72384/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:45:52">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/ten-o-clock-news-broadcast-2</link><title>Ten O'Clock News broadcast</title><description>Ten O'Clock News broadcast

Christopher Lydon and Gail Harris host a Ten O'Clock News broadcast. Lydon ... (more)

Christopher Lydon and Gail Harris host a Ten O'Clock News broadcast. Lydon reports on a budget ceremony held by Ronald Reagan (US President) and on skepticism about the budget by some Republicans and Democrats. The report includes footage of Reagan signing the budget. The lights go out during this report, and Lydon continues to read the news. Harris reports that Michael Dukakis (Governor of Massachusetts) is critical of Reagan's budget. Harris' report is accompanied by footage of Dukakis talking about the budget at a press conference. Hope Kelly reports on preparations by the Boston School Committee and Robert Spillane (Superintendent, Boston Public Schools) for the next day's hearing in the courtroom of Arthur Garrity (federal judge). Kelly notes that Garrity will decide whether the court should withdraw from its supervisory role over the Boston Public Schools. Kelly's report includes footage from interviews with Robert Spillane (Superintendent, Boston Public Schools), Tom Kiley (pollster), Abigail Browne (Boston School Committee) and Shirley Owens Hicks (President, Boston School Committee). Harris reports on the case of five MDC (Metropolitan District Commission) police officers who have filed reverse discrimination complaints against the MDC. Harris and Lydon read international news headlines. John Thorne reports from Yorkshire, England on the return to work by some striking Yorkshire coal miners. Christy George reports that Gary Hart gave a speech about "new patriotism" at Faneuil Hall in Boston today. George analyzes efforts by the Democratic Party to prepare for the 1988 presidential elections. George's report includes footage of Democratic politicians, including Paul Tsongas (former US Senator), Paul Kirk (Chairman, Democratic National Committee), US Senators John Glenn and Edward Kennedy, and former presidential candidates George McGovern and Walter Mondale. Lydon interviews in-studio guests Roger Brinner (President, Data Resources, Inc.) and Hendrik Hertzberg (former editor, The New Republic) about Reagan's budget and the federal budget deficit. Brinner talks about defense spending and Reagan's opposition to tax increases. Hertzberg analyzes how Reagan's philosophy on government has come to dominate the political agenda. This tape includes a portion of a Ten O'Clock News story from November 26, 1984 featuring Tina Packer (Director, Boston Shakespeare Company) and three actors from the Boston Shakespeare Company. This tape also includes a portion of a Ten O'Clock News broadcast from November 6, 1984. Christopher Lydon talks to in-studio guests Anthony Lewis (New York Times), Ellen Goodman (Boston Globe), Martin Kilson (Harvard University) and Barry Kaplovitz (consultant) about Walter Mondale's performance in the second debate against Ronald Reagan in 1984. (less)

Subject:

Business
Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7218_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/70970/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>