<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:15:41" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:15:42">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/15-874-system-dynamics-for-business-policy-fall-2003</link><title>System Dynamics for Business Policy, Fall 2003</title><description>System Dynamics for Business Policy, Fall 2003

Why do so many business strategies fail? Full-term introduction to system dynamics ... (more)

Why do so many business strategies fail? Full-term introduction to system dynamics modeling applied to corporate strategy. Uses simulation models, management "flight simulators," and case studies to develop conceptual and modeling skills for the design and management of high-performance organizations in a dynamic world. Case studies of successful applications of system dynamics in growth strategy, management of technology, operations, project management, and others. Principles for effective use of modeling in the real world. Prerequisite for further work in the field. (less)

Subject:

Business
Material Type:

Case Study
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Syllabi
Other
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Sterman, John

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/317/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:17:05">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/system-dynamics-ii-fall-2010</link><title>System Dynamics II, Fall 2010</title><description>System Dynamics II, Fall 2010

Introduction to System Dynamics is a continuation of Systems Dynamics I. It ... (more)

Introduction to System Dynamics is a continuation of Systems Dynamics I. It emphasizes tools and methods needed to apply systems thinking and simulation modeling successfully in complex real-world settings. The course uses simulation models, management flight simulators and case studies to deepen the conceptual and modeling skills introduced in System Dynamics I. Through models and case studies of successful applications, students learn how to use qualitative and quantitative data to formulate and test models, and how to work effectively with senior executives to implement change successfully. (less)

Subject:

Business
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Case Study
Homework and Assignments
Readings
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Sterman, John

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/35197/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:19:46">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/measuring-dark-energy</link><title>Measuring Dark Energy</title><description>Measuring Dark Energy

Students simulate an experiment in which the discovery of dark energy can ... (more)

Students simulate an experiment in which the discovery of dark energy can be made by plotting modern supernova distances on a Hubble Diagram. Grades 11-12. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

NASA
Provider:

Imagine the Universe, Goddard Space Flight Center, NASA
Author:

James Lochner, Ph.D.

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_03_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/24631/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:21:25">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/passages</link><title>Passages:</title><description>Passages:

A simulation game designed to create better understanding of the problems facing ... (more)

A simulation game designed to create better understanding of the problems facing refugees. Participants go through a number of steps which attempt to simulate the refugee experience, from flight to arrival in the refugee camp as well as the difficulties of integration and repatriation of refugees. (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Games
Simulations
Collection:

United Nations
Provider:

UNHCR´s Regional Office for the Baltic and Nordic countries

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/11489/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:22:46">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/slingshot-to-the-outer-planets</link><title>Slingshot to the Outer Planets</title><description>Slingshot to the Outer Planets

Students are introduced to the engineering challenges involved with interplanetary space travel. ... (more)

Students are introduced to the engineering challenges involved with interplanetary space travel. In particular, they learn about the gravity assist or "slingshot" maneuver often used by engineers to send spacecraft to the outer planets. Using magnets and ball bearings to simulate a planetary flyby, students investigate what factors influence the deflection angle of a gravity assist maneuver. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

TeachEngineering
Provider:

TeachEngineering
Author:

Denise W. Carlson
Jake Lewis
Malinda Schaefer Zarske

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/25208/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:24:43">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/rocketmodeler</link><title>RocketModeler</title><description>RocketModeler

RocketModeler was developed at the NASA Glenn Research Center in an effort ... (more)

RocketModeler was developed at the NASA Glenn Research Center in an effort to foster hands-on, inquiry-based learning in science and math. RocketModeler is a simulator that models the design and flight of a model rocket. The program works in two modes: Design Mode or Flight Mode. In the Design Mode, you can change design variables including the size of the rocket body, the fins, and the nose cone. You can also select different materials for each component. You can select from a variety of standard solid rocket engines. The program computes the center of gravity and pressure for your rocket and determines the stability. When you have a design that you like, you can switch to the Flight Mode (shown below), where you can launch your rocket and observe its flight trajectory. You can pause at any time to record data and then continue the flight through parachute deploy and recovery. This program has recently (Oct 8, 2004) been upgraded to support stomp rockets, bottle rockets, and ballistic shells in addition to solid model rockets. It also supports both English and metric units. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Simulations
Collection:

NASA
Provider:

NASA Glenn Research Center

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17861/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:26:54">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/kitemodeler</link><title>KiteModeler</title><description>KiteModeler

KiteModeler was developed in an effort to foster hands-on, inquiry-based learning in ... (more)

KiteModeler was developed in an effort to foster hands-on, inquiry-based learning in science and math. KiteModeler is a simulator that models the design, trimming, and flight of a kite. The program works in three modes: Design Mode, Trim Mode, or Flight Mode. In the Design Mode (shown below), you pick from five basic types of kite designs. You can then change design variables including the length and width of various sections of the kite. You can also select different materials for each component. When you have a design that you like, you switch to the Trim Mode where you set the length of the bridle string and tail and the location of the knot attaching the bridle to the control line. Based on your inputs, the program computes the center of gravity and pressure, the magnitude of the aerodynamic forces and the weight, and determines the stability of your kite. With a stable kite design, you are ready for Flight Mode. In Flight Mode you set the wind speed and the length of control line. The program then computes the sag of the line caused by the weight of the string and the height and distance that your kite would fly. Using all three modes, you can investigate how a kite flies, and the factors that affect its performance. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Simulations
Collection:

NASA
Provider:

NASA Glenn Research Center

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17862/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:28:38">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/images-of-earth-and-space-sc99-edition</link><title>Images of Earth and Space: SC99 Edition</title><description>Images of Earth and Space: SC99 Edition

From our home planet to distant neutron stars, this narrated videotape presents ... (more)

From our home planet to distant neutron stars, this narrated videotape presents recent scientific visualizations of observation and simulation data. We begin with a dramatic journey over SC99 host city Portland and its surroundings. Later explorations accompany the X-33 aerospace plane on its first test flight, witness Mississippi River flooding, and follow global life over 22 months. New views of Mars reveal a basin that could swallow Mount Everest, while a simulation tests how rovers would navigate the red planets terrain. We conclude with the first-ever supercomputer model producing a black hole from two merging neutron stars. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Alex Kekesi
Craig Miller
Dave Curkendall
David Smith
Greg Shirah
Herb Siegel
James Collier
Joseph Jacob
Lucian Plesea
Marc Pomerantz
Mark Miller
Peggy Li
Randall Jones
Richard Chen
Stuart Snodgrass
Terry Cole
Tony Jacob
Werner Benger

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/29275/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:29:31">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/order-in-spontaneous-behavior</link><title>Order in Spontaneous Behavior</title><description>Order in Spontaneous Behavior

Brains are usually described as input/output systems: they transform sensory input into ... (more)

Brains are usually described as input/output systems: they transform sensory input into motor output. However, the motor output of brains (behavior) is notoriously variable, even under identical sensory conditions. The question of whether this behavioral variability merely reflects residual deviations due to extrinsic random noise in such otherwise deterministic systems or an intrinsic, adaptive indeterminacy trait is central for the basic understanding of brain function. Instead of random noise, we find a fractal order (resembling Lévy flights) in the temporal structure of spontaneous flight maneuvers in tethered Drosophila fruit flies. Lévy-like probabilistic behavior patterns are evolutionarily conserved, suggesting a general neural mechanism underlying spontaneous behavior. Drosophila can produce these patterns endogenously, without any external cues. The fly's behavior is controlled by brain circuits which operate as a nonlinear system with unstable dynamics far from equilibrium. These findings suggest that both general models of brain function and autonomous agents ought to include biologically relevant nonlinear, endogenous behavior-initiating mechanisms if they strive to realistically simulate biological brains or out-compete other agents. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Video Lectures
Collection:

SciVee
Provider:

SciVee
Author:

brembs

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/71403/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:31:11">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/airline-management-spring-2006</link><title>Airline Management, Spring 2006</title><description>Airline Management, Spring 2006

Overview of airline management decision processes, with a focus on economic issues ... (more)

Overview of airline management decision processes, with a focus on economic issues and their relationship to operations planning models and decision support tools. Application of economic models of demand, pricing, costs, and supply to airline markets and networks. Examination of industry practice and emerging methods for fleet planning, route network design, scheduling, pricing and revenue management, with emphasis on the interactions between the components of airline management and profit objectives in competitive environments. Students participate in a competitive airline management simulation game as part of the subject requirements. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Full Course
Lecture Notes
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Belobaba, Peter

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7241_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/1526/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>