<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:50" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/reading-like-a-historian-unit-11-cold-war</link><title>Reading Like a Historian, Unit 11: Cold War</title><description>Reading Like a Historian, Unit 11: Cold War

These lessons focus on events surrounding the Cold War. The first is ... (more)

These lessons focus on events surrounding the Cold War. The first is an inquiry into its causes, comparing Soviet and American perspectives. Opening Up the Textbook lessons ask students to question textbook accounts of the CIA's covert operations in Guatemala, and compare how North and South Korean textbooks cover the Korean War. Students analyze declassified government documents about the Cuban Missile Crisis, and try to determine whether the U.S. intended to escalate military operations in Vietnam before the Gulf of Tonkin Resolution. In the lesson on Truman and MacArthur, students gauge public response to MacArthur's dismissal by analyzing memos and letters sent to President Truman. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Readings
Unit of Study
Collection:

Reading Like a Historian
Provider:

Stanford History Education Group

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/58242/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:41:49">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/history-of-europe-1800-to-the-present</link><title>History of Europe, 1800 to the Present</title><description>History of Europe, 1800 to the Present

This course will introduce the student to the history of Europe from ... (more)

This course will introduce the student to the history of Europe from 1800 to present day. The student will learn about the major political, economic, and social changes that took place in Europe during this period including Industrial Revolution, the First and Second World Wars, imperialism, and the Cold War. By the end of this course, the student will understand how nationalism, industrialization, and imperialism fueled the rise of European nation-states in the nineteenth century, as well as how world war and oppressive regimes devastated Europe during the 1900s. Upon successful completion of this course, students will be able to: Think critically and analytically about European history in the nineteenth and twentieth centuries; Identify and analyze the varying causes and effects of the Industrial Revolution in Europe; Identify, describe, and analyze the development of a coherent set of ideologies in post-Napoleonic Europe: liberalism, socialism, Marxism, nationalism, and Romanticism; Identify and describe the causes and effects of the era of reform and revolution in Europe in the 1820s and 1830s, as well as analyze the Revolutions of 1848; Describe and analyze the effects of urbanizationĺÎĺĚ_ĺÜexpanding cities, rising public health risks, redefined social classes, the evolving nature of the family, and new developments in science and thought; Identify the age of nationalism in Europe between 1850 and 1914. Students will analyze FranceĺÎĺĺÎĺs Second Empire, ItalyĺÎĺĺÎĺs unification, GermanyĺÎĺĺÎĺs unification, and the modernization of Russia. Students will also be able to define the emergence of the modern nation-state during this period; Identify the causes and characteristics of EuropeĺÎĺĺÎĺs ĺÎĺĺĺŤNew ImperialismĄ_ĺĺö of the late nineteenth century. Students will also be able to describe and analyze responses to this imperialism in Africa, India, the Middle East, and the Far East; Assess how and why World War I erupted in 1914. Students will also be able to identify and describe the characteristics and impact of the Great War; Identify and describe the Russian Revolution of 1917, including the fall of the Romanov dynasty and the Bolshevik Revolution; Identify and describe the cultural and social problems that characterized post-WWI Europe. Students will be able to analyze Modernism, ethnic and economic problems in central and eastern Europe, and the Great Depression; Identify and describe the rise of authoritarian regimes in Europe during the 1920s and 1930s. Students will be able to analyze Stalinism, Fascism, and Nazism; Identify and describe the causes and conflicts of World War II. Students will also be able to analyze, identify, and describe the Holocaust; Analyze and explain the Cold War. Students will also be able to analyze, identify, and describe the collapse of Communism and the Soviet Union, as well as the end of the Cold War; Identify and describe the post-WWII social transformations in Europe, including the rise of feminism, the rise of counterculture, and new developments in both science and technology; Analyze and interpret primary source documents from the nineteenth and twentieth centuries, using historical research methods. (History 202) (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Assessments
Full Course
Lecture Notes
Readings
Syllabi
Video Lectures
Collection:

Saylor Foundation
Provider:

The Saylor Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/35866/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:44:53">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/modern-africa</link><title>Modern Africa</title><description>Modern Africa

This course will introduce the student to the history of sub-Saharan Africa ... (more)

This course will introduce the student to the history of sub-Saharan Africa from the European 'scramble for Africa' in the late nineteenth century to the present day. The student will learn about the major political, economic, and social changes that took place in Africa during this period. Each unit will include representative primary-source documents that illustrate important overarching political, economic, and social themes in modern African history, such as the effects of World War I and World War II, the rise of African nationalism, decolonization and wars for independence, the influence of the Cold War, the problems of development, and the causes and consequences of the civil wars that have plagued African countries in the latter twentieth century. By the end of the course, the student will understand the historical origins of the challenges independent African nations face today. Upon successful completion of this course, the student will be able to: Identify and describe the regions of Africa colonized by European powers; Understand the causes of European imperialism and its short and long-term effects on African societies; Describe key African response to colonial rule; Identify and describe the effects of the First and Second World Wars on Africa; Identify and describe the causes of decolonization in Africa; Identify and describe the major political, economic, and social challenges to African states and societies after independence. (History 252) (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Assessments
Audio Lectures
Full Course
Lecture Notes
Readings
Syllabi
Video Lectures
Collection:

Saylor Foundation
Provider:

The Saylor Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/35872/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:46:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17-428-american-foreign-policy-theory-and-method-fall-2004</link><title>American Foreign Policy: Theory and Method, Fall 2004</title><description>American Foreign Policy: Theory and Method, Fall 2004

Examines the causes and consequences of American foreign policy since 1898. Readings ... (more)

Examines the causes and consequences of American foreign policy since 1898. Readings cover theories of American foreign policy, historiography of American foreign policy, central historical episodes including the two World Wars and the Cold War, case study methodology, and historical investigative methods. Open to undergraduates by permission of instructor. (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Case Study
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Van Evera, Stephen

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/387/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:49:48">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/modern-revolutions</link><title>Modern Revolutions</title><description>Modern Revolutions

This course examines some of the most important political revolutions that took ... (more)

This course examines some of the most important political revolutions that took place between the 17th century and today, beginning with pre-revolutionary Europe and the Enlightenment and continuing with the English Revolution of the 17th century, the American and the French Revolutions, the Mexican Revolution, the Russian and the Chinese Revolutions, the Iranian Revolution, and finally, the Eastern European revolutions of 1989, which brought about radical changes without recourse to violence. Upon successful completion of this course, the student will be able to: provide a concise historical narrative of each of the revolutions presented in the course; identify the origins and causes of each revolution, and compare revolutions with respect to their causes; analyze the goals and ideals of the revolutionaries, and compare how these functioned in various modern revolutions; discuss how revolutions in various parts of the world have affected womenĺÎĺ_ĺĚĺ_s rights; analyze how religious and secular worldviews came into conflict during times of upheaval and revolution; discuss the patterns and dynamics of revolutionary violence, and evaluate how revolutionaries have used non violent tactics against oppressive regimes; evaluate connections between revolutionary ideologies and revolutionary events; analyze how the legacies of each revolution are present in modern politics; describe and evaluate competing theoretical models of revolutionary change; interpret primary historical documents. This free course may be completed online at any time. (History 362) (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Assessments
Audio Lectures
Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Readings
Syllabi
Video Lectures
Collection:

Saylor Foundation
Provider:

The Saylor Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/42791/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:50:25">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/korea-chronic-challenges-continued-hopes</link><title>Korea: Chronic Challenges, Continued Hopes</title><description>Korea: Chronic Challenges, Continued Hopes

Most American students' exposure to the Korean Peninsula begins and ends with ... (more)

Most American students' exposure to the Korean Peninsula begins and ends with the teaching of the Korean War and division along the 38th parallel. The sources and activities here aim to take students beyond the Korean War to explore the divergent stories of North and South Korea and to analyze the causes and effects of each country's unique development. The activities introduce learners to the long-lasting economic and political effects of Korea's division by examining South Korea's rapid industrialization, North Korea's continuing struggle to ensure adequate food for its population, and the arguments for and against reunification of the Korean Peninsula. Working with a photo of a South Korean labor strike, graphs depicting the devastating effects of food shortages in North Korea, and a song calling for reunification, students will gain a better understanding of the peninsula's varied history as well as a greater appreciation for the lived experiences of North and South Koreans at home and abroad. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Audio Lectures
Lesson Plans
Readings
Teaching and Learning Strategies
Video Lectures
Collection:

PrimarySource.org
Provider:

PrimarySource.org
Author:

Liz Howald
Sung-Yoon Lee

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/58773/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:52:36">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-great-political-car-and-last-load-of-patriots-dorr-jackson-simmons-and-arnold</link><title>The Great Political Car and Last Load of Patriots. Dorr, Jackson, Simmons and Arnold!</title><description>The Great Political Car and Last Load of Patriots. Dorr, Jackson, Simmons and Arnold!

A virulent attack on the four conservative Rhode Island legislators who broke ... (more)

A virulent attack on the four conservative Rhode Island legislators who broke with the Law and Order Party to support a Democratic movement to free imprisoned radical Thomas Wilson Dorr. (On the Dorrite Rebellion see also "Trouble in the Spartan Ranks, Tyrants Prostrate Liberty Triumphant," and "The Four Traitors, Who Most Infamously Sold Themselves," nos. 1843-6, 1844-19, and 1845-4). The broadside's text comes from a July 1845 letter from John Whipple, a prominent Providence, R.I., Whig, assailing the "cold-blooded treachery" of Charles Jackson, Samuel F. Man, James Fowler Simmons, and Lemuel H. Arnold in their support of the "liberation" ticket in the spring elections of 1845. Whipple alleges political opportunism and personal ambition as their motive, and offers a lengthy rebuttal to aspersions cast on his own political character by Lemuel Arnold. He also compares Lemuel Arnold to Revolutionary War traitor Benedict Arnold. The woodcut illustration shows a chariot drawn by Cerberus, the three-headed hound of hell, and by a cow with the head of Thomas Wilson Dorr. Driving the chariot is a bespectacled demon with the legs of a goat. Entwined about his body is a snake, and he wields a whip and a pitchfork. The demon is probably James F. Simmons, who was elected governor on the Democrats' liberation ticket. His tail is grasped by Lemuel Arnold, who sits behind him holding a staff with a banner "Office." Behind Arnold sit three other figures: a woman (indicating the prominence of women in the Dorrite cause), a man blowing a horn (another conspirator?), and a uniformed officer, either Napoleon Bonaparte or Benedict Arnold. On the back of the chariot rides a man with a bottle in his pocket, waving a newspaper, the "Tribune," and a stovepipe hat. This may be Horace Greeley, editor of the New York "Tribune," although his usual alignment with the Whigs makes his role here questionable. Below the image are the quotations, "We stoop to Conquer" and "Better to reign in Hell than serve in Heaven" (Satan's famous remark from "Paradise Lost)." The chariot is decorated with snakes and a shield and anchor with a death's head on the central panel. The unidentified publisher of the broadside adds, in a colophon, "I have been at considerable trouble, in obtaining a drawing and engraving of "The Worthies;" and would particularly inform my friends, that I shall ever consider myself alone, personally, responsible for all that I shall publish . . . ." Although Marvin Gettleman, in his study of the Dorrite rebellion, dates the broadside March 1845, Whipple clearly states in his letter, "it is now July."|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Gettleman, p. 171n.|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1845-5. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7307_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76037/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>