<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:51:18" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:51:21">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/ready-to-erupt</link><title>Ready to Erupt!</title><description>Ready to Erupt!

Students observe an in-classroom visual representation of a volcanic eruption. The water-powered ... (more)

Students observe an in-classroom visual representation of a volcanic eruption. The water-powered volcano demonstration is made in advance, using sand, hoses and a water balloon, representing the main components of all volcanoes. During the activity, students observe, measure and sketch the volcano, seeing how its behavior provides engineers with indicators used to predict an eruption. (less)

Subject:

Mathematics and Statistics
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Lesson Plans
Collection:

TeachEngineering
Provider:

TeachEngineering
Author:

Denise Carlson
Geoffrey Hill
Malinda Schaefer Zarske

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/25188/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:52:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/vibrant-volcanoes</link><title>Vibrant Volcanoes</title><description>Vibrant Volcanoes

This lesson will introduce elementary students to the fiery and explosive nature ... (more)

This lesson will introduce elementary students to the fiery and explosive nature of volcanoes, using segments from the NATURE film, âKilauea: Mountain of Fire.â Students will get to know different features of volcanoes and volcanic activity: what volcanoes are like, where they are found, how and why they erupt, and what happens after an eruption. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Collection:

PBS Online
Provider:

NATURE

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_02_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/61623/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:55:14">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/mount-etna-eruption</link><title>Mount Etna Eruption</title><description>Mount Etna Eruption

This animation is a zoom into the Ongoing Mount Etna Eruption. The ... (more)

This animation is a zoom into the Ongoing Mount Etna Eruption. The data was acquired from the MODIS instrument at 9:40 UTC on July 24, 2001. The Ash Plume and lava streaming from the volcano are clearly visible. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Lori Perkins
Vincent Salomonson

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/30202/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:55:58">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/eruption</link><title>Eruption!</title><description>Eruption!

Eruption! is a volcanic crisis simulation model that showcases a series of ... (more)

Eruption! is a volcanic crisis simulation model that showcases a series of villages that surround an active volcano and is part of the Interactive Models for Geological Education Online (IMGEO) series. The goal of the exercise is to preserve as many people and as much property as possible in spite of the threat from the volcano. Students role-play as villagers, the governor, volcanologists, and the press. The rules of the simulation, plus guides for teaching assistants and students, are available on the site. Three different versions are downloadable, for different hardware and classroom situations (e.g. one computer per student, one computer and multiple students a networked environment). The activities in each are modified slightly to reflect the level of computer access for the student. On this Starting Point page, teachers can find learning goals, teaching notes and tips, teaching materials, assessment hints and references and resources dealing with this exercise. It also describes the context in which the virtual tour is best used. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

Starting Point (SERC)
Provider:

SERC at Carlton College
Author:

IMGEO, Department of Geology, SUNY Buffalo

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/5532/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:57:17">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/volcanoes-in-the-infrared</link><title>Volcanoes in the Infrared</title><description>Volcanoes in the Infrared

In this video adapted from KUAC-TV and the Geophysical Institute at the ... (more)

In this video adapted from KUAC-TV and the Geophysical Institute at the University of Alaska, Fairbanks, satellite imagery and infrared cameras are used to study and predict eruptions of volcanoes in the Aleutian Islands, Alaska. ***Access to Teacher's Domain content now requires free login to PBS Learning Media. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Video Lectures
Collection:

Teachers' Domain
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/24171/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:57:59">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/mt-etna-eruption-july-24-2001</link><title>Mt Etna Eruption, July 24, 2001</title><description>Mt Etna Eruption, July 24, 2001

This is simple zoom into the Mount Etna eruption. The plume from ... (more)

This is simple zoom into the Mount Etna eruption. The plume from the ongoing eruption has changed color since the last SeaWiFS image. In todays image, collected around 7:00 am EST, the ash plume has a greenish orange color in this 670-555-412 nanometer composite. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Gene Feldman
Lori Perkins
Norman Kuring

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/30203/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:01:08">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/volcanoes-natures-incredible-firework-show</link><title>Volcanoes: Natures Incredible Firework Show</title><description>Volcanoes: Natures Incredible Firework Show

Volcanoes show us how the earth changes. Volcanoes can be made of ... (more)

Volcanoes show us how the earth changes. Volcanoes can be made of lava, gases, hot steam, ground-up rocks and melted rock called lava. Scientists study volcanoes and the earths movement and try to understand how they erupt. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Lesson Plans
Unit of Study
Collection:

Basal Alignment Project
Provider:

West Virginia District
Author:

David L. Harrison

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_07_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/103833/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:04:22">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/mt-pinatubo-eruption-effect-on-equatorial-ozone</link><title>Mt. Pinatubo eruption effect on equatorial ozone</title><description>Mt. Pinatubo eruption effect on equatorial ozone

This animation clearly shows the ozone around Mt Pinatubo reacting to the ... (more)

This animation clearly shows the ozone around Mt Pinatubo reacting to the eruption. A large ozone hole appears during the eruption and sweeps westward along with the ash cloud,stratospheric sulfur dioxide, and stratospheric sulfuric acid H2SO4. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Jay Herman
Lori Perkins
Richard McPeters

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/30115/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:05:16">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/sulfur-dioxide-emission-from-mt-pinatubo-eruption-june-1991</link><title>Sulfur Dioxide emission from Mt Pinatubo Eruption June 1991</title><description>Sulfur Dioxide emission from Mt Pinatubo Eruption June 1991

This animation shows sulfur dioxide in the stratosphere during the Mt. Pinatubo ... (more)

This animation shows sulfur dioxide in the stratosphere during the Mt. Pinatubo Eruption and for a few weeks after the eruption. Stratospheric SO2 dissipates rather quickly compared to volcanic ash and stratospheric H2SO4. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Jay Herman
Lori Perkins
Richard McPeters

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/30114/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:06:48">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/dating-lava-flows-on-mauna-loa-volcano-hawaii</link><title>Dating Lava Flows on Mauna Loa Volcano, Hawaii</title><description>Dating Lava Flows on Mauna Loa Volcano, Hawaii

In this video segment adapted from NOVA, scientists search for carbonized remains ... (more)

In this video segment adapted from NOVA, scientists search for carbonized remains of plants preserved in lava flows to find out how long it has taken rain forests on Hawaii to regenerate after a volcanic eruption. ***Access to Teacher's Domain content now requires free login to PBS Learning Media. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

Teachers' Domain
Provider:

PBS Learning Media
Author:

WGBH Educational Foundation

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7326_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/4184/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>