<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:57" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:58">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/maps-etc-historic-maps-for-teachers-and-students</link><title>MAPS ETC: United States Demographics</title><description>MAPS ETC: United States Demographics

This collection of maps from MAPS ETC show demographic information for the ... (more)

This collection of maps from MAPS ETC show demographic information for the United states ranging from 1700 to the early 20th century. (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Reference
Collection:

Educational Technology Clearinghouse
Provider:

University of South Florida

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/104498/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:03:44">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/ground-water-atlas-of-the-united-states-idaho-oregon-washington</link><title>Ground Water Atlas of the United States: Idaho, Oregon, Washington</title><description>Ground Water Atlas of the United States: Idaho, Oregon, Washington

This website contains a complete hydro-geologic summary of the Columbia Plateau Regional ... (more)

This website contains a complete hydro-geologic summary of the Columbia Plateau Regional Aquifer System. The summary includes thirteen maps and figures that are accompanied by text descriptions. All texts and figures are available for download. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

DLESE Community Service Center (SERC)
Provider:

SERC at Carlton College
Author:

United States Geological Survey

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_02_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/7048/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:06:53">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/nationalatlas-gov</link><title>National Atlas of the United States</title><description>National Atlas of the United States

This is a primary source of U.S. maps and geographic information. Zoom ... (more)

This is a primary source of U.S. maps and geographic information. Zoom in on your state and make your own map by selecting features to display: cities and counties, roads and rivers, population and 109th congressional districts, crops and livestock, amphibians and butterflies, air and water quality, earthquakes and land cover, forest types, and more. Print a U.S. map (with or without names of states and capitals). Find an aerial photo of your neighborhood. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Readings
Collection:

USGS
Provider:

National Atlas

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/10715/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:10:41">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/united-states-population-density-1900</link><title>United States Population Density, 1900</title><description>United States Population Density, 1900

A map from 1912 of the United States, subtitled "Distribution of Population ... (more)

A map from 1912 of the United States, subtitled "Distribution of Population and Railways in 1900" showing the increase in population and expansion of the railroad network since 1850. The map is color–coded to show population densities ranging from areas with fewer than 2 inhabitants per square mile to areas of 90 or more inhabitants per square mile. Cities with populations over 8,000 are shown with circles proportionate to their populations at the time. The map shows the westward progression of the mean centers of population from 1790 to 1900. (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Educational Technology Clearinghouse
Provider:

University of South Florida

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/104512/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:11:31">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/david-rumsey-historical-map-collection</link><title>David Rumsey Historical Map Collection</title><description>David Rumsey Historical Map Collection

The historical map collection has over 35,000 maps and images online. The ... (more)

The historical map collection has over 35,000 maps and images online. The collection focuses on rare 18th and 19th century North American and South American maps and other cartographic materials. Historic maps of the World, Europe, Asia, and Africa are also represented. Popular collection categories include antique atlas, globe, school geography, maritime chart, state, county, city, pocket, wall &amp; case, children's, and manuscript maps. Search examples are United States map, Geology maps, California map, Afghanistan map, America map, New York City map, Chicago map, and U.S. Civil War maps. Browse map categories: What, Where, Who, When. The collection can be used to study history, genealogy, art, explorations, local and family history. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Other
Collection:

David Rumsey Map Collection
Provider:

Cartography Associates

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/63222/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:13:47">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/continental-united-states-population-map</link><title>Continental United States Population Map</title><description>Continental United States Population Map

This image shows the 2001 population distribution estimate made by the US ... (more)

This image shows the 2001 population distribution estimate made by the US Census. This visualization was created in support of a story describing how NASA is assisting the CDC and EPA in tracking the spread of West Nile Virus. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Other
Collection:

NASA GSFC Scientific Visualization Studio
Provider:

NASA
Author:

Bob Venezia
David Rogers
Greg Shirah
Horace Mitchell

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/29295/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:14:39">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/arsenic-in-ground-water-of-the-united-states</link><title>Arsenic in Ground Water of the United States</title><description>Arsenic in Ground Water of the United States

This site provides information about the distribution of arsenic in ground water ... (more)

This site provides information about the distribution of arsenic in ground water of the United States. The site features links to publications such as fact sheets, research and reports, as well as numerical data collected from over 20,000 wells. The site also provides maps that show where and to what extent arsenic occurs in ground water across the country. Links to additional resources related to arsenic and drinking water are also included. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

USGS
Provider:

U.S. Geological Survey

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_07_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/2020/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:16:11">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/united-states-geologic-survey-selected-volcano-information</link><title>United States Geologic Survey: Selected Volcano Information</title><description>United States Geologic Survey: Selected Volcano Information

This United States Geological Survey (USGS) Volcano Hazards Program site contains links ... (more)

This United States Geological Survey (USGS) Volcano Hazards Program site contains links to selected material related to volcanic hazards. Users can access information about the volcanic hazards program, publications, topical maps of volcanoes world wide, aviation safety reports, volcanic hazard reports, computer software, volcano digital series and educational videos. Several USGS fact sheets are also available for volcanoes in Alaska, Arizona, California, Hawaii, the Pacific Northwest and around the world. Fact sheets can be downloaded as pdf files or html. This site contains a wide variety of comprehensive material on the world's volcanoes and the hazards associated with them. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Readings
Collection:

Starting Point (SERC)
Provider:

USGS

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_08_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/16443/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:18:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-hotchkiss-map-collection</link><title>The Hotchkiss Map Collection</title><description>The Hotchkiss Map Collection

The Hotchkiss Map Collection contains cartographic items made by Major Jedediah Hotchkiss ... (more)

The Hotchkiss Map Collection contains cartographic items made by Major Jedediah Hotchkiss (1828-1899), a topographic engineer in the Confederate Army. Hotchkiss made detailed battle maps primarily of the Shenandoah Valley, some of which were used by the Generals Robert E. Lee and Thomas J. "Stonewall" Jackson for their combat planning and strategy. Several of the maps have annotations of various military officers, demonstrating their importance in the military campaigns. The collection also includes maps made or used by Hotchkiss during his post-war years, including maps with information about railroads, minerals and mining, geology and history, most of which focus on Virginia and West Virginia, but also cover other states and even the world. The collection consists of 341 sketchbooks, manuscripts, and annotated printed maps, the originals of which reside in the Library of Congress' Geography and Map Division. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Readings
Collection:

Library of Congress
Provider:

Library of Congress

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_09_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72934/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:20:53">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/establishing-borders-the-expansion-of-the-united-states-1846-48</link><title>Establishing Borders: The Expansion of the United States, 1846-48</title><description>Establishing Borders: The Expansion of the United States, 1846-48

This site offers geography and history activities showing how two years in ... (more)

This site offers geography and history activities showing how two years in history had an indelible impact on American politics and culture. Students interpret historical maps, identify territories acquired by the U.S., identify states later formed from these territories, examine the territorial status of Texas, and identify political, social, and economic issues related to the expansion of the U.S. in the 1840s. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Images and Illustrations
Lesson Plans
Readings
Unit of Study
Collection:

Smithsonian Institutions
Provider:

Smithsonian Center for Education and Museum Studies

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7348_10_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/5614/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>