<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:50:12" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:50:12">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/facebook-101-tutorial</link><title>Facebook 101 Tutorial</title><description>Facebook 101 Tutorial

Learn how to create, use and maintain a Facebook page of your ... (more)

Learn how to create, use and maintain a Facebook page of your own, including setting safe privacy controls. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Readings
Video Lectures
Collection:

GCFLearnFree
Provider:

Goodwill Community Foundation, Inc.

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7438_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/95032/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:52:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/facebook-for-school-counselors</link><title>Facebook for School Counselors</title><description>Facebook for School Counselors

In a world that is becoming more connected and more social, technological ... (more)

In a world that is becoming more connected and more social, technological advancement is having a profound impact on people’s lives – from the way they share to how they learn. Nowhere is this shift clearer than in schools. Social networking can have a productive function in education. However, with the opportunity afforded by exciting new technologies comes a new responsibility for people to learn how to use them safely. School counselors are on the front lines, helping kids navigate this new and changing world. They play a vital role in helping students learn to make safe, smart and responsible choices online. Whether helping students understand the impact of sharing personal information or address incidents of bullying, school counselors are helping to create a new generation of “digital citizens.” (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Readings
Teaching and Learning Strategies
Collection:

Educator Reference Shelf
Provider:

American School Counselor Association

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7438_02_thumb.png">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/42807/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>