<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:54:37" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:54:38">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/make-the-world-safe-for-democracy-every-liberty-bond-you-buy-helps-win-the-war-buy-more-liberty-bonds</link><title>Make the World Safe for Democracy Every Liberty Bond You Buy Helps Win the War : Buy More Liberty Bonds.</title><description>Make the World Safe for Democracy Every Liberty Bond You Buy Helps Win the War : Buy More Liberty Bonds.

Poster showing a hand about to pitch a ball labeled "Second Liberty ... (more)

Poster showing a hand about to pitch a ball labeled "Second Liberty Loan of 1917" at Kaiser Wilhelm with the caption "Swat military autocracy." No. 2. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - World War I Posters
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/92419/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:57:18">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-liberty-chariot</link><title>The Liberty Chariot</title><description>The Liberty Chariot

A burlesque triumphal procession representing victory for the Democratic platform in the ... (more)

A burlesque triumphal procession representing victory for the Democratic platform in the election of 1848. In a chariot drawn by Democrats Lewis Cass and William O. Butler (shown as two horses), Uncle Sam drives toward the White House. On his way he rides over and cuts in two a black man representing abolitionism and then continues over Free Soil candidate Martin Van Buren. Whig candidates Zachary Taylor and Millard Fillmore trail along behind, sharing the saddle of the same bucking horse. Uncle Sam's chariot, called "Firm Confederation," is composed of a cab formed of large eagle wings and a shield. In it ride four crowned Liberty figures. They hold spears with banners reading: "Tariff of 1846," "Welcome [----] Oppressed," "No National Bank," and "Honor and Peace." Uncle Sam remarks enthusiastically, "Do tell now, ain't this the way to make a happy Republic?" Van Buren, visible beneath the chariot's wheels, groans, "Second sober thoughts--I wish I had been out of this muss!" Fillmore comments, "I say Taylor, we two have been too weighty for the Old buster! [i.e., their horse]" Taylor replies, "No, the Old thing was in a very bad condition when we mounted him."|Published by Peter E. Abel &amp; Durang, Philada.|Signed with initials: E.F.D. (E.F. Durang).|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 95.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1848-43. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76456/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:57:56">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/matty-s-perilous-situation-up-salt-river</link><title>Matty's Perilous Situation Up Salt River</title><description>Matty's Perilous Situation Up Salt River

A pro-Whig satire on the presidential campaign of 1840. Martin Van Buren ... (more)

A pro-Whig satire on the presidential campaign of 1840. Martin Van Buren is neck-deep in the waters of "Salt River," a colloquial term for political misfortune or failure. He sinks under the weight of boxes marked "Tariff," "Hooe's Trial," "Negro Suffrage," "Sub Treasury," and "Standing Army of 200,000 Men," surmounted by a crown with a hand holding a purse. His hat, filled with newspapers friendly to the administration, floats away. Whig candidate William Henry Harrison paddles downstream on a barrel of hard cider. On the shore behind him is a shed labeled "Humane Society's Apparatus for the Recovery of Drowned Persons." Van Buren: "Oh that I could shake off this load! I am sinking deeper and deeper into the quicksand of Loco Focoism! Help! Ming! Riel! Slam! Bang! Help!" (He names New York Democratic figures Alexander Ming and Levi Slamm.) Harrison: "It's a pity to let the poor fellow drown; I had an idea of making him Inspector of Cabbages of Kinderhook for that's all he's good for; but I think he will sink. Oh what a weight!"|Entered . . . 1840 by J. Childs. |Published by J. Childs no. 90 Nassau St. N.Y.|Signed with monogram: EWC (Edward Williams Clay).|The Library's impression was deposited for copyright on August 31, 1840. Printed in the lower margin is "Price 25 Cents."|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 65.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1840-55. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76512/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:59:41">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/settin-on-a-rail</link><title>Settin' On A Rail</title><description>Settin' On A Rail

A satire, probably issued during August or September 1837, on the tug-of-war ... (more)

A satire, probably issued during August or September 1837, on the tug-of-war for influence on the President between Jacksonian Democrats and the "soft money" or conservative elements of the party. Here the artist portrays Van Buren as indecisive and secretive about his treasury policy. Sitting on a rail fence, Van Buren is pulled to the left by former President Andrew Jackson, Senator Thomas Hart Benton, and other representatives of the hard money faction. One man holds up the June 1836 "Letter to Sherrod Williams" published during the presidential campaign as a statement of Van Buren's views on monetary matters, internal improvements, and other cogent issues. On the opposite side Van Buren is pulled by a man (possibly editor Thomas Allen) holding a copy of the "Madisonian," a conservative Democratic newspaper initiated in August 1837, and four others. Jack Downing stands to the far right, watching and commenting, "Well I swan, if the Old Gineral aint pullin' tu! Look out Matty or you'll commit yourself this time!" Jackson: "Oh! Major Jack Downing, The base treachery &amp; perfidy of the Deposite Banks! The money making concerns, devoid of patriotism &amp; interest. By the Eternal! They are &amp; ever have been a curse." Benton: "Gold! Gold! Gold! . . . Solitary &amp; alone I still cry Gold! . . . Partially obscured man behind Benton: "The proud Isle! Every man, woman &amp; child is taxed to pay her our debts." Van Buren: "Take care gentlemen, you'll have me off the fence." "Madisonian" man: "Preserve &amp; regulate the spoils but do not destroy them." Second man: "Well regulated monopolies, are the proper balance wheel." In the commotion Van Buren's hat, emblazoned with a royal crown, falls off.|Entered . . . 1837 by H.R. Robinson.|Printed &amp; published by H.R. Robinson, 52 Cortlandt St. N.Y.|Signed with monogram: C (Edward Williams Clay).|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Davison, no. 95.|Weitenkampf, p. 46.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1837-12. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/75911/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:00:16">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/animal-magnetism</link><title>Animal Magnetism</title><description>Animal Magnetism

A swipe at President Van Buren's independent treasury system and his continuation ... (more)

A swipe at President Van Buren's independent treasury system and his continuation of the monetary policies of predecessor Andrew Jackson. The artist, clearly in sympathy with the Whigs, links corruption in the federal customs and postal systems with the sub-treasury system, whereby federal funds were to be retained by the revenue-collecting agencies and other designated repositories, instead of private banks. The artist forecasts Van Buren's defeat in the 1840 elections. Van Buren, hypnotized by Jackson, is on a couch with a royal crown and scepter on one side and sword and purse on the other. Jackson, his toes touching Van Buren's, sits in a chair to the left with his white plug hat and cane next to him. On the right Treasury Secretary Levi Woodbury (arms crossed), Postmaster General Amos Kendall, and "Globe" editor Francis Preston Blair (far right) observe. Jackson: "Are you asleep? Do you hear me? Tell me what you see?" Van Buren: "I am asleep. I hear nobody but you.--I see a great pole, and a crowd of people. They are cheering an elderly man; whom they hail as President of the United States. On their banners are inscribed Whig Principles!!! I see a little man tumbling down a precipice; on his back is a mill stone inscribed Sub-treasury! oh! lord, oh! lord! Why it is myself!" Woodbury: "Ask him Dr. Jackson, if he sees any thing of "Price" or Swartwout?" (See "Price Current" and "Sub Treasurers Meeting in England," nos. 1838-21 and -20.) Kendall: "Ask him at what rate the Express Mail for North is going now?" Blair: "This will make a good paragraph for the Globe!"|Entered . . . 1839 by John Childs.|New York. Published &amp; sold by J. Childs, Lithographer. 119, Fulton-Street.|Signed with monogram: EWC (Edward Williams Clay).|The Library's impression of the print was deposited for copyright on February 22, 1839.|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Davison, no. 122.|Weitenkampf, p. 58.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1839-2. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_05_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76012/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:01:50">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-fox-without-a-tail</link><title>The Fox Without A Tail</title><description>The Fox Without A Tail

A satire on South Carolina's role as instigator of secessionism in the ... (more)

A satire on South Carolina's role as instigator of secessionism in the South. The artist may be lampooning the convention of seceded states which assembled at Montgomery, Alabama, on February 4, 1861. The prominent leaders of the Confederate states are portrayed as foxes. The chief fox (the one "without a tail") is South Carolina governor Francis Pickens. South Carolina was the most radical of the Southern states and the first to leave the Union. Here he tries to entice the others into giving up their tails as well. As the text below puts it, "A cunning fox, having lost his tail in a trap, to save himself from ridicule called a convention of the other foxes and stated to them that having found his tail a great incumbrance he had cut it off, and advised them all to do the same, . . ." Standing on a pedestal supported on the back of a crouching black man, Pickens (center) holds aloft a document "Secession" and says, "All in favor of losing their tails will please say aye contrary no, carried the member from Mississippi will commence operations." The member from Missippi is Jefferson Davis, who stands at right holding a large ax. Before him, with its tail on a block, is a fox "Florida." Davis says (although he doesn't move), "Make ready, take aim, fire! bang!! there she goes slick as a whistle, now then Toombs, your tail if you please, no noise." Georgia secessionist Robert Toombs holds a bowl in front of him, and announces, "After the member from Florida I claim the honor of being the "next Customer." An unidentified man at the far right proclaims, "Until a better substitute is offered, I shal hold on to my tail, that's certain." To the left of Pickens is an ornate table carved with symbols of tyranny and treachery, including a pistol, dagger, crown, whip, and die. On the table rests an inkwell with a statuette of two men fighting with daggers. Behind, two foxes representing Louisiana and Alabama are partly concealed by a large document. On the far left is "Texas," a fox with a foolscap pulled down over its face and holding a musket with bayonet and a liquor bottle. He sings, "Yankee doodle be hanged (hic) Star spangled banner 'hanged, (hic) come lets lick 'er." Another man asks, "In case we cut off our tails and should afterwards repent, is there any description of glue in the market with which we can fasten them on again, and will it stick." In the foreground Buchanan's secretary of the interior Jacob Thompson of Mississippi runs from an emptied safe with a sack of $870,000, saying, "To the victors belong the spoils that good Democractic doctrine." Thompson had resigned the cabinet in 1861. The stolen goods may refer to an episode during his term of office when he was accused of stealing a large sum of money from the Indian funds of the Department of Interior. He was eventually judged innocent of this charge. In the background a fox standing atop a ladder puts a torch to the American flag and eagle.|Drawn by John L. Magee.|Published by John L. Magee, 22 South Fifth St. Phila.|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 126.|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1861-8. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7439_06_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76557/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>