<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:32:12" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:32:13">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/chemistry-of-sports-spring-2009</link><title>Chemistry of Sports, Spring 2009</title><description>Chemistry of Sports, Spring 2009

" This seminar will focus on three sports: swimming, cycling and running. ... (more)

" This seminar will focus on three sports: swimming, cycling and running. There will be two components to the seminar: classroom sessions and a "laboratory" in the form of a structured training program. The classroom component will introduce the students to the chemistry of their own biological system. With swimming, running and cycling as sample sports, students are encouraged to apply their knowledge to complete a triathlon shortly after the term." (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Full Course
Lecture Notes
Video Lectures
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Christie, Patricia
Lyons, Steven

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/33039/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:34:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/chemistry-of-sports-spring-2007</link><title>Chemistry of Sports, Spring 2007</title><description>Chemistry of Sports, Spring 2007

In this new seminar, we will be focusing on three sports, swimming, ... (more)

In this new seminar, we will be focusing on three sports, swimming, cycling and running. There will be two components to the seminar, a classroom and a laboratory. The classroom component will introduce the students to the chemistry of their own biological system. Since we are looking at swimming, running and cycling as our sample sports, we will apply the classroom knowledge to complete a triathlon. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Full Course
Homework and Assignments
Lecture Notes
Syllabi
Collection:

MIT OpenCourseWare
Provider:

M.I.T.
Author:

Christie, Patricia

Remix and Share</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/3103/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:36:04">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/economics-water-use-and-the-environment</link><title>Economics, Water Use, and the Environment</title><description>Economics, Water Use, and the Environment

Lurking beneath our natural desire to ensure that water will always be ... (more)

Lurking beneath our natural desire to ensure that water will always be available to perform its many life-supporting functions is the fear that it will run out. Our thinking (in truth, our feeling) about water tends to be dominated by myth and misunderstanding. We believe that our 'need' for water is exponentially greater than other wants and needs; we also believe that this intense 'need' confers special status, making water a unique resource. We mistrust the ability of people to recognize water's special status, and we assert that only through common or public ownership can we preserve water for future generations. Paradoxically, while our conviction that water is unique derives from our knowledge of its many important uses, we have trouble acknowledging the value of water in anything other than pristine form. We tend to assume that, when it comes to water, there's no such thing as 'too clean.' Unfortunately, in acquiescing to these myths, we make things worse; we create for ourselves an intellectual box that constrains our ability to conserve the resource we value so highly. These lessons challenge the myths and use economic reasoning to suggest a new way to think about our use of this vital resource. In brief, the lessons assert: (1) that in economic terms, water is not fundamentally different from any other resource, good, or service; and (2) that many of the answers to our concerns about water conservation and water quality can be found in markets, the same institution that provides us bread, shoes, underwear, tractors, flowers, computers, charities, flu shots, bubblegum, the collectible craze of the moment, and the myriad other products we find 'essential' to the way we wish to live. (less)

Subject:

Social Sciences
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Assessments
Lesson Plans
Collection:

Foundation for Teaching Economics
Provider:

Foundation for Teaching Economics

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/54398/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:37:20">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/mother-s-little-network</link><title>Mother's Little Network</title><description>Mother's Little Network

Billing itself as 'the only show on PBS with no English host,' ... (more)

Billing itself as 'the only show on PBS with no English host,' this one-of special comic program presents several short skits. Many of these rely on visual gags. A tortilla falls onto a record turntable. Four hard-boiled detectives narrating a story from the wheel of a car turn out to be driving the same car. A flaming cheeseburger crashes into a miniature set. A lucky fisherman literally has fish flying out of the air at him. 'Bionic Bag Boy' runs through the aisles of the supermarket. In a Psycho-esque shower scene a woman is pelted with cream pies. A character reminiscent of 'Taxi Driver's' Travis Bickle gives a cab ride to a group of disgruntled stuffed animals in a skit entitled 'Taxi Dermist.' In a segment evocative of Mr. Rodgers neighborhood, 'Mr. Ernie' takes off his sweater and shoes, continuing to strip down to his boxer shorts. The Coasters provide musical entertainment in a guest spot. Their images are superimposed onto a set of coasters on a table laden with beer and popcorn. Produced by Fred Barzyk. Directed by Dick Bartlett. Based on earlier experiments created at the Workshop by several of the artists, this work was intended to function as a pilot. The 'Television Workshop' created several shows that were broadcast on WGBH without being a part of a series sponsored specifically by the Workshop. Additionally, they were commissioned to create shows showcasing video art for national broadcast and created several shows in collaboration with existing series at other stations, such as WNET''s 'American Playhouse.' (less)

Subject:

Arts
Science and Technology
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7447_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72436/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>