<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:47:30" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:47:31">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/wpa-posters-a-hero-is-born-a-romantic-musical-by-theresa-holburn-based-on-an-original-story-by-andrew-lang-music-by-a-lehman-engel-lyrics-by-agnes-morgan</link><title>WPA Posters: A Hero is Born a Romantic Musical by Theresa Holburn - Based on An Original Story by Andrew Lang : Music by A. Lehman Engel - Lyrics by Agnes Morgan</title><description>WPA Posters: A Hero is Born a Romantic Musical by Theresa Holburn - Based on An Original Story by Andrew Lang : Music by A. Lehman Engel - Lyrics by Agnes Morgan

Poster for Federal Theatre Project presentation of "A Hero is Born" at ... (more)

Poster for Federal Theatre Project presentation of "A Hero is Born" at the Adelphi Theatre, 54th Street east of 7th Avenue, showing a man riding on a magic carpet. Date stamped on verso: Dec 8 1937. Posters of the WPA / Christopher DeNoon. Los Angeles : Wheatly Press, c1987, no. 287 (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Reference
Collection:

Library of Congress - WPA Posters
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/97582/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:48:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/e-l-jones-performs-othello</link><title>E.L. Jones performs Othello</title><description>E.L. Jones performs Othello

From the Say Brother Studio, E.L. Jones performs an excerpt from The ... (more)

From the Say Brother Studio, E.L. Jones performs an excerpt from The Face of Love, a one-man musical theatre piece written by Vantile Whitfield and E.L. Jones, with music and lyrics by Payton-James-Payton and Glaude. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Humanities
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/70461/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:51:53">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/face-of-love-the</link><title>Face of Love, The</title><description>Face of Love, The

E.L. Jones performs Othello. Program consists of a special presentation of The ... (more)

E.L. Jones performs Othello. Program consists of a special presentation of The Face of Love, a one-man musical theater piece starring E.L. James. The Face of Love reflects on the various kinds of love individuals can feel whether for people, material goods, countries, or ideas. Performance consists of short scenes (mostly) punctuated by vocal pieces, and include a construction worker's reading of Othello, the story of a homeless man, a man reflecting on the death of his aunt, a gambler talking about his love for a Spanish woman, a soldier away from home whose girlfriend breaks up with him via mail, an overzealous patriot, an immigrant in the United States to study, and an elderly man reflecting on heaven. Written by Vantile Whitfield and E.L. James with music and lyrics by Payton-James-Payton and Glaude, all of the Face of Love Company, Washington, DC. Program made possible in part by the Communications Institute of New England. Produced by Barbara Barrow-Murray. Directed by David Atwood.Clip is available from the link at the bottom of the page. http://main.wgbh.org/saybrother/programs/sb_0821 (less)

Subject:

Arts
Humanities
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/71058/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:54:46">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/lines-of-force</link><title>Lines of Force</title><description>Lines of Force

"Lines of Force" opens with footage of a dramatic explosion. For most ... (more)

"Lines of Force" opens with footage of a dramatic explosion. For most of the piece, the screen is divided, into a triptych at first, and slowly into horizontal and vertical bars. Electronically manipulated footage shows a man walking, a marching band, ferns, cartoons, a window, and a train arriving on a set of tracks. The naturally occurring lines in the array of images presented mirror the electronically created bars and lines that divide the screen. Natural scenes provide a respite from the frantic pace of the images. The music score was created by Bob Snyder. The music mirrors the pace of the work. When images are at their most frantic, sounds like free jazz horns blare forth. More lyrical electronic music mirrors the more peaceful arrays of natural images." Lines of Force' was broadcast along with 'Winter Notebook.' Both works were created by video and sound artist Bob Snyder. New Television Workshop appears to have presented but not produced the works. "Artist's Showcase' was a series designed to showcase video art and experimental work from WGBH. The program ran on Sunday evenings at 11 P.M., from the fall of 1976 through 1982. In the early 1970's, 'Artist's Showcase' was the only consistent broadcast outlet for many of the Workshop productions. Most materials of broadcast quality created at WGBH in the mid-1970's were shown as part of this series. Additionally, earlier video art experiments and segments of related shows, such as 'Mixed Bag' or 'What's Happening Mr. Silver' were broadcast under these auspices. This series was also a broadcast outlet for a handful of works by video artists that were not created at WGBH but only acquired for this purpose. Some compilation reels showing highlights of Workshop activity were also broadcast. (less)

Subject:

Arts
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

WGBH Open Vault
Provider:

PBS Learning Media

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7457_04_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/70679/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>