<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:34:54" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:34:55">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/what-s-the-big-idea-biodiversity</link><title>What's the Big Idea? Biodiversity</title><description>What's the Big Idea? Biodiversity

This fun Web site is part of OLogy, where kids can collect ... (more)

This fun Web site is part of OLogy, where kids can collect virtual trading cards and create projects with them. Here, they are introduced to biodiversity on our planet. The online slide show covers:the three kinds of biodiversity on Earth -- genes, species, and ecosystems; just how interconnected an ecosystem is;why biodiversity is so important to our planet; the fact that extinction is forever, and how the U.S. Endangered Species Act works to protect endangered species;the ways our actions are leading to a loss of biodiversity; and how kids can get involved to help preserve biodiversity. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7478_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17525/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:35:51">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-adventures-of-george-amato-dna-detective</link><title>The Adventures of George Amato, "DNA Detective"</title><description>The Adventures of George Amato, "DNA Detective"

This fun Web site is part of OLogy, where kids can collect ... (more)

This fun Web site is part of OLogy, where kids can collect virtual trading cards and create projects with them. Here, they see how DNA is used to solve crimes against animals. The activity starts with an introduction to George Amato, an AMNH scientist who sometimes helps the U.S. government solve mysteries. In a three-part online slide show, students see how Amato earned the title "DNA Detective" in 1993 when he helped the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service catch someone trying to sneak protected reptile skin into the United States. Then students are challenged to Crack the Code, an online game in which they play DNA detective and determine which of a collection of handbags, clothing, figurines, and other items are made from protected species. (less)

Subject:

Science and Technology
Material Type:

Activities and Labs
Collection:

American Museum of Natural History
Provider:

American Museum of Natural History

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7478_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/17544/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>