<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:19:40" name="OER Commons" id="FW14-e092"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e092-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:19:40">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/this-muddy-place-mary-ballou-a-boardinghouse-keeper-in-the-california-gold-rush-1852</link><title>"This Muddy Place": Mary Ballou, a Boardinghouse Keeper in the California Gold Rush, 1852</title><description>"This Muddy Place": Mary Ballou, a Boardinghouse Keeper in the California Gold Rush, 1852

Mary Ballou and her husband ran a boarding house in the gold ... (more)

Mary Ballou and her husband ran a boarding house in the gold mining town of Negro Bar, California. While most of the "Forty-niners" who rushed to California went to pan gold, others, like Ballou and her husband, went to reap high profits by providing services to the miners. Ballou's letter to her son, written in 1852, evoked the rough housing, violence, and high prices (from which the Ballous profited) in California during the gold rush. She also described the limited number of women among the flood of male miners, and how important they were to each other for companionship and consolation. Ballou's references to "the States" are an expression of how far from home California must have felt since California was a state÷it had been admitted to the union in 1850. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Material Type:

Primary Source
Readings
Collection:

Many Pasts (CHNM/ASHP)
Provider:

American Social History Project / Center for History Media and Learning
Author:

Center for History and New Media/American Social History Project

Read the Fine Print</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_01_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/72046/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:20:22">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/the-treasury-hen-alarmed</link><title>The Treasury-Hen Alarmed</title><description>The Treasury-Hen Alarmed

A portrayal of Treasury Secretary Levi Woodbury as a hen nurturing corruption ... (more)

A portrayal of Treasury Secretary Levi Woodbury as a hen nurturing corruption and shielding New York City customs house officials from congressional scrutiny. Woodbury spreads his wings over several chicks pecking at gold coins beneath him, as two of the chicks swim off toward Liverpool. The foremost one represents former Collector of the Port Samuel Swartwout, found to have defrauded the government of nearly $1.25 million. The second is federal district attorney William M. Price, a coconspirator. Both fled to England. (See "Price Current" and "Sub Treasurers Meeting in England," nos. 1838-21 and -20.) Woodbury is threatened by a hawk, "Committee of Investigations," with the head of Kentucky congressman James Harlan, who flies overhead calling, "I'll have you! hen &amp; all." Harlan was chairman of the House committee established in January 1839 to probe the Swartwout defalcations. The hen cries: "Hawk! . . . run! . . . Fly Sam [Swartwout] &amp; Bill [Price]! take to the water--quick, before he comes! dive or he'll get you! . . . Here Hoyty [i.e., Swartwout's successor Jesse Hoyt]! hide between my legs! . . . hide Ogden! run Phillips! fly Fleming! come Gratiot! Hawk Boydy! . . . Linn! Scud Harris! Fly Spencer! Drop gold &amp; run all! come under! . . .I'll cover you!"|Entered . . . 1839 by H.R. Robinson.|Printed &amp; publd by H.R. Robinson, 52 Cortlandt &amp; 11-1/2 Wall st. N.Y.|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 57.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1839-1. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_02_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/76429/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e092-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:21:30">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/worse-than-a-spanish-inquisition</link><title>"Worse Than A Spanish Inquisition"</title><description>"Worse Than A Spanish Inquisition"

A commentary on the workings of the January 1839 congressional probe of ... (more)

A commentary on the workings of the January 1839 congressional probe of the Treasury Department in the wake of the Swartwout embezzlement. (See "Price Current" and "Sub Treasurers Meeting in England," nos. 1838-21 and -20.) Led by administration opponent Henry A. Wise and chaired by James Harlan, the committee scrutinized procedures and irregularities in the reporting and handling of federal funds by Treasury Department officials. Here the artist seems unusually sympathetic to Treasury Secretary Levi Woodbury. The secretary sits strapped into a "Scrutiny chair" with its seat of nails, probed and drilled by various committee members including Wise, who bores into his skull at upper right, and Harlan, who sniffs Woodbury's palm saying, "I must say there is no smell of gold on the palm. Tho' he did let others steal I don't think he shared in the booty!" The secretary's left foot is caught in an animal trap. His right leg is stretched to the left by a winch whose base is labeled "Power to employ a Clerk, . . . to employ a Printer, . . , to send for Persons &amp; Papers." William C. Dawson (seated listening through a horn to Woodbury's stomach) says, "Strange sounds in his lower regions. He seems Dispeptic. Possibly Wise's speech has disagreed with him . . ." Standing committee member with forceps: "What a grip he has! but open you shall! Here are secrets worth knowing! He opens the other hand readily enough to Harlan! but this, he keeps as tight as a vice!" Another, boring into Woodbury's right ear: "This must be his deaf ear. They say he kept one for complaints against his Officers . . ." Another, focussing a magnifying glass on Woodbury's temple: "There is no more fire in his brain than in a heap of mouldy straw . . ." Wise: "It seems to me, I shall never get thro' his skull. No hope of discoveries in that quarter! . . ." Another committee member: "No wonder he could not smell out Swartwout's defalcation, the olfactory nerve is wholly wanting!" Another committee member, drilling Woodbury's left side: "My augur is like to be buried! What a "deep" Financier!" The names of the Swartwout investigation committee are listed on a paper at lower right. Weitenkampf mistakes the central figure for Van Buren.|Drawn by Napoleon Sarony?|Entd . . . 1839 by H.R. Robinson.|Printed &amp; publd. by H.R. Robinson, 52 Cortlandt &amp; 11-1/2 Wall st. N.Y.|Title appears as it is written on the item.|Weitenkampf, p. 58.|Forms part of: American cartoon print filing series (Library of Congress)|Published in: American political prints, 1766-1876 / Bernard F. Reilly. Boston : G.K. Hall, 1991, entry 1839-8. (less)

Subject:

Humanities
Social Sciences
Material Type:

Images and Illustrations
Primary Source
Collection:

Library of Congress - Cartoons 1766-1876
Provider:

Library of Congress

No Strings Attached</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e092/7499_03_thumb.jpg">http://www.oercommons.org/courses/75890/thumbnail/index</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>